The person I met at the rose gate.
What a house!
Just like the house from fairy tale!
I'm sure the Prince is living here!
Kurin, let's go in.
Candy was taken into the Leagan family.
Two mean children, Eliza and Neil,
are waiting for her.
However, Candy decided not to give up.
Mother!
What's up with this noise?
Nice to meet you! I'm Candy.
Oh no!
I have to pump up some water!
Oh yes, this is Leagan's house!
Wonderful!
Kurin, wake up!
It's a beautiful morning!
Kurin oversleep again!
Well, I have to cheer up.
My prince.
You are prettier when you're smiling
than when you're crying.
Candy's prince.
Work!
Kurin, I'm so sorry!
Funny thing happened yesterday.
That new girl gave hell to
Eliza and Neal!
I wonder what's her name?
Her name is Candy.
Good morning!
How come you're here?
You're a merry one, aren't you?
What happened yesterday,
must frighten you.
Me? Impossible.
It didn't affect me one bit!
That's funny!
Candy, we are all your friends.
Hang in there!
Thanks.
Can I help you somehow?
You're miss Eliza's playmate,
you don't need to work.
I love to work!
It's fun when you work with your hands!
Isn't that my companion,
doing the job of a cleaning lady?
Good morning!
Why don't you do something
once in a while?
You're supposed to call me miss!
Well then, miss.
I'm sure that
work can bring you a better mood.
I won't give in to them.
It's you again.
I missed.
Wait!
Stop!
Kurin, hold!
Kurin!
Horrible! Mother!!
Candy, you can't keep doing
these unecessary things!
Unnecessary things? I?
That's right.
You are here to be Eliza's playmate.
I don't want you do anything else!
What's that thing?
Help me!
Candy! Throw the raccoon out!
But... it was not Kurin's fault!
You're not entitled to an opinion!
You are not allow to have a raccoon.
Thow him out! Now.
Yes.
Go now.
This road will take you to Pony's home.
Go, quickly.
For your own sake!
Farewell, Kurin.
Stop following me!
Kurin?
He's gone, after all.
I give up.
I have to chase you away!
Wait!
listen, Kurin.
Once you loose the rope,
go back to Pony's home.
Farewell, Kurin!
Farewell, Kurin. Take care.
Kurin. I'm sorry, Kurin.
I just can't leave you behind.
Come!
Calm down!
You can hide in there.
Listen,
come to my room at night.
See you!
I'm not mean that...
Hey! It's Candy!
Candy!
Did you really get rid of Kurin?
Don't lie to me.
It's true!
Got back to them well!
Now that's the way to
avoid an unpleasant situation.
Candy? Are you here?
Yes, come in!
I have a letter for you.
For me?
Something could have happened to it
if Madam or Eliza got to it first.
So I brought it to you myself.
Thank you!
It's from Pony's home!
Dorothy, thank you!
Candy!
I got a letter from Pony's home!
-That's Candy!
-She was with Kurin!
That Candy...
she didn't throw the beast.
She lied to us.
Let's tell mama about this!
Let's wait out a bit.
We could use of this,
if we wait for a better moment.
That's right...
Kurin,
you can't wait to see, right?
Hold on.
It's sister Lane.
Candy, how are you?
Have you found your place
in your new home?
Sister Pony is worried about you.
I'm sure that you'll be okay.
I wish you to be happy.
Both sister Pony and I bless you.
This one is from sister Pony!
Candy, do you pray before bed?
Don't drink too much water,
you'll upset your stomach.
Sister Pony...
Hey, even John sent me a letter!
Candy, how are you?
Ever since you left,
I start wetting my sheets again.
John, you!
Candy, if you feel upsad,
you can always return to Pony's home.
We haven't told sister Pony about it.
All of us are waiting for your return.
If you do that,
I'll stop wetting my sheets!
I remember...
the good times at Pony's home.
Why doesn't my snowman
look anything like Annie's ?
I'll climb on its head!
Candy, are you okay?
They're coming this way!
-Look out! Annie.
-Move it!
My snowman!
Now you've done it!
Stop! Tom.
I'm coming!
Candy!
Candy? where are you?
Candy, I won't forgive you.
Thank you, everyone.
I'll do my best.
Do you enjoy these letters
from Pony's home? Candy.
Neil, Eliza!
What are you doing?
Give them back!
Here! Come on.
What's this?
Give it back!
It's ...
Hey, Candy!
Where did you steal this?
Steal?
Answer me.
A girl from Pony's home
could hardly buy this.
It's mine! Give it back!
Come and get it!
Don't give it back, Neil!
Of course, I'm gonna take it!
-Give it back!
-I'm here!
Candy, you want me to
tell mama about Kurin?
No! I forgot Kurin
when I got the letters!
It's too late to hide now!
We know that
you're hiding in the barn!
If you want us to stay quiet,
hand this over!
No! I'm not giving you that!
Then, you're okay with us
telling to mama?
Do whatever you want!
I'll not let you have it,
no matter what!
Give it back!
Throw it into the lake.
Throw it!
Wait!
-Wait!
-Go get it!
Look, she's crying!
Give me my pendant!
Well, give it to her.
From now on,
you must obey our orders.
That's right!
On your knees beg for forgiveness!
You horrible people!
Give it back!
-Go to hell!
-You're fired!
I'd go anywhere...
never return to this place!
Sister Pony, sister Lane...
I want to return to Pony's home!
Don't cry... miss freckle.
Don't cry... miss freckle!
You're cute when you smile!
The prince from the hill!
It's really my prince!
Who is he? Candy's prince?
You really are cute when you smile!
My prince said the same thing!
After all,
you're cute when you smile.
That's it. I mustn't cry.
That does not like me!
He's gone...
He was here just a moment ago.
Until a moment ago...
It's the same pendant.
Finally,
I have found my Prince!
Aww, the door is locked.
What kind of the house is
behind these gate.
Is my lovely prince lives here.
I won't cry anymore.
I promise.
Please let me see you again.
My prince.
Kurin,
you found the letter from Pony's home?
I really don't like her. It's late.
She might have gone back
to that Pony's home.
Look!
Crybaby is coming!
Give it back...
When will you
return to Pony's home?
Sorry, I am not going
back to Pony's home!
From now on,
you can do anything to me,
I won't care!
What happened to her?
She's weird.
What does she mean?
She really annoys me!
Damn it,
if it's come down to this,
I'll drive her out of here for sure!
They are exactly alike,
it's gone into their heads.
Candy!
Yes.
Where have you been until now?
I'm sorry.
Listen up!
Stop making noises inside the house.
Yes.
Eliza hadn't told her about Kurin.
She'll want something in return.
I don't care! It's all up to them.
Just like the day I met him
at the hill above Pony's home,
The eyes of the prince
are so gentle today.
Inside of Candy...
She is looking forward
to meet the prince again.
Yes! I want to see you again.