Candy staring at Terry's poster.
Show is coming in ten days.
Cand's heart has already
flew to Broadway.
A trip with a partner.
Who is it?
I am Candy.
Come in.
Sorry for disturbing,
I...
I was looking at
your application for leave.
Dr. Reknapp.
Don't you think five days leave
is kind of long? Candy.
But I really need to go to New York.
New York?
Are you going to the Broadways?
No...
I don't want to ask for the reasons.
Is it approved?
Ten days suspension
starts from tomorrow.
No, I...
Go to Florida
before you have your leave.
Florida? It's so far...
You need to deliever a document
for the Principal Clairs.
Principal?
Yes,
you have sufficient time for this.
Yes.
Florida?
Sounds good, Candy.
But Mr.Albert...
Don't worry about me,
I am good.
I will ask Pattie and Annie
to look after you.
I am all good now.
Just can't remember the past.
I will be back real soon.
Don't miss the show in Broadway.
Mr.Albert!
Oh yeah, Candy.
Do you want to bring this poster
to Florida?
I don't know.
Miss,
Are you on this train?
Yes.
Sorry,
Last stop.
Great.
Dell, come here, what you doing?
Dell quick!
Faster!
Miss,
this kid is going to Florida as well.
Please take care of him.
Leave me alone, I am not a child.
You sure?
You bought a child fare.
Please.
Ok.
Why didn't you find a beauty?
What?
You want some chocolate?
Don't treat me like a child,
it's rude.
You...
Oh yeah,
I haven't introduced myself.
I am Candy.
Nice meeting you, Dell.
Dell Butt.
I am sorry,
that ma'am called you Dell
You can just call me Dell.
You look good.
Stear,
Pattie,
Annie told me...
Candy went to Florida,
is it true?
This morning's train.
What? How can she do that!
She left without making a sound.
She was doing her job,
she didn't want us to worry.
I was going to give her a gift.
What is that?
Specially made swimming tube.
Such cold weather?
Florida is warm.
America is so big.
I forgot this is your first time
to going overseas.
But I heard about the storm.
It's a huge storm in Florida
in between summer and autumn.
What a smart student from London.
Where are we?
Don't open.
You are up, Dell.
I don't want to look out the window.
I will think of my father.
Your father?
A lousy doctor killed him.
Don't say that.
But...
I am a nurse.
Nurse?
You are not from
St.Joanna Hospital, are you?
Indeed.
Lousy doctor from that hospital
killed my father.
Nonsense, there is
no lousy doctor in our hospital.
Sorry.
Dell, who exactly is the lousy doctor
you were talking about?
The vice principal.
Murderer,
give me back my father.
I told you,
You father was very sick.
Don't give me that,
he came here one year ago.
You said he had a stomach upset.
We confirmed that it was cancer.
It's a miracle that
he has lived for one year.
You lie.
If my father had the operation,
he wouldn't have died.
I have other things to deal with,
somebody,
Take him out.
What you doing? Stop.
Lousy doctor.
I understand your feeling.
Dr. Reknapp is a good doctor.
I don't care.
Because of his misjudgement,
I need to beg my relatives
in Florida to take me in.
That's why you 're on this train.
You must be going for vacation.
I am on a business trip.
I need to deliver some
important documents to the principal.
Important documents?
Not here, in toilet?
Gone.
The suitcase with the documents.
Dell.
I can't find him.
Did he get off the train
when I fell asleep.
Dell.
Here you are.
Stop playing around.
Let me tell you,
there is nothing in the suitcase.
Dell,
Where are the documents?
Tell me, Dell.
You think your father will be happy
if you do this?
Of course, I avenged for him.
I am the one who suffers
if the documents are gone.
Reknap should be the one suffering.
He is responsible
for the documents.
Have you read the documents?
I hate doctors and nurses.
You won't understand my feelings.
Maybe.
I don't have parents.
Are they dead?
I was abandoned by my parents.
Dell, where are the documents?
Threw away, from here.
-When?
-Crossing the bridge.
Move.
What are you doing?
I will jump off the train
to look for the documents.
Are you serious? Candy.
I won't get hurt at this speed.
Stop Candy.
-Watch out!
-Let go.
I am a good athlete.
No, it's too dangerous.
What you guys doing?
She was trying to
jump off the train.
Don't be stupid.
Someone is sick,
I really need a doctor.
Sick?
There is a ill child
in car number two.
Take me there, I am a nurse.
Looks like appendicitis.
Appendix?
Is she alright, nurse.
When did the pain start?
Before boarding.
How could you let her
board the train?
She always lies about
being uncomfortable.
Captain, how much further
to the next stop?
One hour to go.
Hope it doesn't get worse.
Dell, get me some ice water.
Is there any doctor on this train?
Go ask around.
Ok.
Sorry for disturbing,
We have a patient on the train.
Is there any doctor on this train?
You can do it.
You are going to be fine.
Any doctors?
Not even one.
Why didn't I trust her?
Calm down.
Calm down? I can't.
My daughter could die any second,
how am I going to calm down?
Mom,
Kelly,
Can you speed up?
It's the fasteest we can go.
Nurse, Kelly...
Kelly is not going to die, right?
Five minutes to the station.
Stretcher!
Don't move the patient.
Why?
The station master told me that
the doctor wouldn't be back until late.
What should we do?
How much further
to the next station?
About three hours.
Three hours?
We can't afford another three hours,
nurse.
I have to do this.
The best we can do
is to go to the next station.
Captain, let's move.
Not now.
Why? My daughter is dying.
If we go now we will
collide with the oncoming train.
We need to wait for the oncoming train
to leave for Chicago first.
It's late.
It's coming.
The train to Chicago is coming.
Candy let's go.
Dell, let's go look for doctors.
Doctors?
There must be a lot of passengers
on the train right across.
Maybe...
Your are right.
Any doctors on this train?
We got a patient here,
any doctor here?
Any doctors here?
You...
You are doctor?
We have an emergency here.
Ok, I see.
She needs to have operation
right away.
Please doctor.
But on the train...
There is a clinic in the town.
I will be your assistant.
You?
I am a surigcal nurse.
You are? So get ready.
Clamp.
Yes.
Kelly.
We wouldn't be able to save her
had it been another thirty minutes.
Is Kelly alright now?
Still anaesthetised.
Thank you so much.
The doctor here
will take care of the rest.
I have her medical history ready.
I...
I am in a hurry.
You did a good job,
which hospital are you from?
Chicago, St.Joanna.
I see,
please say hi to Dr. Reknapp for me.
You know vice principal?
Tell him I am his rival
during his school time.
Doctor may I have your name?
That's fine,
the train is waiting for me.
Doctor.
Is Dell waiting for me?
The train is moving.
Before the doctor comes back,
I need to stay and look after Kelly.
Thank you.
But there will be no trains
until tomorrow.
I will go check us in.
Dell, can you take my luggage?
Ok.
Is the doctor back yet?
Don't worry about it.
I wonder if there are horses
for rent here?
Why do you need a horse?
I want to go look for the documents
you threw away.
Candy
This...
Didn't you throw it away?
Sorry, I hid it.
That's so good to know.
Are you alright? Candy.
Why?
I haven't had anything.
I will go look for food.
Wait, Dell,
the restaurants are all closed.
I was wrong about
nurses and doctors.
Candy, and that doctor,
you two saved Kelly.
Dell, the same for doctor Reknapp.
Even if dad didn't have cancer,
He was going to die
sooner or later.
Your dad...
He was the lighting technician
in Elmoe Theater.
Elmoe theater?
The last show was...
Stellas troupe 's King Leo.
Although I didn't know
much about stage play.
Dad was looking more serious
and determined than usual.
Dad...
Dad endures his pain
to finish his last show.
I saw the play.
Really? Candy.
Yes.
Dad told me when he got home...
It's been so long
since he saw such a talented actor.
The King of France...
Terriius G. Glantchester.
I guess that's his name.
Terry is my friend.
Candy's?
When I return
I will go look for him in Broadway.
Broadway.
Dad always wanted to work
in those theaters in Broadway.
It's not the theater that matters,
it's the heart and dedication.
Elmo Theater's lighting technician
is just as respected as the others.
Dad will be happy if he hear this.
This small town is just like a stage.
The moon is in position.
Must be your dad's masterpiece
from heaven.
I will tell Terry about
Dell's father.
An unknown hotel.
Candy seems to have Terry
in her sight already.
Although New York is
miles and miles away.
Terry is somewhere so near.