Candy, who grieved over
Anthony's death,
managed to regain her vigor
with Jimmy's help.
And Candy decided that she would live
strongly from that point on.
A present of angels.
The Christmas day draws near.
What a big tree!
Mr. Cartwright sent you
a very good tree indeed!
It was from Mr. Cartwright?
Yeah. Since it's your
last Christmas here
you deserve a nice big tree...
Last Christmas?
Could you talk to Mr. Cartwright...
Cowboys manage everything
instead of him.
You'd better tell it directly to them.
Sister Pony, what did he mean by
"last Christmas" ?
Uh.. it's nothing.
Now, everyone
let's take the tree inside!
Santa Claus will be so surprised
when he sees this tree!
Yeah, he's gonna dump a whole
lot of presents on us!
I wonder will he be able to
put a present in here...
Don't worry, just put another one!
Okay, I'll do that!
Candy, borrow me your socks!
They are probably the largest here!
Oh, John!
Sister Pony, the children are
so cheerful...
Who knows where they'll be next year...
They are hiding something from us.
I'm sure there is a reason
Sister Pony is so worried.
Why didn't Mr. Cartwright
listen to us?
Cartwright?
It's impossible to get to him
with his cowboys guarding the gate...
Anyway, he'll let us stay here
until the spring, right?
It makes no sense!
He saw us collecting donations
and suddenly came up with this idea!
But it's his land, after all...
And if he wants to extend his farm...
Sister Pony, we should try again
to speak to him.
Yes, we'll go after Christmas...
Pony's home is going to disappear!
Then...
It's your last Christmas here,
you deserve a nice big tree...
It's your last Christmas here.
No...
This can't be happening!
Jimmy! Where are you? Jimmy!
I'm here, boss!
Come here!
Did I do something...?
Jimmy, how old are you?
I'm seven year old...
Alright. You're old enough then.
I'm an adult. Okay?
Now we're going to have
an adult-to-adult talk.
So that's how it is, dammit!
I'm gonna kick that Cartwright's ass!
That's right, because he wants
to kick us out!
Huh? Jimmy?
I'm here!
Boss!
Geez, you sure fell in!
Anyway, we'll first try to talk
to him in a civilized manner!
Yup, in a civilized manner!
And if that doesn't work,
we'll use the force!
Okay!
It's here.
Boss, this house is scary.
You're an adult, aren't you?
Pull yourself together!
I'm okay now!
He already owns such a big house
why does he need the land
where Pony's home is?
That's right!
Now, let's go!
We'll try the main doors first.
If that doesn't work out, we'll have to
look around for him a bit.
What are you two?
Uh... we're looking for
Mr. Cartwright...
I'm in charge of
all the cowboys here.
What business do you have
with Mr. Cartwright?
We'd like to talk to
Mr. Cartwright directly...
He doesn't have time to waste on kids!
Go home!
-Yes!
-Jimmy!
Please tell him that kids from
Pony's home want to speak to him...
Jimmy, smile!
So you're filthy runts from Pony's home?
Filthy?!
Boss, smile!
Well, we may look a bit dingy
when compared to this estate...
Maybe so!
So what business do such dingy kids
have in beautiful Cartwright's estate?
Next year, Mr. Cartwright is going to
become a first cattle herder here!
First one?
If that happens, those meadows will be
completely overrun by cows!
You'd better get out here
before that happens!
Mr. Cartwright had warned you,
he's so nice! Right, kiddies?
What do you mean, " nice" ?
Jimmy
we are going to see Mr. Cartwright.
Hey, wait!
Get out, now!
If you don't get out,
I'll throw you out myself!
What's all that noise?
Throw out those two kids!
-Now they're angry at us, Jimmy!
-Okay!
-Wait!
-They're going towars the barn!
Surround the barn!
Damn it, we have to catch the horses!
Hey, wait!
This is great!
Now, Jimmy
let's find Mr. Cartwright...
Huh? Jimmy?
Where'd he go... Jimmy!
Mr. Hoittman?
No, it couldn't be him.
But... he looks just mr. Hoittman...
the gardener at Leagan's estate.
He looks exactly like him from the back!
The kind Mr. Hoittman
who worked together with Anthony.
Maybe he is Cartwright's gardener?
Hello, young lady.
Aren't you cold like that, mister?
Nah, I'm working here
to protect the trees from cold.
Young lady, where are you from?
I'm a widow from Pony's home!
A widow? That's a good one!
By the way, mister
I came here to speak to
Mr. Cartwright... can I see him?
So why did you come all the way
here to see him?
Because Mr. Cartwright is
a greedy old cheapskate!
A greedy old cheapskate?
That's right!
He wants to drive out
the children from Pony's home
and build a huge farm in its place!
I was raised at Pony's home.
To all abandoned children
Pony's home is their homeland!
If that house disappears...
if that hill disappears...
Mr. Cartwright doesn't think of
the children!
Mister, don't you think so, too?
Hey, don't you think so?
He has so much land and yet
he's a greedy old cheapskate!
-You're hurting me!
-I'm sorry!
Anyway, I have to talk to him.
I'll get him to understand
the issue with Pony's home.
Don't get so angry...
If he still doesn't understand,
Mr. Cartwright isn't human!
He's nothing but a hideous monster!
Stop!
-Help!
-Wait!
Jimmy!
Boss!
Where did you go?
Run for it!
Mr. Cartwright!
What should we do with them?
Mr. Cartwright?
Him?
That's me, a greedy old cheapskate
Cartwright!
I'm so sorry!
I had no idea who you are...
I said a terrible thing...
But you looked so kind, the exact
opposite of a greedy old cheapskate!
I'm sorry!
-Run for it!
-Boss!
-Stop! I'm gonna fire!
-No!
It's all over now.
I wanted to be strong like
sister Pony and sister Lane...
Mr. Cartwright must be mad.
Even though this happened...
sister Pony and sister Lane
will try to speak to him again.
Candy, you idiot!
Doing such a stupid thing...
Stupid!
Jimmy, it wasn't your fault.
But... I provoked them...
That kid!
Wait!
And while they were going after me...
I ran into you, boss.
I'm so sorry!
We can't leave it like this...
I'll have to apologize to him.
Candy!
Come to teacher's room!
Yes!
Sister Lane is mad because of
what I did...
Come in!
Candy, look at all the presents.
Please help us out!
Yes, teacher.
She isn't mad. Mr. Cartwright
didn't tell her anything.
But why didn't he tell her
immediately?
There's no way that he would stay
silent after I lashed out on him.
Anyway, I have to return to
his house and apologize.
And beg him once again...
Sister Pony, sister Lane!
Christmas tree is done!
Please come and see it!
Okay!
You made it very well!
Santa will be happy!
How could anybody chase out
all these cute kids...
That's it!
Jimmy!
Find out when will
Mr. Cartwright be at home.
Okay!
That's right... there is no other way.
Sister Pony!
It's horrible! Sister Pony!
What's the matter, sister Lane?
All children are gone!
What?
Candy!
Jimmy!
You all have your stuff?
Yes!
You'll put that on for Christmas!
Jimmy, it's true what you said, right?
I hid and heard everything!
Tommorow
cowboys will have a day off!
A great time to come to their place!
God, please let this turn out well.
For Mr. Cartwright and his new farm!
Cheers!
Guys, you worked well this year!
Now, I want you to return to your
homes and have a wonderful time!
I haven't been home so long...
I want to see my kids...
My brother will kill me
if I don't get him a present...
What's that jingling sound...?
It's coming from behind the
Christmas tree...
A present of angels!
They will give you happiness
and their kindness.
Uh, Mr. Cartwright...
I'm really sorry for what happened
the other day.
This is a Christmas present
from Pony's home.
Will you accept it?
These angels... all of them
are from Pony's home?
Yes.
Anyway, I let you manage the
expansion of the farm, right?
Yes.
Leave Pony's home as it is, then.
But...
It's an order.
If I chase out these angels
I'm gonna roast in hell!
Mr. Cartwright.
Mr. Cartwright
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I have a tomboyish daughter
she is just like you.
Anyway, I've never got a present
as nice as this one!
Candy!
Sister Pony, sister Lane!
Pony's home is now going to stay
our homeland forever!
-Yes, we heard.
-Candy, we owe it to you.
It was a wonderful Christmas night
to everyone.
Merry Christmas!