Candy worked hard to become
one of the Leagans.
But instead, they turned her
into a servant.
On the same day, Candy met
a well dressed boy called Archibald.
Archie comforted Candy
who lost herself in sadness.
Invitation of happiness.
Candy!
Yes, what is it?
Candy
won't you come with me?
I'm going to town
to buy a new dress!
To buy a new dress?
Eliza, hurry up!
What are you doing there?
It's so fun!
That's right. More good things
are about to happen.
What things?
Things that have nothing
to do with you.
You wait here.
Yup, my thoughts exactly.
Take this.
This too.
Thank you, Mr. Steyn!
Come on, hold them up a bit.
Be careful, Candy
Is this all we had to buy?
That's it.
Candy, can you do something
for me?
Won't you buy two books for me
"Elegance" and " French doll's dream" .
I can do that.
No, it's okay.
Candy, you go.
Here's " Elegance" ,
what's up with " French doll" ?
Dream. " French doll's dream."
I wonder if we have one of those.
Hold on.
They really did
what they had in mind.
Well, got me this time.
Can't help it, I'll have to go
back on foot.
Archie's friend!
How are you?
You're the person who called
Archie from the car?
Going for a walk all alone?
That's not it.
They left me behind.
That's horrible.
I'll give you a lift!
Thanks!
-Well, get in!
-Thanks.
Alright, let's go!
Alistear's special vehicle!
It's a wonderful car!
And incredibly fast, too!
Is it? I built it.
This is a test drive.
Test drive?
I plunged into the lake the other day!
I got lucky though.
Hey, here's the lake!
Are you afraid?
-You don't have to be!
-I'm not!
I could let go of the steering wheel.
The steering is so precise!
Don't let go of that!
-It's okay!
-I'm not so sure!
I know a shortcut from here.
It will get you back faster
to Eliza's place.
You know Eliza?
Unfortunately
Eliza is a relative of mine.
Then... you're one of the Adleys?
Yes. I'm from the Adley family
Archie's older brother
Alistear Cornwell.
-Nice to meet you.
-Archie's brother?
It's okay if you call me Stear.
I'm Candy! Candice White!
That's such a sweet name!
I wonder if he knows anything
about the Prince.
He must know something!
But I still don't know his name.
The wheel fell off again.
Bummers!
What are you going to do?
I'll have to build another one.
How can you be so carefree
after something like this?
Nevertheless, this has
spoiled my day a bit.
By the way,
how will you get back?
It's okay with me.
I planned to go back on foot
anyway.
That would be a sad
way to come back.
I told you, I'm okay with this!
That's right!
Follow me, Candy!
I'll show you another shortcut.
Shortcut?
It might be a little
difficult for a girl.
I'm fine with that!
Leagan's property is on the
far side of this marsh.
You cross it through the trees!
Through the trees?
What, I'll show you.
One might get hurt this way!
Now, come along, Candy!
Hey, you can do it!
Candy, thanks.
I'm used to places like these,
so it's okay.
Okay, let's head that way.
I'm going!
It's the hill behind Leagan's estate!
I almost forgot about you!
You're almost there!
I'm not cut out for this.
Stear, are you okay?
Yeah. I couldn't follow you at all.
I can go alone from here!
Thank you, Stear.
Nah, it's nothing. See you again.
Okay.
-See you then.
-Farewell!
Candy!
What's the matter, Stear?
Now I know the reason Archie
called you " miss tomboy" !
Oh no. I forgot to ask him
about the Prince.
Stear!
Okay. I'll ask you the next time
we meet!
Kurin! I'm back.
Thanks for waiting me here!
Brother!
-What's the matter, Eliza?
-Candy is back!
What? Already?
I thought that she would have come back
late at night, if she went on foot!
I'm sure those two are surprised.
Kurin
I was swimming in the lake!
I'm so good at crawl swim!
-No way.
-That's a lie! She's so rude!
Did you hear? Mistress and Master
say that there'll be trouble!
Mary, who will be arriving then?
The head of the Adley family will
be moving into this place!
The head of the Adley family?
That's grand aunt Elroy, right?
I heard that she's a really
scary person!
That's why entire family
is throwing a big party.
And that's why Eliza
was buying that dress.
Big party...?
This has nothing to do with you!
That's right. It really has
nothing to do with me.
Doesn't this dress
look good on me?
-Candy?
-Yes, come in!
-Why are you sneezing?
-It's nothing.
Aren't you wet?
A bit.
I was in the lake.
They pulled a prank on you, again?
Don't worry!
You were out on a walk?
Yeah! I was trying to find
my Prince!
But I found two of them!
Two princes?
It almost sounds like a fairy tale.
Maybe it really does
sound like a fairy tale!
Candy!
By the way
was there something else?
Oh, I forgot!
Miss Eliza wants to see you!
I see.
Candy?
What's the matter, Dorothy?
Don't give in to them.
Don't worry, Dorothy!
Thanks.
It's Candy!
Enter!
Candy, what do you think?
Does it look good on me?
It's beautiful!
Don't touch it!
You'll get it dirty.
Eliza!
Yes?
Let me see!
Yes!
This time, Mother will wear
her swan-style hat.
-It's pretty.
-Eliza?
Yes! Coming!
It really is pretty.
What are you doing?
That's not the kind of dress to be seen
on someone from Pony's home!
Now, get out.
Quickly, get out!
It was looked so good on me...
What?
These were sent in by the Adley family.
This is...
What?
An invitation to the party!
But we already received all
the invitations.
This one is for Candy.
"We invite miss Candice White
to the Adley family party."
"Please kindly escort her to the party."
"Alistear Cornwell."
What, Stear inviting Candy...?
How come he knows her?
There's an another invitation, exactly
like this one, but it's from Archie.
Archie?
What's the meaning of this?
Anyway, call Candy.
Yes.
Enter!
Candy. Now, come here.
Candy.
You know Stear and Archie?
Yes.
Where did you meet them, Candy?
Where did I...
I met both of them by chance!
But one at a time!
By chance, you say?
No way.
You got invitations from
both of them.
What? lnvitations from Stear
and Archie? Wonderful!
Here they are.
Stear and Archie have invited me!
I don't approve of that!
If you bring Candy with youself,
I will not be going!
These invitations are official, so
there's no way I can't take her.
It's okay to take her
but is that the kind of dress
to wear to the party?
That's right!
She can't go in that dress!
She could borrow
one of your dresses.
What, one of mine...?
Eliza, borrow her something.
If I let her go dressed
like a hillbilly
she'll make all the Leagans
look bad.
I won't !
I understand.
Thank you, Eliza!
Take this.
Wow, it's pretty!
I'll go out, let us
see you when you're done.
Okay.
What's going on, Eliza?
What's on your mind?
I had it made three years ago.
It's a bit tight.
Well, Candy?
You're much fatter than I am!
You won't be able to go
to the party like that!
Give up already!
What are you doing?!
Give it back!
My favorite dress!
Why did you do that?
I'm sorry.
You can't fix this
by apologizing!
What's with her?
-Candy!
-What happened?
Why have Stear and Archie
invited me in the first place?
Stupid!
Candy?
What happened, Candy?
It doesn't suit you!
Dress doesn't matter.
Go to that party.
The dress doesn't matter at all!
Candy, believe in yourself.
Wipe your tears then!
You're a wonderful girl.
And that's why Stear and Archie
invited you.
Even this dress will look
wonderful on you.
Put this on and go.
And smile!
Dorothy...
You're smiling, Candy.
That's right, you're pretty!
And that smile suits you best!
Miss freckle...?
That smile looks good on you.
Your friends will wait for
you there, I'm sure.
-Candy!
-Welcome, Candy!
Dorothy, I'll go!
Even like this!
That's the spirit!
Thank you, Dorothy!
I won't cry anymore.
That's more like it!
They both saw a falling star.
It was the star of unity.
Candy's spirit lightened up,
almost as if it wanted to dance.