Don't know when, Nil began to love Candy.
After knowing this,
Ilasha want her mother to drive
Candy out of Chicargo.
Then, Candy was asked to the dean's offıce.
The recovery memory.
Candy, you don't have to work here after today.
And the other hospital in Chicargo
will not use you either.
Fired, I am fıred by the hospital.
Sir,
I don't understand you.
After all, you're fıred.
Sir,
you said I am fıred and other hospital
will not use me again.
What can I do?
I can't leave my job.
Candy, you must think for me.
Is this the order from the dean?
It's none of his business.
Someone has higher position?
Candy, what's the relation between you and Rain?
It's like this.
Mr. Rain will not do this.
You mean Mrs. Rain.
It must be Mrs. Rain. Dean.
Yes.
It must be Ilasha and Nil.
I know.
It's Mrs. Rain, I can't do anything.
I will resign.
Sorry, Candy.
I want to be a nurse so I came here.
I made it and I want to do more.
But, now, I have to say good bye.
If I said I was fıred
Arupate will be very disappointed.
I will not say it to him.
Arupate, what's wrong?
What's wrong with me, suddenly...
Buby.
I feel bad, very bad.
So beautiful new car.
Nil.
Thank you for you inviting.
I want to drive this car too
where do you want to take me to?
Don't joke, I...
Nil, it's ok, you decided.
Shit.
Kill time in this place, so bored.
I want to go back earlier, tidy my room.
It's Candy.
Good, I will drive by her.
Candy, we want to have a ride.
Yes, Nil.
Nil.
What, Candy.
Nothing, you baster.
Ah, it's a new car.
As you wish, I was fıred by the hospital.
I will not quit.
Who's that, so rude.
Bad.
She must feel bad to see you and me together.
Perhaps.
She's not happy to fınd I break up with her.
You're popular, that's good.
Candy was fıred by the hospital.
Dairy, please get down, please.
What, Nil?
I think some important thing, I am sorry.
Nil, what about me?
Candy, welcome.
I came back, Mr. Tomas.
It's early today.
Yes, I came earlier.
The empty apartment.
Though there's no hope
I will fınd the hospital to hire me.
Tidy the apartment. Surprise Arupate.
Boby.
Where's this place? Why am I here?
It seems I sleep here for a long time.
Boby, haha.
Yes, Candy.
I always think of her smile.
We meet in a lot of place.
When we are in danger on the sea.
When Ansoni died.
And when I was in London
I received your letter from Africa.
Then, there's an explore of the train.
Then, live with Candy.
That's right, I fainted while I throw the dish.
This is the dining room.
Boby, I thought it.
Haha, Candy was fıred by the hospital.
That's you, Ilasha.
Brother is also happy.
En.
Yes.
We had plan to drive Candy out of Chicargo.
It's just for Candy.
What should I do, Boby.
I recovered my memory
can I staty with Candy too?
Because only patient and nurse canbe together.
Boby, you want to see Candy, right?
Yes, back.
Don't tell Candy about it.
Sorry, we are not ready for the nurse.
I am refused by so many hospital.
The other hospital in Chicargo
will not hire you anymore.
Mrs. Rain has a very big power.
Candy, Candy.
Arupate, and Doctor Maqin.
So reflaxed.
You should be fıred by the hopital.
Ah.
Really, Candy.
Yes.
And the lion. Run away.
Arupate.
Candy.
Lion, that's too bad.
Stand back.
Do you hide behind the tree?
Candy.
Arupate.
It can't be like this.
Think someway.
Put down your gun.
The lion is out of control.
Believe, I must shoot.
Don't.
Don't be afraid. I am not your enemy.
I know your hometown in Africa.
Come, I am your friend.
Ok, good boy.
Arupate, you're a real man.
The lion is just like a kitty.
Haha.
I thought I will die this time.
How?
I am really worried.
Candy, you're a really good nurse.
It's a waste to be a nurse.
Little nurse.
Do you want to work under the most
amous doctor in Chicargo?
I will introduce for you.
Which doctor?
I am.
You don't want to?
No, but you called yourself
the fırst in Chicargo.
Please help me in the future.
So it's a deal.
Next one.
It's ok.
Thank you, Candy.
Candy, where's the key?
Here.
You're very brave, give you praise.
After Candy came here
more patients come here too.
I don't know what to do without Candy here.
Here, drink it slowly.
Take a good rest in the noon.
Thank you.
Candy can be the best nurse in the world.
Thank you for your praise.
I will go to dinner now.
I add a half of water here
I don't know whether it will be discovered.
We must help the doctor to recover the clinic.
Candy, get on.
Nil, I am waiting for you.
Candy, don't you hear it?
I heard it.
Get up.
Leave me alone.
I help you to fınd the new job.
Don't worry, I fınd it.
Please help me with other things.
Really, I will listen to you, Candy.
What do you want to do?
Don't follow me anymore.
Idiot, you still miss the bad guy.
Look at the book.
Teli.
On the fırst page
Teli resign the work in the theater.
Teli, don't you want to be an actor anymore.
I don't know where did he go.
After Teli and I depart, he's in sadness.
He must be sadder than me.
That summer just like a dream.
You can't realize your dream.
Susan, Teli and Susan.
After departed with me, he's still in sadness
And susan accompany him.
What, anything else?
What, the continance is terrible.
Arupate.
Arupate, drive the car.
After introducing by Taska,
I fınd a job and save some money.
It's really old.
But, it ride fast.
Don't worry, I have asked doctor Maqin.
I am happy.
I bring food.
Arupate is careful.
But, I only bring for one person.
It doesn't matter, we share it.
Candy, it's good to share with you.
Ah.
Please share your trouble and sadness with me.
Arupate.
It's a deal.
Thank you, Aprupate.
See you tomorrow, Doctor.
Ok, thank you.
Thanks to you, I have a long rest in the noon.
That's ok.
See you.
Don't drink too much.
I know.
Good bye, sister.
Good bye.
Are you Miss Candy?
Yes.
Someone asked me to look for you.
Want to see me?
His name is Dilusy.
Dilusy.
It's Teli, Teli came to see me.
Could you follow me?
Yes.
Teli, I thought everything is over.
I thought you know me.
Everything will be better.
Just in the villa.
Teli, Teli.
Candy was happy while thinking
she can see Teli again.