At the end of the
difficult journey
Mr. Garcia rescued Candy
from attacking bandits
However...
a man in the automobile
took Candy away
Just where is Candy being taken to?
This is... a hotel?
You did good, Sam
Thank you, Mr. George
I'll be departing immediately
I'm leaving the rest to you.
As you wish.
That man must be the
kidnapper's boss!
If I don't run now...
Kurin, now's our chance.
Wait!
Help me, Kurin!
Put me down!
Somebody help me!
Kurin!
Do something!
Let me go!
Put me down!
She's kind of strange.
That's not true!
I was kidnapped!
Help me!
She's coming!
What... what are you doing?
I'll leave her to you.
Yes.
Now, please.
What?
Just who are you?
What are you doing!
Kurin!
I want to be alone
in the bathroom!
We'll make you look
extra pretty for Mr. George
George!
That's the man I saw before!
Just who is this George?
I do'nt know
We are his employees us but we
don't really know him all that well.
Will you let me escape then?
Escape?
I was kidnapped!
Kidnapped? You?
It's true!
That man named Sam
is the one who kidnapped me!
Oh well.
Why would a kidnapper want
to give you such a wonderful dress?
It's ...
It's for me?
Yeah.
What is the meaning of this?
-So beautiful!
-It looks good on you.
Really!
It suits me perfectly.
It looks good on me
But why was I
given such a wonderful dress...?
It's pretty.
I'm sure Mr. George
will be pleased.
George...
you don't know much about him
right?
Yeah. But I know that he's
a good gentleman from London
From London?
Perpetrators are using an
automobile to kidnap children...
who are then sold off to Europe.
Be careful!
I'm sure the sheriff was
talking about this George guy!
But... his gentle face was...
No! One can't judge people
by the look on their face alone!
Mr. Garcia looked scary but he
turned out to be a very good person.
I'm sure that these people
are trying to deceive me as well.
If I don't do something
I'll be sold off to London!
After all, this old dress still
suits me best.
Alright now.
Let's go, Kurin!
It's okay!
Kurin, don't look down!
Follow me!
Kurin, I'm okay!
Hurry up now!
Well, Candy?
Will you promise that
you won't try to flee again?
I had no option but to lock
you up in here.
Can't help it
I'll have to keep you in here
until you depart tommorrow.
Depart tommorrow?
Where to?
First I want you to promise me that
you won't try to flee again!
I'm not sure about that!
I was ordered by mr. George
to bring you to him
Don't hate me for that
It looks like I'll be taken
to London, after all.
Anthony...
You're still thinking that
I've gone to Mexico, right?
But I don't want to go to London
Yeah, I have you, Kurin.
I won't give up!
Anthony, what's the matter?
Can't you dance more cheerfully?
I don't want to dance.
You must
Aunt Elroy did this party for me
am I right?
I'm just not in the mood for this
I'm sure he's thinking about Candy!
Ever since Candy left...
he has become cold to me again
-No!
-Eliza?
No! We have to dance!
-Oh, boy
-Poor Anthony!
What's the matter?
-Garcia!
-Madam
I'm very sorry!
What happened?
Candy was...
Candy was kidnapped!
Candy...!?
Calm down, everyone.
Tell us everything
in the back room.
Everyone
please continue the party!
I haven't noticed that they were
following us day and night!
How could you
allow this to happen?
I'm so sorry!
When we were around
Yellow Rock, suddenly...
Immediately inform Pony's home
about this incident!
This is of utmost importance
I am sorry
Do everything you can...
to take Candy away from
hands of those kidnappers!
Yes!
Stear, Archie!
Let's rescue Candy ourselves!
That's right, Anthony!
It was in Yellow Rock, right?
Alright, let's go!
Wait!
Anthony! Stear! Archie!
Anthony!
Candy... We'll save you...
we'll save you for sure!
Hang in there.
-I called the car for you.
-Thanks.
Thank you for your work.
Send my regards to Mr. George
Miss, take care
Everyone is being deceived by
this George guy.
Give this to sheriff!
Sheriff?
Please!
Yes
"I was kidnapped
please send help. Candy."
Just what is this?
Maybe she's a bit fuzzy in here?
They all go crazy once they
hit puberty!
Why do you keep looking behind?
It's nothing...
It seems that sheriff
won't be coming to help me
Brother, are you sure
we're going the right way?
Don't say that!
Stear, can't you go any faster?
I can do that, but
the car will come apart!
If we don't get there soon
Candy will...
Hey there, Mr. lmpatient.
We don't even know
where Candy is yet.
Candy was kidnapped
near Yellow Rock!
She couldn't have gotten far!
Brother
understand Anthony's feelings!
Alright, I'll step on it!
Why are you giving me treats and
letting me bathe every day?
I want you to look a little bit
more pretty and elegant.
That was George's idea, too?
That's right
When I bring you home...
I want you to look like a real lady
I knew it!
They want me to look elegant
so I could be sold at a higher price!
I won't let you do that!
Stop the car!
What's the matter?
Candy!
If I do this
nobody will want me!
I'll have you washed
as soon as we return!
But you won't be able to
wash the dress!
You've got plenty of clothes
to change into!
This.. This too!
This is Mississippi.
A ship!
They descend down the river and
go across the ocean to Europe.
To Europe?
London! That means...
I'm supposed to board this ship?
No! I don't want to go!
Candy!
Damn it.
It seems that he hasn't noticed us!
An automobile!
A tire blew out!
Just when we were in such a hurry!
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
Did you see a girl with a raccoon?
What?
That girl... was she called Candy?
That's right.
-That means...
-It's you!
What are you doing?
Where is Candy?
-She escaped!
-Escaped?
Alright, let's go!
What are you doing?
We'll trade cars!
But...
Hey, wait!
Keep going...
I already got this far.
A station!
Sam's car!
I happen to see her,
I'll report it.
Please.
It's time!
Candy... where are you?
But I'm glad that you managed
to get away from the bad guys.
I wonder where is this train
going to.
I don't care where it takes me.
As long as it goes to America
where Anthony is it'll be okay
We've stopped.
I wonder where am I.
-And what are you?
-Kurin!
What are you doing there?
Hey, wait!
If you go into that forrest,
you'll get lost!
There are Sam's accomplices
on this station, too.
If they caught me this time
I'd be done for!
Where...
Just where am I?
I'm so tired.
I can't walk anymore.
Anthony!
Kurin, you were watching over me
the whole time?
Thank you!
This smell...!
The rose gates!
This place is then...
This is Anthony's ...
Anthony!
Candy!
I believed that
you would make it home!
But to find you in this place...
-Hey, you two!
-Come with us!
Where to?
Of course, to talk to aunt Elroy!
I am right here.
Aunt!
Wasn't Candy kidnapped?
So what is she doing here?
Candy managed to escape.
Escape?
Then all of this was just
another one of your pranks?
You've misunderstood us!
That's grandfather William's car.
Grandfather William is here?
George!
Candy,
why do you know George?
I was abducted by him!
That's impossible!
Aunt, it really is true that I ordered
Sam to kidnap Candy
Just why did you...
I was instructed to do so
by grandfather William himself.
By William?
I'm here to deliver you this letter
from Mr. William.
Servant of the Leagan family.
Candice White.
Now my foster daughter.
Signed William A. Adley.
I am... adopted
by the Adley family?
He really read my letter!
What?
you wrote him a letter as well?
Bro, you too?
Of course! I wrote it as well.
I'm sure I wrote it before you guys
This guy...
George! Take Candy away now!
You and William
are working together...
how else could he have made
such a whimsical decision...
Such important affairs.
I am responsible to Mr. William
I understand
William's decisions are final
There's nothing I can do.
William's whims again...!
Aunt is so scary and cold.
But if I can live with Anthony...
I can bear anything!
That's great, Candy.
Miss Candice White Adley.
Sounds great!
Thank you, everyone!
Thanks to everybody, I am...
There were tears in Candy's eyes
Yet those were warm tears, tears
which have already long forgotten...
everything bad that had happened
up until now.