Candy saved the Susan in the storm.
Leave me alone.
Live, Susan.
Susan loves Taris so much.
She wanted to protect Taris even
to lose her own feet.
She loved Taris so much,
and she wishes them happy all the time.
Leave the footprint in Broadway in the snow.
The sorrow platform.
Candy,
don't leave me.
Let time stop.
Taris.
Don't say anything, let me hug you.
Taris
My dearest Taris, let's break up.
Please be happy, Candy,
or I will not forgive you.
The same to Taris.
Why should I come to Broadway?
Why?
Hot.
A lillte hot.
Caught cold while walking in the snow.
It's noisy, please keep quiet.
Sorry.
Darling, it's ok, don't be afraid.
Sit down please.
But#
I am ok. Please sit down, poor child.
Thank you.
Someone can help us.
I am sorry.
It doesn't matter. Don't cry.
Come.
Good. Baby loves you.
Sleep.
Thank you.
Thank you for your help.
Where?
Cidy, the happy music box
makes the baby happy.
I don't feel well. The couple need help.
I dreamed to love each other
with Taris.
But#
It's only a dream.
And the dream is over.
Taris.
We will meet again.
Of course. I believe it.
But, we can't see each other again.
We can't.
Taris.
Miss, what's wrong?
Have a high fever.
Do you have any credentials?
A letter
Candy Arid.
From Arid family.
Arid family, contact as soon as possible.
Where's the music from?
Cidy's music box.
It can make you happy.
Cidy, I don't feel happy with this rhythm.
Your invention failed.
Why are you luaghing? Who are you?
Fragrant rose.
Antoni.
No, this is Taris'rose.
Fans sent it to Taris.
Don't leave, Taris.
I am here, Candy.
Candy, cheer up.
Anne.
Good. You recover at last.
Where#
Adri's home.
You fainted in the train.
But, why am I in Adri's home?
You have a letter with you.
The letter Taris sent to me for
the receipt paper.
After he receive it
Alqi went there as soon as possible.
Alqi?
Candy, you are nurse. Why are you ill?
Nearly caught pneumonia.
Come in.
Candy.
Pady Alqi.
Good. You wake up.
It's ok. Just faint.
Candy.
Pady.
Why?
Alqi and Anne. Everyone knows
I broke up with Taris.
I must cheer up and don't upset them.
Pady, don't cry. Cheer up.
It's a pity, but this is the fortune.
Candy.
I will not give up.
No word for goodbye.
Goodbye, to whom?
I didn't see Cidy.
Pady, why goodbye?
Everybody, what's wrong with Cidy?
Anne.
Big brother join the army in France.
Cidy joined the army in France?
So,
in the European battle
the situation becomes worse to worse.
After you went to Broadway,
no word left only a key.
In the platform, Cidy sent me in the train.
Then, Cidy made up his mind.
It's a pity to travel alone.
Does he come to say goodbye to us?
Why didn't I know it then?
Cidy.
That's too much, Candy.
He left this letter and hope I will forgive him.
Dear Patria,
I hope you will not blame me.
When I write the letter
your smile is in my mind.
I decided to join the army.
Not just playing the plane.
See you later.
Why see me later?
What about dead?
Pady, don't think too much.
Pady, don't be sad.
Cidy needs your considering for him.
You're the best friend of big brother.
Best? Why didn't hide it from me?
Why is there no one telling me?
Pady, don't cry.
I broke up with Taris.
I can't help it.
I negelect the big brother's thought.
I always thought he's just joking.
Alqi.
Taris, Cidy.
I have a headache.
Granny.
How dare you to come here!
Alqi, why did you pick her up?
Daughter?
It's a shame.
This kind of daughter from Adrie's family.
After you came to Adrie's, there's bad fortune.
Atoni had accident
Lord William never comes back.
Now, it's Cidy.
Antoni, then Cidy.
The granny lost two young master.
Adopting you is Lord William's biggest failure.
I can't stand it.
I don't allow you to step
in Adrie's home once more.
Granny.
Ok.
Candy, Aldrie,
I want to give up this name earlier.
Candy, you have fever.
I go back.
You know the shame.
Listen carefully, not come here any more.
Granny. That's too much.
Don't be so cruel.
That's ok, Alqi.
Ask Ilasa and Nil to go home
to talk about Cidy.
Candy, I am sorry.
Granny is always like this.
After big brother left, she became worse.
No, I can understand her.
Are you all right, Candy?
Cheer up.
Cidy said to see you later.
He will come back soon, just like before.
Really?
Of course.
He wrote in his letter, he will not really leave.
Really?
You can't see him again for he really leaves.
Just like Taris and me.
Cidy, I really want to see you.
Complain your happy music box.
No happiness at all.
This is the music box for break up.
That's too bad.
He'll smile and apologize to me.
Cidy.
Are you all right, Candy?
Be careful about the laders.
That's ok.
I am tired.
I hope Mr. Albert will make me relax.
He sure will.
Mr. Albert.
Candy.
Welcome, Candy.
She has a high fever.
And she fainted in the train.
They informed us.
Thank you.
Is Candy ok?
Don't worry about her, I will take care of her.
Thank you, Mr. Albert.
Alqi, for Cidy, you must be tired about it.
Yes.
Cidy will come back.
Good bye, Mr. Albert.
Please look after Candy.
Leave her to me. I will take good care of her.
Candy is ill. That's rarely.
Candy.
What's wrong?
Mr. Albert.
I broke up with Taris.
We met each other again.
But now, we can't see each other any more.
Candy.
If only I was
a selfish man.
Leave me alone.
I will make Taris sadder.
And you will not be happy either.
Susan.
For Taris, I must die.
I can't let you do it.
You are sad, Taris is just the same as you.
Leave me alone, Candy.
I will just disturb you.
Live, Susan.
She'd rather die to make Taris and me happy.
I can't speak it out. I love Taris.
If it's me, I will do the same thing.
If Taris gave up Susan, will you love him?
This is the Taris I loved.
Cry, Candy, and forget all.
Are you tired?
Have a good rest.
The fever gone.
The fever is running away.
You can joke, that's all right.
I will buy some food for you.
Thank you, Mr. Albert.
Pupy, look after Candy.
Come here, Pupy.
It's ok that Mr. Albert look after me.
Do you go back for food?
And let Candy to have it.
I miss Candy's smile.
I will make her recover as soon as possible.
Dangerous.
Too bad.
Many are shouting.
The consciousness are vague and vague.
Candy.
She didn't know Mr. Albert had an accident,
and she just fell into sleep.