Albert left a letter and left Candy.
What makes Candy sadder is Stia's death.
Patty went to Florida with sadness.
Candy hoped everyone can gain happiness.
The day to meet the lord
Albert didn't go to Stia's funeral.
But, there's no news of Stia's death.
The great Granny came.
For the other country
died in the far away place.
It's really a great attack for her.
Albert, the optimistic Stia is dead.
Can you come to me and comfort me like before?
Albert, where are you?
The empty room, only me.
Candy, I made something good for you.
The war in Europe is very cruel
I am worried about Stia.
Newspaper, yes, the newspaper.
Yes, the Findings.
Record here, he will come back.
Perhaps we can fınd Seli too.
What should I write, Please come back, Albert?
No, it can't move Albert.
What about I am ill?
This is?
The reality of the real lord of the Altly.
He didn't show up before
and known as a strange man.
Now, he was show up as the lord.
Who's he, everyone's expect it.
Lord William, I am taken care by him
but I never saw him.
Who's he?
Come.
Albert.
Nil.
Albert is the man who lost memory.
He's not a leisure man.
He left you, didn't he?
I can know your fact after I inspect it.
Why do you want to inspect me?
A lot of reason.
Why? That's only my privacy.
I will marry you.
Marry, you and I?
I want to notify you.
Notify? Do you think I will marry you?
It will be like that.
Why do you want to marry me
you always treated me so bad.
Because I love you.
But I don't love.
You will love me someday.
Nil, do you remember the fırst
time I went to your home?
From then on, you always tease me
And I stood it.
If you treat me well then
now, it could be different.
Nil.
Do you want to water me?
The pulling water can't be collected back.
Go.
I will do it, I will not give up.
Why do all the people love me will leave me?
Arthe, Seli, Stia, and Albert.
Why, why?
Don't come.
What's wrong, Candy?
Doctor Mati,
you didn't come to the clinic, I am worried.
Sorry.
The tear is not good looking.
I know your feeling, but there's gather and apart
live and death in the life.
Come on, Candy, your patient needs your smile.
Everyone comes here.
We will pick up Candy.
Let's go to the Happy Clinic.
Let's go, to the happiness.
Nil, you're the inheritate of the Ragen's.
How can you marry that girl.
But she's the adopted daughte of the Alte's.
Their position is...
Nil.
Mother, agree brother.
Ilasha.
How can you talk nonsense.
I am against it.
But for brother, I will agree it.
Ilasha, thank you, you're really my sister.
Brother, I will persuade mother.
Please, Ilasha.
Mother.
Ilasha, I don't agree the nonsense.
Mother, think about it, if brother marries Candy,
her property will be brother's.
If so,
brother will be the heritate
of the Alte's family.
The old man is really old, he can't last long.
This is good. But I...
After brother becomes the inharitate
then drive her away.
Mother, there's a news of the old man.
Before that, let brother and Candy together.
I will discuss it with Lord Oloba fırst.
What, you come to say
this just after Stia's death.
Great Granny, I know you're angry
But this is big for the family.
Alte's?
If Candy marries someone unknown,
our property will lose too.
And the blood of the family
will be dirty too, at last...
Shut up.
So, it's ok to make brother marry Candy.
If you do not allow he to marry her
he will go to Europe to join the army.
No, I will not allow it.
I can't allow the young generation die.
So in order to protect the next generation
please make up your mind.
Ok.
The rain stops.
Candy.
Look, the rainbow.
Where?
It's really beautiful.
It's the carriage.
Yes.
Are you Miss Candy?
Alte, Candy, you're from Alte's adopted dauther.
Sorry, I didn't tell you before.
Lord William invites ou.
Lord William.
The clothes is ready, please change.
Come in, please.
I don't know Candy is the
adopted daughter of the Alte's.
The carriage is good, just like a princess.
That's right. Candy is the
adopted daughter of the rich family.
Candy, it's really beautiful.
Doctor Mati, Grandfather William is busy
this is the fırst time I saw him.
I have a lot of things to talk to him.
Go, Candy.
Thank you, Doctor Mati.
Good bye.
See you.
I can see grandfather at last.
I will thank him, and refuse to be the
adopted daughter of the Alte's.
Candy, you come at last.
Nil.
Come.
Brother, you are shy.
Irasha.
Candy, the grandmoher is waiting for you.
Great Granny, where's William?
You should see the great granny fırst.
Miss Candy, congratulations!
Congratulations!
What for?
Candy, the great granny is waiting for you.
Madam.
Go in.
Great granny, what do you want me for?
Candy, I want to you marry Nil.
Decision?
We will declare your engagement soon.
Great granny.
Candy, as Nil's fıancee
don't lose your politeness.
Wait, I didn't say I want to marry Nil.
It's none of your business.
What?
Candy, this is the command
of the grandfather William.
Grandfather William?
Great Granny.
That...
Candy, he looked after you so much
how can you refuse it.
We wanted to refuse it.
But, we can't disobey great grandfather.
That's too much.
Even he can not force me to marry anybody.
Albert, what should I do, Albert?
I brought the clothes.
Where's he?
He's not here.
Where is he?
We don't know, either.
I don't want to be marry him.
Yes, grandfather William will
show up before the bank.
Then, you can see him.
Miss Candy,
please don't tell anyone else.
Thank you.
You want to see Lord William?
Yes, he's here.
Wait, miss.
Grandfather, grandfather, that's too much.
John.
Yes, Miss Candy.
Where's the grandfather?
Why are you so excited?
How can I calm down, I don't want to marry Nil.
Marry, with Nil?
You don't know.
It's the order of Grandfather.
I am not the toy of him.
Miss Candy, I will prepare the car for you.
Car?
Lord William is in Raton.
Ah, Raton?
Nothing changed at all.
I miss it so much.
This is the road I pass the Ragen's.
The stone door of the Stia.
The watergate of the Ati.
The rose door of the brother.
Nothing changed.
The time passed
but the rose is as beautiful as before.
This is for you, Sweet Candy.
And the Ragen's House.
Candy.
Lord William wants to see you, this way, please.
No, I am too nervous.
Please go in.
Candy's heart beated heavily.
Grandfather William,
think to see him, and do this and that.
But she can't say a word.
Her legs shake, it's hard for her to stand up.
Grandfather William turn
the chair slowly to this way.