Thanks to Anti and Anne.
The cook made it.
In this way,
the car stopped outside.
And Maliu went on it.
No one knows it.
The sounds shakes the valley.
Now the sound of the air.
Cheear up.
You are young.
One can't drive that car.
That's right.
Because I drive it.
Then...
Let's begin to eat.
What's wrong with Maliu?
I didn't see her yet.
What's wrong with her. I will look for her.
Keli,did you see Maliu?
Really? Strange.
Where did she go?
Keli,follow me. Let's go to look for her.
How can you make it move.
It can't be moved.
Is this way?
It moves,moves.
Good,good.
I can find mother.
Hurry,hurry.
Hurry.
Maliu,it's dangerous. Stop.
Stop.
Candy. Maliu.
Maliu is on the top. What does she want to do?
Inspector.
It will run to the valley like this.
Who go to stop it.
Maliu,Candy,do it again?
Because,I want to go to mother.
Mother? Maliu.
Candy.
Help.
Come,hurry.
Help,help.
Is that Candy?
Candy is beside the car.
Maliu,can you hear me?
Candy,Maliu,stop.
Stop,hurry,please.
It's terrbile. Candy.
How to stop it,I don't know.
Calm down.
Listen. How did you make it move.
Turn it back.
Think of it. I can't.
Please.
Hurry,how it move.
You can do it,Maliu.
You can do it,please.
Hurry,hurry.
Ok.
Candy,she's dead.
Maliu's ok.
Candy is not dead.
Candy,where's Maliu.
Candy,Candy. Maliu.
Sleep at last.
She wants to see her mother.
I want to let her see her ealier.
A dream with mother in.
Candy,do you sleep with me tonight?
Yes,think of Boni's House.
When I feel lonely,
I will go to Candy's bed.
I met this.
I feel ashamed after I came here.
Why?
In Chicargo,Pady accompany me to the music hall.
But...
Compare to Candy working so hard here,
it's not right,Anne.
I like this place. It's good to me.
I don't want to go back to Chicargo.
I want to work with Candy here all the time.
Yes,left,yes. Yes.
The flower is lonely on the desk.
Where's brother?
Play.
Please come back before the party.
Anti and Anne will not come.
They will come back tonight.
Do you want to go to skiing with them?
You mean not go to ski?
Friends said,
they only see the villa.
So, two of them,
said where do they go.
Only Candy goes there.
Go,Candy.
I feel strange at first.
Too bad.
There's no party any more.
Remember.
Candy.
Anne,hurry up,it's neally 12.
Yes,yes.
They just come here for meat.
Anti becomes more like a cook.
She's so proud.
Inspector.
I will do it before noon.
Mr. Anti Brute Kel
Miss Anne White.
Why do you know their full name?
That's it.
We have telegram.
The daughter of the big boss can't be here.
We came by ourselves.
But how do you know?
Ilasha made it.
No matter what, go back to your home in Chicargo.
How.
You know it's Aduray's home.
How can he let they come to the desert.
Let me help more.
The hand.
It's impossible.
Candy,stop it.
That's all right,just break.
Do as what I said.
If not,I will fire you.
Why?
Why don't let me do it?
Look at this.
This is command.
Go the the set in Alaska.
It's the command from the Chicargo hospital.
It's the inform from the company.
Send the patient.
They can change the place freely.
But,in Alaska.
So, before fired you,
you don't have to go to Alaska.
So inspector...
I want to say something.
That's too much.
Why should I go too far.
Candy,does any one hate you so much?
Hate?
It must be Ilasha.
It must be the hand in our company.
We don't talk too much.
Fired. Go back to Chicargo with them.
I write a letter said not too many patient.
So you should go back.
No,I don't want.
So,you must go to Alaska.
I will go. I don't want to be fired.
Ilasha is so rude.
How?
Sorry.
Can Anti and Anne go back to Chicargo now?
If so,
what about Maliu?
Please,inspector.
Inspector.
The four sit in the car.
Then,Maliu.
After one week,the project will be finished.
We will become 1 1.
Then,you can see your mother.
Maliu,Candy.
I think it,bring Maliu to the Boni's House.
Yes,why didn't I think about it.
Candy,go to the car.
Inspector.
I will be fired.
Anti can cook very well.
Sorry to bring you so much trouble.
No. Candy.
Yes.
Inspector should be spiritual.
I am.
Maliu,come on.
Inspector.
We will start.
Thank you very much.
Good bye,Inspector.
Good bye,be careful.
Goodbye.
Just because I am here,it makes Candy trouble.
I am happy to work with Anne and Anti.
I didn't expect to work with Candy.
Candy,Candy.
It's the iron ball.
Black.
Why it's so dark?
The light in the kitchin is open.
Inspector.
What are you doing.
What's up?
Mother,it's mother.
Maliu.
Mother will come here.
Mother,Maliu.
It's dangerous,get away.
Are you alright,Magu,it's Magu.
Magu,mother. Magu,Mother.
Magu,cheer up.
Maliu,Mother.
That's all right,send to the clinic.
Runaway?
No,no.
After they think it,
they thought I am innocent.
That's good.
Inspector.
Can I sit in the car tomorrow?
First?
I want to go back to Chicargo ealier.
Stop her to work in Alaska.
I can do it.
We are the same with Ilasha.
So we have the same right.
I know. Let me arrange it.
Is this ok?
Not send her friend away.
You said good bye just now.
Candy,thanks for your caring.
This is my job.
Magu,you will be alright soon.
I am worried about the food too.
I must be working hard.
No matter what others say, before the project finished, I will not leave.
I will work hard.
The burn is ok. So don't worry.
Sorry,I didn't concern it.
Be patient.
Work,work.
Inspector.
Let Mr. Maliu have a rest.
What? So many wounds.
Just like imagine.
No time for rest now.
Stand up,back to the set.
Inspector.
It's too disordered.
Inspector,the nurse should be fired.
But,it needs a nurse here.
Don't be rude.
Or,you must go.
Thank you. We are saved.
Good weather.
It seems the spring is coming.
Candy.
Inspector ask you to go over.
Will he teach me again?
Why ask me to come here?
Don't be disturbed.
Are you angry,inspector?
Why everyone here?
Candy,come here.
But,but...
The inspector is looking for you.
Stop there.
Candy,press the handle of the box.
Handle of the box.
Hurry. Press it to the end of it.
I do it.
Look,it's ok.
Candy.
Inspector asked Candy to press the button
Inspector.
That man.
He's the hardest man here.
Hardest.
I am,I am...
Thank you,everyone.
Let's celebrate it.
Candy,the order from Chicargo.
Go back to the Chicargo hospital.
Before this,you have a week holiday.
Anti,contact with the company so soon.
Candy,you must learn to enjoy the date.
If you have boy friend.
That's too much.
Candy,Maliu,shout once more.
Candy,I am really moved. Maliu.
Thank you very much.
This is where Candy come.
Perhaps this is the honeymoon.
Honeymoon travel?
You can go with the car.
But the other one should be there.
Mr. Maliu.
Good bye,everyone.
Good bye.
Candy,she...
has great memory in the set of the Gulei town.
After one week,the project will be finished. all the people will leave here,
even the clinic will move away.
-----