Candy meets Grandfather William at last.
Grandfather is just before her.
She can't say a word.
William turn back.
The flowers blooms in Boni Hill.
Candy.
Albert.
Albert, why are you here?
Hide, or you will be found.
Candy, I don't have to hide
My name is William Albert.
William Albert.
Yes, I am Grandfather William.
Albert is Grandfather William.
You will not believe me.
But Grandfather Roy let me get this position.
Mr. Roy.
My parents died early
I have to inherit the Albert's.
But I am too young to be the lord.
So my father let my sister to help me
to grow up in the normal enviroment.
The future lord of Albert's is very important.
So, the great granny said
I am grandfather William.
This is the secret known by few people.
Before he grows up, don't let anybody know it.
So, John always takes care of me.
Grandfather William is Albert.
What's wrong, Candy?
Nothing, I think Grandfather
William is an old man.
Everyone thinks so. Even Stia and Aqi.
Stia.
You are the lord of the family
why don't you go the the funeral?
I want to go, and pray with others.
But, I can't.
I can morn in a place with no people.
Candy, let's go out.
Here's a lot of memory.
I want to adjust my feeling
before open my identity.
I have a lot of memory here too.
Candy, do you remember the waterfall?
Yes.
Go to have a look.
This is the fırst place to meet Albert.
My boat was pushing to the waterfall.
Help, help.
Are you awake?
I saved you, why are you fainting?
Now, I remember, it's not strange
at all while you are here.
This is your place.
But I always chase by the animal.
Ah, I really miss it.
Nothing changed at all.
Boby.
Boby came here to play.
It has his own memory.
Nothing changed at all.
Lovely.
Pass.
My name's Candy. Let's be good friend.
I was ordered to Mexico before.
Then, you were chased by the security.
He saved me from the basters.
Then, Albert...
Letter from Lord William, look.
Adopted Candy as your family member.
I am the adopted daughter of the family.
Albert, why am I the adotpted
daughter of your family?
Because Stia, Aqi, Aselin wrote to William,
let me to adopt you.
And you're quite like Aselin's mother.
Aselin's mother. Aselin said so.
Candy is very good. She's my sister.
Aselin's mother. Albert's sister.
Sister died early. Only I am.
Yes, Albert also has bad memory.
I remembered. He encourage me before.
Candy, do you want to cry
for the child all your life?
Albert.
Not only you have the sad memory.
Be strong, Candy, you can control your life.
You'd better leave America.
So I sent you to London.
Candy, do you hate me to send you there?
Why? For me,that's a new point.
I miss London.
I knew Pady, and Ani.
And we have a very good time.
Ilasha and Nil treated me bad.
Dili helped me.
Dili came to my room.
I went to buy the medicine for him
then, I met Albert.
Albert.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
It's really you, Albert.
I didn't expect to see you in London.
It's quite misterious to meet Albert in London.
Albert is protecting me all the time.
Then, you loved Dili.
Dili.
Someone take care of you.
That's the aniversary day.
Yes.
Then, I ran away from the room and ask
Albert to help to take care of the turtle.
So, you know I am in the room
so you sent me the gift.
What's wrong with the clothes
Just like Romio and Julia's clothes.
Even the fake hair
Do you forget whether I am a girl or a boy?
But, I have a good idea.
I know, it's the best to wear
that when you run away.
Thanks to you, everything's alright.
One day, John write me a later
that you left school.
I fınd my own way.
At last, you write to me
that you choose to be a nurse.
So, I want to see you
and it's time to open my identity.
The train explore then.
You hurt badly, the face is like that man.
No.
I am very nervous.
Candy, thanks to you.
Really.
No, I didn't pay Albert and Granny's favor.
I contact with John.
And ready to open my identity.
So the neighbors said you are
talking with an unknown person.
But you know I am here.
Yes, too many things happened. I nearlly forget.
I, I was forced to marry Nil.
They said this is the order
of Grandfather William.
I din't say a thing.
That must be Mrs. Rain's tric.
Candy, no one can force you to do anything.
Leave it to me, you can do what you like.
Thank you, Albert.
Don't cry, Candy.
But, but...
Dry your tears.
Candy, go back to your hometown
fınd yourself back.
I didn't go to the hill for a long time.
I miss there.
We have so many dreams, but it didn't happen.
Brother.
Stia.
Dili.
Good bye, Dili, good bye, memory.
What a similar name.
It's the price in the hill.
Prince in the hill, he comes back.
Who are you?
Who do you think I am?
You like a stranger.
Saucerman.
You're a boy, but you wear a skirt
and take the strange whistle.
What skirt? This is the Scotland Skirt.
And this instrument.
You blow wrong.
It's my fault.
You laugh is beautiful than tear.
Wait.
You're beautiful.
Albert.
Candy.
That's the seal of the prince.
Albert is the prince of the hill.
Candy, for me, it's the good memory of the youth.
I see the prince at last.
Candy.
Ani, Aqi.
It's funny. I will play it too.
Everyone's quite curious.
Candy, look at this.
Dili.
The young actor Dili came back.
Dili came back to the theater.
Dili came back to the theater
so with Aqi and Ani.
I see the prince. I will live.
Candy, the banquet start. Let's go.
Good, run, everyone.
Hurry, hurry. Wait.
I am here. Candy is fırst.
Just like before.
Yes, leave the guest behind.
Hurry, Albert, Aqi and Ani.
Candy.
Dumen, Jim is here too.
Today is really good. Everyone's here.
Don't just play, everyone comes
to prepare for the party.
Candy's bread is ok.
Ami, that's not yours.
Ah.
Candy, let's cheers for it.
En, I hope everyone's happy. Cheers.
Cheers.
Candy is as calm as the wind in the hill
no matter what, she can live strongly.