As Tom wished,
the engagement was canceled.
Candy happily
went back to Pony's Home.
Mr.Sailor on the hill.
Thank you so much for your help.
I was glad to see your fiancee, too!
Stop teasing me!
I am talking about Father's health.
I am a practice nurse.
It's my job to send him to the hospital
as soon as possible.
That's good.
I am back!
How come nobody is here?
Strange.
Sister Pony.
Is Pony's Home closed?
Tom, stop joking!
Sorry.
There is a letter.
We are helping in Mr.Kartlet's farm.
Candy, please watch the house for us.
I see. It scared me.
That's why.
I am going home.
You don't want to take a rest?
My farm is busy, too!
Say ''Hi!''to Sister Pony for me.
-Thanks for taking me back!
-Good-bye!
Good-bye!
Terry!
Is it Terry?
You are....
I am not Terry, sorry.
-Candy.
-Cookie.
Finally you become a sailor!
Yeah! Finally.
Congratulations!
I work at the Sea Gull.
The Sea Gull?
I miss it so much.
I came to Pony's Home to see you
as soon as I got off the ship.
Welcome.
How can a minor smoke?
I am just pretending to smoke.
It's cool.
Come on.
Really?
It's so cool.
Looks like a sailor.
Not just looks like,
Cookie is a real sailor.
A kid can be a sailor?
I am already fifteen.
Jimmy said that.
Cookie is an orphan like us.
Really?
Tell us about the ship.
Alright, let me tell you a story
about the Atlantic Ocean.
I want to be a sailor,too.
About three years ago....
It's very cool!
A brave young man.
Sister Pony,
can Cookie stay here tonight?
Sure.
The kids must be very excited about it.
Can I wear it?
Smells like a sailor.
I want to wear it, too....
Take turns.
Line up.
Salute!
No, you need to straighten your arm.
Straighten it!
Ok, put down your hands.
Cookie has grown up.
He doesn't look like a kid now.
What's wrong? Mina.Kurin.
Somebody is here.
Mr.Mathew.
Thank you.
Candy.
What's wrong?
Is that young man Cookie?
Yes, what's wrong?
Some strangers are looking for him
in the village.
Who?
They didn't tell us their names.
They are gonna find it here eventually.
Here?
What do you want to tell me, Candy?
Is it about brother Terry?
Terry?
I didn't find him.
Cookie,
there are people looking for you.
Are they here?
Just around here.
Candy.
Don't tell anyone that I am here.
Why are you hiding?
I am not.
Why are you sneaking around?
Candy, I left the Sea Gull.
Didn't you want to be a sailor?
Not just the Sea Gull.
Cookie, that wound....
The sailors did it.
They are so mean?
Why?
Because I am an easy target.
I am an orphan, I am all by myself.
Ok.
Aren't they good guys?
They treated us like guests, when
we were trying to escape on the sea,
Did Captain Neiben stop them?
He pretended he didn't see it.
Unbelievable!
How could Captain Neiben....
-Alright.
-What should we do?
Everyone gather here!
Ok.
Bummer!
Where did Cookie go?
Let's go back, brother!
Let's look for it for another while.
Hey, little guy!
Where is Pony's Home?
A place for orphans.
Say it again?
Go!
What are they doing?
Wait a minute!
Let me go!
Stop it!
Jimmy!
No!
Help!
Mr. Viva! Mr. Vokado!
Jimmy, stop!
Mina.
Take it easy.
These children are so mean.
Sorry.
Jimmy, apologize to the guests.
No!
Jimmy, you were rude to the guests
on their first visit.
Sister, we want to revenge for Cookie.
Cookie?
Candy, is Cookie here?
Yes.
Finally.
You came for Cookie, right?
John, it's rude.
But, they were mean to Cookie
because he was an orphan.
John, you listened to
my conversation with Cookie?
Anyway, it's unforgivable.
Yes.
What's the noise?
Candy!
Cookie told you
he was beated because he was an orphan?
Yes.
This guy....
-He lied?
-No!
He was undisciplined and impatient.
We didn't know what to do with him.
What did you say?
Jimmy!
Stop it!
Sister!
Did Pony's Home
teach these children attack the guests?
I...
Let's go, Viva!
But, brother...
Candy, tell Cookie,
he doesn't have to come back.
Mr. Vokado.
This guy Cookie
has no gratitude for our grace.
If it's not Captain Neiben....
Candy, why did you...
I am taking the shortcut.
Candy,
I don't want to explain it to you.
Cookie was really beaten very often.
Idiot!
How did you be a sailor?
But, they didn't have to go over.
Candy, you are a practice nurse.
What's the most important thing
in the world?
People's lives.
If....
If the Sea Gull has sinked at that time,
many people would be dead.
I was beaten really bad before, too.
This is what
every sailor should go through.
This guy Cookie,
thought we beat him
because he was an orphan.
Candy. Captain Neiben
wanted us to look for Cookie.
Captain Neiben?
It's the same for every man on the sea.
We have no parents, no brothers.
Everyone is alone.
Mr. Vokado,
please give Cookie one more chance.
But, we can't find him.
Don't worry, wait here.
Candy.
I see. Cookie left these things.
We surched every place around here.
Jimmy, let me borrow the horse.
Candy, why are you looking for Cookie?
Go back to the ship.
Poor kid, he could be beaten anytime.
Let's find him first!
Cookie!
Where did Cookie go?
I can't find him anywhere.
Sorry.
My friend is causing everyone trouble.
That's ok, Candy.
I haven't seen these kids being
so enthusiastic for a long time.
True.
Candy,
Cookie is popular among the kids...
not because he is a sailor.
But...
Cookie and you
are the role models for the kids.
Role models?
Yes, the good role models.
Cookie and I
are the role models for the kids?
Candy, was it alright?
Nursing school.
That's great. Good night.
Nibbie.
Candy, we never told you this.
Every time you come back,
You are always the one who decides
whether the kids are happy or not.
-Me?
-Yes.
You are happy or not.
How much you've been through.
I never noticed.
You are our favorate.
One more thing.
You have not changed.
You have to tell us things about Cookie
so that we don't get worried.
I always come back to Pony's Home
when I feel frustrated.
I am going back to the hospital
tomorrow.
Next time when I come, I will
tell you everything, both good and bad.
Ok.
Mina, Kurin, be good!
The carriage is here!
That's Tom's carriage.
Cookie.
What's wrong, Cookie?
I found him wandering on the street
last night,
and let him stay a night at my place.
Candy.
Are the hat and pipe still here?
Are you going back to the Sea Gull?
Tom was blaming me last night.
How would everyone look for Cookie,
if we didn't like him?
You are an orphan,
you are gonna take some fists.
Actually, I deserve it.
-Really?
-Sorry.
I lied to you.
I see.
Thank you. I kept
dreaming about the ship last night.
Helm to the left!
Can't believe you were shouting
in the middle of the night.
Mr.Steave.
Father.
Thank you for everything
you've done to me all these times.
Mr.Steave, what's wrong?
I want to see you guys.
I am afraid
this is gonna be the last time.
Come on, Father!
We are just doing a regular visit
to the hospital.
I know I am not going to make it.
Are you cold, Mr.Steave?
He is trembling because he is scared.
This is my father's first time
to the hospital.
Tom, let's go home! We'll go next time.
No way!
Mr.Steave, let me go with you.
Good-bye, Sister!
Take care of yourself. Good luck!
Good luck, Cookie!
I'll apologize to the captain.
Good luck, Candy!
Good luck, Cookie!
Bye!
Mr.Steave. Sorry for the wait.
Come on, Father.
Tom, thank you for doing this.
Don't say that, Father.
Cheer up!
Candy, are you going to welcome me
with a knife?
To have a cut here.
There won't be any surgeries,
don't worry.
Please.
Father.
Sorry.
Excuse me,
which way is to the church in the town?
This way.
Thank you!
God, please protect Father!
-Father!
-Open the door of the next room.
Candy, Father...
Fainted after the examination.
That serious?
Because of this.
Whiskey?
Mr.Steave was nervous about
seeing the doctor, and he drank a lot.
Father!
His heart is ok,
he just needs some rest.
Really?
I am going to work harder for Father.
Cheer up, Tom!
Sorry, I have other patients.
Thank you, Candy!
Candy is back to her busy life again.
At the same time,
Cookie returned to the port.
Candy says it to herself...
Next time
when she goes back to Pony's Home,
She is gonna let the kids know
everything that happened.