Pony's home, which was to be
disbanded in the spring,
would remain forever as it is,
thanks to Candy's efforts.
The land owner, Mr. Cartwright,
allowed them to stay.
Scar on the healed soul.
There it is!
It got away! Wait!
Stop!
Boss!
Candy will catch it for sure!
Boss?
I got you!
Boss, the rabbit is over there!
It's okay this way!
Don't pick on poor animals.
Now, everybody, come!
Boss!
Sister Pony.
I haven't heard anything
from the Adley family.
Will Candy be okay like this?
The Adleys must decided to
leave Candy alone for recovery.
That would be fine.
But... what are Candy's plans?
It seems that she doesn't think
what to do from now on...
-Is it okay?
-It's okay!
Look!
Take a good look at my lasso skills!
That's great, boss!
I'll do it again, pay attention!
Mr. Matthew!
Boss, you did it again!
Good day, Mr. Matthew.
Candy, a letter from Tom.
From Tom?
Who is Tom?
Successor of the Steve farm.
He got adopted from here.
He's become a great cowboy!
He's very devoted to his work.
He was from Pony's home.
Amazing!
Jimmy, you could get adopted
to some good place too.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'll stay with boss.
Jimmy.
Candy,
you can stay here forever.
You don't have to return to Lakewood,
right?
You'd be lonely again.
Mr. Matthew,
aren't you take a break?
I have letters to deliver.
See you again!
Goodbye, Mr. Matthew!
Boss going back to Lakewood.
That's not true, right?
No, I won't.
You'll stay here forever, right?
That's right. I left the Adley family
with no intent of comimg back.
Stear, Archie,
I'm going to strike out on my own.
Please, forgive me,
for leaving without seeing you.
Boss!
What does Tom say?
Read it to us!
Ok!
What did he write?
He invites us to to his farm
tommorrow!
Great!
Everyone, get prepared!
Alright. You can go!
Candy?
I'm sorry!
Only big kids can go!
-Sister Pony?
-Candy,
it's a long walk to Tom's farm!
Little kids couldn't manage that.
You'd be too tired to have fun.
No, I want to go!
Take us along!
Sister Pony, sister Lane,
I can take everybody along!
But Candy...
-Wait for me!
-Candy!
Boss!
That's it, we'll ask Mr. Cartwright!
A cart would be okay?
-Yes!
-Alright, I'll let you have it.
Thank you, Mr. Cartwright!
This is great, boss!
Candy, you said that
you're a widow from Pony's home.
How about
become my daughter then?
What? Your daughter?
You're somebody I could rely on.
But I...
No need to answer immediately!
Candy, think about it.
I will.
Boss,
why didn't you agree rightaway?
To become his daughter,
that's amazing!
Maybe I could become happy like Tom.
That's right! A girl-cowboy!
Isn't that great?
That's right. But I can't do that.
Why?
Abandoning the Adley family.
Became Cartwright's daughter...
I couldn't really do that!
It sounds pretty good though...
I think there are other ways
for me to live.
What do you mean?
I don't really know yet.
Everybody, get in the carriage!
Candy,
can you manage them alone?
We'd like to go along,
but we are too busy...
Leave it to me, sister Pony!
I have experience
from my voyage to Mexico!
-Are you guys all in?
-Yeah!
Everyone, listen to Candy!
Yeah!
Well then, Candy, take care!
Yes!
Send our regards to Tom!
Yes, here we go.
Take care!
Here we go.
Sister Pony, the children are so happy!
That's right!
They never been on a trip before!
Hey, I see Tom's farm!
Candy!
It's Tom! Tom!
Tom!
Candy!
Tom, long time no see!
You're in high spirits!
Everyone, you got here well?
What happened?
She forgot that
we were riding in the back!
Sorry!
You haven't changed at all, Candy!
Hello, Candy!
Good day, Mr. Steve.
I heard what happened to Anthony...
Dad!
It's okay, Tom.
I'm alright with that.
That's good.
You can't keep crying forever!
That's great!
Let me introduce you to other guests!
Other guests?
Hi, Miss Tomboy!
Stear! Archie!
We wanted to see you, Candy!
Hey, Candy...
We didn't come all the way here
to see you in sorrow!
No, it's not that...
I just got so nostalgic...
So these tears are from nostalgia...
If that's the case, great!
Tom wants to encourage you, Candy,
and invited us here as well.
-Tom, thank you.
-Well.
Candy, at first,
we thought it is not a good idea,
for you to see us.
I'm glad we came.
I'm happy to see you, too.
Everybody, are you thirsty?
It's fresh milk! Have some!
Wait!
You can't pig out like that!
Everybody, take a cup
and can get a round!
Yes!
Candy,
I'm so glad you recovered.
Now we don't have to worry anymore!
But I...
...have no idea what should I do
from now on.
No need to hurry.
That's right! You just recovered!
Take it easy,
the world can wait a bit!
Boss, have some!
Boss?
Candy, you're already the boss?
That's a good one!
I haven't laughed like this
in a long time...
Hey, everybody!
Take a look at this horse!
It's a great horse!
It was Tom who trained it.
Amazing!
You're a real cowboy, Tom!
Show us what it can do!
Alright!
Wow, he's cool!
Want to see a rodeo?
Anthony!
Candy!
Stop it! Stop it!
-Candy!
-Wait, Archie!
-Wait.
-Why did you stop me?
It would be better
tp left her alone a bit.
Candy. I'm sorry.
Anthony!
People will die,
they will reborn
inside human's hearts forever.
Anthony!
Living in my heart
has no good for me, Anthony.
I want to hear your voice.
I want to see the sparkle in your eyes.
I want to hold your hand,
Anthony!
Mr. Albert!
What's up with that face?
Is that the Candy I know?
Anthony... Anthony's dead!
You liked that boy, didn't you?
We loved each other
from the very first moment.
He was so kind to me!
And he have his love to you?
He gave you his kindness?
That's right. That's why...
that's why I can't forget him.
Candy,
do you have any plans?
This weepy, hesitant face
is not all you have.
Candy, you want to
memories him whole life?
Mr. Albert...
You're not the only one
who is living with sadness.
Be strong, Candy.
Find your own path in life!
Candy!
They are looking for you.
I'll be on my way, then.
Mr. Albert!
When will I see you again?
When you smile again, Candy.
Candy.
I'm sorry. I'm alright now.
Candy!
I see the smile, Candy!
That's better, Candy!
Candy, I'm sorry.
I made you go through
your painful memories.
It's my fault for not letting go.
I'll be stronger from now on!
Don't you worry!
You need some fun
to forget sad things!
Come, everybody. Dance!
Now, Candy!
That's it, Candy! Dance!
Archie, I'm going to tell her.
Alright.
Candy, it might surprise you,
but we're going to England.
To England?
Without you and Anthony,
the house became boring!
So you're going to England?
To find our own paths in life.
Own paths...
But Candy,
I'm sure we'll meet again.
Yes, someday.
Now, smile, Candy!
You must handle your own fate.
That's the reason Stear
and Archie going to England.
What will I do...
Boss, will you take us
on a trip once again?
Ok!
You were awake!
How could they sleep?
Boss, banzai!
Banzai!
Alright, since you're awake,
I don't have to drive slowly.
Look, We'll heading to
Pony's home on a double.
Everybody needs me.
They depend on me.
How come I haven't noticed this before?
I want to help sister Pony
and sister Lane.
Stay at Pony's home,
taking care of the children!
Candy realized
what she wanted to do in her life.