Stear and the others celebrated
as Candy passed the test.
Candy had a wonderful time
and returned to the hospital.
Mr.Albert has left the hospital
and left a message.
Mr.Albert.
The vanished Mr.Albert.
Mr.Albert has left.
Thank you, Candy.
I will never forget you.
Mr.Albert.
Mr.Albert, where are you?
Mr.Albert said before...
It's better to ignore a hopeless
hopeless patient.
Let me die here.
Die here...
Mr.Albert.
Mr.Albret.
No sign of him in the hospital.
He must have gone outside.
I came right back after
I finished with Stear and the others.
He wouldn't go too far.
It's dark and cold now.
Where is Mr.Albert?
I need to find him.
Yeah, ask Stear to help.
Hey boy,
watch where you are going.
Candy.
Stear.
Why did you hit me?
This cart came out of nowhere.
Neo, no more driving in the future,
you can't drive.
Who wants ro drive
this piece of metal.
Hurts.
Hopeless.
True.
Candy, look, my new invention
Why did you came back?
You forgot something?
No, Mr.Albert is gone.
Help me to find him.
Mr.Albert was so impulsive,
He left the hospital
without knowing his past.
Mr.Albert was recovering well.
So I left him by himself.
I sould have stayed by his side.
We asked you out,
we are responsible for this too.
Stear, stop there.
Where is Mr.Albert?
Where is he?
No, we should split and
look for Mr.Albert seperately.
That makes sense, we should split.
Right, brother,
take me to the station.
I will stop Mr.Albert
from taking the train.
I will look around the alleys.
I will drive around.
Candy. I will meet you at
the hospital's entrance in two hours.
-Let's go
-Please.
What's the big deal about wife.
The old Mr.Albert.
I won't worry about him
no matter where he goes.
Even if we are seperated,
I still believe
we can meet again.
But not now.
I need to saty by his side
until he remembers the past.
Mr.Albert,
Where are you in such
complicated city?
Why didn't I come to that?
He must be there.
Mr.Albert must be in his
favourite spot.
In the peaceful green land,
Close to a small lake.
Mr.Albert must be there.
Candy,
You are a kind nurse.
Is my name really Albert?
Sorry,
Albert is my brother's name
You look like my brother.
Besides, it would be hard
to call you without a name.
You don't like it?
It's alright,
but that's your brother's name.
But my name...
My name...
No, I can't remember it.
Don't force yourself.
You will remember when
you recovered.
You will remember your name then.
Don't underestimate me, I am a
well known nurse in this hospital.
You were just a trainee.
And...
I am a well known nurse
in this hospital.
And...
Mr.Albert, look,
I passed the test.
Look.
Congratulations, Candy.
Thank you.
From now on
I can take care of Mr.Albert.
Thank you, Candy.
But I can't cause you
any more trouble.
I will give you back the name
Albert.
My memory is lost.
No future and hope.
Losing my past is
like losing myself.
How was I brought up?
How did I grow up?
To have present,
I need to have the past.
So that I can decide my future.
But
I know nothing about my past.
What should I do now?
What should I do in the future?
Who am I?
How should I live?
It's getting darker,
I need to hurry.
Candy.
I am not you family,
I can't rely on you.
The memory I lost.
I will take it back
with my own hands.
Poopet,
I will search for my lost memory.
Are you coming with me?
Poopet, let's go.
Mr.Albert.
Candy?
He is not here.
Where exactly is Mr.Albert.?
I thought he would be here.
Mr.Albert, where are you?
Mr.Albert, you fool.
I am so worried about you.
Where are you?
Why would Candy come here
looking for me?
We are not related...
This voice...
Mr.Albert.
Candy, you...
You fool, why did you leave?
Why?
I have looked everywhere for you.
How did you know I was here?
Candy, leave me alone.
We are just strangers,
I can't cause you any more trouble.
You are wrong.
I knew you,
that's why I came here.
Candy,
You love the nature.
You used to travel to places
like this.
The Lakecity's forest,
London's Zoo and Africa.
We knew each other for a long time.
The first time we met.
I fell from the waterfall...
Help!
Sombody help me!
It's her?
You saved my life.
And whenever I felt upset.
You always showed up
and encouraged me.
I want to hold your hand,
Anthony.
Mr.Albert.
Why are you so sad?
Where is the Candy I knew?
Anthony,
Anthony is dead.
You like him?
We fell in love.
He was so good to me.
He loved you, cared for you.
Yes, that's why
I can't forget about him.
Candy,
Do you have any plans for the future?
The things you told me,
I will return to you now.
If I am the Albert
you were talking about...
Am I any different now?
No name, no address and no job.
Come and gone.
Maybe I am just a wanderer.
I could even be a escape.
How is that possible?
I know you are a good man.
What do you know about me?
Candy, You have no idea
what is my background and occupation.
So?
As long as you are bright,
brave and kind.
That's enough.
Is that really me?
I can't remember a bit.
You will.
Please don't look at the bad side,
live on bravely.
I will take care of you
before until you remember everything.
No.
Go back to the hospital.
I have recovered.
I have no reasons to stay there.
Good bye, Candy.
Leave me alone.
Mr.Albert.
I will live on.
Thank you for everything.
Don't go.
I will come back to you
if I remember my past.
Please don't leave me.
Mr.Albert.
You saved me from the waterfall.
You encouraged me
when Anthony died.
Terry left me.
I wanted to seek for you comfort.
This time I will help you.
Candy,
Please let me take care of you.
You were always there for me.
I want to repay you.
I lied to you that I had a brother.
Actually I don't have parents.
So
I always see you as my brother.
My real brother.
I feel so safe
as long as you are with me.
We are like family.
Candy, thank you.
Thank you, Candy.
Mr.Albert.
I will take good care of you.
Having her around.
Makes me so relax.
I should stay with her
for the time being.
Candy is so slow,
it has been three hours.
Brother.
Candy,
She found Mr.Albert.
Stear, Archie.
Great, Candy.
Candy told me about you guys.
Sorry to keep you all so much time.
Never mind.
Mr.Albert,
we want to ask you a favor.
Don't make Candy sad again.
It's ok now.
We are home, Poopet.
What is going on?
Since when this ward
became a store room?
I remember the doctor on duty tonight
is doctor Reknapp.
Right.
Candy, it's my fault.
Why?
I told doctor Reknapp.
when I left the hospital.
He thought I wouldn't be back.
But, it's so mean to change this ward
in to a store room right away.
I wasn't told about this.
Candy,
Excuse me,
is doctor Reknapp here?
What is it?
No, I come to speak to him
about the ward number zero.
He is inside.
Didn't you know that
the patient asked to be discharged?
I wouldn't let him leave.
You were responsible to
look after him, why didn't you know?
What were you ding?
Because, I was taking a leave,
I didn't know...
Forget it,
I don't want to know the reasons.
Candy,
I want to make this clear,
That man can't stay
in this hospital any loger.
Why?
He can recover without
staying in the hospital.
But his memory...
You think he can regain his memory?
We have done our best.
We have no obligation
to look after him.
But headmaster Merry Jane
said before...
Caring is the cure for
regaining memory.
Take good care of him.
Candy, I am not against you
taking care of him.
But we cant let him stay for free.
Candy, did it work out?
I didn't know
he was such a unreasonable man.
Thank you, Candy.
I appreciate your help.
Mr.Albert...
It's alright,
I could sleep anywhere.
I used to yeah?
Yes, you can sleep in my van.
That's right.
So tired today.
Have a good rest.
Thank you, Candy.
Mr.Albert,
don't try to run away again.
Good night, Mr.Albert.
Good night, Candy.
Sleep yet?
So quiet.
Having Candy by his side,
It definitely won't take long
to regain his memory.
Mr.Albert told himself.