Stear, you are thinking about the war
even on a picnic.
Pattie, we are supposed
to be happy today.
Stear insisted on going into the war
in Europe.
However, after Candy and Mr.Albert
trying to talk him down,
he finally started to doubt
his own decision.
A Cupid with wrinkle.
Excuse me.
Candy, here.
Sorry, there was an emergency.
I just got here, too.
I got lost.
It is not polite to let the host wait.
Right! It's Pattie's treat today!
This restaurant has very nice food.
Of course.
Mr.Albert works part-time here
everyday.
Why aren't there any people
serving us?
Yeah.
I said ''no!''
What happened?
I really can't take it.
I can not accept something like this.
Grandmother, are you kidding me?
Kidding you?
I said I don't want it.
You must be kidding.
I have hired many workers.
You are the first one
who doesn't want any pay.
I can't take the money.
I work for fun, not for money.
Right! I should thank you for this.
What?
That grandmother...
Grandmother?
Maybe I recognized her wrong.
You must be wrong.
Pattie's grandmother is very rich.
Come on, Grandmother!
Please take it.
Grandmother.
Pattie.
Boss, I have something to do,
I gotta go now.
-Grandmother.
-The pay.
She started working here
a month ago?
You didn't notice at all?
She always said she was going to
have tea at her friend's.
She helped me a lot.
Since you are her grand daughter.
It is so troublesome.
Pattie, let her take over.
Great, I am going to get prepared.
Yummy.
Thank you for the treat, Pattie.
It's my pleasure.
You helped me convince Stear.
Pattie is so sweet.
It is not true.
I'll treat you
when I receive my pay.
Candy, it's my treat next time.
I have a job.
You are going to Broadway,
you should save the money for it.
Annie
Is going to see Terry soon.
Come on.
Pattie and I will take the carriage
here. Be careful.
Pattie, what's wrong?
Wait a minute.
Pattie, that grandmother...
-Seems to be Grandmother.
-No way.
Grandmother is really healthy.
Take it easy, don't get too tired.
You worry too much.
Sorry.
Candy.
Long time no see.
You, too. Thanks for
taking care of me in London.
Grandmother.
Pattie.
Why are you with Candy?
Good night, Grandmother.
Annie is here, too.
It's so rare.
Grandmother.
Coming.
Excuse me, I have to work.
Grandmother, why do you work?
My interest.
It feels rewarding after hard work.
Do you want to try?
If dad in Lodon knows about this...
This is America.
A free country.
I am going to work now,
excuse me.
We just solved Stear's problem.
Now is Grandmother...
This is shocking to me.
That grandmother
who took over my shift?
When we were in London, she went to
the school and wanted to register.
Will Candy become like that
when she gets old?
Mr.Albert will.
Sorry.
She is too old to go to work.
That's true.
Of course Candy would be worried.
Ok, I am going to convince her
tomorrow.
Thank you so much.
Good morning, Candy.
Candy?
Grandmother
From now on,
I'll be working in this hospital.
Thank you very much.
This hospital...
how about the other places?
I'll leave for the restaurant
in the evening,
and pave the road at night.
When do you sleep?
Candy, old people only need
four hours of sleep.
No, you will be too tired.
No problem.
Working is the secret to long life.
Candy,
let's work hard together today!
Thank you for all the work.
-Wait!
-What?
What did you say?
Thank you for all the work.
I really heard it right.
You are very polite.
You don't have to thank me for this.
No. It's not easy to
have a young person like you.
Here, some tip for you.
I can't.
A little something to
show my appreciation.
-It's not necessary.
-Grandmother.
Candy, work is wonderful.
You had to wrok from a young age.
You must feel blessed.
Grandmother has never worked before?
Not to mention work.
I couldn't even step out of the door.
My marriage was
my parents'decision, too.
I was like a bird in a cage.
How about now?
I was so lucky to
come to America with Pattie.
Right! We can have lunch together!
Let's eat!
So much food.
I got to improve my nutrition.
I have three jobs.
Pattie is very worried about you.
She is a chicken.
Candy, I heard you have a boyfriend.
Grandmother.
I heard he is in New York.
Why don't you go visit him?
I'll visit him next month.
Why didn't he come to see you?
Terry is preparing for a show.
You parted for work.
Chicago and New York
are one thousand kilos away.
But that shouldn't be a reason
for not seeing each other.
Soon, the vacation is coming.
Let me help you.
Wait, Doctor.
Not the tips.
I have a small favor to ask you.
A small favor?
Where is the middle of
Chicago and New York?
Probably...
Pittsburgh in Pennsylvania.
Pittsburgh.
Let's meet there, Candy.
I...
You leave from Chicago.
Terry goes to Pittsburgh
from New York.
Two people meet at one place,
it's so romantic.
Grandmother.
Wire a telegram to Terry now.
When do you have a vacation?
But, Terry might not have the time.
If you always hesitate,
you will never get things done.
Leave it to me.
Telegram is not convenient.
I'll let Pattie make a trip.
Pattie to Broadway?
Yeah, she has a lot of time.
But...
It's ok. I feel I am younger.
Let me be the Cupid for you two.
I go to New York alone?
Isn't it great to take the train
all day long?
Grandmother,
can I ask Annie to go with me?
Pattie, how old are you?
I am the same age
with Candy and Annie.
Listen!
Candy went to England alone.
-But...
-Pattie.
Don't be a bird in the cage
like me.
Come in, please.
Candy White is here.
Candy.
Sorry to bother you.
I was just thinking about you.
Have a seat.
I have been thinking, and...
You don't want to see Terry?
No, but Terry is preparing
for the show.
Would it be better for
Pattie to visit Terry?
Then Pattie would know
how Terry is doing.
Although it sounds right...
Don't hesitate anymore.
Take the first train to New York
tomorrow.
Grandmother.
I'll got to the station to
purchase the ticket before work.
Pattie, you are going alone...
I can manage it by myself.
Pattie.
Good! That's my girl!
But, Grandmother
has to promise one thing.
Spending money? No problem.
No work for you anymore.
How could you deprive me
of my hobby?
I agree with Pattie.
Candy, you, too....
You will be tired out by three jobs.
Wouldn't you make me quit all three?
Just one of them.
Alright, as long as
Pattie completes the task.
Really?
Deal!
Pattie, don't put too much pressure
on Terry.
You don't need to do this.
Pattie is very thoughtful.
Don't worry, Candy,
please take care of Grandmother.
I'll take care of myself.
Good-bye!
Be careful on the road.
Pattie.
Candy.
It's getting romantic.
Candy, you haven't been to Pittsburgh,
have you?
Terry must have not been there.
Within limited time,
a couple dating in a foreign city.
It's so romantic!
Terry.
I never thought
we could meet a month earlier,
in the middle of Chicago
and New York.
Why are you smiling to yourself,
Candy?
Any good news?
Nothing.
I am going to take the temperature.
You forgot the thermometer.
Terrible.
Grandmother,
why did you fall asleep?
Grandmother, what's wrong?
Nothing, I just don't feel well.
She still has two jobs?
Yes. Dish washer in the restaurant
and paving worker.
-Paving worker?
-Yes.
Can she afford to do laboring jobs?
She is enthusiastic.
Idiot! Are you really a nurse?
I have talked to her about this,
but...
If she has done the medical checkup,
things would not be as bad.
The doctor is right.
Although she likes to work,
I should have stopped her.
Notify her family
as soon as possible.
Is it that bad?
She is old.
I am sorry, Grandmother.
I am even a nurse.
How is Grandmother?
The telegram for Pattie
should have got there.
It takes three days
for a round trip to New York.
Candy, Pattie can see the telegram
on the way.
Should be around Pittsburgh.
Pittsburgh.
That's where Terry and I will meet.
Pattie...
Archie, the train seems to be delayed.
Was there an accident?
No, it seems like the train broke down.
Why at this moment?
Archie, let's drive there.
Go!
If she keeps being in a coma...
Doctor,
please try to help Grandmother!
I only hope she can wake up soon.
You didn't sleep all night?
I am ok.
Brother, drive safely.
Be careful not to bite your tongue.
Grandmother.
Pattie.
She's coming.
Pattie is almost here.
-Pattie.
-Hang in there, Grandmother!
Grandmother!
Hurry!
Grandmother, Pattie is back!
Grandmother, hang in there!
Doctor,
the pulse is getting faster!
Prepare for shots.
Don't make it difficult for us,
please come for visit tomorrow.
Grandmother is dying,
how can we wait?
Right.
Quiet! This is the hospital.
Miss,
what happened to Grandmother?
She is back to conscious.
Really?
Grandmother, hang in there!
Quiet, this is the hospital.
I won't die.
Hang in there!
Grandmother.
Why did you come back?
-Because...
-Grandmother.
I am fine.
It's my fault.
No, I don't regret anything.
Because of work,
I got to know those friends.
That's great, Pattie!
Thank you.
Sorry, Candy.
I got off the train in Pittsburgh.
But,
I saw Terry in Pittsburgh.
Terry?
You'll know it when you go home.
Go home?
Let's go, Candy!
Grandmother is alright now.
Ok.
Saw Terry in Pittsburgh?
Can it be that...
-I am back!
-Thank you for hard work.
Terry is waiting for you.
Terry?
Terry, where are you?
Terry
Romeo and Juliet.
Terry is so cool!
Pattie found this poster
in the lounge in Pittsburgh.
She really met Terry.
Candy forgot everything,
she's just staring at Terry
in the poster.
Terry.
She is concerntrating on it so much
as if she is walking into the poster.
But, the woman in Terry's arm,
makes Candy hesitate.