Summer school at the shore of a lake.
Summertime is here.
Candy went to the Summer school
in Scotland.
They say that Edinburgh
a center of Scotland...
is one of the most beautiful places
in the world.
Away from Edinburgh...
there is a small village on the shore
of a lake.
Candy and the others will stay there
during their summer vacation.
That's the Summer school's church?
Mr. God followed us even
on a summer vacation...
Can't help it, our school is a
religious school.
Bagpipes!
There is a festival in the village.
I wanted to see that!
Candy, wait!
The prince on the hill...
so this is your homeland?
Hey! Stop!
Wait, number 93!
-It's looking this way!
-I'm afraid!
Sheep are calm creatures.
There, there.
-Why did you run away again?!
-Don't be so violent!
But this thing keeps running away!
It ran away while you were shearing it?
You're gonna get some
if you do that again!
-It's probably afraid of cold!
-Afraid of cold?
So funny of you to say that!
I've never heard of such a thing before!
What?
Freckles... that flat nose...
I remember!
You're Candy!
Sis, you're Candy, aren't you?
How come you know my name?
You look exactly like her!
Like who?
Like someone my brother told me about.
Brother...?
Teacher! Candy and the others are there!
What are you doing there?
You'll have some free time later on!
-Sorry!
-We'll go back rightaway!
You got her mad!
Now, thanks for nr. 93!
-Wait up!
-Candy!
Instead of watching the festivities,
you'd better unpack your luggage!
Luggage?
Clint!
Now, go!
I must hurry.
I totally forgot about you!
Clint!
Sorry.
I was so engrosses in festivities
that I totally forgot about you.
Sisters will take notice
if you keep growling like that.
Will you forgive me if I bring you
something nice for dinner?
Thanks.
Now, Clint, your favorite food
smoked salmon.
Yes!
Come in!
We have something for Clint!
This one is from us.
But you shouldn't have...
We're partially at fault for this, too.
Right, Patty?
Clint, this is for you.
But what about that sheep?
It's probaby sneezing now that
all of its wool is gone.
By the way
just who was that shepherd boy?
He said that
his older brother knows you.
-Candy?
-What?
Maybe the older brother of that boy
is the Prince on the hill!
You're kidding me!
There's no way that an older brother of
such a naughty kid would be Prince!
Do you know anyone else in Scotland?
When you put it that way...
Alright. I'm going to find him tomorrow
and ask him about this.
Okay. Looks like this is the only way.
Got out all right.
Candy!
Teacher! Good morning!
Good morning.
Candy, before going out for a walk...
regulations say that you have to
participate in a morning mass.
I'll forgive you if you come back.
Don't break the rules
without hesitation.
Yes!
Seeing the crowds
Jesus went up on the mountain...
and when he sat down
his disciples came to him.
He spoke up and taught them, saying:
Blessed are the poor in spirit...
-Candy!
-Yes!
What's the meaning of this?
Uh, that sheep...
What sheep?
Sister, it's true!
It really is!
Quiet! Everyone, calm down!
You escaped again?
You know this sheep?
Yes, sister! Since it's a bother,
can I go and return it to its owner?
Yes! Do you know its owner?
-Yes!
-Candy...
I'll be back soon!
Don't take too long.
Okay. Go, go...
You saved me back there.
But I'm confused...
I don't know the name of
that boy or where he lives...
I'll ask that old man.
Mister!
Can I help you?
Do you know of a farm that keeps sheep?
A farm that keeps sheep?
Everyone in this village has sheep.
Don't you know
where that sheep came from?
I'm sure it was called nr. 93...
It could be one of Mark's sheep.
Mark's ?
Hey, Mark!
What is it?
Huh?
You!
Can I help you?
Freckled lady!
Freckled lady? And I brought
your sheep back to you!
What? It came back again?
Nr. 93 didn't run away!
I actually wanted it to run away!
Shoo! Go away!
You're free!
Say, what's the meaning of this?
It keeps running away
from my brother's farm.
Since it wants to run away so much
I let it go free!
Who is your brother?
Of course, Terry!
Terry?
Grandchester's Terry?
Terrius G. Grandchester!
Then, you're Terry's little brother?
Call me Mark!
So that's why you knew about me?
Bro is a funny guy
he lets me hang around!
Say, Terry comes to this place?
He has a mansion here!
Mark, I'd like you to take me there!
What about your Summer school?
Sisters allowed me out.
-Hop in, then.
-Thanks.
Can't help it, I guess!
-Grampa, thanks!
-Thank you!
I expected nothing less of
Duke Grandchester's mansion!
Bro!
So that's Terry's room?
Bro! Freckles is here!
Don't call me like that!
Strange...
-Maybe he's out?
-Bro!
Mark!
Mark, I'll punish you if you keep
calling Master by whistling!
Lady, good day.
Welcome to Scotland.
Mom, bro isn't here?
Mom?
Yes, it's my son
I've already told you about.
Then, he's not Terry's real brother?
No way!
But master Terry doesn't have a problem
with that since he really likes my son.
I'm Terry's best friend!
Mark!
Uh, is Terry...
He told me that
he doesn't want to see anyone.
Has something happened?
Terry...
This melody...
It's a Scottish poem,
Auld lang syne.
Auld lang syne?
It's a song we sing
when we part from someone.
Part from someone?
Terry!
It's me! Candy!
If you're there, let me see you!
Just what happened to him?
He said he wanted to be alone for a while.
He even gave me a few days off.
Alone?
All guys want to be alone sometimes!
You're rude!
Women always want to cackle together!
Mark!
Isn't that the same sheep?
Annie, Candice supposed to
return the sheep. What happened?
She's so much trouble...
You got in just a right moment.
I'll prepare a lunch for you.
Mark, get the cheese from the cellar!
Yes!
Our place is a bit dingy
does it surprise you?
Not at all!
Your place looks exactly like
Pony's home where I grew up.
-You lived in such a house?
-Yes!
Until I was about Mark's age.
So that's why you're a tomboy!
Mark!
-Here! I made this cheese!
-Looks tasty!
Looks tasty?
It's doesn't just look that way
it actually tastes great!
I know.
Mark, while your mother was
working in London...
He took good care of this house!
Right, Mark?
I'm glad you weren't alone.
It's because Dad was with me!
With your father?
Over there!
Tartan check?
His father used to make them.
He was the best craftsman
in the entire village...
So warm!
I'll continue in my father's footsteps!
Do your best then!
The Prince's kilt...
maybe it was made of
tartan check Mark's father made?
Is something wrong?
No, I just got a feeling as if I
returned to my homeland.
Now, your soup is getting cold!
Okay! Let's eat!
You're the first student
to go missing for eight hours!
I didn't realize it until it got dark...
Here...
What is that?
Cheese.
I want to give it to you as a present.
My! You're also the first student
to bring cheese as a present...
-Candy!
-They scolded you?
Stear and Archie arrived during the day.
Both of them?
Candy,
Aunt Elroy rented a nearby mansion.
Then, it means that
Neil and Eliza are here too?
Yes.
Oh boy, I have to look at their faces
even here in Scotland...
Stear borrowed it to us!
It's dark outside,
you won't see a thing.
Terry's mansion is on the other side.
There it is!
Lights are on
in Terry's room only.
-Candy?
-Eh?
What are you looking at?
It's nothing!
Candy, Stear and Archie promised they'd take
us for a boat ride during tomorrow's free time!
Archie is going to come!
I see.
Aren't you glad, Candy?
Of course I am!
Say, let's call it a day.
I'm so tired.
Okay. Good night!
A woman?
Do you best, Stear!
Archie, don't give up!
Archie, I'm running behind!
Take it easy there!
That's how things are, bro!
Terry...
Score! We won, Annie!
Candy, if you're not afraid
wanna ride the boat?
Come on!
It's so fun!
It's okay, I'm going for a walk.
Candy?
Something happened to her?
Yes. She's been acting strange
since last night.
She keeps watching that mansion
with binoculars...
Just who was the person in
Terry's room last night?
It's ... Eleanor Baker?
It's Terry's real mother.
Then, the shadow I saw last night...
Uh...
Did she come from America
to see Terry?
Hey! Wait!
Terry!
Catch it!
He was sulking yesterday, and now...
Hey! Wait!
Hey! It's here!
Hello, Freckled Tarzan.
Terry, over there I...
Uh, over there...
What, you tripped on purpose again?
Terry!
Don't tell anyone about that woman.
Terry, last night...
Last night, my brother stayed at home!
-Right?
-Yeah.
But... you two didn't meet?
What nonsense is that?
-It ran away again! Bro!
-Alright, catch it!
Bro, quickly!
Alright, don't let it go.
I thought you let that sheep go free?
Yeah, but I changed my mind.
-Mark! Get the shears!
-Ok.
Terry, I saw your mother over there.
I'm sure she came to see you.
It's already noon
but you're still dreaming?
But,
she came all the way from America.
My mother is in London.
Eleanor Baker isn't your real mother?
I really did it!
What is so funny?
You actually bought that story?
So that was a lie?
Of course.
Bro, the shears!
Alright! Now, let's get to work!
Get ready, Eleanor!
Eleanor?
The number was stupid
so my bro made up this name!
Eleanor, I'm going to
tear that disguise off you.
Terry...
It's your duty to keep human warm.
The same way a mother has a duty to
protect her child with her kind heart!
If you can't do that,
you're not a sheep!
nor a mother!
Do you understand, Eleanor?
While Terry was saying these words...
Candy remembered Mark's house...
where she saw a poor mother and
her son helping each other.