The situation of the war in Europe
is getting worse and worse.
The Merry Jane Nurse School...
is recruiting a nurse
for the army under order.
Frannie volunteers
for this nursing job.
As a result,
Frannie and Candy
are heading with sorrows,
for the European battlefield.
The family with love and hated.
I really wonder how's Frannie going.
After she went to the front-line
for nursing,
I start to get the feeling the war
was never that close to my life.
I wanna write to her,
but without knowing
where she might be.
Frannie, when we were together,
there were times
I wanted you to go away.
Now I'm feeling very lonely.
Good morning, everyone.
Morning.
What happened to the
coldhearted four-eyes frog?
Coldhearted four-eyes frog?
That's very rude.
Because she's as cold as ice.
Coldhearted four-eye frog.
She deserves that.
Frannie goes to the front-line
voluntarily for nursing the army.
We should be nicer to her.
Let's pray for Frannie.
Frannie will be the nurse for army.
She didn't tell her parents at all.
Are you kidding?
Even though I go to the battlefields,
my family would't worry about me.
My father gets drunk everyday
and quarrels with my mom.
My brother and sister
never give a helping hand to others.
Everybody lives their own lives.
You think a family like that
would care anything about me?
Don't be silly.
And don't worry about me either.
But Frannie...
Frannie,
Even if we're not your family,
we do worry about you.
The patients prays for your safety.
It may noy be my business,
but I need to tell your family.
I have a day off tomorrow.
By the way,
I have no idea where Frannie lives.
We've been getting along with
each other for a long time,
but I hardly even know her address.
Frannie Hamilton.
I got it.
Thank you!
Wester Street No.360,
Chicago City.
Frannie's home is a little bit far
from here,
I think I could be back
before evening.
Oh, no.
The bus is never showing up.
Candy!
Stear!
Are you on your day off?
Yes.
Why don't you tell me, Candy?
I am quite busy today.
I am going to visit Frannie's family.
You're going to Frannie's house?
I can give you a ride.
-But....
-Is that inconvenient?
I don't want to bother you.
Not at all, Archie and Annie
are going out for a date.
I have nothing to do, so
keeping hanging out on the street.
I see.
Today I can drive you anywhere
you like.
Hop on!
Thank you, Stear.
It's my honor to offer you a ride.
Let's go!
Frannie's decision of nursing
for the army is very respectable.
But I still don't think she should
hide this decision from her parents.
You're going to tell her family?
Am I being officious?
No. You're doing the right thing.
I feel more relieved, thank you.
Stear, the car is on fire!
That's ok. It's only overheated.
Let's get some water from the store.
It's hot!
Candy, hand me some water.
The water is behind you.
Done!
Stear,
has Pattie ever written to you?
yes, just a couple weeks ago.
Is everything ok with her?
She says hi to you.
She didn't write me a word.
She told me in the letter that...
She really wants to meet you
and have a chat about old times.
Our ears would be overused
and callused next time we meet.
That's possible.
I wish she could come to the States.
Serve in the army voluntarily.
Our country needs
voluteer soldiers to the front.
There will be more people
going to the battlefields.
The war would be
more and more intense.
Let's go.
My face is all covered with dust.
I wanna find a place to wash my face.
OK.
So pretty!
Before the war,
Europe is as beautiful as it is.
Here's Frannie's hometown.
If Frannie has a boyfriend now,
do you think she's still going?
Frannie's definitely going
according to her personality.
She values the mission
of nursing the most.
Stop!
I'm going for asking directions.
Excuse me,
how can I get to this address?
What address?
Frannie Hamiliton, she's the daughter
of Hamiliton the Drunk.
I know him.
Hamiliton the Drunk?
Yes.
Just go straight along this street.
Drive a little further.
It's that apartment over there.
Here we are.
It's weird!
Excuse me, anybody home?
Hi,
I am Candy, a friend of Frannie.
Can I come in?
Nobody's home?
I wanna meet your parents.
Where are they?
Brother,
you have to come back today.
Idiot, I won't.
You little street gangster!
Are they there?
Drunk, get out of here!
You're such an
annoying old wmoman.
Annoying old woman.
Is he your father?
Mr. Hamiliton, are you alright?
Put yourself together!
That's ok. He's always like that.
But we can't let him lie down
on the road.
Help me, Stear.
Sure.
Come on.
I don't know who you are.
Please mind your own business.
But....
It's ok. He's my husband.
You're Frannie's mom?
Old woman, listen up,
Nobody can bully me out
if I ain't here.
Excuse me,
are you Frannie's mother?
Frannie? Who are you?
I am Frannie's friend, Candy White.
I am Candy's friend.
My name is Stear.
Did Frannie ask you to come?
No.
If you are looking for Frannie,
I know nothing about her.
She left this home without
saying goodbye for being a nurse.
I've got no message from her
since then.
Frannie left
without saying good bye?
She's always being selfish,
without any consideration
of my pain.
Please don't worry about her.
Frannie is an outstanding nurse.
What kind of outstanding nurse?
She abandoned her parents
and left her family behind.
She's not qualified
to be a nurse at all.
Is there Mr.Hamiliton's store?
Yes.
You have a package.
A package?
Thank you.
Who sent it? It's Frannie.
Frannie?
Dear mom, I become a real nurse
as I always dream of.
Now I'll continue my nursing work
in Europe.
The pipe is for dad,
the hair pin is for mom,
the harmonica is for my brother,
and the candies are for my sister.
All my money is saved
in this piggy bank,
and I hope these things
can give some help to you. Frannie.
There isn't much money.
Do you think this little money
is enough to pay us back?
Silly girl.
No, Frannie is really respectable.
Respectable for what?
She didn't mention in the letter...
but in fact she stands out
for the victims in the front.
She goes to the European battlefields.
She'll be the nurse for the army.
Frannie is going to be the nurse
for the army?
Why didn't she get back
and discuss with us?
She's trying to let me worry
on purpose.
She is afraid of making you worry,
that's why she didn't send
any word to you.
She sent you all her savings,
because she has already
made her mind.
Going to the front voluntarily.
Such a silly girl.
She shouldn't have done that.
It makes no difference for victims
and patients from different nations.
We, as nurses, can't have
discriminations on anybody.
The nationality and race
don't matter.
Everyone is equal.
Frannie knows it well.
Maybe she hates her family.
No, she wish
she could hate her family,
but she just can't
leave you behind in the end.
She's eager to meet you all.
That's why she sent this package
after all.
Luckily I had come here.
I finally understand
the difficulties that Frannie faces.
It makes me admire her
and feel sorry for her.
Get out!
Get out immediately!
Our family is without any merits,
we don't need any luster and glory.
Angel in white.
That's so hilarious.
The hair pin is for mom,
the pipe is for dad,
the harmonica is for my brother,
and the candies are for my sister.
Frannie
Good bye.
Here you are, Candy.
Thank you for today, Stear.
No, I wanna say thank you, too.
I understand a lot of things today.
Frannie's family will change
eventually.
They definitely will.
Good bye, Stear.
Good bye, Candy.
Bye.
What happened in the hospital?
It's noising.
What happened?
That guy is frightening.
His ID hasn't been identified yet.
What's wrong?
Candy, he seems to be a spy.
A spy?
We're not sure.
We heard that he's a prisoner.
I don't like that.
And he was sent to our hospital
from the European battlefields.
From battlefields?
Make a way!
Make a way, nurses.
He's that guy.
He looks like losing all his energy
and as white as a sheet.
His mouth looks familiar.
Is it really possible that
he is...
Skunk.
-Is that a skunk?
-It's stinky!
Get out!
Isn't that Poopet?
Poopet.
Poopet, it's really you!
Poopet, that guy...
His name is Poopet.
He wants to be friends with you.
My name's Candy.
Nice to meet you!
Mr. Albert is always
encouraging me.
Good morning, Candy.
Mr. Albert.
I got the letter.
Let's get inside the house.
This place is really desolate.
Wait a second.
You have to pass a test
before you get in.
A test?
You'll know.
Here comes the guests!
There are so many of them!
Clint, they are all your partners.
Itching!
They're so cute!
Long time no see, Candy.
It's really you, Mr. Albert!
Before I came to London,
I was really afraid that
I couldn't see you again.
Don't cry, Candy.
Let me take a closer look of you.
You're getting prettier.
So is Mr, Albert.
Mr. Albert...
Why did he come back
from the European battlefields?
Candy can't believe it's true.
That's impossible!
Candy repeats this sentence
in her heart again and again.