Inspector Meilu
wanted to dry Candy away
as doctor Keli is not here.
He caused Candy to the carve.
The gentle runaway
How about it?
No,I will not go back. I am the nurse
I will not quit the patient.
You talked very well.
I will throw you to the train.
What do you want,help?
Put the capative to the train.
Then go to the clinic for her luggage
Don't forget a big cloth.
Send her to the station in the midnight
for the early train tomorrow morning.
Wrap her and throw her to the train.
Do it.
What a stubborn girl.
The time is not enough.
No one dare to be lazy tomorrow.
Too noisy. I have no mood to talk.
Too noisy.
Ok,that's enough.
No,she will be in the train tomorrow.
Keli.
Keli,thank you.
The harun.
Keli,that's right.
Look,she's run away.
Keli,hurry. Sit here.
Wait,stop. It's dangerous.
Put on this.
Hey.
Stop. It's dangerous.
It seems heavier and quicker than here.
Stop,stop.
Keli,there.
Keli,come on.
Too bad.
Don't let her run away.
Help.
What,do you want to give up?
No,don't go anywhere.
That's good. How nice.
Who are you?
I don't know what did she do.
I want to take care of her.
Who are you,what do you want?
I want to work here.
What,work here,don't joke. I am the inspector.
How can I let you work here.
You want to refuse me.
Wait,it's better to let him be the porter.
That's right. That's much better.
Do what you like.
Thank you.
It's dangerous. Are you hurt?
Thanks to you.
Your hand. Please come to the clinic.
That's nothing.
It will turn big wound. Let's go.
The bear.
Yes,we are together when we are young.
That's good.
Don't drag like this all the time.
You are.
That's right.
That's ok,Mr. Sha.
You...
Don't worry. I am your friend.
I have heard about you from your sister.
Sister,you meet her? Where is her?
She's working here.
Here?
Where,where?
Not now. She found you were in Chicargo.
Is she in Chicargo now?
Must meet somewhere.
Why like this.
Doctor Keli must come back to the clinic.
No,I will not stay in the same place for twice.
Do you know why?
I know why.
You know I am a murderer.
I know how much I can believe you.
Doctor Keli's bed is empty.
Thank you very much.
What do you do now?
I went to a lot of place
Not the same place twice.
It's ok in here. You can have a good sleep.
Thank you,Candy.
Good night.
Thank you,Candy
I didn't sleep well for a long time.
After he murder a man,he never slept well.
Write to Anti,let her know Sha.
Mother,that's all right.
Then,knock the spoon.
Yes.
Get up,get up. The breakfast is ready.
Malu,it's bean rice today?
You're the fattest.
That's right.
Get up,breakfast is ready.
It's Keli. Good morning.
Keli,that's moving. Go to wash your face.
Good morning,Mr. Sha.
Do you get up?
Yes. You can open the door.
Morning,Mr. Sha.
Morning,Candy.
Do you sleep well?
Thank you. This is the first time
I slept so well.
That's good. The breakfast is ready
Do you have work to do today?
Open the door light.
It's not big dinner. But it tastes delicious.
Good. That's good.
Good. I am a little worried.
I didn't eat the hot food for a long time.
Candy,where's your breakfast.
Magu will send to me later.
It's only for me?
That's right.
Thank you.
The inspector must be bad to you.
That's all right. I can stand it.
The new one,hurry up,don't fly away.
Yes,go now.
Be careful. Don't be careless.
That's all right. Thank you,Candy.
Hurry up,everyone's waiting.
Be careful.
Come back soon.
Anti,what a warm welcome.
If there's any news
contact Candy as soon as possible.
Thank you.
To the Newao station.
Let Candy to come on.
Ok,bye bye.
Bye,bye.
Anti,are you there?
Where am I,Anti?
The urgent letter,from Candy.
Sha comes here. Who's Sha?
Anti wrote back to Candy.
Sha is the murderer. Candy hide the murderer.
To the police station,quick.
Ilasha,where are you going?
Candy will lose the qualification as the nurse
if it's known she hide the murderer.
This time,Candy must...
It's 8,the work is over
What's wrong with Mr. Sha?
I am worried. I will go to have a look.
What's wrong. Cheer up.
Cheer up. Do yo see who did it?
Not the man from here.
Everyonw knows the inspector
treats him as his own son.
Cheer up,Ma.
What's wrong?
Candy,you come at last.
Please,save Ma.
Sir,he's ill.
Ill,someone makes it.
What's the illness.
This.
You are just a nurse
even do not know the illness.
I am the nurse to see the people.
Ma is just the same as man.
Brother to study as well as the animial doctor.
Sir,someone can save him.
Where?
Mr. Sha.
The young kid?
He's the animal doctor in the future.
That's it. Sha is too tired to get up.
What do you say?
That's all right. Bring him here,let he cure Ma.
Inspector.
Open the mouth. That's all right. Don't worry.
I will see it in the morning.
Ok.
How can he be a murderer?
Ticket please.
The last station.
Yes.
To the set in Gulei town.
All the people will be there
Tomorrow night can be there.
That's good,Ma,can eat more now.
I will feed him. You take a rest
Sorry to make you work so hard.
The same to you. Forget the murderer.
Just think taking care of Ma.
It seems go back to before. That's good feeling.
Mr. Sha.
The breakfast's here.
Eat,Candy.
Thank you.
That's luxury.
Command from inspector.
Inspector?
Not mine,it's Ma's.
Eat it together,Mr. Sha.
Excuse,please move to the box before.
It will stop for about an hour.
To Gulei town,it's really hard.
For the telegram from Gulei town.
So to find the man.
That's it.
It's too tired for you.
Perhaps brother is in Gulei town.
Then,only two of us
It seems the work,that's great.
There's one too.
Sorry,is it to the Gulei set?
Yes.
Do you work there before.
For a short time.
There's a nurse called Candy,do you know her?
Nurse?
It seems the nurse hide a murderer.
Excuse me.
It's Sha.
Big rain. Doctor Keli will come back later.
Big rain. There must be a lot mud on the way.
Is there any hotel nearby?
None,we must stay here tonight.
Really?
Do you want to have a drink,it's warm.
Where's other passanger?
He said he went to the WC
But he didn't come back yet. Strange guy.
Do not let others see your face
I will see outside.
So do I.
Be careful.
Let Sha went to the police station.
What?
No where. Where did he go?
Is there anything to do with the murderer?
Don't worry.
Before the Carve be used,it can't go there.
It won't stop.
After the rain,Candy and Sha knows
nothing about who will come to visit.
The clinic in the moutain,becomes quiet.