In order to save Candy
Terry left the school in her place.
When she realized what had happened
Candy went after him.
However, Terry' s ship already left
Candy was unable to say farewell to him.
And so... a week had passed.
Departure shrouded by the morning mist.
Enter.
Candice' s here.
Candice White Adley.
A week of room confinement has passed.
From now on, I' d like you to make
an effort at becoming a prominent lady.
-Do you understand?
-Yes.
Becoming a prominent lady?
What is so great about being a lady?
Candy!
You' re free again?
Yes!
Thank goodness.
You must have been verry worried, right?
Don't worry about us.
We' re really sorry for Terry.
Patty!
No! I ' m not supposed to bring up this
topic in front of Candy.
-Silly me...
-It' s okay, Patty.
But, I really wanted to
bid my farewell to him.
We understand how you feel.
Now, let' s go to the classroom.
You have some nerve to show up here.
That' s right. If not for Terry,
you would've been expelled now.
Candy, how come that people who
bring calamity to others always survive?
I bring calamity to others?
Isn't it true?
You caused Anthony' s death...
you also drove Terry out of school.
Horrible! Eliza.
Just who is horrible?
You snatch away people
leading them to their ruin.
Eliza, you and Terry...
Don't say such stupid things.
I just can't forgive you.
I see. So that' s what it was.
Eliza had an eye on Terry.
As for me...
After Terry was expelled instaed of her
she only spent a week in detention...
I can't forgive that.
That' s right.
How come the strict rules
so easily bent this time?
We must have Candy expelled.
You' re saying horrible things. Eliza.
That' s right!
She already bore her punishment.
We can't agree with that.
First of all, such a problem in school
concerns every one of us.
That' s right! Girls come to this school
in order to become ladies.
Now we had nothing but trouble
since we got the girls from Pony' s home.
Everyone, be quite!
Assume your seats, please.
Sister Chrisse
We' d like an explanation
of Candy' s punishment.
What?
Candy isn't working at becoming a lady.
And yet, why is she still in this school?
Are you asking why Candice
isn't making any effort?
Candice always causes so many trouble.
When she was a dogsbody in my house
she kept stealing from us.
That' s not true. She' s making up.
Wait a second.
Are you complaining the punishment
Sister Gray gave to Candy?
Exactly.
If you have any complaints
let' s hear it.
Sister Gray.
Eliza Leagan. Speak up.
Sister Gray
her punishment was ridiculous.
Pick your words, Eliza.
I never thought that
you would be the one to bend rules.
Is there something behind this?
Eliza Leagan.
You are henceforth
confined to your room for a week.
Sister Gray...
I' m returning you the letter
which you sent to Terrius.
Eliza was confined to her room?
Feels graet.
I planned to use my lie detector
to get a confession out of her but...
this is way better.
What' s the matter? Candy.
I' d like to see Other Pony' s hill.
That' s right.
Why don't we go together?
No! I meant alone.
That' s right.
Candy wants some solitude to think.
I' m sorry.
Candy, feel free to go.
Just make sure that you' d come back
with your usual smile, okay?
She is preoccupied with Terry.
Wait.
Neil! What' s the meaning of this?
Candy! it was your fault that
Eliza confined to her room.
It was not my fault.
You have not left this school
so it has come down to this.
What are you doing?
-Go away!
-Stop!
Cry all you want.
Terry can't help you anymore.
You should've gone away with Terry.
Go away.
We' ll get it out on you
for every single time Terry hurts us.
Remember this well.
Let' s go!
Terry, why didn't you take me
with yourself?.
I want to leave, too.
Kurin.
Thank you, Kurin.
I' m fine now.
You want me to climb it?
Okay!
So many sweets.
Terry let you have them?
Terry!
I don't want to live in a place
where you aren't around.
If I leave this place...
I would've trampled over everything
Terry did for me.
Terry! I want to do my best.
I' m not going to give in to
Eliza' s and Neil' s ploys.
Confining me to my room for a week.
Very well, I' m sure I' ll come up with
something fun in the meantime.
I' ll have Candy expelled for sure.
Welcome, Duke Grandchester.
Sister Gray
I' m here to have a word with you.
Please this way.
How can I help you?
Please take a look at this.
Terrius wrote about how he left school
in place that girl, Candy.
Terrius wrote...
Is this true? Sister Gray.
I thought you already knew about it.
So that' s how it was.
I heard him mentioning this...
but I didn't think that
he was serious about it.
Sister Gray
Why don't you inform me sooner?
It' s...
The name of Grandchester might get hurt
if I made too much noise.
And where is my son now?
Well... most likely to America.
America?
That means... to Eleanor' s.
Sister Gray
I want you to bring back my son.
If you can't find him back.
I' ll stop donation to this school.
Duke Grandchester...
Am I not correct?
Why should I support a school
my son doesn't attend?
I understand.
I' ll do my best to bring him back.
Do you have any traces?
Candice might know more about
where Terrius is heading.
In that case, Sister Gray.
Why don't you call over this Candice?
-You' re Candice?
-Yes!
You know where is Terrius?
No!
Candice, do you know whether Terrius
made this decision on his own accord?
Terry... no, Terrius only wrote that
he' s going to America...
he didn't mention any details.
Is that true?
It' s true.
I wish he told me where he was going.
You were brought up in Pony' s home
am I correct?
Yes!
You tended horses, too.
am I correct?
You must heard this from Eliza.
Eliza?
I only heard the truth.
You were correct about these things.
And then you were adopted by the Adleys.
Otherwise you wouldn't have
had the chance to study in this school.
Maybe Terrius came to his senses...
when he decided to leave this school.
Sister Gray.
When you bring him back...
I will have him
transfered to a different school.
What will happen with your donations?
We need not talk about that.
Duke Grandchester
If you stop the donation
the school can not survive.
Please, if I ask for just a little...
Excuse me, Sister Gray.
Duke Grandchester.
Please wait.
Candice.
I' d like to speak with you.
Go!
Wait.
Duke Grandchester.
Please! I need to speak to you.
Stop the carriage.
Nobody will see us here.
You can speak now.
Why didn't you tried to
understand Terrius?
You understand him
better than his father?
Yes!
You' re preety fresh.
You have no parents, how can you tell?
Exactly because of that.
Because I have no parents...
I understand Terry' s loneliness.
Terrius needs the love from his father.
He needs the love from his mother.
He already has that.
What?
Terrius has Eleanor' s...
You didn't know that?
No! You didn't want to know anything
about Terrius.
He never mentioned that
he wanted to see Eleanor...
He was forcibly
separated from his mother...
No wonder he started defying you.
And you didn't even try to
understand his feelings.
Terrius is really a gentle, considerate
wonderful person.
You like Terrius?
Yes!
Candy, I decided to quit school
and go to America.
There' s something I' d like to do.
Wherever I might end up
I' ll be praying for your happiness.
Terrius.
What is he planning to do in America?
I don't know.
I' m sure that he' s trying to find
his own path in life.
Therefore, please don't call him back
and take his freedom away.
This is all I want to say.
I don't think we' ll see eachother again.
Farewell, Duke Grandcheater.
Hold on, Candy.
I' ll take you back to school.
No! I' ll go back on foot.
I have something to do
at the school, as well.
Things to do?
To talk about restoring my donation
to the school.
Terry' s younger brother and sister
will go to the same school someday.
Duke Grandchester.
Well, hop in.
Yes!
Candy, you save our school.
No, Duke Grandcheater is a good man.
Anyway, the school is saved.
Excuse me, Sister Gray.
A telegram came from Louise' s house.
Louise' s house?
Call Louise.
Yes!
Well then, you may return to your class.
What' s going on?
Since you flunked your class...
your father is having you removed
from this school.
My father?
You will stay here
until they send you a carriage.
My father...
What happened? Louise.
What' s the matter?
I can't become a lady anymore.
They want me to quit this school.
Louise...
I can't become a lady anymore.
You' re wrong, Louise.
You can't become a lady
simply by being in this school.
It' s not true that one can't be a lady
unless she is wealthy.
Otherwise, she is a shame lady.
Up till now, I've completely relied
on benevolence of the Adley family.
Just what were trying to turn me into
by sending me here?
I don't want to turn into a shame lady
like Louise and Eliza.
Such a thing has no sence.
Terry went to America
to build his own path.
Mr. Albert is taking pride
in his hard working in Africa.
Just like Terry renounced
his Grandchester name.
I will renounce my Adley name.
I' ll tread my own path in life.
I' m sure that Terry and Mr. Albert
would've understand.
I feel like I got something heavy
off my chest.
Eliza is going to stay here and
work hard to become a lady.
I somehow feel sorry for her.
What is it? this late.
Sister Gray
Please amend Eliza' s punishment.
Please.
Candice
Her best friend Louise is gone
I' m sure that Eliza will be lonely.
I don't want to cause her anymore...
I understand, Candice.
It was you who saved the school,
I' ll give her a special treatment.
Thank you, Sister Gray.
Kurin.
Kurin, let' s get out of here.
Alright.
Come, Kurin.
Farewell, Stear, Archie, Annie, Patty...
Farewell, St. Paul academy.
Let' s go, Kurin.
The morning mist completely engulfed
the St. Paul academy.
Candy flew to her freedom
like a little bird released from a cage.