The decision which took away
my happiness.
Candy went on her first vacation
back to Pony's home.
She then managed to
save her beloved father-tree.
Feeling the kindness of sister Pony's
and sister Lane's heart,
Candy felt content again
after such a long time.
Sorry for not being here with you!
Did you miss me?
Kurin, it's okay now.
Thanks.
Here, take this.
They came from the garden
in Pony's home.
I thought that Candy won't return,
but she's back all refreshed now.
And Anthony...
While Candy was gone,
I was frequently riding together
with Anthony.
What's up with that?
As Candy came back,
Anthony became cold to me!
Eliza, I'm sorry, but
you're being way too soft today!
-Brother
-Eliza
What's matter?
Look, Eliza.
It's Dorothy.
Candy
I might have to say farewell
to you soon.
Why?
I'm going to Mexico.
Mexico?
Why are you going to
such a faraway place?
There is an Ardley property
in Mexico.
They are lacking in
manpower there, so...
I've been ordered to go there
and help them.
Many things have happened while
I was away at Pony's home, right?
Yes.
But... why you?
They said it's because
I'm useless in this estate.
But...!
And... it's decided?
And now what...
I don't want to go!
I don't want that!
Why didn't you turn them down?
Candy!
I have many little brothers and
sisters in my home.
If I get fired...
I won't have any money
to send back home!
I'll ask mr. Leagan then!
He's a reasonable person
I'm sure he'll listen to your story.
He won't be back for a long time.
Anyway,I already make my mind
so it's alright!
I'm sorry, Dorothy.
You always knew
how to give me strength.
But I'm not sure what should I do
to give you the strength now.
It's okay, Candy.
Well, I have things to do.
Dorothy!
Poor Dorothy.
If she goes to
such a faraway place...
she might not come back at all.
Kurin, I'm much luckier than her.
Pony's home isn't very far
and I'm living close to
Anthony and the others.
If I set aside
Eliza and Neil's pranks
This is actually a wonderful place!
-How can she say that?
-Eliza!
If she's already become
content with our pranks
Let's see how much
she can really take!
Right, Eliza?
That's it! I wonder if I could
give this to Dorothy as a memento.
Sister Pony!
This is a lucky cross.
If something bad happens to you
I'm sure this cross
will keep you happy.
I'm sure sister Pony
would understand!
I'll remember this, Candy!
Cleopatra, go!
It's a lucky cross.
Thank you, Candy!
I know that it's important to you.
Cleopatra?
I wonder why is she running away.
Dorothy, I'll borrow this rope.
Wait! Cleopatra!
Isn't that Leagan's Cleopatra?
Cleopatra!
Candy!
Anthony!
Quickly, get on!
Hang on!
He appeared at such a great place!
He really is my prince!
You're really good with lasso.
I never planned to show you that.
Why?
Because...
it's the tomboyish Candy.
I like it.
Really?
Anthony... I like you, too!
Alright! You're home.
Thank you, Anthony.
Candy
let's ride again some time.
Well then, goodbye.
Anthony...
Candy was in trouble and he...!
I'll remember this, Candy!
I'll get you thrown out
from here, for sure!
Got it? Be extremely careful
during the dinner!
And don't rush with anything.
Grand aunt Elroy
is a very strict person.
You understand?
-Eliza!
-Yes, Mother!
Do you know
where is my emerald brooch?
No, and moreover
I can't find my bracelet!
That's strange.
I must have dropped it somewhere
underneath the dresser...
Mother!
Aunt Elroy's car
is coming this way!
Oh, no!
Everyone, hurry up!
Hey!
Is it Anthony?
Sorry, it's aunt.
I wanted him to see how
perfect I am.
Great aunt Elroy has just arrived.
Welcome, great aunt Elroy.
Welcome, aunt.
What's with that sad face?
I'm very sorry.
It seems that a brooch
I got from you disappeared somehow.
My bracelet is gone, too!
That's your own fault.
Mother! It's an emergency!
What are you doing?
Why are you running
in front of aunt Elroy?
I found both the brooch
and the bracelet!
I've been looking for those!
Where have you found them?
In the barn, with Candy's things.
She might have taken other
things, as well.
How horrible.
So that's how
she's repaying your kindness.
I'll go look.
I'll go as well.
The barrel is finally full now.
What's the matter?
Everybody has that scary look...
Candy
We are going to take a look
in the barn.
Neil, Eliza
turn everything upside down.
Yes!
Wait!
You allowed them to go through
my things and luggage?
-That's right.
-Stop that!
I won't let you do that!
What did you say?
Thieves don't have the right
to say that!
Thieves?
Eliza
what is the meaning of that?
Just what is this?
It's my dress!
Mother's ring!
I don't know about that!
What's this ribbon?
That's Annie's ribbon!
Candy
what's up with this ribbon?
That's ...
I won't tell them.
I won't tell the truth.
That we both lived in Pony's home.
I'll keep quiet for Annie's sake.
You even stole the ribbon
from Annie?
I didn't !
How did you get it then?
Miss Annie gave it to me!
Annie wouldn't give something like this
to a complete stranger!
I'm disgusted!
What a horrible child!
She exposed her true nature now.
I don't know!
I know nothing about this!
I don't remember anything!
Candy
I won't put up with this anymore!
Instead of Dorothy,
I'm sending you to Mexico!
Me? To Mexico!?
Yes. I won't allow thieves
to live in this household!
But... if Mr. Leagan knew this
I'm sure he'd be against it!
A servant, she even dares to
drag Mr. Leagan into this!
I'm sure he would understand...!
I'm going to write a letter to him
and explain the situation!
The girl he brought here as a playmate
for Eliza turned out to be a thief!
There's no way
Father could forgive her!
Madam! please!
Just don't send Candy to Mexico!
Dorothy!
I'm the one who's supposed
to go to Mexico!
Yes. It would be better if you
just handed her over to the police.
No, aunt.
If people learned that
we were harboring a thief,
it would bring great shame
to the Leagan family.
Even the Adleys would look bad.
Maybe that's so...
Do you understand, Candy?
You'll be heading for Mexico
as soon as possible!
Pack your bags now!
-Candy.
-Dorothy.
Finally...
Finally, it came to an end.
Candy, I'll return this to you.
If it's become like this,
I'll let you have it again!
Because the situation with you
and me had reversed completely!
Dorothy!
Candy, don't let go of this.
Because this is a lucky cross!
I am not going to Mexico!
I'm going to run away from here.
Candy! You mustn't do that!
Why?
This is not a problem of you alone!
You have many children in Pony's
home behind you!
Children in Pony's home...
If you run away from here,
the rumours will spread around,
and people who want to adopt children
will stop coming to Pony's home.
Then... are you saying I should
keep quiet and go to Mexico?
Be patient. I'm sure the truth
will come out someday.
If you have that lucky cross,
you can make yourself a chance!
Candy!
Candy.
What a rain!
It cooled me off a bit!
Candy.
Dorothy
you'd better head back in.
Candy!
If you don't come back soon,
they'll scold you again!
Yeah! See you then!
Because they said I'm a thief...
I have to go to Mexico.
To a faraway place, with no
memories or people I know.
I don't want that!
I don't want to go to Mexico!
I don't want to part
from Anthony.
I want to stay here forever.
But... what should I do?
There's Mr. Albert, too!
Candy is going to Mexico?
Raise your hands!
A bum, right?
What are you doing here?
The guard had found me.
However, I'm not ready
to leave this place yet.
Running away
some guy you are!
I'll throw you out myself.
Pack your stuff
Get out of this place!
Move it!
What's that?
-Don't touch that!
-Got it?
If I find you inside
he Ardley property again
I'm gonna shoot you dead!
Candy...
Mr. Albert!
Why didn't you come soon?
Mr. Albert?
Mr. Albert's sunglasses.
Mr. Albert already left this place.
Leaving... to some new places...
Mr. Albert is trying to find
a new place for himself.
Anthony, Archie and Stear...
I want all of you to believe.
Believe that I'm not a thief.
I'm going to Mexico.
I'm going for sure!
Courage appeared in Candy's heart.
A heart which was not afraid
of the unknown.