After leaving London,
Candy went into a journey.
The moment when she got back.
She missed a carriage on the way home.
The carriage is now leaving.
It is Terry who on that carriage.
Silvery homeland.
Kurin, do your best! Come.
Kurin,
we can't keep moving forward.
Where can we stay?
There' s nothing I can see.
Who is there?
It' s...
Mr. Matthew?
Candy, it' s really you.
It is real. Kurin is here too.
I thought it was a snowman.
That's great!
If not for Mr. Matthew.
I might be trouble by now.
I thought you were ghosts,
at the moment I found you.
Do you want to eat something?
That' s all right.
Kurin, don't be naughty.
The snow has stopped.
Mr. Matthew, I should leave now.
Say hello to sister Pony
and sister Lane for me.
Yes!
Excuse me.
Candy!
Your luggage.
My goodness!
Good-bye.
Even comes back from England
didn't change a bit.
What do you say?
Nothing! The weather is fine.
Kurin, wait!
Pony' s home
is right at the end of the road.
sister Pony, sister Lane,
I' m home.
Candy!
Boss Candy!
Stop!
Jimmy
It is really you.
Jimmy!
Boss!
Boss, It' s not a dream, is it?
Yes, Jimmy. I' m home.
I...
I saw someone there,
didn't sure it' s you.
It is you for sure.
Jimmy, you' re grown tall already,
still like a child.
Let me have a look.
I am working for Mr. Cartwright now.
The cowboy?
Something like that!
Boss, sister Pony and others
will be happy to see you.
They' re worrying about you yesterday.
How are sister Pony and others?
Of course, everybody is fine.
Let's hurry!
Give everybody a big surprise.
They' ll Talk about this endlessly.
Just like before.
Just like before?
Yes, there' s a man here.
A man was here? What kind of man?
Handsome and disagreeable.
Disagreeable? Handsome?
What is his name? Jimmy.
Something like Terrius, I remember.
Terrius?
It' s Terry.
Terry, I've never expected
you will come to the Pony' s home.
Could it be a dream?
that you come to the Pony' s home.
Terry.
Boss!
I want to see you, Terry.
Pony' s home... Terry is there.
Terry.
Pony' s home.
Candy!
Sister Lane.
Where is Terry?
Why are you here? Candy.
Terry!
Candy, wait!
Sister Pony!
What's the matter?
-Terry!
-Candy!
Terry.
Sister Pony, where is Terry?
Terrius G. Grandchester.
He had already left thirty minutes ago.
After visiting the Pony' s hill
he just left.
Candy!
Candy, wait!
He took the carriage already.
Candy!
Maybe I can still catch up with him.
Terry.
Terry, I can find you nowhere.
The moment I get home,
Terry is here by himself.
Wearing the overcoats and stand here.
The coffee cup is still warm.
The footprint in the snowfield
is still there.
Terry, I' m coming home now.
I miss you so much...
I miss you.
It' s about noon...
He stood in front of Pony' s home
looking sad.
You are Candy' s friend from London?
Is something wrong with Candy?
No, she is fine.
I' d like to visit the place
where Candy grew up.
Excuse me, you and Candy...
We are good friend.
Sorry to bother you.
You' re leaving?
I am in a hurry.
Where is Pony' s hill?
That father tree over there.
There' s a road on it' s left side
follow it and cross the river.
He asked the carriage to wait.
Then he walked to the hill step by step.
Terry.
You visit the Pony' s home
what do you want to know?
This is my second Pony' s hill.
You can't smoking here.
Give the cigarette.
Not just one, I want them all.
Here! exchange for that.
Don't be sad, Candy!
Is the body warm?
It smells so good. I' ll take it.
Candy,
how can you leave the St. Paul academy?
Why you so panic?
Sister Lane
let's talk about it tomorrow.
It better make it clear now.
Candy,
have something to do with Terry?
No, it' s only because
I don't want to rely on anyone.
It is not shame
to accept others' s help.
Sister Lane.
Candy, you must be tired,
why don't you take some sleep.
Sister Pony always dotes on Candy.
Never mind!
Let' s talk about it tomorrow.
Sister Pony, sister Lane,
you didn't change a bit.
Okay! Let' s talk about it tomorrow.
-OKay? Candy.
-Yes.
Candy!
I will get up early tomorrow.
Good night, Sister Pony.
Good night!
Sister Pony, What happened to Candy?
She' s leaving us for a long time.
Is that so?
The day Candy and Annie were abanded
is also snowing too.
What can I say?
We brought her up since she was a baby.
Return from London,
she became a lady now.
No, Candy is changed.
She is not a child anymore.
Sister Pony.
Have you noticed?
The expression when she got home.
We haven't seen her for one year
Whose name did she call?
Terry.
Really.
She no longer shouts for us,
sister Pony.
Candy is ripe already.
From now on, we may not...
treat her as a child anymore.
Terry visits my homeland alone.
I should treasure his compliment.
Terry, at this moment
the most important thing for us...
It' s not meet again.
We must look for the goal and go for it.
We will meet again someday.
They' re all slept.
Candy' s bed has been diminished.
Really, She has grown up indeed.
Sister Pony, sister Lane.
They take care of me all the time.
It' s so good at home. Really good.
Boss.
Boss, get up quickly.
Who' s shouting there? I' m not...
It' s cold!
You' re getting weak,
the boss is not like this before.
What do you say?
I am just careless.
Wait there, I' ll change the clothes.
Jimmy, turn around.
Thanks, Jimmy.
I' ll catch you out there.
Where are you going? Candy.
Sister Lane,
I need some exercise before breakfast.
Jimmy.
Boss, you' re doing well, over here.
You are too cunning.
You' re just standing there.
Candy' s still naughty.
Back to the old time, I guess.
Boss!
Jimmy, what are you doing?
Over here, quick!
I almost forget.
We have something to show you.
Something?
Right! For your coming home.
Hurry up!
All finished by everybody.
Please unveil.
Claps hands, everybody.
We got up very early for this.
Boss, welcome back!
Thank you!
This present is excellent.
-It' s you, right?
-Which one is really?
Yes, It' s really look like me.
Only those two pigtails...
Everybody,
let' s dance welcome the boss.
Standing in the snowfield,
Candy feels no cold at all.
Everything make her feel so warm.
Terry called on the Pony' s home.
Sister Pony, sister Lane,
and the children.
Candy feel so warm about everything.