Candy came to the Adleys in Chicago.
Encountered Neal and his sister Elisa.
And then,she visited Grand Aunt Elroy
who she hadn't seen for a while.
Grand Aunt Elroy was as expected,
not very friendly to Candy.
A cabin for memory.
Candy, let's stay in this place tonight,
and we can chat all night!
I found a good place for us.
Everyone must be excited about it.
Everyone?
Including Pattie?
Archie, what did you say?
Pattie is coming?
Brother, we should tell her.
Pattie wrote us in the middle of this month.
France was in critical condition
after the war started.
It's just a matter of time for England
to join the war.
Although Pattie is safe in London so far,
she will be involved sooner or later.
I hope she can come to America
as soon as possible.
I saw Brother's face when reading the letter,
Candy.
-Archie
-Come, Annie, Candy.
This way.
It's here.
What place is this?
Take your time to look around.
Stear, Archie
The door is not that way.
Door? What do you mean?
Isn't Candy leaving?
No, Candy is leaving tomorrow.
They are spending a night here getting good rest.
Shouldn't you be leaving?
Who wants to leave?
We are staying over tonight, right, Brother?
Sure!
Stear and Archie, take them away right now!
I don't want to be with them.
Neal, shut up!
Don't be rude to the ladies.
I know.
But, they are not ladies.
They are orphans from Pony's Home.
Bastard! Let's fight!
No, Archie, please!
Right, it's a waste of time.
Don't waste our time.
Right, Archie?
Let's go!
Annie, don't keep it in mind.
Come, let's go!
I can't believe you dare to come back.
Candy is a big mouth, it's annoying.
- Right, Brother?
- Right.
That two people have to go.
What a broad grassland!
There is a hourse-riding field, too!
It's great!
Look at that big tree!
That is the good place I was talking about.
It's great, Annie, Let's go!
Candy, we haven't running
together for a long time.
It feels so comfortable.
- Can I climb up?
- Sure.
Good.
Amazing, Candy always brings us surprise.
I am coming.
Annie, it's your turn.
Me too?
Candy, put down the rope ladder.
Ok.
Annie, hurry, it's so beautiful here!
Don't be afraid.
Come on.
Thank you, Stear.
Annie, isn't it great?
Looks like a door in Lilliput.
Can I come in?
Sure.
Annie, come along.
This was built by Uncle Marian
when I was little.
Kids who caused any trouble would hide here.
Especially Anthony.
He loved to hide here.
That's ok, Stear.
Anthony must be very cute when he was a kid.
Very cute.
Brother,
I was cuter than Anthony, right?
That's not true, Archie.
I am the cutest without wearing my glasses.
Look.
You can't go back to childhood,
even if you take off your glasses.
Everyone is cute when little.
We, too. Right, Candy?
Candy, why are you smiling with yourself?
I am imagining
how you looked like when little.
You are as silly as Candy.
True.
What are you laughing about, Annie?
Candy was really a silly child.
She still is.
Archie, I hate you.
But, the house is smaller.
It's because we are bigger now.
Sounds like it.
Look, the shoes we used to wear!
- So cute.
- They are worn out.
You were too naughty, that's why.
Come in.
Hello, Mr.Bird.
It likes us.
So peaceful.
Doesn't feel like war at all.
Cool wind blowing
in a clear sky,
with birds singing.
How long can this last?
It will definately last.
Right, but, things are hard to predict.
Young people in England are joining the war.
To protect the country.
We should do the same.
Willing to sacrifice for peace.
Sooner or later, we...
Stop it.
Stop talking about the war.
Sorry, Annie.
Brother was just expressing his feeling.
Stear and Archie are worried about the war, too.
America is about to be involved.
It's true that
we might become the war nurses.
Quiet!
There are no nationalities in medical treatment.
Care giving should be fairly
provided to everyone.
It has nothing to do with countries or races.
Everyone is equal.
I will be recruited anytime.
I want to cherish everything in present.
Don't think too much, cheer up!
You are right.
Watch me.
Stear, are you alright?
Brother, are you out of your mind?
Come on, don't just stay there.
Let's race!
- Race?
- Ok! That's just what I was thinking.
Ready? Go!
Candy, I almost catch you.
Annie, you run so fast.
Come on, Annie.
You guys are good, I can't catch up with you.
Candy hasn't changed.
Of course, I am from the north.
You really are.
Archie, bring Candy and others to their room.
Ok.
Here, it's your room.
So pretty!
Tonight, have a nice chat with Annie
about the old times.
Thank you.
See you later.
What's wrong, Elisa?
Archie and Stear...
arranged what kind of the room for them.
Do you know?
The place tonight?
VIProom.
The best room?
Right.
Arrogant guy.
We should have different positions.
I am not allowing this!
Brother, those two guys must go!
Elisa, come in!
Elisa, I have an idea!
Let's irritate Candy in front
of Grand Aunt Elroy.
So that Grand Aunt Elroy might get mad.
How?
I have an idea!
Grand Aunt Elroy's favorate vase.
Get Candy break the vase
in front of Grand Aunt Elroy?
Coming
Elisa
How lucky that everybody is here!
What can I do for you, Elisa?
Would you like to have some tea together?
What's this about?
It's so boring to drink the tea by myself.
Please go with me.
Thank you, Elisa.
Come on!
She must be playing some trick.
Come on, Stear, let's go!
Hope she doesn't poison the tea.
Candy sit by the vase.
I am going to pick up Grand Aunt Elroy.
Why?
Grand Aunt Elroy is joining us?
She often does things alone.
We should have the tea with her.
Sounds easy, but...
Grand Aunt Elroy used to avoid us
and stay in her room alone.
Is it possible that
she accepted our suggestion?
Grand Aunt Elroy!
Come, Grand Aunt Elroy!
I...
Let me pour out the tea for you.
What is going on?
Elisa, come into my room.
Yes.
Brother, Grand Aunt Elroy was so mad at me.
I am afraid she is gonna kick me
out of there soon.
How did I know Candy would
stand up at that moment?
It was an accident.
Let's think about something else.
Brother, drive!
Hurry!
Elisa, where are we going?
I think I understand.
We are here.
Thank you, Neal.
Let's go visit Grand Aunt Elroy.
Yes, Mother.
- Come in, please!
- Sorry to bother you.
Welcome!
Elisa broke the precious vase
by accident.
I am very sorry.
Candy suddenly stood up...
The kid was careless.
That kid is really a trouble.
Grand Aunt Elroy, why did you let her stay?
I couldn't say anything.
It was Grandfather William's decision.
She is still the Adleys'foster child.
This is the Adley's old house.
She keeps staying here.
What if there is any gossip in the neighborhood?
It will humiliate the Adleys.
Annie is also an orphan of Pony's Home.
An orphan of Pony's Home
going in and out the Adley's.
What would people think about that?
The Adleys will be ashamed,
if people know about this.
Grand Aunt Elroy.
I am willing to take care of this...
for Grand Aunt Elroy.
Please allow it, good-bye.
Candy, isn't it a pretty dress?
It is!
Archie gave it to me.
- Great!
- Candy
Would you like to try it on?
Me?
No, thanks. I am not interested.
Candy,
it's ok for girls to dress up once in a while.
But, I am a nurse...
That's ok.
Look, it fits you!
Let's comb the hair a little bit.
Don't move.
Come here.
So beautiful! You are a pretty woman completely.
It doesn't look like me at all, I am embarrassed.
You will meet Terry again anytime in the future.
You need to learn how to dress up.
Terry
Candy
Mrs.Leagan
Candy, leave here right away!
Annie, you, too.
Why?
Mother represents the Adleys.
Leave here right now.
Listen, this is not the cottage in Lakewood.
This is the Adleys'old house.
Although you are the Adleys'foster child,
if people know that an orphan of Pony's Home
is going in and out the house,
how are the Adleys going to live with that?
Besides,
you are all orphans from Pony's Home.
Hold on.
Mrs.Leagan,
they are our guests.
Archie,
you are a member of the Adleys.
Do not hang out with the orphans
from Pony's Home.
This has nothing to do with Aunt.
Archie, you are being nonsense.
You hang out with these wild kids all day,
no wonder you are getting wild.
Is this an order from Grand Aunt Elroy?
Grand Aunt Elroy doesn't know about this.
I do this for the good of the Adleys.
- Neal
- Yes
- Get the luggage.
- Yes, Mother.
Neal, dare you...
Ouch, Mother!
-Archie
- Don't touch the luggage!
Grand Aunt Elroy doesn't know about this?
Ok, I'll talk to her.
Stop it!
No matter what,
Candy is the Adleys'foster child.
The Leagans has no right to step in.
Understand?
What are you talking about? I can't forgive you!
Stear, forget it.
Enough! I don't care the family is
famous or distinguished.
I am not interested in either.
Of course.
You are orphans of Pony's Home.
Let's get out of here.
Stear, Archie, let's live in the tree house.
Can we, Annie?
But, how can we live in such a small tree house?
I would rather live in a tree house
than a beautiful house.
As long as we feel at ease and justified.
Ok, I understand.
If you really want to do this, go ahead!
Thank you.
That tree house is ours.
Don't come to bother us anymore.
You've never lived in this kind of place.
Can't fall asleep?
As long as we are together,
I don't care where we live.
I have slept in many places.
The straws on the carriage.
You've been through a lot, Candy.
That day...
The Christmas Eve with snow flakes falling...
We were abandoned by our families,
on the same day, at the same place.
We were adopted together.
We grew up together.
We walked towards different
directions in life until now.
Good-bye, Annie.
But,you've been through a lot
you're brave and strong.
I can't compare to you.
Candy
Don't leave me!
What are you talking about?
We are good sisters forever.
- Candy
-Annie
Sister Pony and Sister Lane,
are they doing alright?
Candy, was there any change in Pony's Home?
Same as usual.
- How about Kurin?
- Fine.
I wish I could go back to where I grew up.
Candy and Annie forgot all their worry.
They are immersed in the memory of Pony's Home.