Stear, Archie,
I'm going to strike out on my own.
After losing her beloved Anthony,
Candy returned to Pony's home.
Father-tree knows.
Pony's home,
the place Candy was so fond of,
...hasn't changed at all.
However, what she found there
were more memories of Anthony.
Candy, let's ride!
Candy, relax.
Just don't fall from my arms!
It's okay.
I'm holding on tightly!
Candy?
Sister Pony, do you know that
Candy keeps crying?
Yes, I know.
I wonder was it good for her
to return at this time...
That's the very reason
why she returned now.
She returned here to draw her attention
away from the sadness within.
I'm sure that she's now gathering the
strenght to overcome the sadness.
What, " Candy, candy" ...!
Wasting too many words on her!
Jimmy, you just came to Pony's home,
You don't know anything about Candy,
you can't say such things!
John
you're always talking about Candy.
She's really a no-good weepy bitch!
Don't say such things!
What was that again?
Want some?
Listen up!
Candy is no more boss here.
The real boss is right here.
But...
Candy gets all scary when she's mad.
Let's make her angry, then!
-Don't do that!
-Shut up!
-Hey, don't ...
-She's just a crybaby!
It's a rose!
Got you there!
You like roses, don't you!
Hey, what are you doing?
Now she's gonna get mad.
Wait up!
I'm not scared of you!
You're just moping around alone,
as if a saddest thing in the world!
Crybaby!
Crybaby?
Come to think of it,
when I first met Anthony...
Hello, Miss Crybaby!
Anthony.
There she goes again!
Sir, your voyage was so long.
Maybe so.
I'm indebted to you two
for taking care of Anthony.
As a father,
there was nothing I could do.
Mister, we are your friends.
We'll be waiting.
Please come see us again.
Thank you. Take care.
Mister, you take care, too.
I would like you two to take
all Anthony's belongings.
Afterwards...
Give them to that girl
you've been telling me about.
I would like to meet her someday.
We understand, mister.
Take care!
Take me to rose gates!
Yes.
He lost his wife before.
Now, this kind old man lost his son.
What is left for him now?
How can he laugh again
or say hello to someone?
Yesterday, he stood at the
rose gates all night long.
I know. It was such a cold night.
How's Candy doing right now.
Let's leave her alone
until she regains her footing.
Everyone seems to be
lost in sadness right now.
There she goes again.
I'm gonna get her mad this time!
Just look at this!
What's this...
Now you did it!
Aaah! "We did it?!"
I'm gonna kick your assess!
Run!
She's gone nuts!
Wait, you coward!
Pony's hill.
It's Pony's hill.
The hill where I first met the Prince.
And so, Candy came to the hill
where she promised with Anthony.
I hear the sound of bagpipes!
These are bagpipes. Okay?
Want to hear?
It sounds like
snails are having a party!
Snails? That's a good one!
Prince!
Cheer up, Miss Freckle!
This weepy face looks strange on you!
But...
But... Anthony have died!
Candy!
Anthony!
Candy, I'm right here.
Look. Right next to you. Always.
Anthony!
Candy, winter is drawing near.
Roses are going to die.
For this reason,
when the summer came...
The roses will bloom beautifully.
The flowers die,
but inside of human hearts...
they keep living eternally.
What's the matter, Candy!
You can't catch up to us!
Crybaby Candy!
Candy?
Why are you looking so lonely?
Anthony...
Are you not going to appear
in my memories anymore?
Anthony! My Anthony!
It went pretty well today.
If everybody try a little harder
the next time...
That's right.
it's almost Christmas.
Sister Pony, sister Lane and everybody
are rising donations.
Sister Pony,
let's give it another try tommorrow.
That's right. We'll buy presents
for the children with this money.
-Candy?
-Sister
Let me handle the donations!
Candy, eavesdropping is bad!
I'm sorry. But I want to be helpful!
Thank you, Candy.
But it's okay.
Why is that?
Don't you have something to do?
-Something to do?
-That's right.
You need to get well quickly,
through the heart broken.
Candy, there's more than sadness
over one's death,
you should be happy
because you had met a good boy!
I miss Anthony...
Candy,
you have to handle your fate!
-Understand?
-That's right, Candy.
You came back to Pony's home,
a place where you lived
ever since you were a baby.
I'm sure you'll be able to
find your strength here.
That's right.
That's why I came back here.
Instead, I was just moping around...
Candy, do you know Jimmy?
Jimmy? That mischievous kid?
That's right. He came here
after his mother was sold off.
His mother?
I didn't know that...
Yes. He appears lively and brazen,
but I think that it's just his way
of bearing this situation.
It's his way of bearing this...
You're just moping around alone,
as if a saddest thing in the world!
I have to bear it too.
All children are waiting for your smile!
My smile?
I see, sister Pony, sister Lane.
Joe, you're bad, as always!
Milly,
what did you do with your pillow?
So troublesome.
John,
you didn't pee again, right?
He really stopped wetting his bed!
Clint, did you pee again...
Huh? Jimmy is gone.
Where did he go in this cold night?
It's Jimmy's hat.
He's so reckless, dropping it out here.
Jimmy?
Mom...
You looked strong. In reality...
Jimmy!
Mom...
I'd better leave him.
Jimmy, you're lonely, too?
It's already morning.
I'm gonna work hard from today!
Clint, when did you...
John!
Get up, John!
When did you get in here?
I'm sorry. I messed up my bed.
You wet your bed again?
you changed your pajama?
And you went into my bed like that!
Look, it's already dry!
That's not the problem,
you filthy runt!
I thought
you've stopped wetting your bed!
I did, but...
It doesn't seem so!
I was worried about you...
And so... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for making you worry...
Come here!
Clint!
Jimmy,
what are you doing to Clint?
I'm teaching it to follow me!
You bad.
Stop that! Jimmy.
Why were you doing that?
I was the boss around here!
You just came here
and you're already the boss?
What? You came after me!
I was here long before you came!
But... I went away for awhile...
Alright, I understand.
We need to decide who the boss is.
Naturally, I should be the boss!
You shouldn't !
What are you going to do about it?
Okay! Come here!
Listen up. Race to that tree!
Who gets there first is a boss!
-Fine with me!
-Okay, start!
It's Christmas' cracker...
Where did you take it?
Candy, hurry!
Tat's right.
I remember now,
just like when I was little.
Running to the hill
with one breath...
Sister Pony and Lane
were after me every day...
Candy, don't run like that,
you'll get hurt!
Oh, that girl!
Piece of cake!
Goin' ahead!
I'm here!
Well, Jimmy,
am I the boss?
What, after this?
I'm not feeling well today.
How about tree climbing!
Okay with that!
I'm much better than her,
she's totally fallen behind.
Whenever I climbed this tree,
I got scolded by teachers...
It was this branch!
Annie always worried
and watched from below!
Candy, look out!
Teachers will be mad!
It's okay!
Candy!
Candy, again?! Get down!
They found me!
How many times have I told you?
No dinner tonight.
-Get down!
-I'm sorry!
Candy, what are you doing?
You're going to lose to Jimmy!
Oh, no!
You can't catch up to me!
Just a little bit more.
Candy is all the way down there...
She's already here!
She's incredible!
Candy! You're incredible!
I'm there!
Here, take my hand.
I don't want your help!
You're so stubborn...
Jimmy, this tree is a father-tree!
-Father?
-That's right.
This tree will listen to
everything you say!
Jimmy, you already know that!
I don't know that.
You were crying here last night,
weren't you?
Candy, you saw me?
I came for the same reason,
then I saw you got here first.
Candy,
so you were crying here, as well?
But I forget it quickly!
One can't keep moping forever!
Jimmy, thanks to you,
I'm feeling better now.
Wonderful!
It's been a long time
since I felt something this good!
Sister Pony, sister Lane!!!
No!
-Get down, Candy!
-Slowly!
Just like the old time.
they will scold us again.
It's okay, they may be loud
but they never get mean!
You look just like me from the past!
We look away a bit and you...
Candy first thought of it!
Jimmy.
Boss.
Did he say " boss" ?
-It's snowing!
-Yes!
The flakes look like rose petals!
Everything is turning to white...
I... won't cry anymore.
I'll live strongly from now on.
The snow gently covered all sadness.
Christmas was just around the corner.