Candy took care of a granny
whom she met in the street.
This granny happened to be
the headmaster Merry Jane.
The headmaster
gave her the permission...
to enter the nursing school.
And then,
she started the life of nursing school.
Dim-wit of the hospital.
Good morning!
Mr. Smith, how do you feel today?
Candy,
I felt much better after you came here.
You 're doing a good job.
Thank you!
Mr. Fred.
Candy, My chest is not feeling well.
Don 't get up, you need rest.
I'll take you for a walk,
after you are getting better.
You are a good nurse.
I am not a nurse yet,
I am a student of nursing school.
No, you can handle everything already.
That's right,
you are the pride of this hospital.
We need your caring everyday.
So much praising... Troublesome!
Miss Candy.
Miss Candy, get up!
It is a dream.
Time is running out, hurry up!
It's my first day at the nursing school.
May the dream come true.
Miss Candy, what are you doing?
Coming.
So early for the class? Frannie.
To look after the patients.
The practice course.
Good morning!
Late for one minute.
I am sorry!
It is all my fault.
I 'm out of the condition.
You are...
The new classmate, Candice White.
Nice to meet you.
-Candy.
-Yes!
The disease won 't wait you
even for one minute.
Yes, I won 't do that again.
The true nurse is really different.
But, what is clinical thermometer?
Frannie...
What's the matter?
What is clinical thermometer?
Uh... I know nothing.
It's a tool,
measuring the patient's temperature.
I see! Thank you, Frannie.
Take temperature.
You,
take care of the patients over there.
Okay!
Open your mouth, please!
I am sorry!
How can I eat a thermometer?
No! It's up side down.
I am sorry!
I am a fool, I should be more careful.
Open your mouth.
Dim-wit!
Headmaster!
Is the patient alright?
-I think so.
-You think so?
Don't be stupid!
How can the nose take temperature?
I did it again.
What a dim-wit!
Miss Candice.
Miss Candice
Frannie,
please don 't call me miss Candice.
Just call me Candy!
Alright!
Would you please stop being foolish.
-I'll do that!
-And, Candy...
I have other patients to take care of.
I'll leave you here,
to collect the thermometers.
Yes!
Each patient's temperature,
must write it down right here.
Don't make mistake.
I know that!
All by myself.
It sounds like that
I'm a real nurse already!
She 's coming.
Back to the bed, quick!
Excuse me!
Collect the thermometers.
40 degrees.
40 degrees?
How about me?
42 degrees.
It's 40 degrees too.
Terrible!
Hurts!
Headmaster!
Why did you running at the corridor?
It's terrible!
All the patients had a high fever.
What?
It's normal.
This is normal too.
I saw that just now...
Your eyes might had problems.
Look! It's normal too.
I was confused, I felt no fever at all.
You told me that I'm 40 degrees...
I thought I was dying.
But, I'm sure...
If anything goes wrong,
take a pulse reading at once.
-Dim-wit!
-I am sorry!
They treat you as a fool.
A fool?
Yes! You are a fresh man here.
They want to give you a lesson.
A lesson?
Is Frannie here?
Frannie,
take care of the patient of Room 15.
Okay!
Candy, go with Frannie to practice.
Yes!
Pigeon!
I'd like to fly in the sky too.
You should defeat the illness
get yourself recovery.
You still can 't fly like pigeon,
even though.
Frannie,
why don 't we go to the brighter place.
-Candy!
-Yes!
You talk too much.
Frannie!
I know nothing, but...
Ignore the patient...
Not to talk to the patient...
Frannie,
Let me look after her, Please!
It's not a easy job
to take care of patients.
No problem.
-Be careful!
-Leave it to me.
Where are we going?
-That way.
-Good!
What's the direction this time?
I'll take you to anywhere
you like to go.
What's the matter?
Don 't you believe me?
Anywhere you like to go.
I'll do everything I can.
How about the hill over there?
We can overlook the city there.
Let's go!
I...
What's the matter?
It's hot!
The Pulse is jumping fast.
What should I do?
That girl...
I shouldn 't leave her to you.
But... I do nothing.
I also didn 't ask her to do anything.
I took care of her carefully.
What's wrong with you two?
How can we comfort the patients
while you were quarreling here.
Get lost!
-But...
-Get lost!
Yes!
She is a trouble maker.
Why did Frannie
leave the patient to a fresh man?
She 's a trouble alright.
She knew nothing
about taking care of patients.
How is the patient?
She is alright now.
That's great!
Both of you, go to the headmaster.
Yes!
Frannie, It's your fault.
She 's your patient,
how could you leave her to Candice?
I am sorry!
Candice.
How could you take care of a patient
whom you don 't understand.
That girl has heart problem.
A tiny shock might kill her.
What did I say about you?
Your mind is not clear enough.
The kindness is not the only thing
that patients need.
She is a special case.
She used to rely on others.
That's why we treat her coldness.
Suddenly, someone was cordial to her...
She would get back
to the situation of the past.
The shock...
It's complicated to look after patients.
-Do you understand?
-Yes!
I am very sorry!
I am sorry, Frannie.
Both of you can leave now!
Yes!
Frannie, your patients are hungry.
They are waiting for the meal.
It'll be there at once.
I am sorry, it is all my fault.
I'm so starving.
The lunch has not come yet. Lunch...
Hurry up!
Sorry, lunch is coming.
I'm coming.
Please!
Dim-wit! feed me, please.
-Stop joking.
-Terrible.
Don't learn from the elder.
I can 't eat by hand.
Alright! I'll feed you.
Put your hands down.
Hurts...
Be good!
Here!
Idiot! I am not a baby.
You can 't eat by yourself, can you?
I'll cool it for you.
Here!
I'll have the meal by myself.
I see! I know how to
deal with these patients now.
Candy,
you know how to deal with the patient.
I'll leave this room to you.
This child is horrible.
Leave it to me!
Good morning! Time for breakfast.
What's the matter?
I hate the food of this hospital.
That's why you are here.
You know nothing.
I don 't want it, take it back!
If I get soft, he will getting worse.
Eat!
What are you doing? Give it to me.
Do as I said, eat!
I am a fierce person.
Dim-wit!
I am sorry!
But, his attitude...
You should go back to the Pony's home.
I was wrong about you.
Do you really mean that? Headmaster.
Enough! Get out!
I'm so useless.
What are you doing here?
You should take care of that child
instead of crying here.
Yes!
Please forgive me.
I am a fresh man, knowing nothing.
Please forgive my impoliteness
But...
The food of hospital
can help you recovery quickly.
As lively as the healthy children.
It's cowboy.
I have a friend who 's about your age,
he wants to be a cowboy too.
He is not old enough, but
he is good at the noose.
How's Jimmy now?
Do you know the lasso trick?
I am good at that,
better than a really cowboy.
I'll teach you that after your recovery.
Get out! Quickly!
The food...
As lively as the healthy children.
You done that!
It's you again.
Thank you!
Teach me the noose.
Dim-wit!
Headmaster.
You have done it.
Dim-wit!
Don 't forget to teach me.
Headmaster!
Stop calling me that!
The patients will not trust me.
Sounds reasonable,
what happened to your cap?
Wrong direction.
Stop laughing! Go take a walk.
You should sleep now.
Have you taken the medicine after meal?
How's your pain?
Be an obedient baby.
The time
when I ran into her in the street.
She can 't even walk normally.
And now...
She looks after every patients
without the case history.
She's a real nurse...
a headmaster of nursing school,
a director of the hospital...
a good friend of sister Pony.
You can 't tell that from her appearance.
Are you dreaming there?
It's time for class.
No!
Don't forget the book.
Who swept this?
Stear, Archie, Annie, pattie.
How are you?
I'm now in Merry Jane nursing school.
I wish to become a nurse.
I found my own direction
through all kinds of things.
Candy!
Do me a favor, will you? It's dazzling.
I am sorry!
Stear, Archie, Annie, pattie.
I wish to become a nurse.
I know it's not easy,
but I will do my best!
Take care of yourselves, see you!
The light is turning off.
Terry, Mr. Albert.
I can 't write you a letter.
I will insist my own goal, don 't worry!
We will meet each other some day.
I will be a really nurse, then.
Candy recalls the memories of past.
But, she fall asleep quickly,
because the hard working of the daytime.