The channel is finished after
everyone's hard work.
Then,Candy will go back to
the Saint Johna's Hospital.
The tears of the cowboy
I will go back,don't follow me this time.
Don't be like this.
Thanks for Keli,I can go back to Boni's House.
A little left. Hurry.
Keli,it's Boni's House.
That's father's tree.
Come,Keli.
Come.
Enjoy yourself.
Mr. Boni.
En?
Candy.
What's wrong with Mr. Boni?
Mr. Boni.
Candy.
Mr. Rain.
Mr. Boni.
Candy.
I find you at last.
Now,I came back.
So you finised your job.
En.
It's so good to see you.
I heard it's very terrible there.
Welcome home,Candy.
I came back,sir.
You even carry the duck.
So as Mr. Rain.
Hurry,Candy.
Yes.
Where are the children?
Jim brought them out.
Come in.
He often take them out for playing.
Don't teach them the strange game.
Shoot,start.
Peng...
Attack.
Look,Candy,the children drew them.
They are very good.
I ask them to draw their dream.
Yeah.
Ah,nurse.
That's because of Candy.
That's because of Mr. Boni.
You all have your ideas.
It takes me a long time to decide to be a nurse
En,we all need a long time
to make the final decision.
Someone comes here.
That's Mr. Carrot.
I don't know what happened.
Mr. Carrot.
Candy.
Isn't it Candy?
I didn't see you for a long time.
I miss it.
You grow up,becomes a beauty.
You are healthy too.
I seem healthy.
What happened?
En,some...
What's wrong,Mr. Carrot?
About Jim,I want to discuss about it.
Jim?
Candy comes to hear too.
That's a problem.
Because Jim wanted to be a soldier.
Soldier?
But why?
Don't know when the solider will practice here.
Father,I want to be a soldier in the future.
Jim.
Then,he wants to be a soldier.
And he throw the job away.
Then,ask the boys around be play the game.
So he often take the boys out.
Jim will go to the European battle in the future.
I don't say you can't be a soldier.
What about my field.
Jim was adopted by the Carrot's.
Jim knows this.
I can understand Mr. Carrot.
We must talk to Jim.
Mr. Boni,Mr. Rain,Let me do it.
This...
Perhaps it's better for her to say it.
Jim will do as Candy says.
Ok,Candy. Please help me.
That's all right,Mr. Carrot.
Attack.
Stop,everyone.
Now,the game over today.
I will give you a good thing to see.
Raffle.
Yes,it should be used in the battle.
I have bullet too.
Wa.
I will shoot it now.
Can you?
Don't look down upon me.
Come,look at the tree.
Everyone,go back to the house.
Stay here,don't move.
Jim.
What's the sound?
The cows.
They rush to here now.
Kids,
it's too dangerous outside.
Kids.
Mr. Boni.
Candy.
You stay here.
Where are the children?
Gaomi,Ganma.
Mr. Boni.
Candy.
Go back to the house.
Kids...
They will be alright.
Dangerous.
Mr. Carrot.
Stop. Stop.
God.
Mr. Carrot.
Father,he,I made him...
Jim.
Candy,go to see Mr. Carrot first.
Yes.
I killed my father.
Mr. Carrot.
There's still pulse,he's alive.
He's still alive.
Save him.
Candy,what about Mr. Carrot.
He's ok,just faint.
That's good.
He fell to the carve.
Why is here a carve?
So,you mean then...
That's the trap.
It's just for fun.
Are you awake?
Thank god.
Mr. Boni.
Everyone's all right. That's good.
Candy.
Everyone did very good.
I will praise you today.
Yes.
We just hurt a bit. Don't worry about us.
Go to find back the cows.
I know.
Then I will leave my horse here.
Ok,that's alright.
Thank you,you're really good.
Father's still alive.
Father,he...
Jim,what's wrong with him?
After he went out,there's no news from him.
For he knew he did something bad?
He's a useless thing.
How can he be a soldier?
Yes,I want to be a soldier,I can't run away.
Ok,I will find back the cows.
Hey.
Jim,Stop.
No,he wants to catch the cows,he can't do it.
Mr. Carrot,I want to borrow a horse.
Go.
Jim,wait for me.
He went to the forest.
Ok,I will catch this cow for my fame.
Go.
That's good.
Jim.
Jim,leave.
Who will leave it.
Jim.
Is Jim ok?
Why do you interfere me?
You mean it's none of my business?
Yes.
I want to catch it to save my fame.
What do you say abou the fame?
Why do you still speak like a soldier.
I want to be a soldier.
Jim.
You made such a big trouble
you still wanted to be the soldier?
I make up my mind.
I want to be a soldier to fight in the battle.
If there's battle,there need soldier.
But,we also need cowboy.
And battle is not as easy as what you thought.
This,do you know what the battle like?
What's battle like?
I know it.
I saw many patient from the battle,so I know it.
And many are dead during the war.
And there are many nurse in the battle.
War is very terrible.
Only coward thought it's terrible.
I am not afraid of it at all
Look how I deal with the enemy.
Peng...
Jim,you idiot.
How dare you beat me
you are not my sister any more.
Jim.
What else do you want to say?
I don't want to show you at first
But now,I want to show you.
Follow me.
Why did this happen?
Jim,don't turn your head away. Look.
Look at this sad scene.
They are human too.
They all lost their important people.
Just like veryday life.
That's the war.
These cow,you brought them up,don't you?
Jim,that's ok,if you can understand it.
Sorry,father,sorry.
I will take over the field.
Jim,Jim.
Mr. Carrot,if he did anything wrong
please fix him.
Ah,that's a must.
Father.
Just father and son.
En.
Ah,the general of the enemy is crying.
Crying. Strange.
What,how dare you look down upon me,stop.
Boni's House.
Good bye.
Candy feels very happy while
she goes back to Chicargo.