Terry is in New york,
Taking part in the audition
for Romeo and Juliet.
Candy is in Chicago,
Sitting for
the nurse qualification test.
The day we fly towards the sky.
Good morning.
You look spirited today.
Don't let Candy pass the test.
God, please don't let her pass.
Please.
Candy.
Why do you want me
to fail the test?
Because...
Honestly speaking,
You are going to be an
official nurse once you passed the test.
Who will take care of us?
Don't worry.
Even if I am an official nurse
I am still be Candy.
Will you play with us
just like before?
Sure.
We shall pray again then.
We hope Candy can pass her test,
please.
I didn't really show it
but actually I am a little worried.
I just hope I can pass the test.
How is Terry going?
The result is out.
Who is it?
Romeo is going to be Terry.
Expected.
We knew it.
Terry,
Yes? Suzanna.
Why didn't you knock?
Terry, the result is out.
Congratulations, I am so happy.
Do I get to play Romeo?
You are playing Romeo,
I am playing Juliet, that's great.
I will quit if someone else
got to paly Romeo.
Terry wait.
Romeo,
Terrius. G Glanchester.
It's me indeed.
I did it.
Terry Baker,
congratulations.
You are the main man.
Sorry?
Could you repeat my name again.
My name is not Terry Baker.
Say that again.
You don't have to hide it?
Everybody knows that you are
Eleanor Baker's love child.
So?
We envy you.
Yes, you have a good mother.
Wait,
what has it to do with my mother?
-Terry.
-What exactly are you talking about?
Terry, no violence.
Eleanor was here
during the audition
What?
Terry.
Hey...
Terry has the ability.
There is no lobbying.
Stop being sarcastic.
That's really despicable.
If you guys can't accept it,
why don't you try to
prove yourselves capable.
You all owe Terry an apology.
I never seen Suzanna such angry.
Yeah,
she is really serious about Terry.
Captain,
I have something to ask you.
Right, I was looking for you.
You saw the list.
This is major, you can do it.
I actually doubt about this.
Why is that?
Did I win the audition
with my ability?
What do you mean?
Is anyone behind this?
Eleanor?
I heard she was here
during the audition.
You have underestimated me.
There is no such thing
as lobbying in this business.
It all depends on ability.
No talents no talk.
It's different from
the outside world.
The crew and I
picked the performers.
Do you doubt yourself?
I am sorry,
I was just being paranoid.
From now on, there are going to be more
and more slandering rumours about you.
Every performers
can't escape from that.
Eleanor Baker,
I will challenge you.
I can't change the fact that
you are my mother.
But, I will overtake you.
And become a great actor.
Candy, I would like to invite you
to come to Broadway...
And enjoy my performance
as Romeo.
This is my first step
in the showbiz.
Congratulations, Terry.
I am glad you did it.
It must be really cool
for Terry to play Romeo.
Romeo and Juliet.
Obstacles seperated them apart.
There is nothing between me and Terry
that baffles our love.
Suzanna?
I trust Terry.
Candy.
Candy, the results
are going to be announced.
Is it time?
You look relax.
I am so nervous.
It's shameful to fail the test.
That's no big deal?
You should be more relax.
I need to pass the test
in order to take care of Mr.Albert.
You are just an amateur.
Violations of the hospital rules
are not allowed.
Amateur?
Candy, since you insist.
I hope you can pass the
nurse qualification test this month.
Once you became a real nurse
You would be in charge of
ward number zero.
The results are ready
to be published.
I am so nervous.
It's coming, here it comes.
I did it.
Yes, Elly passes as well.
I saw my name.
-Where is it?
-Right there.
That's excellent,
third in the test.
How about Candy?
I...
Are you on the list?
It's getting blur.
I can't really see.
Come on, Cady.
Candice White.
Yes.
Look, the seventh.
Candice White.
We all passed the test.
Great.
Now we proved ourselves.
Congratulations.
Headmaster Merry Jane.
All of you did a good job,
congratulations.
Thank you.
Now we will award
the nurse certificate.
Natalie Bees.
Candice White.
I am a real nurse now.
Candy,
Can you be a real nurse?
Next, Judy Max.
Elly Lesman.
How is it? Must be delighted.
Yes.
Candy, I thought you were excited
about this?
You don't look like you normally do.
No.
Blanny didn't get to sit for the test
because she went to the front line.
Blanny is a humble girl.
She didn't write to tell you all.
She sat for the test
at the front line.
She is already an official nurse.
Yeah? That's great.
All trainees in Merry Jane Nurse School
have passed the test.
I feel so honored.
The real challenge starts from now.
You all have to continue to work hard
and be a outstanding nurse.
Dismiss.
Candy stays.
Yes.
Sorry, What is it about...
You are a dim wit,
Things about ward number zero
has been bothering doctor Reknap.
Yes.
He compalined to me about you.
I wouldn't want to face any student
from your school.
But, you did a good job.
You are the seventh in this test,
And second in this school,
just right after Natalie.
Pony must be happy
Headmaster should be the happiest.
What doctor Reknapp
has promised you,
I think you are determined to do it,
right?
Yes.
I will to leave you here.
Natalie will go back with me.
You must do everyting seriously.
Yes.
I can look after Mr.Albert now.
Caring is the best cure
for reviving memory.
Take good care of him.
Yes,
please forgive my insistence.
I will write to sister Pony.
What a weak nurse?
Pull yourself together.
Don't take things for granted.
Yes.
Great.
I can take care of Mr.Albert now.
Mr.Albert.
Mr.Albert look,
I passed the test.
Look.
Congratulations Candy.
Poopet,
Are you happy for me as well?
Thank you.
I wanted to give you a present,
But I have nothing.
That's alright.
From now on
I can look after Mr.Albert with care.
I am contented with that.
Candy, you...
Move,
Do you smell Candy?
Help.
Candy is a real nurse now.
Yeah, this is her picture
with her uniform.
Let me see.
No, give me back, one by one.
Give me back.
Good morning
Mr.Albert, Poopet.
Good morning, Candy.
Stear is going to celebertae for me.
May I go?
You are off today.
Don't worry about me,
go ahead.
I will be back as soon as possible.
Candy,
Nothing, thank you.
Good bye.
Candy, we have been waiting.
-Stear.
-Candy.
Annie, Pattie.
Candy.
It's been a long time.
Candy is still full of energy.
Candy, coongratulations for
passing the test.
Thank you, Annie.
Mr.albert will be alright
with Candy taking care of him.
I am worried about his health,
I can't stay too long.
It won't take too long,
let1s go.
Archie,
where is Grand Aunt Elroy?
She went out with Elisa.
I asked Pattie and Annie
to come here.
Candy,
you happened to be off today.
candy, yesterday I...
Archie,
What do you mean? Archie.
Nothing, righ? Archie.
Candy, yesterday I...
I asked everyone to come here
to give you a big present.
To invite you to board the plane.
Brother built it himself.
I am leaving.
Candy.
This is once in a lifetime chance.
I am honored,
but Pattie deserves it.
Pattie, the chance is yours.
He said I was too heavy.
We gave it up,
right? Annie.
How come?
Candy, let's go.
But Stear...
Airplane is differnt from car,
it's too dangerous.
Look, the king of the sky.
How is it?
You must be loving it.
The name sounds alright.
It's going to crash.
Come, get dressed.
And the pants.
All done.
Turn aorund.
Looks alright.
Stear...
Get on the plane,
we are ready for take off.
Is it alright?
I don't know, it's brother's invention.
Stear!
Sit tight, we are moving.
See you later, let's go.
The king of the sky! Go!
Candy,
hold on to the parachute.
It's alright, Candy.
Tree!
Not good!
Hit it!
They are through.
Candy, open your eyes.
-We are flying!
-Of course.
That's The Adley's,
how magnificent.
So beautiful.
This is cool, they are flying.
Yeah.
Nothing.
Stear, lets get lower ok?
They are just down there.
Sure, it was good yeah.
It didn't feel so good when
I think of other countries having wars.
Candy.
Help!
Run!
Jump!
I knew it.
Candy.
In the end
it's brother's invention.
Candy, brother,
are you alright?
-Candy.
-Stear.
Candy, that was funny,
right?
That was the
first successful test-fly.
First time?
Yeah, the first time
to take someone on.
-Stear
-Candy...
Stear has put in a lot of effort.
Candy, don't you think
this parachute looks strange?
Yes.
Candy jumped off
with the parachute,
In such a cool way.
I am so happy to
receive so many presents.
I want to tell Mr.Albert about it.
Maybe that will cheer him up.
Mr.Albert.
Mr.Albert, I am back.
Not here, where did he go?
Thank you, Candy,
I will never forget about you.
Albert with no name.
Mr.Albert.
Mr.Albert lost his memory
due to injury.
Where exactly did he go?
Candy's heart is filled with
a sudden emptiness.