Night fog at Southampton port.
After parting from Mr. Carson' s
Candy went to the Southampton.
In order to help Candy...
Mr. Carson gave her a letter to
his friend, who runs a shipping company.
Clint, this is Southampton port.
Terry departured to America from here.
Let' s find Mr. Carson' s friend
and his shipping company.
Juskin?
Let' s see, do I know this guy?
You know him?
Never heard of him.
I was told that I' d find him
as soon as I ask around Southampton.
There' s a big company that way.
Ask around there.
-You should do that.
-Thank you.
I don't think that
Mr. Carson meant to fool me.
Thief.
Thief?.
Hey! Show some respect.
That' s my trunk.
I' m working here as a luggage carrier.
Working?
I' m sorry, I have no money to pay you.
Cheapskate.
Hey! you...
I already told you that I' m broke.
I got your trunk
you don't get to be stingy anymore.
I' ll carry it.
Wait! I' m not going anywhere.
Don't tell me you' re some bum?
I' m looking for Mr. Juskin.
But, I can't find him...
Juskin?
You know him?
I saw it on a billboard somewhere...
Please, remember.
Juskin...
-You remember?
-Yes.
It' s in such a desolate place?
I' m sure it was around here.
There it is.
Juskin.
Anyhow, it looks like
a horrible company.
Yes...
A customer. See you then.
But I need to thank you...
I got that customer because of you!
Bye!
Thank you!
Maybe this company went broke?
Mr. Juskin, when will we get paid?
Really!
You ain't paying us enough!
Isn't there a way out of this?
If it' s come down to this, we' ll have to
sell our children to foreign country.
Of course! We might even
earn something from them.
You gotta be kidding me.
Ouch!
Who is that?
Uh! I... got the wrong way...
Who is that girl?
You got a nice office there.
Here.
Huh? A letter for me?
No! That' s...
Carson? Who is Carson...
Uh! I' m sure this is a mistake.
I' ll be on my way now.
Hold on! Girl!
Hey! hold on.
I remember now.
I borrowed money from that
weirdo Carson.
Is he doing well?
Yes!
Hey, girl, come to my office.
Welcome, Miss.
So, Carson is still the same.
That' s right.
No, I mean...
By the way, Miss. Is it true
that you want to go to America?
Yes!
To America?
But I don't want to be sold.
Sold?
You were eavesdropping on us
a little while ago?
eavesdropping?
You spoke so loude and I head that.
I' m leaving.
We' re kidding, Right?
Conversation becomes lighter
when we do that.
Yes, just a joke.
Do we look like we' re up to
something that bad?
Here! Take a good look into my eyes.
Miss, you wanna go to America?
-Yes!
-Leave it to me.
We' ll think of something.
But it won't be easy.
How much money do you have?
I don't have any.
What do you mean?
You want to travel to America
without a penny.
Mr. Carson said that
you' d be able to do something.
Since you' re managing a big company.
This is bad.
Mr. Juskin,
another drunken hillbilly friends?
I happened upon that Carson
in town' s bar last year.
But, you really have a
shippping company.
I did that for some time, yes.
Seagull.
Mr. Juskin, seagull' s coming.
We finally have a job.
Finally, a job after such a long time.
We don't get to do this too often.
-Everything okay there?
-Yeah!
Mr. Juskin, is this your boat?
Yeah! You got that right.
It' s a piece of junk.
How can she going to America.
Alright! release brakes.
I really thought that
I' d get to travel to America.
That' s...
It' s Terry.
Terry! It' s Terry playing the melody.
He must have stayed in the port.
Terry.
It was you.
Hello, homeless girl.
Please show me the harmonica.
Hey! what are you doing?
It' s not Terry' s.
Terry? You know Terry?
You know him?
I do. He bought this for me.
Terry.
The world is so small.
Say, won't you tell me about him?
It was a foggy night, just like tonight...
I couldn't find a job.
Wandering around the street.
Fresh fried...
Watch where you' re going.
It' s my fault though...
I can manage!
Boy. Is there a cheap hotel around?
What! You' re looking for a hotel?
Anything around Southampton,
just leave it to Cookie.
Follow me.
That' s great. I' m so full.
Cookie, was it?
Candy will be surprised
when she hears about you.
Who is this Candy?
Telling Candy about Cookie...
That' s a nice melody.
Say, would you let me play it a bit?
I can't give you this.
-Just for a minute...
-No!
I' ll go back then.
The dinner was good. Thank you.
Cookie.
Do you have a place to stay?
There' s no place to stay, but...
I can sleep in a warehouse
around the port.
If you want to, you can stay here.
And tomorrow
I' ll buy you a new harmonica.
I' ll teach you how to play
before I leave.
Bro.
He bought you this harmonica?
This one is much better.
His harmonica
was smaller and somewhat old.
Terry.
I farewelled Terry
by playing this harmonica.
But it sounded so sad.
I've seen many people
part from each other in that port.
He looks like leaving from someone
very dear to him.
I think her name was Candy.
So Terry wasn't lonely when he left.
Wasn't he?
Don't tell me you' re...
Candy.
What, you were there?
Mr. Juskin is worried about you.
I need to go now.
So that' s how it was.
Looks great.
-Now, Candy, eat up.
-Thank you.
It' s the littlest I could do for you.
We aren't unemployed anymore.
You must be hungry.
But, what about you?
Don't worry,
we' re fine just with our drinks.
And you, Candy.
You' re like a goddess.
Goddess?
Our business has been doing very well
since you came to visit us.
And tomorrow, we' re doing
our biggest shipping order ever.
We secured a permanent job.
We' re out of poor.
Really, a shipping order to America.
Mr. Juskin.
Don't scare me.
I' m sorry.
Tomorrow morning you' ll shipping
a big cargo load to America?
That' s right.
Please, put me in the cargo.
Gotcha...
What? you' d be a stowaway then.
That' s unreasonable.
You' ll be caught.
I want to travel to America
as soon as possible.
Mr. Juskin.
If they discover her
our business will be ruined.
I won't cause any trouble.
I' m begging you.
Cargo holds on freighters
are cramped and dark.
Anyhow, it' s just like in a tiny box.
I don't care.
Sneak into a freighter
heading to America.
You' ll be trouble in pain.
I can take it.
No food, no water.
You' ll be trapped in a hot dark box.
Don't do that.
Do you have any idea what will those
sailors do to you if they find you?
I don't care.
Alright! You depart tomorrow at dawn.
Thank you.
That' s great! Clint.
Have a drink.
A week has passed
since I left St. Paul academy.
As I wrote this.
I' m at the port in Southampton.
Finally, I' ll be departing to America
tomorrow at dawn.
Stear, Archie...
excuse my selfishness for leaving you
with nothing but this letter.
Annie, Patty...
I realized that living a life
where others provide isn't right.
Two men made me realize this fact.
One of them is working in Africa
right now.
The other one ventured on a journey
leaving everything behind.
I am leaving as well,
to find my own path.
Please understand my feeling....
You' re still awake?
Yes, I' m almost done my writing.
Tonight is the last time
you can sleep in a normal bed.
Yes.
Candy.
I' ll be praying for you.
Thank you, Mr. Juskin.
Well, don't catch a cold. Good night.
Good night.
Both Mr. Carson and Mr. Juskin
they' re good people.
I' ll do my best from now on.
Sorry if I saddened you.
Idiot! You should pretend like
you don't know anything.
Hurry! You' re running late.
Alright! Untied the ropes.
Candy, we' re finally parting.
Candy, don't let them find you.
Be careful.
Lift it!
Take care and don't forget to pray.
Lift.
-Winch ok.
-Winch going.
What' s this?
Hey! It' s said
Do not turn upside-down.
Okay! Let' s turn it back.
Hey! Don't turn over that crate.
He' s fussing over cargo.
-That' s it.
-How do we carry it then?
-Let' s use this.
-Okay.
You heard something?
Come to think of it
It' s like a cry of some animal.
Aren't you two done yet?
Hurry and put it in the cargo bay.
Alright! This is the last one.
Moving away.
Candy! Stay well.
Candy managed to sneak aboard the
freighter ship heading to America.
Will she be able to reach America
without anyone finds her?
Leaving the shore, the ship ventured
into the endless, peaceful ocean.