Appearing unexpectedly, almost like a
magician, Patricia's grandmother...
managed to tightly bind Candy's
and Patricia's hearts together.
Now that grandmother Marhsa is gone,
the dorm suddenly feels lonely.
Life has returned to normal.
The inverted envelope.
-I'm done!
-Candice!
I can't get up before
everybody is done eating...
She doesn't know anything!
As expected from a barn dogsbody!
Why are they eating like that?
Maybe the food is no good?
What a waste, she left so much!
-Just take a look at that.
-She would've choked on it.
Everyone, you're done, aren't you?
Let's thank God for this meal.
Now I'll hand out the mail you received.
-Patricia O'Brien!
-Yes!
-Eliza Leagan!
Wow, so many!
It'll be a lot of work answering
all of these!
That's great!
Archibald Cornwell!
This letter should've been delivered
to boys' ward.
Teacher, can I go and deliver it then?
No, I'll deliver it later on.
Candice White Ardley.
For me?
It's from America!
It's from sister Pony!
It even smells like American land!
Candice!
I have to read it right now!
-Candice, you mustn't run!
-Oops.
Candy, I'm sure you'll begin enjoying
your days in London...
as soon as you get used
to the new kind of life.
Sister Lane and I are spending our
days looking after children.
Speaking of kids...
now that the spring had come
so many animals have been born.
All at once, we got six chicks and
seven piglets.
Everyone was thrilled!
That's so cute!
Eliza?
Why, this is a weird envelope.
What are you doing? Give it back!
Hey, there is something written
on the inside of the envelope.
Really, that's a weird envelope!
I said, give it back!
Receiving a letter in an inverted
old envelope...
Exactly what I'd expect from you
Candy.
You've been using this ever since
you transferred?
Pony's home is so poor!
Eliza!
What a violent person!
Why would reusing an old evnelope
be so bad?
That's enough!
Where do you think you are?
Teacher, Candy was violent!
I saw it.
-Did she hurt you, Eliza?
-Nah...
Teacher, I don't want to live with
such a volatile person!
That's right. She's a bad person.
Taking and reading other people's mail
and then using it for a prank
is much worse!
That's not what a lady would've done!
Teacher...
All of you, return to your rooms!
Candy!
Thanks!
That's horrible! Candy even turned
a teacher into her ally!
Do you think I'll leave it like this?
What will you do, Eliza?
Tomorrow, after the morning prayer...
Candy?
It's Eliza.
Maybe she's discussing a new prank
with her brother.
-I'm afraid.
-It's okay!
Pretend you didn't see them.
Hey, Candy!
I want to talk to you.
-Candy!
-It's okay! Go ahead, Patty.
Now, let's go, Patty.
Let go of my arm!
I can walk on my own.
What did you want to talk about, Neil?
Long time no see.
I really didn't think I'd find
you here in London.
Really! I'm pretty disappointed though!
You're still trailing along with
your sister. Even to this place!
What was that?
Neil, you're still a wimpy show-off
even here in London.
Damn...!
Hey!
I had a hunch that something was up!
You still haven't changed your
habit of crying for help!
You've got some nerve!
I think your clothes are turned
inside-out, Candy!
You like it when things are
inside-out, don't you?
I'll check it out!
That girl!
What are you doing?
Stand still!
Ow! What are you doing?
She's built up some muscle
from working the stables!
Let go of me!
We want to see you cry!
We'll let you go if you cry!
Let go of me!
Cry! Now!
This school is not for your kind!
But it's okay for my kind?
Right, boy?
Terry!
I think I heard you saying
"you're free to stay" .
Well then?
Please do...
I see.
You said it because I'm the oldest son
of an eminent English nobleman.
Yes...
Are rich people really so admirable?
So three rich Americans are
messing around a single girl?
Of course.
In that case, I'll teach you everything
about kind ways of English aristocracy!
Get out of here!
I'll remember this!
Wait!
Can I help you?
Thank you...I...
You don't need to thank me.
Besides, I wasn't trying to protect you.
I loathe their kind.
That's pretty much it.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Want to confess your love
Lady freckles?
He remembers what happened on the ship.
He remembers... and yet, he's been
ignoring me the whole time!
I know of an ideal place
for love confessions!
Want to come?
Who'd want to say that?
Thank goodness. I'm sorry, but...
I'm not interested in freckled girls.
Well then, excuse me.
What's up with that, I just wanted to
express my sincere gratitude to him!
And my name isn't Lady freckles!
It's Candice White Ardley!
I have too much to write about,
the letter won't turn out okay...
Terry!
Who'd write about that guy, anyway?
He's a whimsical snob.. I hate him!
Yes, come in!
Patty!
Uh, after the prayer...
a guy with glasses approached me
with this...
It's Stear, right?
Thank you!
I wonder what it's about.
What is this?
Take a look, Patty.
No...!
Reading other people's letters...
It's not a letter...
It's a code of some kind.
In that case, excuse me...
It's Morse code!
This is what they use in telegraphy?
Yes.
It's Stear!
I see, he's signalling me with lights...
This was... E...
Uh, Patty, what is he saying?
Chi...o..ko...re...to...ari...
They have chocolate?
Ku...ri...n...mo...
Kurin is with them, too?
o...i...de...ko...u...
They're telling me to come over?
Alright!
Say, Patty, won't you come along?
Where to?
Of course, to boys' ward!
God won't forgive us if we do that!
It's so late
God already went to bed!
What are you going to do?
Patty, it might be too difficult for you.
I'll bring you some chocolate however!
Ca... Candy!
I'm off!
Candy, is that you?
Good evening, Archie!
Take care, Candy!
Don't worry! I'm used to high places!
Are you okay?
I'm okay, Kurin.
I haven't climbed a tree in a long time
I must've gotten rusty...
Now, hurry inside!
We'll get in trouble
if they find you here.
Kurin, long time no see...
-I wanted to see you!
-Welcome, Candy!
Where are you, Stear?
I'm here... up here.
Stear!
Candy, my new invention
spider shoes.
Incredible, what an invention!
Well there you have my brother...
I can't look at this anymore...
I can walk on the ceiling...
Even Edison didn't think of this!
Can I borrow them sometime?
Okay... Now if I do this, uh...
The problem is that they're
pretty unreliable.
I'll improve them by the next time...
I can't wait to see them!
Would you like some tea?
Allow me!
Say, who is in the next room?
One nasty dude.
It's the guy who made an incident
during the prayer.
Terry?
That's right, Grandchester Terrius!
One day, he and Archie almost
had a fight in the main hall.
Archie?
See, I missed the room.
Oh, hello.
Excuse me...
Don't come near my room.
Why did you just punch me?
I apologized, haven't I?
Wait! You hurt my face!
Wait!
Stop, Archie. He's always like that.
We have no idea
what's he thinking about.
I'll challenge him next time!
So that's what happened...
Here, Kurin.
Anyway, I don't like him.
Me, too!
Candy, something happened to you?
Huh? A little...
Come to think of it...
what happened to the letter for Archie
that was delivered to our ward?
Huh... it's here.
-Was it this letter?
-That's the one!
You haven't read it yet, Archie?
That's right. This Archie guy
he's totally freaking over it.
Give it, brother!
If you really don't want to read this
letter...
why don't you dump it then?
That's fine with me!
He can't do that!
Say, who wrote it to him?
To beloved mr. Archie...
...from Annie Brighton.
Stop that!
Annie...?
Yes! She writes to him every week!
Really?
Annie is... she is sending letters
to Archie every week.
Archie
why won't you read Annie's letter?
I don't want to read it.
Anyway, it seems as if Annie
wants to transfer to this school.
Annie wants to...
Open the door.
It's the teacher patrol!
What'll I do...
Hurry, to the next room!
-Archibald Cornwell.
-Yes!
-Alistear Cornwell.
Lights-off time has passed already.
Just what were you doing in here?
We noticed that the moon in London
is different from America.
We're discussing how it's possible
from a a scientific point of view...
The moon in America...
One... two... three.
Uh, I was drinking two cups...
Take a look in the neighboring room.
Candy...!
Candy isn't the kind of girl
who just hides quietly.
Kurin, if Annie really comes...
That's right.
We won't be able to be
too personal with her.
Annie wouldn't like people know that
we were live together in Pony's home.
I would've better keep the secrect
about our past in Pony's home.
My life in Pony's home gave Eliza
and others a reason to ridicule me.
That inverted envelope is one of those
things, too.
It seems that I'll learn how Annie felt
when she had to hide our friendship.
Oh, no! Patty is still waiting for me!
Kurin, I'm going back to my room.
Good night.
I'm so sorry, Patty!
A teacher patrol suddenly barged in,
I couldn't pick up the chocolate...
No, I waited here because
I have to apologize to you.
What do you want to apologize for?
I made a stupid mistake.
A mistake?
That letter...
I saw it in that inverted envelope...
and I...
What, I don't care if you read it!
There aren't any secrets or
nasty stuff in that letter!
It made me cry!
I was so jealous of you!
Of me?
Whenever I read a letter,
I try to imagine the sender
as the letter was being written.
-At the moment of writing?
-Yes!
Carefully taking apart
an used envelope...
flipping it inside-out into a new letter
while sending you a piece of her heart.
I was envisioning that person.
That's what sister Pony does
after all the children fall asleep.
I'm so happy that you got such a letter!
Thank you, Patty!
I was stupid!
Up until a moment ago,
I hated this overturned envelope!
If you did that
God would have punished you!
I knew you'd understand, Patty!
I'm not the only one!
Sister Margaret understood, too!
That's why she punished Eliza!
If you truly have a heart...
you'll understand the hearts of others!
Patty!
The one bearing a heart
can understand the hearts of others.
That's exactly what Candy thought.
However, there was one heart
that Candy could not understand.
It was Terry's heart.
Behind his violent exterior, just what
kind of person was Terry?
No matter how much she thought
he remained a mystery.