The audience were talking about it.
Candy finally knew the truth
about Suzanna's accident.
Candy was no longer in the mood
to watch the show.
And she was heading to the hospital
to visit Suzanna.
The seperation on a snowy day.
Uncle, go to the Royal Hotel first
and then to Jacob Hospital.
Suzanna was injured
because of him.
I heard Terry was going to marry her.
That's so mean.
No matter how much she loves Terry,
she souldn't have done this.
This is not love.
Suzanna.
I want to see her.
Terry kept the secret from me.
He must been struggling.
Terry, forgive me
to leave in the middle of the show.
But, I am not in the mood anymore.
If a sweet dream could be deceived,
I would rather believe it.
A sweet dream is going to visit today.
Our love will finally get approved.
Today, I will not be worried
and afraid anymore.
Bravely take this step.
The final scene is about to end.
Suzanna, take some rest.
I wonder how Terry did in the show.
Don't worry, rest well.
If Terry comes,
I will let you know.
Mother, did you force him
to come again?
No, I didn't.
Terry wanted to come himself.
You are lying.
I know it. You must have forced
Terry to come to see me.
What for?
I am already happy that
he was willing to come.
Suzanna, take some rest.
The audience must love Terry.
Of course.
-Mother.
-What?
I want to eat strawberries.
Now...
I'll see if I can find some.
You have some sleep.
Mother
What?
Forgive me to be so self-centered.
It's ok.
Terry's struggle,
Suzanna must know it clearly.
Come! The pathetic initiator.
Come! The notorious ruler.
The desperate eyes,
are as short-visioned as
those of the seasick men.
Going to stranded on the beach.
For the person I love.
I hope this poison really works.
I will be gone with you,
after I touch your lips.
Thank you.
Excuse me,
where is Suzanna Malue's room?
Room 15 on the second floor.
Thank you.
Calm down, Candy.
Miss Suzanna.
Did you fall asleep?
Sorry to bother you.
The wheelchair...
Suzanna's injury...
Suzanna
I bring back the strawberries.
Where is Susana?
When I came...
She wanted me to buy
some strawberries.
Suzanna
Don't look for me, let me die.
Doctor
I am sorry, Mother.
Terry already has someone he loves.
Forgive my stupidity.
Wish Mother a fulfilled life.
Suzanna.
Suzanna
Miss Suzanna
Miss Juliet
Somebody is coming.
Please wake up.
I am willing to.
My chest is your sheath.
I am so happy that
I can lie beside you.
Suzanna
Don't worry,
we will find Miss Suzanna.
Suzanna
-Did you find her?
-Not yet.
Could it be possible
she went to see Terry?
Ok, you go to the theatre.
Others check around the hospital.
The chilly wind
is blowing from the roof.
Suzanna
Suzanna, where are you?
Suzanna, don't do stupid things.
Suzanna, your legs...
Let me go.
Please, let me die.
Suzanna, you...
Candy
Suzanna's legs...
Now you understand, Candy?
Let go,
pretend you didn't see me.
Susana
My being alive will only
make Terry suffer more.
You will never be happy.
-Susana
-Let me die.
For Terry, I must die.
I can't let you do foolish things.
If you suffer,
Terry will suffer, too.
Let me go, Candy.
I will only get between you.
Let me go.
Stay alive, Suzanna.
Stay alive.
Suzanna is deeply in love
with Terry.
She was injured because of Terry.
It was not easy for her
to be able to play the role Juliet.
She became disabled for Terry.
She loves Terry.
Found her!
Suzanna
Suzanna,
why did you do such a stupid thing?
It's wonderful.
Doctor, Suzanna...
Suzanna
Please do not worry.
Is Suzanna alright?
Candy
Terry, hold her to the room.
Terry, your play...
Is over.
Hurry back to the room.
Candy saved me.
My arms are so heavy.
I can't go back.
Suzanna's love for Terry
is the same with mine.
This three people relationship
is not resolvable.
If it continues,
it will only make Terry suffer more.
If I don't make a decision.
Terry...
Candy,
Suzanna wants to see you.
She does? Just the right time.
I should leave.
Leave?
I'll take the train back tonight.
Back? Tonight?
We already met.
The vacation is over.
I am very worried about
Mr.Albert.
Candy
Treat Suzanna well.
If it had been me,
I would not have saved you.
Candy
Suzanna
You are beautiful and gentle.
Willing to sacrifice for Terry.
I came to say good-bye.
I am going to take the train back
tonight.
Candy, I...
Don't say anything, Suzanna.
Live well.
Terry will be beside you.
Hope you will get well soon.
Candy, I know the person
he loves is you.
But, I...
Don't say it, Suzanna.
No, let me finish!
I don't want to get between you,
but...
Whenever I see Terry,
I feel like living again.
It doesn't matter
I go back to the stage or not.
I just want to be with him.
Then let it be, Suzanna.
As long as you are happy.
Candy, I am sorry.
Don't say sorry, Suzanna.
It's not your fault.
Get well soon.
This is the only thing
Terry and I expect for.
Good-bye, Suzanna.
Candy
Never let Terry go.
Bye!
-Let me see you away.
-No, thanks.
Let me see you away.
No, thanks.
I'll see you away.
Why make it harder?
Terry a stupid guy,
don't come.
Candy
Don't leave me.
Let the time stops here.
Terry
Don't say anything,
just let me hold you.
Terry cried.
My favorate Terry, my lover.
We are going to break up.
You have to be happy, Candy.
Or I'll never forgive you.
Terry, too.
Candy left me again.
Terry, you can still change your mind.
Get her back, it's ok.
Don't make yourself suffer more,
for me.
Suzanna
The person I chose was you.
Terry
It's right, the person I chose was
Suzanna Marlu.
Freckled lady,
freckled woman Tarzan.
The days of St. Paul Academy.
The lost youth.
Time can't go back.
All the smiles, all the shines.
Candy
I'd rather not seeing you
if I knew this was gonna happen.
What are you talking about?
Terry.
I am thankful that I could see you.
It's so cold.
The train is tonight.
Let me go back to the hotel first.
Stear
The musicbox of happiness.
Candy, this melody
will help you reach happiness.
You have to be happy!
Terry, good-bye.
Really good-bye.
This is enough.
Candy keeps telling herself that
in her mind.
Thus...
She opened Stear's
musicbox of happiness.
And left her footprints
on snowy Broadway.