Grandfather William claimed
Candy as his foster daughter
Grandfather William's
decision is final
Aunt Elroy had no reason to reject Candy
as a daughter of the Adley family.
Happy like in a dream.
Candy, this is your room!
Here you go!
This is my room?
Candy
all of these things are yours
Really?
Am I really going to live in here
from today?
Anthony, this bed is so soft!
And the sofa is pretty!
Candy
this cushion is soft as well!
It's so cute!
It's wonderful, Anthony
Candy, everybody is so glad
that you made it back
I'm glad, as well.
Kurin, you're our friend now!
Come in!
Kurin! No
This is great, Kurin!
I'm so happy!
This smile suits you best.
You'll be happy from now on
Happiest in the world
Candy, you must be tired.
Get a good rest!
That's right!
We'll excuse ourselves!
Thank you
Anthony, Stear, Archie.
Sleep well, Candy!
What?
Okay, we're outta here!
Sweet dreams, Candy!
You were on your way out!
Good night, Stear
-What?
-Thank you so much, Stear!
No... good night!
Out!
I'm a daughter of the Adleys
It's almost as if I were dreaming
If sister Pony and sister Lane
knew it
I can't imagine how happy
they would be
Yes, and Mr. Albert, too!
I wonder what happened to
that gentle man who liked animals
Maybe he is still living somewhere
with his animals
The day I got the pendant
from the Prince on the hill
Sister Pony, sister Lane
and Mr. Albert.
Archie, Stear, Anthony...
and grandfather William
whom I haven't yet met
Thank you... everyone
Because of grandfather William's letter
in which he claimed me as his daughter
my destiny finally seems to be
looking up
I never knew that one little bit of
paper could bring me this much happiness
If this is a dream
I never want to wake up.
Never
Birds are crying...
This is...
That's it!
This is Adley's house!
It's not a dream!
I'm a daughter of the Adleys!
Good morning, Kurin!
A wonderful breeze!
The roses are swaying
in the breeze.
Roses which Anthony grew...
Good morning!
You're...
Dorothy, it's you!
Candy, I'm so glad!
Dorothy
how come you are you here?
They have allowed me
to take care of you personally!
Dorothy
You don't have to
speak so formally to me!
I did my best!
Oh my!
But I'm glad for you!
I was ordered by Aunt Elroy,
to take care of the new mistress.
until a replacement servant is found
And it was you?
That's right!
Now that Candy is gone
we have an excess of servants!
I understand, madam!
And that's how it was!
I'm so glad that you made it here!
You're a princess from today!
Congratulations, Candy.
Thank you, Dorothy.
Well then, miss,
it's time to get dressed!
Oh, I forgot about that!
Choose just about any
dress you like!
They are all incredible!
When did...
I brought them here
the night before
It was Aunt Elroy's idea.
Aunt Elroy?
Dresses... for me?
What do you think about this one?
Maybe aunt Elroy is actually
a kind person, after all?
I need to thank her for this.
Aunt!
Why did you adopt Candy!?
Why did you do that?
It was grandfather William's decision.
But... you don't acknowledge it?
That's right. I can't acknowledge it
Candy stole from us! She is a thief!
-I'm not!
-Candy.
That's not true!
I would never do such a thing!
Enough!
What's up with this tacky dress?
It looks horrible!
What are you saying! It was aunt
Elroy who gave me this dress!
She had it perfectly tailored to my
sizes and then gave the dress to me!
She only thinks that ladies of the Adley
family hate unusual things...
Such things don't suit the
girl from Pony's home!
And just what is Neil saying...?
-Anyway, Candy is...
-Neil!
Anthony!
Candy isn't Leagan's servant
anymore!
Neither she's a horse keeper!
She's a daughter
of the Adley family!
Candice White... Adley!
Speak properly to her!
Aunt Elroy
Will you really allow this thief
to become an Adley?
You won't acknowledge her?
Right? Aunt
I can't go against William.
But... I won't acknowledge her!
-Eliza!
-Stop!
Haven't you promised that
you'd say it before aunt Elroy?
Yes. Is Candy a thief, or not?
Neil, remember what you promised just
before Candy went to Mexico?
I hope you haven't forgotten already!
Wait, Neil!
Get it? Tell the truth now!
So it was yours and Eliza's ploy
after all!
Tell the truth to aunt Elroy
first thing in the morning!
Do you swear on the honour of the
Adley family?
Now speak, like you promised!
Before aunt Elroy...
Be a honourable Adley!
Is Candice White Adley a thief?!
Aunt Elroy, running away?
I'm not running away!
We have a party tonight
I have to make preparations.
A party! That's right
it's in Candy's honour!
Can't wait!
Don't tell me... a party for me?
Aunt!
Hold right there!
Neil, this isn't over yet.
Neil, is Candy a thief?
Well?!
-She... she's not.
-Say it out louder!
Candy is not a thief.
You and Eliza made it up
in order to drive Candy...
out of the house!
Is that right?
Apologize to Candy!
Neil, we know...
what happened on the day
when Candy arrived to Leagan family.
Now we expect you to do the same thing!
You made Candy apologize
to prevent Dorothy from getting fired!
He and Eliza even told Candy
how to apologize!
Candy, apologize to Neil and Eliza!
Candy, you're supposed to
apologize on your knees.
You haven't apologized unless you say
"Forgive me, I was wrong."
Forgive me, I was wrong.
Say it louder!
Forgive me, I was wrong!
Louder!
You know how to do it, then.
Get on your knees!
And say
"Forgive me, I was wrong."
Now, hurry up!
Wait!
Candy!
It's okay. That's enough!
Hey!
Candy, why did you stop him?
They treated you so badly.
But I'm okay with that.
I'll remember this!
I don't bear a grudge against
Neil and Eliza!
Why?
If the two of them
hadn't framed me for theft
I wouldn't have been
sent to Mexico.
And I wouldn't have become
an Adley.
Candy, you...
Sister Pony and Sister Lane
have told me this
These are the words from the Lord
If one can forgive
other people's mistakes...
his heavenly Father
will forgive him as well.
If one doesn't wish to forgive
his heavenly Father
won't forgive him as well
What a wonderful smell.
Anthony!
Candy,
you really are a kind girl.
You know, Anthony...
-What is it?
-I'm sorry.
For what?
I sold the Sweet Candy
you gave me...
in order to help somebody.
It's okay, Candy.
Look around!
There are so many
Sweet Candies now!
And they are all yours!
Anthony!
Drop it!
That's ...
-This?
-That pendant...
My Prince lost it.
-Your Prince?
-I don't know his name.
I just call him like that.
You know, you startled me
when I first saw you.
I thought you looked
exactly like the Prince!
On the Pony's hill,
wearing a kilt and carrying bagpipes.
Candy, men of the Adley family
usually have that pendant.
Really?
Then...
The Prince was an Adley?
Maybe... I think so
Who was it?
Who met Candy
during her childhood?
Just who was it?
Was it an Adley
who captured her heart?
What's the matter, Anthony?
Candy...
You still haven't forgotten
about your prince?
Was it...
because I look a bit like him?
Anthony! That's not true!
I don't care who the Prince is!
Anthony, it's because...
Because... I like you
Candy!
I said it. My heart is pounding.
Anthony is wonderful!
I like Anthony!
I like him more than anyone else!
Anthony!
-Candy!
-Yes?
Where did you go?
Yes... I was going for a walk.
You're not a servant anymore.
You're a daughter of an Adley!
Yes
You can't just leave the estate
whenever you feel like to.
Yes.
Tonight we are doing a dinner party
in your honor
Dinner party?
Got it?
Behave yourself and don't do anything
to embarrass the family.
Yes, I understand!
They are doing a party for me.
For me!
This is the first time in my life!
Excuse me!
Dorothy!
You are invited to join everyone!
Dorothy
please don't be so formal!
But... you are my master now!
Dorothy... you and I
will be friends forever!
But...
Alright then, we'll talk like friends
whenever nobody can see us!
Well then, Candy!
The dinner will be served now!
Alright then!
Dinner...
I think I can go in this dress
No!
For a dinner
you need an evening gown.
You'll make me angry!
Now, we have to get you
looking good first!
There are so many annoying
regulations, right?
You'll learn to cope with them!
Maybe so.
Dorothy, are you happy?
I'm as happy as I can be
Candy, you?
I'm the happiest one in the world!
I'm glad.
Don't do anything stupid now!
Candy, it's dinner time!
The three of us
are here to escort you!
May we enter, Miss Candy?
-Please do!
-I'm entering then!
-Wonderful!
-Let me see!
Pretty!
A green evening gown...
Mama.
This Anthony dude
is totally speechless.
Thank you for inviting us tonight!
Welcome. Here, come in.
Okay, Eliza?
Don't give up to anyone.
Behave yourself and be elegant.
I understand, mother.
He's totally obsessed over Candy.
I'll let him see all of her faults.
I'll make you look like a
redneck before everybody.
Thank you for waiting!
Everyone,
meet Candice White Adley.
Her dress is better than mine...
and that ribbon... it's silk!
I think it's time to begin
Grandfather William
in his whims decided to...
adopt Candy into the Adley family
as his daughter.
She will be introduced to
the rest of the family later on
Today, I specially invited
the Leagan family to know her.
Now, Candy, it's your turn.
Nice to meet you!
Now, Candice
your seat is over there.
Yes
You're better than me?
I'll show you.
She sat closer to the head
of the table...
I'm going back!
Eliza!
Wait, Eliza!
Mother
Candy is sitting closer to the
head of the table than I am!
-I don't want that!
-Eliza
I understand your feelings, but...
Adleys are ranked
much higher than Leagans.
Please bear this
Candy is still no match for you
Right?
I understand
Candy
Elegant people drink their soup
without slurping.
Thank you, I won't do that!
They didn't really teach you any
table manners in Pony's home?
Damn it...
Eliza,
please teach me from now on!
I want to become an elegant
gentle lady, just like you!
Sorry, Aunt.
That'll be good
I know she won't give up to Eliza!
That's right. I'm sure that
Candy will become a wonderful lady.
After everyone in the Adley family
takes a liking to her
I will...
It's nothing!
I haven't said anything.
Yes!
Dorothy!
Candy! What happened?
I snuck away from the party.
Candy, you mustn't come to
this place!
Dorothy, I just got a good idea.
We can stay together forever!
I will ask aunt Elroy...
Candy!
If I do that, you could become
even happier!
Okay? Come with me, Dorothy!
Hold on, Candy!
It's true that I've become much
happier now that I'm your servant.
But...
Can you really call it happiness?
Dorothy?
Candy
Happiness isn't just something that
can be passed from one to another
Happiness is something
you build for yourself
Just like you can only be saved
by God
Actually
it's just like Dorothy said
I thought that I'd be happy if
I got adopted by the Adley family
But that was just
my wishful thinking.
Yes. I need to
catch my own happiness.
I've made up my mind
Dorothy, thank you.
In that moment
Candy swore that
she will pursue her own happiness.
And it was such a beautiful
moonlit evening.