The day they spent together
in Lakewood
Became an unforgettable memory
for Candy and Anthony
However...
Aunt Elroy
awaited for their return
My Anthony
Did you have a good time
riding those wooden horses, Candy?
It was wonderful
Aunt, would you like
to ride them one day?
Be quiet!
A girl from high society...
doesn't participate in
such primitive amusement!
Primitive? But Aunt
I'm sure you would like it
Anthony? And what did you do?
You were seen eating bread with
your bare hands while standing!
A hot dog!
Hot dog?
You eat them standing up
and they are very tasty!
-Right, Candy?
-Yes...
That's enough!
Didn't you climb a bell tower in
the church after that?
But... how come everybody
knows about this?
Townspeople were very curious
about you two
They're some pretty nosy people!
Enough! Listen.
Members of our Ardley family...
are drawing a lot of attention
from the society
The last thing we need is behavior
that would harm our reputation.
You two are the only ones that have
ever inflicted shame upon our family.
-Candy!
-Yes.
-Think twice before you act out
-Yes
Anthony
you'll have to be careful as well...
-What's the matter?
-Anthony?
My head hurts a bit.
Please return to your room
and get some rest
I'll call Dorothy
We'll give you a water-filled pillow
Dorothy, will you help me?
It's my fault, too.
Anthony did it for me...
Miss Candy
you don't need to worry!
He doesn't have a fever!
Candy!
Yes
Don't get up!
I was faking it.
Faking?
Then, you were lying to Aunt?
If I hadn't fallen sick...
there would be no end
to Aunt's preachings!
Anthony, you rascal!
You know, it was hard for me
to see you being scolded there.
Oh, I'm already used to it!
Aunt doesn't know the real you!
That's why they see you
as their enemy
But what can I do?
Aunt isn't the only one!
Neil and Eliza
don't know you as well!
But instead, it was you
who got to know the real me!
That's enough for me!
I wish my mama were alive
Your mother?
I'm sure that my mama would've
become a good friend of yours.
She was a gentle person
I'm sure.
She loved roses.
Mama!
Whenever mama wasn't around
I would look in the rose garden
And I would find her there
-But that day...
-Mama!
Seeing those
scattering rose petals
I realized that mama could be
going to a faraway place
Mama?
What's the matter, Anthony?
Mama!
Why are you crying...?
The roses are dying.
Anthony, flowers are beautiful
because they die.
And when flowers die...
they become immortal as
their petals scatter in the wind
They don't die.
Mama, you won't die?
If your mama dies...
she will forever continue
living inside your heart
And not too long after that
mama died
I finally understood what
she was trying to say
That your gentle mother now
lives inside your heart, right?
I finally understood what
she was trying to say
That your gentle mother now
lives inside your heart, right?
Yes
Mama from those times
will live forever with me.
And that's why you like roses
I'm growing roses
just like she used to...
and these roses I'm growing now...
-Candy
-Yes?
If I happen to die...
No, please don't say that!
It's a figure of speech!
Anthony!
What a nightmare.
Why are so many flowers dying?
Sweet Candy is...
At that fortune telling...
only bad cards came up.
And you didn't get any sleep?
Bad things just keep coming
one after another!
God wouldn't bring misfortune
to someone like Candy!
That's right! I forgot to pray!
But I wonder will God listen to me?
I wasn't always serious
in my prayers...
You know...
Because of my grandma
wished for something ...
she will give up the coffee she likes.
Coffee?
Give up on something you like...
and then
you can pray for something!
That's right
I'll stop my unpleasant thoughts
with God's help
Dorothy, for Anthony's sake
I'll give up on eating pies
which I like so much!
I'll give up on ham and eggs.
Dorothy, you too?
Yes! It's for you, Miss Candy
Dorothy, thanks.
Kurin!
Kurin, you still get to eat
whatever you want!
Come quickly then
breakfast will be served soon
-Good morning, Stear!
-Hello, Candy!
-What are you building?
-What, this?
I'm preparing for the fox hunt.
Fox hunt?
You didn't know?
Entire family gathers and
shoots stuff.
That's pretty sick.
Everybody...
every member of the Ardley family?
That's right. Candy, you too
-Me too?
-Probably...
they will introduce you to
the rest of the family at that time
What am I going to do?
Just be your normal self!
Anthony!
Anthony, what do you think of
my new machine?
It's okay
Anyway, building it must have been
easy for someone like you!
Anyhow, look at this
I'll try it out now
You see, if I do this, it will
immobilize the fox with gas...
This is strange
I'm sleepy...
Stear!
You always do these things!
Hey, everyone!
Aunt Elroy is calling you!
She is going to preach again?
She said it's some kind
of emergency
Anyway, come inside
Alright, let's go
Hey, I smell a pie!
This is the first time she
directly called us for some pie!
It's the first time in ten years
that I made something in the kitchen!
It would be a shame
just to eat it!
Everyone, enjoy!
Let's eat!
It's great!
Candy, what's the matter?
Don't you want to eat?
Candy, what happened?
I thought you liked pie!
It's just...
Candy, have some pie!
It's really tasty
you mean that you don't want
to eat the pie I made myself?
I'm not saying that!
Is there some other reason?
No, it's ...
You're still mad at me
for scolding you last night?
That's not true!
Dorothy!
Take away Candy's plate!
Yes!
Uh, I...
If you don't want to eat
I'm fine with that!
Grand Aunt!
Candy
you can tell me everything
Why didn't you want to eat the pie?
I talked to everybody about this...
We wondererd
why did Aunt make those pies
Aunt was being mean to you
from the beginning...
but her opinion on you
has been changing
That pie...
it was from all of us...
Candy...
She made it for you.
For me?
I think that Aunt is sorry for
scolding you yesterday.
Anthony...
To refuse a token of
my friendship...!
Enter!
Dorothy?
You don't have any chores
in this place
I have a butler for that
Madam, it's my fault
What are you talking about?
That Candy didn't eat the pie
You came to tell me that?
Yes!
Anthony!
Sorry, but it's just not like you!
When did you become so religious?
-But...
-Look over there!
It's the time of the year
when roses die
They die every year,
but then they bloom again.
By the way, that fortune telling
doesn't worry me at all
I believe happiness is
something a man...
has to grasp with his own hands
A trump card doesn't matter at all!
Yeah, I think that too!
Now that's the real Candy!
Suddenly I feel hungry!
Let's eat some pie!
Aunt!
Candy, Dorothy told me.
Forgive me
You can't speak with food
in your mouth!
Yes
You will be introduced to the family
before the annual fox hunt.
-I'm glad, Candy
-Yes
In return...
I expect you to behave
like a real Ardley...
without embarrassing yourself.
Yes!
-Candy
-Yes?
You've got pie on your face
Oh no!
You're a lady, don't pig out!
That's the girl who was adopted?
I hear that she has noone of her own.
Candy, you look great!
I wonder if
she can greet them like a lady
Can't wait to see that!
Everyone, this time...
grandfather William decided to
adopt her as his daughter!
Meet Candice White
Now, Candy, introduce yourself
Yes
Everyone, how do you do?
I'm Candice White
And, uh... my dream is to become
a beautiful bride and...
I'm shocked
That's supposed to be an introduction?
No, but before that...
I thought I'd have to
become a pretty lady and...
but I don't really know anything yet
I'm working hard
so please teach me everyhing!
That was a wonderful introduction
Candy!
I was so scared, I have no idea
what I said back there!
You startled everybody...
telling everybody about how you
want to become Anthony's bride...
I really said that?
Stear is kidding you!
You bad, Stear.
Candy!
Anthony,
want to come with me?
I'm sorry, but I'll escort Candy.
It's the first time she's on a fox hunt
so I'll have to teach her everything
I see. Candy...
be careful not to fall off the horse!
Eliza, take care, too!
Cleopatra doesn't seem to be
in a good mood.
So what!
Go!
-Candy, let's go!
-Yeah!
Archie, let's go!
Anthony, I think
we got separated from the rest
I did that on purpose!
There's one hill I like.
-A hill?
-Let's go!
It's here, Candy!
-It's exactly alike...!
-Like what?
Pony's hill!
I grew up at Pony's hill.
My homeland is Pony's hill
and Pony's home
I'd like to see them
Because you have so many
memories of that place!
Yeah
Let's go there together!
Really?
I want to see the place
where you grew up
It's a promise!
Sister Pony and sister Lane
will be startled when they see us!
Candy!
I got something!
Well, it seems that
we're in for a run!
-Candy, look at me!
-What will you do?
Candy, look at this!
Anthony, that's dangerous!
Candy, you coward!
But when you're so high up
in the saddle...
I have confidence in my horse.
How did it feel?
It's wonderful!
I wonder if I could do that!
I'd like to fly like that, too!
I'd like to fly!
Candy...
Whenever my mama
would talk about horses...
her eyes would light up
just like yours are now
Because she wanted to ride
Your mother?
Her body was so weak,
so doctors made her stop
Before dying...
she wanted to ride
just one last time
Candy?
About the prince on the hill...
Anthony, I don't care about him
anymore
I've already found my prince
Anthony, it's you
You're my dear prince
Candy?
I'll say what you just told me now...
Once we're together at Pony's hill
Anthony!
So the prince you met at Pony's hill
looked exactly like me?
That's right, Anthony!
I may even know him
When I was little
there was one boy who loved nature
and he always took care after mama
Who was he?
I'll try to remember!
Look out!
Anthony...