They were attacked by winter storm.
They worked together
to overcome the storm.
Cookie was Injured unexpectedly.
After the storm,
there' s something in front of them...
A land over the horizon.
It' s America.
The America
is now right in front of her.
The port through the window.
It is America.
I' m home,
sister Pony, sister Lane.
And Terry
You are now in America too.
America, I'm coming
America.
How do you feel?
The first time to America.
It feels so real.
The ship can stop at the port directly.
You know that too, Cookie.
I have learnt the details already.
Arrived safely at last.
Thank you, captain Niven.
I hope that this is the last time
shipping the people as cargos.
Yes, I won't run a blockade again.
I' ll send you to the hospital, Cookie.
What would happened, If my foot...
Don't worry, I' ll go with you.
Captain.
Is that your lovely daughter?
Papa!
Sandra!
Welcome back, papa.
Is she your daughter?
She' s too lively.
Welcome back, papa.
They are...
Glad to meet you, I am Candy.
I' m Cookie.
The stowaway of Sea-gull?
No, I am...
Sandra,
back to the house and wait for me.
Cookie needs to see the doctor.
Papa.
Hurts!
How is the situation? Doctor.
It is not a simple fracture.
Is the nerve ok?
Who wrapped up for him?
I did.
Is there any proplem?
No, you were doing very well.
He will be recovered soon.
Cookie can walk then?
No need to worry!
Can I be a sailor?
Doctor can't decide that.
I can only guarantee that,
you can walk again a month later.
Wonderful! I can be a sailor.
Cookie!
Thanks for your help, Candy.
Let' s do the treatment now.
Sandra!
I want to talk to you, papa.
Papa cares the stowaway
More than the daughter.
What are you talking about?
Sandra.
I hate you, papa.
I was right,
you do have other women.
Sandra.
Wait! Captain Niven
worries about Cookie' s injury.
So he bring him to the doctor.
He got hurt because
you've sneak into papa's ship.
Sandra.
Papa never cares about me.
Where are you going? Sandra.
The police office, of course.
Papa came home with two stowaways.
-What?
-Just a moment.
Don't act foolishly, Sandra.
Let me talk to her.
Sandra, let me explanation.
You' re Candy, aren't you?
It' s over six months...
Papa stays with me only two days.
Two days?
From England to America
you are all together.
Accompany others' daughter
more than his own daughter.
Is that right?
It' s captain' s work.
Work... Nonsense!
Wait! Sandra.
Sandra,
is she a stowaway from England?
Yes!
Are you Sandra's friends?
That' s right, We are friends.
Such a lovely girl,
how could be the stowaway?
What do you want? Stop!
You' re very brave.
Isn't that a racoon?
Go get it!
May sell for a good price.
Stop it! Don't hurt kurin.
How about join us?
I' m not coming back to America
for join a faction.
You bitch!
You are nothing but a stowaway.
Sandra, I' ll make it into the sample
as a present for you.
Thanks!
Clint.
Clint, hurry up.
Stop!
Over there! Get her.
Look out! Clint.
That's great!
For what?
Look down upon us!
Give me the money,
if you don't want to join us.
I have no money.
Then, I' ll take the the racoon.
Someone' s coming!
What?
Crew of Sea-gull.
Let' s go!
-Don't leave, Sandra.
-Let go of me.
-Hurry up!
-Candy!
-Go!
-Are you hurt?
-I am fine.
What is the matter?
I was taking a walk with Sandra,
run into them...
It might be a ploy, be careful.
Are you ok? Lady.
The stair is dark, be careful.
Yes!
Papa cares about Candy very much.
I need a bath.
The port.
Why did you cover it for me?
I didn't.
You can tell the truth to my father
that Sandra is a bad girl.
Where is your mother?
She passed away when I was six.
I live with grandmother,
didn't go home until evening.
Any questions?
Waitting for your father by yourself.
Your father was busy on the ship.
Can you understand how I feel?
So comfortable.
You seem to become reconciled.
I should leave now.
Why don't you stay with us for dinner?
You've not stay with Sandra
over six months.
Don't worry about that.
The doctors will look after Cookie.
I' d like to have dinner on the ship.
-There' s no need.
-It' s because...
Candy, look!
Don't be anxious to leave.
Why did Sandra took Candy home?
It' s getting cold here.
Quick!
Back to the company at once?
They want you to...
OK, let me put on the uniform.
Another navigation now?
I don't know. Candy, Help yourself.
It' s always like that!
He works hard.
The daughter is more arduous.
They seem to gave up already.
Sandra! Why did you join the faction?
I have no father, no siblings...
You...
Keep quiet!
Charlie likes you very much.
You better be well-behaved, Candy.
Come over!
Charlie.
I've been waiting for you.
Your uniform ...
Good looking, right?
Let me take a look.
What's wrong with the uniform?
Have you been to England?
England?
It' s the uniform of St. Paul academy.
Terry already said that before.
Terry?
You know Terrius Grandchester?
Yes, it' s about a month ago...
Charlie, get ready!
Stop! I have a word to you!
Terry?
Aren't you Terry?
Charlie, you are Charlie.
You' re back to America. Terry.
You looked just like before.
You too.
Is Terry still around?
He stayed for only one night.
Going to somewhere
and looking for something.
We missed.
Do you like the drama?
The drama is a kind of magic.
You can be anyone, once you' re in it.
No matter what kind of characters.
The orphan, the prince, the hero.
You can be anyone.
I love the drama very much.
Terry.
You like Terry, don't you?
How come...?
You become lovely,
when we talk about him.
It' okay, let's dance.
Wait!
Are you the leader of the faction?
Don't be so unpleasant.
Sorry, I have a request.
What is it?
Can Sandra withdraw the faction?
It' s her idea to join us.
-So, she can leave?
-Candy!
What are you doing?
Mind your own business!
I have my own ideas.
Join the faction isn't your idea.
Stop talking like that!
Why are you in charge of my business?
It' s not my business,
but your father is being sad.
Officious! Let's go, Charlie.
Papa.
Don't hit her!
Sandra is lonely, that' s why she join...
She is not the only one who felt lonely.
If you pester my daughter again,
I' ll break your arms.
As you wish.
Stop it! Idiot.
Charlie,
why do you listen to an old man?
Do you think I will fear a knife?
What?
Your hands are shivering.
Damm it!
Don't be silly. Stop it!
Stop it!
Stop it! Jose.
Stop it! Don't hurt my father.
-Damn!
-Stop it!
Sandra.
Papa.
Sandra!
Thanks for your help.
The help is from you!
I will look after Cookie.
After I fully recovered,
I' ll work with Captain Niven.
Congratulations! Cookie.
For your courage and friendship.
Thanks.
As a present for you, Cookie.
Become a good sailor.
Certainly!
Candy,
a present from France by papa.
It' s too precious, I can't take it.
Please accept it. Candy.
The glove is Sandra's compliment.
Sandra.
I won't be lonely anymore.
Candy.
Just in time! Brother.
The food, Candy!
So many?
You' re Feeding an elephant.
Captain.
Get on the train quickly.
Thank you, everyone.
May Candice White has a happy tour.
Salute!
Good-bye!
Good-bye, Cookie.
Good-bye, captain Niven, Sandra,
Viva, Vokado.
The kind grandfather and Pink...
Cordial shopkeeper...
Mr. Carson of the village,
captain Justkin...
With all your helps,
I can go back to America.
The people in the journey,
we may be unable to meet again.
It' s getting cold.
Sister Pony, Sister Lane
I' m now coming home.
It is snowing.
We did it, Clint.
Let' s go find a carriages.
A carriage,
it' s heading to the village.
Just a moment, take me with you.
We missed.
There' s a passenger on the carriage.
Both Terry and Cany didn't knew that.
Terry should be in New York,
why did he come here?
They did not found each other.
They are farther and farther apart.