A wrinkled transferee!
A small hill which Clint found
looked exactly like Pony's hill.
Candy's heart found a new hope after
being overwhelmed by circumstances.
I won't give up.
I'm going to get back to Eliza
for her pranks.
So I named that hill
"The other Pony's hill" .
I could clearly see sister Lane and you
while I was up there.
What was that?
Say, what's the matter?
Terry!
Terrius, this is girls' ward.
I know.
Why did you sneak in here then?
How did that punk get inside?
He's got some guts...
Terrius, were you drinking?
If you'd like, you can join me.
What are you saying?
Good evening, my ladies!
Your staring expressions
are pretty amusing.
Maybe I snuck into a zoo by mistake.
Terrius!
Return to boys' ward immediately!
-Tommorrow...
-Report to director's office, right?
Terrius!
Well then, I bid you farewell.
Oh, and put the broken glass on
my dad's account
Sister Margaret.
How can he be so cool?
He likes upsetting other people!
Be quiet!
Everybody, return to your rooms!
-Patty, I haven't seen you in a while.
-Yes...
-Patty!
-Candy, I'm sorry.
I have to go.
Of course. Eliza and others
told her not to speak to me.
Never mind then!
-Candice!
-Yes?
Hurry back to your room.
I will!
Patty?
Patty!
Uh, you... I'm sorry!
It seems though I missed the room!
Missed...? Uh...
I'm looking for
my granddaughter Patty!
Oh, Patty is right next door!
Here you go.
Thank you!
Grandma!
You look great, Patty!
How come you got in here?
I used a little magic!
There'll be trouble if
they find you here!
This is a nice room...
Your wardrobe is here, right?
Grandma...
I'll put my clothes on the hangers
so that they don't get all wrinkled.
Wrinkled...?
I came in order to enjoy a student's
life together with you, Patty!
Grandma... but...!
Aren't you glad that you won't
be alone, Patty?
You're kidding me!
Family members aren't supposed
to enter these buildings!
Moreover...
Don't worry. I'll take care that
nobody discovers me.
It's impossible!
Whenever some of my friends
stopped by...
they knew straightaway!
Patty, you're a fraidycat,
just like your grandpa!
-But...
-Say, Patty...
If it's okay with you
she could stay in my room.
Your room?
Yes. Since noone comes to my room...
nobody will be able to discover her!
But...
I'd be grateful if you did that for me!
Grandma...!
Your heart is pounding so much!
You'll have a coronary if I stay here!
And you are...?
Call me Candy!
That's a nice name!
I am Marsha.
I'll help you with your luggage!
Thank you.
-I can carry this.
-Okay.
Candy!
Make sure that nobody sees her.
That's right!
That was close!
Granny, now's the time!
Okay!
I somehow feel like a young girl again!
Welcome! It's a little cramped but...
Candy, I'm a little worried
about one thing.
What is it?
Why don't you have friends
over at your room?
They've turned their backs on me.
They did that?
Yes. But I don't worry about that.
That's right. the worst thing one could
do is to worry over such things.
That's right... here
I made the bed for you.
But how come you didn't want
to sleep in Patty's room?
I didn't come here
to see my granddaughter.
In that case... why?
I finally wanted to experience
the students' way of life.
Granny, so you never went to school?
No, never.
Your family didn't treat you right...
It was exactly the opposite.
I was a daughter of a rich family.
My parents didn't want me to get
bullied in the school for that
so they brought seven teachers
who educated me at home.
Seven teachers?
But I wanted to attend an
ordinary school so much!
That's why you came to this dorm...
I wanted to make my dream come true!
That's right!
I'll let you hear something nice!
That's a violin, right?
It's a memento of a late grandfather.
Grandma!
They'll find her if somebody hears this!
God...
It's like
I'm being beckoned into a dream.
Somebody is here!
I'd better hurry...!
I'm right there!
Candice, if you play your violin
this late at night...
it could bother other people.
I'm sorry.
That's strange...
Candy playing a violin...
The coast is clear!
The student's life is so much fun!
I don't think anybody will come
after this.
I wanted to play a little more...
That's right! I'd better study maths
for tomorrow!
Let me see.
I'm not good in maths.
This is easy! I can show you.
Granny, you?
I told you that I had seven teachers!
You did well.
You must be working hard, Candice.
Yes... a little.
Everyone, do your best.
Candice just transferred to our school
but she's already ahead of everybody.
That's strange...
last night she did great on violin
today she's good at maths...
Candy!
I have a favor to ask.
You want ideas for new pranks?
I'd like you to play your violin for us.
Does that sound like a prank?
Eliza...
This evening, at the dance salon.
You have let us hear your playing again!
I'm still not comfortable with
playing in front of the audience...
It doesn't matter. If you can play like
you did last night, it'll be great!
We have to hear it!
But...
if you let me practice a little more.
Or maybe you're hiding something
in your room?
You wouldn't mind us taking a look then?
I understand.
If you want to hear it that much
I'll play for you.
So, unless you do great laying a violin
they'll discover that
you're hiding the old lady?
That's right.
Don't you have any good ideas?
We'd help you but...
there's no way
you'd learn how to play by tonight...
My best inventions always come
in the time of dire need...
that's it!
Hey, it's not one of your shoddy
inventions again, isn't it?
Actually, there is a very simple
solution to Candy's problem!
Tell me, Stear!
You see, I'll build another violin.
Can you build a violin so easily?
What, I only need to know the
shape of a violin.
And you, Candy, will take that violin!
But the trick will be in this!
Almost like a childish prank!
What, with a little help from us...
you'll be playing well in no time.
Now it's up to me to make a violin.
I'm suspicious... will it be alright?
I'm on it!
So this is the fake violin?
I'm sorry but...
could you practice a bit
while hiding behind the curtain?
Can do!
My student's life is suddenly
becoming even more fun!
What, it's you, Patty!
Granny!
Scaring your grandma like that
you bad, bad granddaughter!
Say, Candy, is it true that
you're going to play violin?
Yes, I'll play for them.
But Candy...
I'll just move my arms
like I'm playing the instrument.
Then the grandma will...
A student's life is supposed to
have some suspense and excitement!
If you do that...
and if they discover you...
Patty, your heart is pounding again...
Patty, maybe we'll really pull it off.
Yeah, a student's life can be
incredibly fun indeed!
I, Candice White Ardley
will now play the violin for you.
But before that, could you turn
the lights down a bit?
I won't be in the mood otherwise.
I'm not very good yet.
Where did you learn this, Candy?
She's good.
But it's nothing special!
Candy, you're not playing right!
Stop!
What, can't your comments
wait till the end?
I want you to show me that violin.
It's a very important violin to me...
Let me see.
It's a fake!
It could never make that melody.
What's the meaning of this, Candy?
There is somebody behind the curtain!
That's the wind... it's nothing!
Patty!
Of course. Just what I thought.
You were playing violin
in Candy's room.
You showed her
how to do the maths, too.
-It was you, right?
-Yeah...
That means that
you're Candy's friend.
I'll remember this!
Everyone, let's return to our rooms!
They made fools of us!
Exactly what I thought!
Candy could never play the violin!
That's right, she was a dogsbody
up until now!
-What happened?
-Terrius was here again?
A ghost...
A ghost you say?
It wore a school's uniform...
but its face was all rattled!
Which way did it go?
It disappeared around here...
Now I even became a ghost!
A student's life is great!
But when did you and Patty
switch places?
When I realized that
she might get discovered...
I hid behind the curtains.
This is the most exciting thing
I've ever done in my life!
Those seven teachers couldn't have
taught me things this fun!
Patty!
Oh! Is something in your eye?
Grandma... I'm begging you
please go home...
Come on, don't cry... okay?
Ever since you came here...
I keep thinking that
my heart is going to explode...
I see.
Before leaving, I still have
one favor to ask of you!
What is it?
I've never been in a classroom before.
I want to go there and attend class!
Grandma!
Patty, hang in there!
She's a bit faint-hearted, isn't she?
Hurry!
The classrooms are that way.
Granny!
Hide your face!
Uh...
She isn't feeling too well
so I'm taking her to the nurse's room...
So exciting!
life in school...
So this is the classroom?
Who'd think that I would get to
use this book in school...
it's a dream come true!
I wish I could take you to our classroom
but...
This one is fine!
If I listen carefully
I can hear everything!
Anyway, I'm off to class!
-I'll sit right here.
-Okay!
-Where were you, Candice?
-Sorry!
You can't become a prominent
lady if you aren't puncutal.
I'll be more careful!
We will be grading today.
Hand over your exam prints.
Grading?
Are you saying that you didn't
receive a print, just like Patricia?
Patty...
-Louise!
-Yes!
You gave a print to Candice
haven't you?
Of course!
I went to her room and delivered it.
That's a lie!
I haven't received anything!
Be quiet!
Since you forgot about the print
why are you saying that
you didn't even receive one?
Patricia and Candice
stand out in front of the class!
What are they saying that
they delivered the prints to her!
I was there all the time!
What is that?
The neighboring classroom
should have been vacant.
I'll take a look!
Candice!
There is nobody over there.
Candice, I want you to stand still.
So this is the best school in England?
With everybody being so mean to Candy...
I don't want to live as a student
anymore.
But not all people are bad as them!
No, that goes for the students.
As for the teachers
I don't agree with
their teaching methods!
Grandma, your voice is too loud!
I was grateful to my parents for
not sending me into a regular school.
Although the seven teachers
may not better than regular school.
I would've taken Patty
back with myself.
Grandma...
However, there is one thing which you
can't possibly get with home schooling.
One thing?
Yes.
Llocked up in the house,
you can never make friends like Candy.
Candy, take care after Patty.
Yeah...
Send my regards to the young man
who help me get in here.
To Terrius?
Yeah.
I sneak in here because
he's drawing away all the attention!
Well then, goodbye.
Grandma, if someone sees you...
It's okay. Getting out of here
will be much easier!
I snuck like a thief on my way in!
Grandma!
Patty, I'm sure
your grandma has a good idea.
Uh...
My granddaughter, Patricia
lives in this dormitory.
Patricia?
Yes! I'd like to see her
even if for just a moment.
Unfortunately...
To meet students within the dormitory
is against the regulation.
Oh, I see... well if that's the case,
I'll be on my way...
Where is the exit then?
I'll show you.
Let me help with your luggagge.
Oh, thank you...
So, that's what she had in mind...
She's so much trouble.
She's so nice!
Someday, I want to be a nice granny
just like her!
Candy, would you be my friend?
Of course!
She said that the best thing about
school is making friends, right?
Yeah!
Coming and going like the wind
it was Patricia's grandmother...
who built a firm bond between
Candy's and Patricia's hearts.