Candy did her best to take care
of the young lady.
The young lady was healed from
her psychological problem.
Candy received her Thank-You Letter.
The hard work paid off.
A sense of duty for being
a nurse arised in her heart.
Rumors about Terry.
It's going to be hotter after the rain
isn't it?
Silly girl.
Yes, Principal.
Your letter and package.
Thanks.
You often receive letters lately.
Stear and Archie have been very sweet to me
after they returned to America.
It must be very tiring being a nurse.
A little treat for you.
What did they give me?
Candy!
Everyone.
Everyone, have one of these.
- So beautiful!
- Nice candy!
From my friend.
Must be the boyfriend.
Thanks.
- Let's eat!
- Please.
Have more.
So tasty.
Do you want some, Frannie?
A gift from my friend.
I don't want it.
Don't be shy, please.
Candy, I told you before.
I hate people who talk too much.
Do you really understand what I said?
Honestly, I hate people like you.
Frannie, why did you say that?
That's true.
This is my first time
to be criticized like this.
I don't know how much she hates me.
I'd better be quiet.
Did you hear that?
Something terrible happened!
An ambassador from Austria was assassinated!
A Serbian man?
It's getting complicated.
I hope the war won't start.
Bad news came one after another.
Dark clounds are everywhere.
Finally the sky got clearer.
The sun is brighter and brighter.
I want to go swimming in the lake
when the weather is a little bit nicer.
Annie, Archie, Stear.
And Pattie'd better go together, too!
Sister Candy.
What is Sister Candy thinking?
You must have something in your mind,
Otherwise you wouldn't stare out of the window.
Nothing.
Then what are you doing?
I am taking a sunbath.
Please don't tell Headmaster Merry Jane.
Only if you give us some drawing books.
It's too boring.
- Me, too!
-Alright.
I'll go get some during the break time.
You guys behave yourselves!
Ok!
We stay in the hospital everyday.
There are so many excitements in downtown.
Grandpa, do they sell drawing books here?
There seems to be a couple.
Here?
This is....
Terry.
A new member with unlimited future.
Terry is playing in a Shakespeare play.
A new actor at Broadway.
Terry.
Finally we found you!
Terry, how are you?
You became so mature!
I miss you so much!
The Broadway. Terry is working in the
entertainment business.
Last summer....
It was the first time he talked about drama
in the Scottish summer school.
Shakespeare.
This is your book.
You like dramas, Terry?
- No.
- Liar!
There are notes everywhere in your book.
You still want to deny it?
I do like dramas, a lot.
Terry was so devoted back then.
Terry.
In order to be able to see you....
I took the carriage chasing you all night.
The boat was sailing away in the first
ray of the morning sun.
The sound of the steam
whistle came from the distance.
As long as we stay alive
we will meet again someday.
Because of this sentence.
It has been half of a year
since I saw the boat going away
in the first ray of the morning sun.
I chose to be a nurse.
You head towards
the entertainment business.
You are now in New York.
Who is it?
What's your name?
Don't be afraid if I tell you.
It won't happen
I am not even afraid of hell.
My name is Mark White.
Devil!
Do not speak such a dirty name.
Hearing my name does make you afraid.
You are lying.
Mark White is a cursed name.
Let me cut your delusion with my sword.
Extraspecial!
Hawk His Majesty is still a minor
He doesn't deserve to die.
The evil Mark White. Stole his talent.
Is he dead?
Long life to Hawk His Majesty!
Good news, look!
The man who made us suffer was decapitated.
We are free!
Scotland! Hooray!
Extraspecial!
The war started!
Extraspecial! The war started!
Extraspecial!
The war between Austria and Serbia started!
Hurry!
War?
The war between Austria and Serbia started!
Extraspecial!
The war started!
It has nothing to do with America.
It's awful! Let me see.
How will the troupe survive
if the war started?
There might be less shows.
What are we gonna do with our jobs?
Things will find their ways.
I have nothing to do with this.
Everyone, did you read
the morning newspaper?
Look! Terry's photo.
- Terry?
- Where?
A new man with bright future.
Skillful and eye-catching acting.
A new man worthy of great expectation.
Terry, did you read the newspaper?
Yes, I did.
You received good credit. And a photo, too!
Everybody is looking forward to you.
An arising shiny star.
Thanks. Excuse me.
He is too arrogant.
Excuse me.
He is too new to be so arrogant.
He is so handsome!
True. Young and good at acting.
Unlimited future.
I am so sad.
The war is going to affect America anytime.
Candy.
Are you still in England?
I really hope that
I can cross the ocean to find Candy.
The St. Paul Academy in London.
Those memorable days won't come back again.
Mr. Terry.
Warrick Troupe in New York
wants to have an interview with you.
I'll go right away.
Candy, I am already in the
entertainment business.
I can't go back.
When will we reunion again?
God bless England.
The rumor finally came true.
We will get involved sooner or later.
America will join the war then.
The whole city is talking about the war.
However, the patients here are still relaxed.
The hospital won't be affected.
Candy, where are you going?
Excuse me. Anything wrong?
Headmaster Merry Jane wants everyone
to gather in the Principal's Office.
Headmaster?
Go!
Big news! You heard about that?
Don't mention the war
in front of the patients!
In case the patients will be anxious.
Please be aware of that.
Also,
there will be an important
matter announced soon.
You have to stay calm.
Yes.
Dismissed.
What important matter?
What's the school gonna do
once we join the war?
Everyone, watch your conversation.
That's Frannie.
Assertive like Headmaster Merry Jane.
Beautiful sunset!
What happened today was so unreal.
But it was real.
This news.
And the war.
Bad news!
England declared war to Germany!
England?
This way, America....
Finally England was involved in the war.
Pattie is still in England.
Will Pattie be alright?
Stear must be worried.
Sister.
Sister Candy.
You promised you would give
me the drawing book.
You didn't keep the promise.
Sorry.
I can't make the patient anxious.
I have to be more cheerful.
I am good at telling the stories.
Sit down.
Doctor Frank.
How was it? Did silly girl get lazy again?
Don't worry, Principal.
She is there.
The big wolf could only....
Cheerful as usual.
We need more of these nurses.
No, Mr.Daniel!
Doctor Frank said that
you were not allowed to move yet.
But, I want to go back to work.
I know. Please bear with it
for a little longer.
Mr.Daniel.
How come you are here?
I....
Candy, he is not allowed to walk around.
Didn't you know that?
It's not hurting anymore.
You don't care if you will
be a cripple forever?
Frannie, he is just trying
to walk a little bit.
It's not that serious.
You are not sensitive enough.
Our carelessness
can make the patients'problems more serious.
It is a good thing
that the patients like you,
but you still need to work hard.
Yes.
Right, Headmaster is looking for you.
Frannie.
Sorry, Candy.
That's alright. Let me walk
you back to the room.
Frannie, Hamilton,
Judy! Max!
Natalie, Biss,
Ellie, Lemans,
Candy White.
Yes!
No need to answer.
The above people
go check in at St.Joanna in Chicago.
Chicago?
St.Joanna Hospital is our
headquarters.
The surgical department is
the best among its field.
Stear, Archie, Annie
are all in Chicago.
Learn the surgical skill well,
And be an outstanding nurse.
Surgical skill?
Must be for the war.
Are they the war nurses?
War nurses?
Going to the cruel battlefield to
take care of the wounded soldiers.
It's true that
we might become the war nurses.
America is ready to join the war.
How about Terry's
entertainment business?
Headmaster, America won't
join the war, right?
Quiet!
There are no nationalities
in medical treatment.
Care giving should be fairly
provided to everyone.
It has nothing to do
with countries or races.
Everyone is equal.
Great saying!
Candy's heart
is echoing with what Headmaster Merry Jane said.
She decided to go to Chicago
to learn the surgical skill.
Candy is expecting herself.