I... I don't want that guy to take you!
Archie!
For that bastard to take you...
From the first time I saw you
Candy, I...
Stop it!
Please, stop it!
Realizing that her beloved Archie
likes Candy, Annie was shocked.
Moreover, Eliza found out the secret
that Annie was raised in Pony's home.
Archie comforted Annie's hurt feelings.
And finally, Candy and Annie
managed to mend their lost friendship.
A wondrous encounter.
-Can you manage?
-I'm okay.
-I'll walk the rest by myself.
-Alright. Take care.
Thanks...
A thief?
Te... Terry?
Terry, what happened to you?
So this is Tarzan-girl's room?
That guy made a mistake...
Blood!
Terry, you have wounds
all over your body!
What have you gotten yourself into?
I got some.
Just a stupid fight.
They got you pretty well.
They were a real bunch of ninjas.
However, a passer-by came to my help.
He also brought me back to this place.
You reek of alcohol, Terry!
Can you tell?
You punk!
You break all the rules
but it's never enough for you!
-They got you with a knife.
-Yeah...
I'd better stop the bleeding.
He's a bloody mess... just why did he
have to fight in the first place?
After all, he's a son of a rich
and famous nobleman.
You're hurting me!
Watch what you're doing!
You don't get to complain
while I'm tending your wounds!
Ouch!
Are you paying me back for
what I did to you before...
-Tarzan lady?
-I'm freckled Tarzan.
You made it up yourself
don't forget that!
You have good memory.
That's right. Freckled Tarzan.
Oh crap!
Sorry. I'll leave as soon as
I pull myself together.
If that guy hadn't made mistake,
I wouldn't have entered your room.
Don't talk.
You'll upset your wounds.
He's all sweaty...
maybe he's having a fever?
What should I do?
I can't just leave him like this.
He needs some medicine.
They keep some in the nurse's office...
but I can't simply ask sisters for it.
Is there a better solution...?
Alright!
Terry! I'm going out
to buy some medicine for you!
Don't do anything stupid!
Just leave it like this!
You're asking me
to leave a wounded person?
You're lucky, I'm not the kind of lady
who faints at the first sight of blood!
Candy.
Okay? Just lay still.
Candy!
Bye!
She does such unreasonable things...
Most stores are closed already.
Only the bars are still open.
He-hey, lady...
wanna help me finish this off?
I wonder if Terry was drinking
at a place like this.
Just where is the pharmacy...
That's ...!
You! Wait a second!
Candy!
You're Candy, aren't you?
Don't try to random-guess my name!
You're not my friend!
It's me.
Have you forgotten me, Candy?
It's me! Have you forgotten me
Candy?
Mr. Albert?
He doesn't have a beard
but that voice...
And that smile!
Mr. Albert!
It's been a long time, Candy!
Really, Mr. Albert, it was!
It really was!
When I went to London,
I thought I'd never meet him again.
But now, he's so close to me!
Mr. Albert!
Now, now, don't cry, Candy!
Let me see your face!
You've turned into a real beauty!
Mr. Albert, you did too!
I've turned beautiful?
Why, I'm glad to hear that!
So you've shaved your beard?
I thought you were an old man!
Come on!
Actually, I'm still in my twenties.
Sorry for calling out your name,
it's the best way to confront someone.
Confront?
Yes. Since I'm good with animals,
I got myself a job at the zoo.
When my animals were caught,
they were taken to the London zoo.
Instead of parting with my animals
I went along with them.
You know how to raise animals.
Yes. They are in the
Blue River zoo right now.
It's a small zoo, but
a very nice one, Candy.
Then, next time we're allowed out
I'll come to visit you.
I'll be waiting. However
meeting you in this place...
That's right, this is London
not America...
If I hadn't snuck out to buy medicine...
-I have to buy medicine!
-Medicine?
Is there a pharmacy somewhere near?
My friend was hurt
and it's an emergency!
Hurt? There was one guy
who was beaten up tonight...
Anyway, how is he doing?
Not too well.
I'd better buy the medicine and
hurry back!
I see. I know of a pharmacy
let's go there.
Okay!
I fell asleep.
Looks like the bleeding stopped.
She bound my leg so tightly.
That nosy freckled Tarzan girl.
If I'm already this well,
I guess I can walk, too.
Farewell, Candy!
Say, Clint, are you lonely now that
you're at St. Paul academy?
Want to come to my zoo?
Clint is doing well on his own!
Is that so? I'm glad to hear that.
Mr. Albert, I want to talk to you more
but...
You'd better hurry with the medicine.
I'll come to see you
during the holidays!
I'll be waiting for you, Candy.
Now, Candy!
Thank you, Mr. Albert.
-Mr. Albert, goodbye!
-Goodbye, Candy!
Good night, Candy!
Terry?
He's ... He's gone.
I tried so hard to buy medicine for him,
but he ran away.
He even left without thanking me...
I finally met Mr. Albert
but I was in such a hurry to get back
that I didn't speak properly to him!
Terry, you're such a pain in the ass!
Why did I cast pearls
before a swine like you!
Candy? What are you doing in there?
Candy?
You're asleep?
I see, she talks in sleep.
Candice.
If you're pretending that you're asleep
at least take your shoes off.
Caught me.
But I'm lucky it wasn't sister Gray.
And that Terry...
His actions are really...
But thanks to him, I got the chance
to meet Mr. Albert.
If he was able to move, I guess
I don't have to worry about his wounds.
Terry.
I haven't seen him in the hall.
Terry is nowhere to be found.
And there are no rumours of
anyone being hurt.
I don't believe he had no reason
to come to my room.
Say, Annie...
what kind of sports were you into?
While you were in Pony's home?
Weren't you in some sports club?
But I'm not really good...
-You can't tell unless you try!
-But...
Eliza. She is pestering Annie
because she isn't good at sports.
Archery sounds good for you.
That's right, give it a try, Annie!
If you want to join a club, we'll
inform you about the procedures.
-Annie!
-Candy!
She gets along better with the girl
from Pony's home than with us.
We don't deal with such nasties.
Say, Louise, when you said nasties
you meant us?
Yes, that's right.
I see, I'm so glad!
Don't join our club then!
We'd rather be nasty than disgusting!
Don't you think that, Louise?
Thank you.
I don't want you to worry about
Eliza and the others!
I don't mind being called
"girl from Pony's home" anymore!
I don't have to hide it anymore!
That's the spirit, Annie!
Candy, Archie and Stear invite you
to the boys' lab during the recess.
Archie and Stear?
I wonder what is this about...
Who knows... They only wanted me to
transfer the message to you.
Annie, it'll go just fine!
With Archie!
Candy, you...
The coast is clear!
-Hi, Candy, Annie.
-Hurry!
Well now, everyone...
I'd like to present you
my newest invetion!
What did you invent?
Well now.
You'll see something nice!
It's a flying carrier boat!
What's that flying carrier-boat thing?
Press the button on the device
atop the table!
This?
It's flying!
Incredible, isn't it?
If you put a letter inside...
it can take it from the window
of one room to another!
It's pretty!
You're great, Stear!
Because it's so quiet...
you'll be able to send messages
to that nobleman without worry!
Nobleman?
Come to think of it...
what happened to Terry after
he got beaten up the other day?
I heard about this today.
But only that his leg was hurt.
If he was wounded
maybe he went home?
I'm glad. He'll be okay.
Aaah - - Candy!
Oh, no!
The boat is in pieces!
I... I'm sorry.
I did something bad to Stear.
And that Terry guy...
I wish he would come back to see me.
Seeing a girl lying in grass
is such a nice sight.
Terry!
You've recovered so quickly!
I'm glad!
You don't need to worry about me.
Freckled Tarzan.
You're so stubborn
I'm Candy! I went out the other day
to buy medicine for you...
Why, you break the rules too!
You went out without permission.
I'm not kidding...
how can you say that!
I did that for your sake!
You're going to ask something
in return for your favor?
It's ...
such a frigtening expression.
So cold.
I'm not going to ask anything in return!
Not even if you beg me to!
Farewell!
What a piece of work he is!
Why is he so fickle?
Well then, everyone...
let's show our gratitude to our Lord
by offering a prayer.
It's even in the soup...
the reflection of his hateful face.
I thought that
there was a gentle side to him.
He drinks and gets into fights...
I have no idea
what's going through his mind.
I've never met someone
that strange before!
Anyway
I won't bother with him anymore.
If I happen upon him
I'll pretend we're strangers.
Amen.
Yeah, sunglasses... You'll find him
in that shack over there
He's on a break now.
Thank you.
So that's his office?
I thought it would've looked
much better.
Mr. Albert?
Come in!
Boo, Mr. Albert!
Te-Terry!
Candy!
What, you two know each other?
Yes... we go to the same school.
I love this! Two troublemakers of
St. Paul academy gathered here!
Troublemakers?
I love this! Two troublemakers of
St. Paul academy gathered here!
Troublemakers?
Candy is being her normal self.
You drank too much the other day
and picked a fight.
That means...
the man who helped Terry was...
Yeah. If he didn't come to my help...
I would've fared much worse.
It's just that...
Just... what?
You mistook the girls' ward
for boys' ward.
And then you barged into my room.
So that was girls' ward?
Candy told me someone was hurt
I ran together with her
to buy medicine for you.
I'm sorry.
But you saved Terry, Mr. Albert!
You must be tough!
Nah, I just have more experience
in fighting!
That means, you used to be a
troublemaker as well?
I still am!
Perhaps I'll stay that way forever!
Me too!
Terry is laughing.
Light from the window reflects
so beautifully in his gentle smile.
I'm so glad!
But... I swore to God that
I'd forget everything about Terry.
And yet...
Without really knowing the reason,
Terry came to stay in her thoughts.