Gangster Charlie has
entered Candy's life.
And after leaving his last flower
with gratitude.
He left the hospital.
The ghost of cards
Sister Pony, sister Lane
It has been a long time,
how is everything?
I am on my night duty,
just writing to you guys while I can.
There is no one in the hospital,
it is so quiet.
I am by myself in the room.
I can't even see a rat.
Who?
Who is there?
Who is it?
Someone there?
You are...
You don't look very good.
That was scaring!
Are you the only one
who is on night shift?
Are you from this hospital?
I am a patient
from the internal department,
I came to take a walk.
I see,
no wonder I don't recognise you.
Nurses there wouldn't talk to me,
I was so bored.
That's amazing!
I am Tony.
I am Candy.
Candy, we should play a game
since it is our first meeting.
No, I am working.
You were writing.
You saw?
Come on, Hold'em.
-Just one game
-Right
Three of a kind.
Full house.
Lose again!
I will win this time.
You should surrender.
I will win.
Four of a kind.
Straight Flush.
Again
Shoot! it is time check the rooms.
Hey. it is going to be 15 cents.
Are we playing cash?
It gets pretty relistic
when it comes to gambling.
I have no money.
You don't have to pay now.
Candy, surgical department,
15 cents.
Thanks, see you!
Tony?
He didn't look sick,
I wonder what is wrong with him?
Not this room.
I never seen you before,
which department you from?
I am a trainee nurse
from surgical department.
This is internal medicine.
I would like to ask you for a favor.
Why would a nurse
from surgical department...
want to know about an
internal medicine's patient?
I am looking for a boy called Tony.
Tony?
He is around ten years old.
I can check by myself
if you are busy.
You don't trust me?
No.
I got it.
Tony yeah?
He died of lung diease last month.
Died?
What happened to this boy?
Tony passed away one month ago.
It can't be,
was I playing with a ghost?
Candy
I think this is yours.
Where did you find this?
Common room, under the table
No card game
when you are working, Candy.
Natalie
Were you on night shift
two days ago?
Yes
Anything unusual happened?
No.
Thanks
You look bad, what is wrong?
Nothing.
Yeah?
Blanny is on night shift tonight,
I am worried.
I shall sleep
with the light opened tonight.
Blanny?
Natalie?
It is me.
Tony!
Open the door!
Wait!
How did you know my room?
I know everything
about this hospital.
Here, Hold'em
Tony
I went to the internal medicine
this morning.
What did the nurse say?
There was no patient called Tony
Looks like I am exposed,
as a ghost.
Stop playing around.
I am not afraid of ghost.
Play some card game with the ghost.
Your room-mate
won't be back until morning.
You owe me 95 cents altogether.
I surrender.
You are the winner.
See you next time,
practice hard.
Good night!
Did he just disappear?
Who is there?
Shoot!
-Come down!
-Yes.
Why are you on the tree
in the middle of the night?
To investigate about the ghost.
Listen!
The nurse from internal medicine
told me.
Can't we just go to the wards?
You went straight-away to internal
medicine and checked patients'profiles.
That is ridiculous!
Watch yourself!
Yes.
They could be more flexible,
we are colleagues.
Please take care of my son.
He should come to the hospital
earlier.
Tony has been enduring the pain,
That's why we didn't notice that
the situation got worse.
Tony?
Sorry.
The boy who passed away
one month ago?
Do you know Tony Renne?
Yes, he is very good with cards.
Nonsense!
Tony is a smart student.
Still as a painting.
I have said something inappropriate.
Who exactly is Tony?
Candy!
I am waiting for you, Tony.
Don't try to scare me.
Tonight I will
find out Tony's true identity.
I don't thnik so.
No.
Is Tony your real name?
Of course!
Tony Charles.
The surname is different from
that boy who passed away.
Come, Hold'em
I know you are not a ghost.
And you are not a patient
from this hospital neither.
Candy...
I will call the security
if you don't tell the truth.
Alright!
Why do you come to hospital
with your pajamas?
I won't get suspicious
by wearing pajamas.
Smart ass.
You don't just come here
to play cards, do you?
Right.
Wandering out at this time...
Your family
is going to worry about you?
Mom has to work at night.
I was bored, so
I came to the hospital...
Just to play cards?
Enough?
Candy
Where do you live?
Someone is coming!
Hide, Tony
Doctor Popson.
Candy,
I have got some cakes here,
come over for a cup of tea.
Ok, thanks.
You play cards?
Intersting.
Since we are not busy tonight,
we shall play cards.
I...
Huh?
Lets go.
-What is wrong?
-Nothing
Lets go.
Weird, shouldn't it be here?
Got it!
These cards are old.
Yeah
Do nurses always play cards?
No, we use cards for fortune-telling
when we are bored.
I see.
Candy, how many cards do you want?
Two, please.
That's it for me.
Pharmacy, got it!
Tony?
I am in Jackson's house
right downstairs.
You are disturbing others
at such hours
Tony, that bottle...
Medicine for your heart.
It is from Mr.Jackson's
nurse friend.
Such expensive medicine?
Tony you...
She gave it to us.
What is the name of the nurse?
Candy, with a lot of freckles
on the face.
Which hospital?
St.Joanna hospital.
Candy from St.Joanna hospital?
She is a good person.
To give me such expensive medicine...
Mom, you won't have to go to the
hospital if you take these medicine.
I must thank her after I recovered.
That nurse called Candy.
Did you open the medicine cabinet
when you were on your night shift?
No
But some medicine is missing.
There is no sign of breaking here,
I think the cabinet was opened
by a spare key.
Spare key?
These medicine are very strong
Very strong?
More than 0.6 grams will be fatal.
Could it be Tony?
Any suspicious person?
Yes.
Mom, I got some milk and eggs.
Fell asleep?
The medicine from the hospital
is working.
When you were on your night shift...
how can you let someone out there
to enter the hospital?
I believe he didn't steal that
strong medicine on purpose
Maybe he took the wrong medicine.
If the medicine is taken
without knowing the consequences...
We should find the boy immediately.
But we don't have any clues.
Just these cards.
Is there any name or address
on it?
No, I...
Candy is trying to say that...
maybe someone might recognise this.
I will go ask around.
It has been quite a while
since mom had such a good sleep.
She doesn't seem to be in pain
as usual.
No one recognise this these cards.
We will have to look house by house.
Cany, these cards...
Does it ring any bell to you?
That belongs to Tony.
You know Tony?
His mother used to stay
in this hospital.
His mother?
She seemed to have heart disease.
Heart?
Tony took the wrong medicine.
Why didn't you eat?
It is so wasteful.
How are you going to recover
if you don't take the medicine?
-Come!
-Thanks.
I guess this is enough.
Here.
Thanks.
You don't need to thank me
I was thanking Miss.Candy
Hey! Here.
Mom.
This medicine...
Mom! Spit it out!
Tony!
-Candy
-lets take mom to hospital.
Doctor...
We made it in time
It is alright now, Tony.
Is mom alright?
Tony come to my room.
Lets play one game, if you win...
I will pay for your mom's so that
she can stay in the hospital.
Doctor Popson!
But...
I can't afford the medical fees,
It is better to discuss with
doctors and nurses.
I can't allow your mom
to leave the hospital.
Mom does not want to
cause any inconvenience.
Candy
Do you want to be a nurse for money?
No.
The same for me.
Do you understand? Tony
Yes!
Money does not seperate patients.
Life is precious.
We discriminate anyone.
We treat everybody equal.
I think so.
Three of a kind.
Full house.
I am no different from Candy
Tony's mother didn't have money
to receive medical treatment.
Candy was surprised.
But...
The kindness that Doctor Popson
treated his patients with,
Makes Candy even more grateful.
She has decided...
To give more care and love
to every patients.