Candy served as doctor's assistant.
She decided to become a nurse.
The headmaster of the nursing school
happened to be sister Pony's old friend.
The recommendation will be replied
in spring.
The whistle of the new journey.
Sister Pony,
when will the school give me the reply?
It might be sent out already,
just wait for the good news.
It's not easy to make my decision.
I can 't wait to be there.
Don't be so haste, Candy.
Even the school promised,
there still have other problems.
Why?
They won 't accept you without vacancy.
Sister Pony, what should I do...
Don't worry,
we 'll get something by then.
Sister Pony, The children are gone.
How come?
They might be somewhere
playing something.
No, it's not like playing games.
Where are they?
I'll find them.
You guys, where are you? Answer me!
Kurin, come out.
Kurin is with them.
Kurin!
It's not here, where are they?
They're In the forest.
Keep on, John.
Do you best, higher!
Keep on, John!
Everybody's supporting you.
What are you doing here?
Candy boss!
Why did John climb the tree?
It's a test.
To become my inheritor.
Jimmy's inheritor?
The leader after Candy boss.
I will become
Mr. Cratwright's inheritor.
John hopes to inherit my position.
John?
He is now doing the test.
Don 't you think it's too high for him?
It's John 's idea, he needs to
prove his ability to everyone.
I'm here at last!
Look!
I am the leader next to Candy boss.
That's great!
Don 't call me sister anymore.
We won 't do that.
John is Jimmy's inheritor,
I'm the leader next to Candy boss.
Great!
The new leader seems not bad.
Congratulations! John.
You passed the test.
Thank you! Big boss.
I am now the big boss?
That would be fine.
I am now leaving for the pasture.
Jimmy boss!
You 're the boss, aren 't you?
That's right!
Look! everyone,
do as the new boss said.
-Yes!
-Good bye, Candy boss.
Look after Mr. Cartwright carefully.
Leave it to me!
Good bye!
Jimmy is a good inheritor's for sure!
Come! Let's go back.
It's Mr. Matthew!
Hello! Candy!
Mr. Matthew!
Mr. Matthew,
are there letters for sister Pony?
-Here!
-That's great!
-But, Candy...
-Merry Jane nursing school.
We got it!
The headmaster is very fond of you.
Fond of me?
That you wish to become a nurse.
Candy's going to be a nurse?
Mr. Matthew!
I...
Sister Pony, The Nurse School...
Okay!
That's great!
That's great! Candy.
Thank you, sister Pony, sister Lane.
Candy boss wants to be a nurse?
She is leaving us again.
We will be lonely again.
Everybody, over here!
Have you forgotten?
I am the leader,
you should do as I said.
Sister Lane,
Candy felt so happy about this letter.
Must be a good news.
Of course, Mr. Matthew.
That's great!
Everybody,
It's Candy boss 's wish to be a nurse.
We should agree with her.
We maybe lonely without boss, but...
We should think for her!
Please!
Excuse me.
What's the matter? Candy.
Sister Pony, sister Lane,
I'm leaving tomorrow morning.
Tomorrow?
What's so urgent?
I hate to say goodbye to everyone,
I'd like to leave quietly.
Jimmy had follow me stealthily
before.
What should we do? Sister Pony.
Let's leave this to Candy.
From now on,
you have to decide everything.
Thanks!
I'm leaving again.
It's different this time,
It's my own idea.
It's my own journey,
you will be happy for that, right?
Kurin.
Kurin,
I can't take you with me this time.
It is different from St. Paul academy.
I'm going to learn about
how to look after the patients.
That's why I can 't take you with me.
You looked so dirty,
People will disagree with that.
I'm leaving tomorrow morning.
You must not follow me, understand?
Can you really understand that?
I should tell Jimmy about this, But...
What should I do?
if he refuses to become the inheritor...
I should go quietly.
Give me the soap.
Kurin took the soap...
Wait! Kurin.
My God!
What happened?
What's the matter?
Why you do that?
Kurin took the soap away.
Kurin took the soap?
Why did Kurin do such thing?
Could it be...
Kurin, if you do that again,
I'll drove you out of here,
There 's no other way,
Let's leave here together.
It must be for this...
I'll find it.
Here you are!
Kurin,
I can't take you with me this time.
You looked so dirty,
People will disagree with that.
Kurin knew that.
Taking a bath, leave with me tomorrow.
Kurin.
Kurin, you do understand what I said.
But, I can't take you with me.
It's better for you
to live in the nature.
Sorry! I have to tie you up.
Kurin!
Kurin, don't you worry!
Wait!
Kurin, wait!
Kurin!
kurin!
Kurin, where are you?
Come out! Kurin, where are you?
Answer me!
I am too rash,
I should talk to him with patience.
Kurin will understand that for sure.
I am sorry, Kurin.
It's hiding somewhere nearby.
Waiting for the moment when I'm leaving.
Kurin, where are you?
Kurin, It is you.
Are you hungry?
Here! Have some fresh milk.
Take it.
You looked so hungry.
What's the matter?
Did you make Candy boss angry?
Kurin has not come back yet.
But, I must go now!
It's your own direction, don 't Hesitate!
Yes!
Wish you to become a nurse
as soon as possible.
I will do my best
Go now, Candy!
The children are still in bed.
We will not see you off.
-Sister Pony.
-Candy!
Take care of yourself.
Sister Pony.
Sister Lane.
Candy!
Go now!
You...
You knew that?
Candy boss acted strange last night.
We get up early on purpose.
Is that so?
Don 't worry!
We won 't stop you, right?
We feel happy for you!
We worry too much.
-Really!
-In return...
Can we see off Candy to the station?
Of course!
Here we are, Kurin, the Pony's home.
Good morning!
Jimmy, Kurin.
Boss, will you leave again?
That's right!
I want to become a nurse.
So, you want to leave again...
Jimmy, will you tail me again?
I won 't do that. though I felt lonely.
I am Mr. Cartwright's inheritor.
I can 't break the promise.
What a competent inheritor you are!
The problem is...
This guy?
Come over!
Here, boss!
Kurin, forgive me, please!
I hate to separate with you.
We have been together.
I really can't take you with me
this time.
You must stay at home obediently,
so that...
I can work without worry.
Can you understand that? Kurin.
Everybody, get on the carriage.
Sister Pony, sister Lane.
We 're coming.
-Get on, boss!
-Thanks Jimmy!
Let's go!
The train is coming.
Well done, John!
I can leave without worry now.
Look out! Step back!
Good bye, Candy!
Take care of yourself.
Sister Pony, sister Lane, guys,
takes care of yourself.
Candy boss, long live!
Candy boss!
Kurin!
No, Kurin!
Take care of yourself.
Be careful.
Don't give up, Candy.
Boss, I'll take care of Kurin.
Thank you, Jimmy, please!
Boss, do your best!
Good bye, Everyone!
Good bye, Teacher!
Candy boss!
Kurin!
Kurin, no, go back!
Kurin, Everyone, Good bye!
Candy gets on the train...
Starting the journey of nurse.