Who is Albert?
Why do you call me that name?
Mr.Albert lost his memory.
I will have to wait until
Mr.Albert remembers everything.
Candy told herslef.
Two people's trial.
Good morning, Mr.Albert.
What is wrong? Mr.Albert.
I don't know.
I can't remember anything.
What is my real name?
Who am I?
Mr.Albert, take a rest.
Mr.Albert?
Isn't that your brother's name?
Sorry.
I didn't mean it.
Don't force yourself
to remember anything.
You will remember about
the past naturally.
Thank you, Miss Candy.
Just call me Candy.
Right, Candy.
Did you take your morning pills?
I have some dessert for you.
That's plenty.
Eating gives you more strength
right?
Thank you, Candy.
Do you want to eat now?
Maybe later, I am tired.
Have a good rest then.
Ok.
Poopet, be quiet.
Poor Mr.Albert.
I will help you
to remember everything.
Yeah.
I should let him meet Terry.
Terry and Mr.Albert are good friends.
Maybe that will help.
Terry.
Anyone seen Terry?
He already left.
Yeah?
He is a typical loner.
Lives in expensive hotel,
Has so much money.
He seems to be planning something?
Not sure what he is busy with?
Return ticket and accomodation.
All done.
Come in.
May I?
Hello,
it's regarding something urgent.
Sorry to disturb you.
Come,
I bought a cake on the way.
It omes with the flower.
How did you find me?
The troupe manager told me.
I thought your room
would be a mess.
But it turned out so clean.
Speak,
didn't you say it's urgent.?
Aren't you going to
get me a cup of tea?
I am sorry, I don't have
anything here for rich miss
What is so urgent?
The next show is decided.
Romeo and Juliet.
An audition will be held soon.
Audition?
You going to come,
right? Terry.
Sure.
Me too.
You will be Romeo,
I will be Juliet.
It's going to be so wonderful
if this works out.
We will start practicing tonight.
Terry, where are you going?
I will go ask about the audition.
Terry, I go with you.
Terry
Terry, you are such a loner.
Romeo and Juliet.
If I could play the role as Romeo,
Candy would come to Broadway
to see me.
That would be great.
The May Festival of
St.Paul Instituition.
The Romeo and Juliet
in my memory.
Candy danced gracefuuly.
And her beautiful dress.
It was like one year ago.
-Misss Candy
-Yes
Your letter.
Letter?
It's from Terry.
I am preparing for
next show's audition.
If I get to play this role.
I will invite you to Broadway.
Terry.
You need to work hard
so that you could apply for leave.
Freckled angel.
That's not funny.
But, Terry wants to
invite me to Broadway
I wish I could be there right away.
Misss Candy,
Is climbing tree a course for nurse?
Vice principal Reknap.
Does Merry Jane Nurse School
teach tree climbing?
No, this is my hobby.
I need to talk to you,
come down quick.
The patient in ward number three...
I have already swapped with the
nurse in charge of ward number zero.
What? How could you do that
without permission?
I know that patient and
I wanted to take care of him.
Candy, are you a real nurse?
Only real nurse can take charge
of ward number zero.
Even if you knew that patient,
I can't leave the patient
to a trainee.
Please ask someone
who is qualified to look after him.
We need to follow the rules.
Mr.Albert needs someone
specialised to look after him.
Candy, since you insist,
I hope you can pass the
nurse qualification test this month.
Once you become a real nurse,
You can take charge of
ward number zero.
But I assume it would be
hard for you wouldn't it.
You are just an amateur.
Violation of the hospital regulations
is not allowed.
Amateur?
How could he say that.
But
I have forgot all about the test.
I came here
to be a real nurse.
Wake up! Candy.
Everything will be in vain if
I don't pass the test.
I have to pass the test.
Lung is consisted of
bronchia and alveolus.
Bronchia delivers oxygen
to alveolus.
Alveolus deals with the
exchange of oxygen.
Good morning Mr.Albert.
How do you feel?
I have been quite busy lately.
I am soory that
I can't look after you just I did.
That's alright.
Here, your favourite chestnut.
Mr.Albert doesn't seem
to be recovering.
Mr.Albert,
just hold on for a few more days.
After I passed my test.
I will be taking care of you.
I don't seem to be quite
welcomed in this hospital.
Why?
We treat every patients the same.
No bias.
No, Candy.
I am grateful that
you have been good to me.
Don't say that Mr.Albert.
I used to stay in
Italy's substandard hospital.
I lost me memory and unidentified,
Never going to get any respect.
You will remember everything
when you recovered.
You just have to
take good care of yourself.
It's better that you stay away from
a hopeless patient.
Even if I die here.
Mr.Albert.
Mr.Albert just won't rally himself
no matter what I do.
Mr.Albert used to be
such a bright man.
Now...
See you later.
I must help him to recover.
In order to look after him,
I have to pass the test.
Only I can save Mr.Albert now.
Terry,
good luck for the audition.
I will work hard for the
nurse qualification test as well.
Adjust the light.
-Is this alright?
-More.
Aren't you Misss Eleanor Baker?
Please don't tell anyone.
I know.
Did your son know you are here?
No, I didn't tell Terry.
Come here, all of you.
Ok!
The audition for Romeo and Juliet
starts from now.
Listen,
I hope all of you try your best.
Everyone, good luck.
Firstly, we have Harry Grant
as Romeo.
Yes.
Suzanna Marlu as Juliet.
Shouldn't it be Terry?
If Terry was here,
I would be doing much better.
Stop complaining, Suzanna.
Yes, I know.
Right, starts.
People who never get hurt,
Will dig into others'scars
in their hearts.
Wait,
Why is there light
dimming from the window?
That's the East.
Juliet is the sun.
Rise, the beautiful sun.
And lights up the dark night.
You are the slave of the moon.
Even so,
you are more beautiful than the moon.
I must get this role.
And invite Candy over.
No, I need to stay focus.
I should memorised the lines.
Romeo,
Why are you Romeo?
Please end everyting with your father,
and discard your surname.
Or,
Please swear to God that you love me.
I will leave my home
if you are willing to do that.
Next.
You guys are too nervous, relax.
Romeo,
Terrius. G. Glanchester.
Yes.
Juliet, Karen Clairs.
You can do it, Terry.
He looks so serious.
I wonder how is Terry's audition going?
Candy,
What are you thinking? Candy.
Nothing.
How's it going?
You have any confidence?
Not until I have tried.
Right.
It's lucky to have the test
in the hospital.
I won't get too nervous.
Actually I am nervous.
My legs are shaking.
The test starts now.
At last.
Pass down the papers.
I must pass this test.
For Mr.Albert.
I hope I could accept
Terry's invitation as a real nurse.
Why are you here?
The stone wall is so high,
I had a hard time getting up here.
You will get yourself killed
if you are seen by anyone.
The wings of love will help me
to overcome this stone wall.
Even iron wall
can't stop my love.
The fire of passion and love
in my heart will never go off.
How is your family going to stop
such man like me?
You still going to get yourself killed
if someone sees you.
I am talking about an assault
by ten or twenty people.
Your suspicious eyes
discourages me.
Please protect me
with your gentle eyes.
Despite the numbers of enemies,
I will stand firm for you.
But...
I hope you will hide somewhere
that nobody can find you.
Fortunately,
I am protected by the darkness.
No one will see me.
If you don't love me,
Please tell them I am here.
It's meaningless to live
if I can't have your love.
I would rather die.
Who helped you to get here?
The power of love.
It helps me to search, it saves me
and it gives me wisdom.
It's all about the power of love.
I am a seedling
whcih absorbs the power of love.
Candy is in Chicago,
Terry is in New York.
Two of them seperated
in two places.
They are facing different challenges
for their own lives.