There is no one in the audience
stands on third floor
Candy is comfortably enjoying Terry's
performance.
Terry left the banquet.
Searching for Candy
on the dark streets.
An unexpected reunion.
Terry, where are you going?
Terry
He went looking for Candy.
Candy
Who is Candy?
Terry,
is Candy the one in your heart?
Candy
Can...
Sorry
What is the probelm
Candy is in this town
I really heard she yelling...
Terry wait
Terry
I am sure it was Candy
How stupid
Why didn't I see her?
Archie
Terry
Where is Candy?
We are looking for her as well
She didn't come to the banquet
Where does she live?
Pony's home? The Adley's?
Terry, watch your attitude?
Archie, stop
Annie, do you know?
Candy...
Always wanted to see you
So, where is Candy?
St. John hospital, nurse hostel.
Nurse?
Candy is a nurse trainee in St. John hospital.
St. John hospital...
How rude
He lost his temper
What are you doing? Lets go
I am not taking you
What?
I don't take people who don't respect ladies
I am going to St. John hospital
Hospital?
I am in a rush to meet someone
You could have told me earlier, we are moving
Is that someone alright?
the person you are going to see
No problem.
My cart is the fastest in Chicago.
Here we are.
Emergency is over there
Sir, don't give up
Goodbye
Thank you
It looks like we are in the St. Paul Academy
Emergency?
No, I am looking for a nurse
At this time?
I won't take too long, please
I don't think so, come tomorrow
I am leaving tomorrow
You are looking for...
Candy, no, Candy Adley
Candy?
Natalie, why are you here?
Blanny
Isn't Candy here today?
Em...
He is not a patient is he?
This gentleman...
I am looking for Candy
Look, Candy is not here
She seemed to swap shift with someone else
Swap shift...
Isn't she back yet?
What do you think
Can i wait for her here?
Please leave
Blanny
It is quite late now
How can he stay here if he is not a patient?
I won't cause you any problem
You are a problem if you stay here
Please
I will call security if you don't leave
Go ahead, I am sure they will understand
Candy is going to lose her job
because of this
You...
There is only one way out in this hospital
Natalie, knock it off
Please leave
Candy
You swap you shift just to watch my peformance
Who is that lady with the glasses?
Looks so young
but talk like a old granny
Lets wait, there is only one way out
Trainee nurse...
It suits her
In London...
If I was mature enough
I would take you with me and left the school.
Two of us will live together
I will be more and more matured.
Candy
Terry where are you?
Where can I see you?
I can't go on
wandering on the street like this
I can't
I can't go on like this, come on! Candy
Lets go back to the hospital.
Last yell
Terry, you fool.
why didn't you hear me?
Suzanna Marlu
So beautiful, so elegant.
If only I could be more gentle
Did't you know what is going on
between Suzanna and Terry?
Terry has forgot about you.
That is not true
I will not believe it unless Terry
tells me himslef
I won't listen to remour.
Where exactly is Terry?
Hotel
He is leaving tomorrow and
he is going to stay in the hotel tonight.
Why didn't I come to that?
If that was the case
I could have found out which
hotel they were staying?
This is the last hotel
I am sorry to bother at this time...
Suzanna Marlu
She looks so pretty in person.
Yes?
My name is Candy
Candy! It is her!
I am here to see someone
Terry, no I am looking for
Mr. Terry.
Not tonight I am afraid.
He has fell asleep because he is very tired.
But...
He reminded us not
to disturb him sleeping
Him?
Would you come another day?
Please let him rest
Right,
I should let Terry take his rest.
I am sorry
I can't do anything for you
I am so sorry to disturb you at this time,
I will leave now.
Excuse me... Do you want me to pass any message?
Something to encourage him
Encourage? Please tell Terry...
Tonight's show was really great.
I hope he can become an excellent actor.
Don't blame me, Terry
You left me behind to look for her
I am sorry Candy
I like Terry too...
In the end, I still didn't get to see Candy
Candy I left a message for you
at the hospital's entrance
Come to see me
Goodnight
No, I guess good morning
How could you!
I can't believe you came back at this time
Sorry, I didn't want to do this...
Candy, do you respect your job as a nurse?
Please forgive me this time
If anybody knows
about this
You will be fired
I didn't...
The supervisor has came to check, Candy
Really?
I said you were sick.
You went back to take a rest.
Thank you Blanny
Don't take this wrong, I am not helping you
To have a student like you
in Merry Jane Nursing Institution
is a shame
From now onwards,
I won't cause any troubles.
Of course!
I need to get dressed at once
to make up what I have done.
Thank you
I guess Candy has seen my message
We might meet anytime.
He is still thinking about Candy
I find it so hard to say
anything about last night
Terry have you finished eating?
I would like to take a nap before we set off
Terry didn't sleep all night
Must because of Candy
It hurts
Don't cry
It is alright, I will make a face for you
It is not hurting anymore is it
That is it
Candy, time for break
Right
Don't do anything stupid again
It is so tired to stay awake overnight
You must be Candy
Yes
Have you see the message?
What message?
A boy came to look for you
when it was dawning
Terry?
He left a message,
I have attached it on the door
On the door?
I didn't see it
Yes
Candy I didn't to see you
at the hospital's entrance.
Are you really in Chicago?
I am taking the train at 12 o'clock
Miss you so much, Terry.
Terry
It is half to 12,
we need to hurry
Sorry, please
Sorry
Please take me to the station
I beg you...
Sorry, could you let me take this cart?
Young lady, you need to follow the rules
You are a nurse?
Yes, I beg you
Chicago Station
Alright, since nurses take care of patients
You have it
Thank you
Lets go
Can you get there before 12 O'clock?
My cart can't fly
Can you do it?
I will try
Please. I am in such as hurry to meet someone
Terry must be looking for me, dodge.
Terry, I came to see you off.
Thank you.
I will see you in Broadway! Wait for me alright
What happened to Candy? Did she see the message?
Terry, it is time
You are still waiting Terry
Terry
No! Candy does not show up yet
Quick
This is not the way to the station
I can't get to the station in time
Terry
Terry, it is dangerous out there
Do you want to get on the cart?
Candy
Terry
You haven't changed at all, Candy
Just like I thought
You look very nice in this dress Candy
Terry
Candy is in Chicago,
she is in America just like I am.
We not longer longing for each other
with endless sea between us
Terry
Candy
Everything is so familiar
In a split second
Just that moment of reunion
Terry and Candy
Seemed to attach each other
with the deepest love.