Candy realized that taking care
of children is hard work.
She realized that she ought to study
more and become a good person.
Thus, Candy went on a journey across
the ocean to study in London.
Love transcends raging waves.
The trip to England has extended
for many days already.
What's the matter, Kurin?
Something happened?
A seagull fell onto the deck.
Kurin, so that's why you called me?
Poor thing, you are hurt...
Is there a doctor among you?
I'm a doctor.
Please, take a look at this seagull!
I'm not a vet!
I'm a doctor for people!
But...
don't you know how to treat birds?
It's a living creature, as well!
Are you making fun of me?
I'm insulted!
Miss Candy
let's head back to the cabin.
But...
There is a first aid kit in the room.
Now, let's go.
I've applied this medicine,
so you'll be okay.
You'll have to rest after this.
But how come you injured yourself?
Maybe it was attracted by a
reflection from the window.
It flew towards the window
and struck the glass.
You must have been in pain.
But I'll make sure you'll be
able to fly again.
Come in.
Excuse me, Miss Candice White
the captain
would like to see you.
Captain?
wants to see me?
Come in!
I'm Candice White Ardley.
But you can call me Candy.
I'm captain Wells.
I hope you're not mad
for calling you out of the cabin.
I'm not!
First of all
I'd like to express my gratitude.
Thank you.
You gave my last journey
something to remember it by.
Last journey?
That's right. I am going to retire
after this journey.
I will fill in the last page
of the ship's diary...
with the story of a kind young
girl who saved a seagull.
And how is your seagull doing?
-It's good.
-I'm glad to hear that.
Now the only thing left is praying
that we safely finish our journey.
Uh, Captain Wells... what are you
going to do after you retire?
I'll take the severance and
settle somewhere near the sea.
-Captain!
-What's the matter?
-We've received a SOS call!
-What?
Tidal wave overturned
a small fishing boat!
Which ship is closest to them?
This one.
We can't just leave them.
I'll command the rescue operations.
So we'll run a day late because the ship
will detour on a rescue operation?
Stear and Archie
will probably be very worried.
Stear and Archie are waiting for us?
No! You can't do that!
You can't detour the ship.
You can't do this on your own accord
Captain.
Your job is to get this ship to
England in time.
But... since we received a SOS...
Some other rescue ship
will pick them up.
Besides,
there are other reasons for this.
Come with me.
They're here!
Come in!
Excuse me!
My name is Stafford.
Wouldn't it be a problem for you
if you didn't get to England in time?
I'm only a subordinate of Miss Candy.
So you're in charge, right?
Miss Candy, this is one of the
richest men in the world
Mr. Stafford.
What do you think, Miss?
You'd like to arrive
as soon as possible, right?
Yes, but...
I'd rather leave everything
to Captain Wells.
I invested a lot into this venture.
If we run late,
I'm going to lose a lot of money!
Unfortunately, I know that lost
human lives can't be recovered.
We'll come to their rescue.
Wait!
Are you going to disregard
my orders, captain Wells?
I can have you fired!
Fired?
If I fire you, you and your
career will be done for!
You'll have a hard time
making a living after this!
Are you fine with that?
I am.
Damn it, I'll show you!
We're commencing a rescue operation!
Change course to north-east!
Captain Wells?
Oh, Candy.
The one who enabled you to do this
is right here, I guess.
That's correct.
Do you think I'll let you do this?
I'll show you my power!
Excuse me!
Did you need something
Mr. Stafford?
Send this telegram. It's urgent.
As you wish.
That's right!
The view from up here is excellent!
Yes... but Captain
you said that you wanted
your last journey to pass uneventfully.
That's right. But just look how
hectic it's become now!
But... I think you should get a medal
for carrying out this rescue operation.
You too, for saving that seagull.
Captain!
This message just came in
from headquarters!
What does it say?
No need to detour to the accident site.
Return immediately.
Mr. Stafford is the largest shareholder.
You are to follow his orders.
Mr. Stafford must have informed
the headquarters.
What will you do?
They'll fire me if I
don't follow their orders, eh?
Same course, full speed ahead!
-Miss Candice.
-George.
Captain Wells is going on a rescue
mission which will get him fired.
-He's a great man.
-Yes.
But I wonder what will happen to him
after he gets fired.
Because he disregarded orders
given to him
he probably won't get his severance pay.
The punishment will be that bad?
Yes.
He didn't follow orders from
the headquarters.
In that case, the only thing he left
will be the diary full of memories!
They will probably confiscate
the diary and fire him.
That's horrible!
He's doing a good thing, isn't he?
I won't let that happen!
Miss Candy!
-Mr. Stafford!
-What is it?
Having Captain fired is unfair!
If he doesn't want that to happen;
he'd better get this ship
to England in time.
It's his obligation
to all the passengers.
It's so bright!
I think we've changed course...
Maybe...?
It's okay. We're going directly
towards them.
I wonder will those people be okay.
30 degrees to starboard!
Engines full speed ahead!
-Take a look.
-Yes.
-There they are!
-Where?
Over there!
We got them!
Commence the operation!
A ship!
-They are waving to us!
-Lower the boat!
Be careful! If you get overturned
you're done for!
Hold on tightly!
Alright. It's okay now.
Thank you!
-Is everyone okay?
-Thank you!
Good. Very good.
Captain Wells is crying.
He's moved to the point of crying.
Everyone, thank you for your
cooperation.
We successfully saved all fishermen.
Yes, come in!
Captain Wells.
It's because I'll be dismissed
as soon as we get to England.
I'm packing up while I have time.
All of these things are my keepsakes.
-What about that photo?
-That's my son.
So you'll be living with him
from now on?
My son is dead.
The sea...
My son was a sailor.
One day, his ship got overturned...
and he never came back after that.
This photo became the only thing that
lessen my loneliness during voyages.
What is it?
Barging in without knocking!
Mr. Stafford
have you ever loved somebody?
You have some nerve!
Do you have any idea how hard it is
when you lose somebody you love?
The son of captain Wells died at sea.
If somebody truly knows the value
of a human life, it's Captain Wells.
That's why he couldn't have
abandoned those people.
I too, know how it feels to lose
a beloved person.
Lost money can return eventually
but once a human life is lost...
it can't return.
You tried to stop Captain from saving
lives with that single telegram!
That is so wrong!
Wrong!
I can't give you any strength.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, Candy.
If this seagull is fine
I'll be fine as well.
Now, set it free.
Okay? Don't push yourself too hard.
If you don't have enough strength
you can come back.
It flew!
Farewell!
Won't you all gather in the great hall?
In the great hall? What for?
It's a party in honor of captain Wells's
last journey!
Mr. Stafford!
We'll be waiting for you.
Cheers!
-Congratulations, Captain.
-Thank you.
Captain Wells, congratulations
on your last journey.
Thank you, Candy.
Thank you, everyone!
I will remember this happiness
for a very long time!
I am so fortunate.
Cheers!
Miss Candy, you'll get sick if
you drink too much champagne.
No, that's not it... it's ...
What'll I do... I guess I really
had too much.
What a fog!
England... I wonder what it's alike.
I'll get to meet more wonderful
people, just like Captain Wells!
I'm glad I came!
I wonder if Stear and Archie are
waiting for me.
If I'll be together with those two,
any place could be wonderful.
Anthony?
Candy saw Anthony's image
in the dense fog.
Was it an illusion?
London is almost a stone-throw away.