Angry aunt Elroy sent Anthony
to live in the forrest mansion
However, a single carrier pigeon still
connects separated Anthony and Candy.
Don't give up, Anthony!
What's the matter, Kurin?
A message from Anthony!
Thank you!
Good morning, aunt Elroy.
It's grand Aunt!
Y.. yes, grand Aunt.
And what's the meaning of this?
Yelling from such a high place
just to greet me?
I'm sorry.
Close the window.
But...
Close it!
A girl from the upper class...
doesn't show her face
on the window like that
She's taking my freedom again...
Are you deaf, Candy?
Yes!
The pigeon...
Oh no! Grand aunt is going to
discover a letter from Anthony!
Do you understand?
Close the window!
Somebody...!
Madam, what a beautiful hat
with feathers!
It's a real pigeon!
A real...
Let's see why it stopped again...
Maybe the brakes are...
Is it yours, Archie?
It seems to be carrying a note
It's a carrier pigeon.
Thank you! Aunt was just about
to discover the note!
But to use a carrier pigeon...
Anthony is so considerate.
It was Tom's idea
Yeah, it's that cowboy, right?
Hello, Candy!
I've already gotten used to
life in the forrest
Tom comes to see me
from time to time
Aunt Elroy can't boss me
around anymore
I have some news that's going
to startle you!
I'll participate in a rodeo
at Tom's village.
Anthony will be in a rodeo?
What's that rodeo-thing?
You only ride in cars
so no wonder you don't know!
It's a competition of cowboys where they
catch cows while riding on wild horses!
I wonder will Anthony be okay.
He's been away for a few days
and just look at him!
We could ride wild horses too
I'm sure
Anyway, he's not about to give up.
Kurin, do you see a pigeon
waiting over there?
Maybe it went back.
Alright, Candy,
leave this to us!
What do you think, Candy?
What kind of aircraft is that?
-What, an aircraft?
-It's a balloon.
Candy could establish communication
with Anthony using this thing?
It's much better than
a carrier pigeon.
But... will it be able to reach
Anthony's place?
Of course! it can go across
the Pacific all the way to Japan
And, unlike a carrier pigeon
it can carry a lot of cargo!
Then, I can send him the pie
he likes so much, right?
Of course!
I'll tell Dorothy about this
and I'll send him some roses
Can it carry so much cargo
brother?
Of course!
Kurin, would you like to go as well?
It's Ok
Archie is keeping Aunt busy
Alright.
It's time to launch it, then.
Ignition!
The wind is just right!
It's flying!
Everything went perfectly!
It's pretty!
Aunt, it's your turn!
Archie... did you see something
flying outside? Just now.
Nothing to worry about!
Now, it's your turn, Aunt!
Its course it just as expected.
It will really reach Anthony's place
right?
It can go much further
than a pigeon
Mr. Stear and miss Candy!
What are you doing out here?
We're looking at the stars.
Stars?
It was over there!
Yeah, look this way!
Brother!
Brother, it's an emergency!
What, did you get any new ideas?
Out there...!
What's that thing?
I have a bad feeling...
It's coming this way!
Mother!
I didn't think you would
miss Anthony to the point...
when you'd use something like this
Your thing there went off the mark
since it was dark
It just didn't work, Candy
Are you sure you set it
in the right direction, brother?
It's strange...
Candy wrote this letter, right?
Yes
Aunt, it would be better if
you used your glasses.
I know
Rodeo?!
Are you saying that Anthony
is going on that dangerous rodeo?!
Yes
I won't let him!
A pride of the Ardley family
can't be seen as a cowboy!
What would we do if something
was to happen to Anthony?
I'm sure that it was Candy
who put that idea in his head.
That's not true!
Yes, entering a rodeo
was Anthony's own idea!
There is no way that
this gentle Anthony...
would have entered a
violent rodeo competition
-Right, aunt?
-No...
this has nothing to do with Candy!
Anyway, I'll have to make Anthony
quit from the rodeo
Aunt
I'll go to the forrest mansion.
I'm sure that Anthony will...
I'm not really sure...
What do you mean?
Be quiet
Candy!
Yes!
Go to the forrest mansion immediately ,
understand?
Aunt!
Talking Anthony out of this
is Candy's duty
Mine...?
If it's you...
Anthony might
listen to your words.
Are you saying that he wouldn't
have listened to me?
Do you understand, Candy?
Uh...
If Anthony enters the rodeo
and something happens to him,
I will hold you responsible, Candy.
Yes.
Keep it like that!
Get down, Anthony!
Real horses are
much wilder than this one!
Alright, let's try again!
Somebody is coming
It's Candy!
Candy is coming this way!
Candy?
Candy!
Anthony!
Candy It's been a while
How are you?
This greeting it not like you,
Candy!
You're looking much tougher from the
time we last saw each other.
And you've become more like a lady!
What? To give up the rodeo?
Isn't it dangerous?
Of course it is
Much more dangerous
than growing roses, right?
Aunt Elroy is very
determined about this!
Of couse, it was aunt
who sent you here!
May be!
And now you are going to
tell me to quit?
That's right, but...
when I saw you up there
it didn't seem that dangerous...
Candy, one can get hurt even
while taking care of the roses!
That's right!
Candy, as you know...
as a member of the Ardley family
wealthy life and high social status
were guaranteed for me.
To be rich all your life, right?
But lately, such a lifestyle
has become a huge burden for me.
I want to work and shed sweat
just like Tom.
Anthony
I understand your feelings
Then, do you agree with me
going on a rodeo?
Yes, of course!
But Candy...
won't you get in trouble
if he enters the rodeo?
Yes, there is still
aunt to worry about.
I just got a good idea!
Candy, enter the rodeo as well!
You want me to ride wild horses?
There is also a lasso-throwing
competition at a rodeo!
I'm pretty good at that!
That's right! I'll get Stear
and Archie to participate as well!
Good idea!
If all of us
enter the competition
maybe aunt Elroy
won't be able to refuse then!
If we all stick together
we could oppose aunt!
Alright!
What? We too?
Yeah!
We can't do that!
None of us can ride horses
or throw a lasso.
We'll make fool out of ourselves...
Even little kids
are going to participate!
But I don't think I can do that...
Don't worry! I know of a perfect
kind of competition for you!
What kind of competition?
A cow-milking competition!
Milking...?
My! I wanted Anthony to quit.
and now even the rest of you
plan on entering?
Yes, aunt.
It's grand aunt!
We are going to compete in
cow-milking, which is safe.
Stear, an Ardley's should milk a cow
in front of other people?
Aunt, please come and watch us!
It's an incredibly fun festival!
Get out!
I don't want to speak to you!
Want to try it out after Dorothy?
Okay.
It's embarassing
touching someone's breasts...
Just think that it's a car's engine!
Engine?
Anthony!
What's the matter, Anthony?
We can't go to the rodeo.
What happened?
It's not just me... none of us
can go to the rodeo.
What do you mean, Anthony?
Aunt Elroy paid a visit
to the rodeo managers...
and arranged so that
we wouldn't be accepted
Such a thing...
She said that...
as long as we're living here,
we can't against her order.
Anthony!
In that case
I will leave this house!
Calm down, Anthony!
I'm Anthony Brown!
I'm not aunt's puppet!
Wait, Anthony!
Aunt Elroy doesn't want us
to enter the rodeo...
for the sake of the
Ardley family reputation!
That's right.
Proud and respectable...
Adleys wouldn't take part in
uncivilized things like rodeos
It's okay!
I have a good idea.
Finally, a rodeo!
Hey, Ardley!
You cowards!
Stop the carriage!
Thank you!
Ardley granny!
Granny...?
What are you saying!
Is that coward Anthony okay?
Who are you to call
Anthony a coward?
It's not only Anthony
The whole town knows that
every single Ardley is a coward.
That's enough!
I won't let you insult
the Ardley family any more!
But they suddenly chickened out
from the rodeo...
maybe they were
ashamed to admit this...
Wasn't it because you forbade them
from taking part in the rodeo?
Who told you that?!
Everybody in the town knows that
That all Adleys are big cowards
Let's go!
I heard it in the marketplace...
People there are spreading the
rumours around...
I can't believe this
Call the children.
As you wish.
I will allow you to enter the rodeo
Aunt Elroy...
but what about the
Ardley family reputation...
Our reputation
is exactly the reason why
In return, I expect you to win!
Aunt, banzai!
I mean... grand aunt
Anthony, let's cheer each other on.
-Yeah
Thanks to you, we won the fight
against aunt Elroy
And now, I'm going to win
against wild horses!
Hey, it's Tom's turn!
Tom, if you don't win...
you won't get anything
for dinner!
Don't worry, dad!
Leave it to me!
Okay, don't give up!
Tom, hang in there!
Twenty seconds exactly!
That's great, Tom!
He did it!
It's Anthony's turn now!
Go!
Go, Anthony!
Master Anthony!
Candy, when is he going to fall?
Anthony...
He can't hear you!
He has the best time!
Anthony!
Aunt Elroy...?
38 seconds!
By far, the best time!
You did it, brother!
Congratulations, Anthony!
Congratulations!
Anthony won.
Against grand aunt Elroy
and in the rodeo as well
Congratulations, Anthony.