Transcending the saddness
for the sake of tommorrow.
-Candy, let's go!
-Okay!
There's one hill I like
and it's this way.
A hill?
Look out!
Anthony!
Anthony, hang in there!
But Anthony did not answer.
She called and called
yet he did not answer.
Anthony!
Miss Candy!
-Dorothy?
-Miss Candy is...
-She woke up?
-Candy!
Candy!
Stear, Archie...
Anthony? Where is he?
Where is Anthony?
He's dead?
He hit his head against the ground.
We ran to help him but...
You're lying!
You're lying that Anthony died!
...that he died...
If only it were a lie!
He was well and joking this morning,
suddenly gone by the evening...
it's such a bad joke!
Right, Archie?
Why did he have to die?
He was such a good guy...
Why did he die?
He's dead.
Anthony is dead.
Candy?
Now, let's go, Candy!
To attend such a wonderful party...!
Go, Anthony!
Mr. Anthony!
Candy... you still haven't forgotten
about your prince?
because I look a bit like him?
Anthony!
That's not true!
I don't care who the Prince is!
Anthony, it's because...
I like you.
It's a bell...
Dorothy, that bell...
You look so sad.
It's Mr. Anthony's ...
I have to go!
You mustn't !
You can't go out with this fever!
Please, let me go!
You mustn't !
You can't go out with this fever!
Please, let me go!
Don't be unreasonable! You haven't
eaten anything in two days!
Doctor will scold you!
Anthony?
Doctor!
Now, go back to your bed.
Our Father, who are in heaven...
accept the soul of your humble servant
Anthony Brown Ardley,
and let it rest in peace.
Amen.
All roses have died during the night.
Now they were beautiful bloomed.
It's almost as if
rose petals turned into tears.
Come to think of it, the garden looks
as if it were tired from crying.
It's not only the rose bushes!
The entire Ardley family
is mourning the loss.
Aunt Elroy used to be so loud.
Now she has withdrawn
into herself completely.
And Candy,
who used to be so cheerful,
has now locked herself up in her room.
As if the whole place died.
And, you haven't invented
anything unusual in a long time!
-Maybe you're right!
-Brother
at times like this, you've got to build
something crazy to cheer up everyone!
Alright!
Come in.
Hello, Candy!
A rabbit?
Anthony.
Candy?
I'm sorry.
I remembered Anthony
when I saw the rabbit.
A rabbit?
Uh, Candy...
It's supposed to be a squirrel.
So it's a squirrel?
Candy laughed!
Candy really...
Thank you, Stear and Archie.
You did this for me...
I won't cry anymore.
That's great!
Miss Candy!
Has something happened?
there is somebody in Anthony's room!
Anthony's room?
It's Anthony!
Brother!
Anthony?!
Anthony...?
Anthony!
Neil?
Hi.
What are you doing, Neil?
Aren't those Anthony's clothes?
Lookin' good, right?
But it's nothing special.
Hey Neil, since when
did you become a petty thief?
Let me go!
I have Aunt's permission!
-Aunt?
-That's right.
Aunt said that
I can take Anthony's things.
Aunt said...
Now, take it please.
Put it in here.
Anthony's roses...!
I'll take them.
I will be the only one...
who will continue to care after roses
of my beloved Anthony!
Anthony's roses are beautiful
because they grow in this garden!
Shut up! You murdered Anthony!
Eliza!
If you two hadn't separated from
the rest during the fox hunt
such a thing would have never
happened to Anthony!
If I were riding with him, I wouldn't
allowed him to come in such danger.
Hoittman! Get to work!
Yes, miss.
Eliza, please!
Don't take Anthony's roses!
I got permission from Aunt Elroy.
Anthony worked so hard to
foster those roses!
Candy, I'm trying to
forget about Anthony.
I want to forget everything.
And that's why
you're giving roses away?
If I let them be, they will bloom again
and remember me of him.
I don't want that!
Candy?
I don't want to forget about Anthony!
Candy,
are you questioning my decisions?
Yes!
I support Candy's idea!
Me too.
Why did you two...
Anthony cared that rose garden
for remember his late mother.
Now that Anthony is gone
We must continue
to take care of it!
I won't allow it.
You don't get to decide
on such family matters.
Hoittman, hurry up.
Take this bush now.
But, these withered flowers
won't look good in your garden.
How can you tell
if you don't plant them?
But now that all the flowers
have withered away...
Okay? Just do what I tell you!
Candy!
Eliza! Return all roses to the ground!
What?
These roses belong to Anthony!
But Anthony is...
Anthony is living in this rose garden!
When spring comes
and roses blossom again
I'm sure that
Anthony will come back too.
This garden is his life now.
Close your eyes and look well...
Can you see him?
I can see Mr. Anthony, too...
Hoittman?
What's the meaning of this?
The soul of Mr. Anthony resides
in these roses!
Didn't you hear what I just said?
I did. I've been minding
Leagan's gardens for thirty years
but I've never once defied you.
Aren't you doing that right now?
Yes. I can betray you, miss
but now...
that God called Mr. Anthony to his side
how could I ever betray him?
Mr. Hoittman!
Mr. Anthony may be gone, but...
he's still living in hearts
of every one of us!
-I can see him.
-I see him too!
Mr. Anthony!
Stop that!
That's enough!
It was Aunt Elroy's decision!
Now, hurry and take these roses!
Are you deaf?
Aunt Elroy ordered this!
All of you will be fired!
These are Aunt Elroy's orders!
You'll be fired! All of you!
You're defying Aunt's orders!
Eliza! Why do you
want these roses so much?
It would be better
if you took those white bushes.
Are you saying that I should
be satisfied with that?
Anthony grew these roses from dirt
using his bare hands!
That's right!
Every day, Mr. Anthony would
get up early in the morning for this!
I'll remember this!
I'll tell aunt Elroy,
she'll fire every single one of you!
Anthony...
Anthony... what should I do?
The only thing I have here
is the memory of you.
I can't do anything.
Candy!
Candy, where are you?
-Candy!
-That's ...
That's Annie's voice!
Kurin, long time no see!
Annie!
Candy!
Annie, how come you're here?
I heard that you shut yourself into
your room when Anthony died.
I worried so much about you
Until I got permission
from Father to visit you.
Now it's my turn to console you!
But Annie, how did you find me here?
Mr. Hoittman said that I'll probably
find you around here.
I see, it was Mr. Hoittman...
Candy, it's my turn
to give you strength! Cheer up!
Thank you, Annie.
But I'm glad to have found you so well.
Candy, quickly return into your old
cheerful self!
I'm okay now.
I'll start anew once I leave this place.
There are too many memories
of Anthony in this place.
That might be for the best.
You quickly recovered from sadness
in only one day...
Hey, I wonder what are everybody doing
at Pony's home now!
Are they making dolls or necklaces
from fallen leaves?
That's right... Pony's home.
If I climb that big tree, I could
scream at the top of my lungs...
sending all the sadness away from me
and bidding my farewell to Anthony.
Huh? That rose...
It's blooming! Sweet Candy!
Others have all withered away,
but this one remained.
Anthony bestowed it with my name.
It's a new kind of rose I made!
Its name is " Sweet Candy."
Anthony...
That's right
it does look a bit like you!
It's the only one with enough
strength to bloom here.
Annie, I'm not giving up.
Candy!
I'd like to see it.
Because you have so many
memories of that place!
Let's go there together!
Really?
I want to see the place
where you grew up.
It's a promise!
Let's go, Anthony!
To Pony's hill.
Mr. Stear! Mr. Archie!
-What's the matter, Dorothy?
-Read this!
Stear, Archie,
I'm going to strike out on my own.
Please, forgive me for leaving
without seeing you
it would've been too painful that way.
Candy will never forget just
how gentle you were to her!
I'd like to thank grandfather William
for adopting me as his daughter.
Please send my best regards to Aunt.
Farewell, Candy.
-Brother, let's go after her!
-But how?
We're almost there, Anthony.
Pony's home...
We're home, Anthony!
This is my strong father tree...
that's the hill where I met the Prince.
It hasn't changed at all!
This is Pony's home, with gentle,
mother-like sister Pony and sister Lane.
It's Candy!
Candy came back!
Candy!
I'm home, everybody!
Candy is back!
Anthony, I came home, too.
Just like you returned to your mother,
I returned to Pony's home.
Candy came back to Pony's home,
a place she calls her homeland.
At the top of Pony's hill,
she planted Sweet Candy for Anthony.