Candy and others
head towards St. Joanna Hospital in Chicago.
Candy met a wounded boy
in the busy hospital.
She helped him right away.
Grandfather William's Home
Candy,
you sleep in that one, I sleep in this one.
Ok
Please
- Relax
- Yes
- You can come in.
You have two free days
from today.
A break?
There is enough time.
I would like to see
Stear, Archie and Annie.
There will be a series of hard training
from the day after tomorrow.
You need to be prepared for it.
Yes.
I am done. Good-bye!
Everyone, let's go to downtown!
- Good idea!
- Let's go together, Frannie.
Alright, group activity is important.
We can build up our team spirit
by doing things together.
Right, Candy?
I won't be able to meet them.
Next time, maybe.
Candy
Stear! Archie!
You really came to Chicago, Candy!
I thought I was having a dream
when I received the letter.
Are they your friends from Joseph Hospital?
Her name is Frannie.
Stear and Archie.
Nice to meet you.
And Judy, Natalie, Ellie.
Candy, a gift from us.
Welcome to Chicago.
Great brand!
Pull that string.
What's this?
It's great it came out quick!
Are you alright, Candy?
Brother's invention always has problems.
Sorry, Candy.
Actually, we came to pick you up.
Annie is almost here.
Annie? I miss her so much!
Let's go together!
Stear and Archie,
thanks for your invitation.
We are just about to have a tour in downtown.
Candy, don't worry about us.
Frannie
Ladies, how about taking the bus together?
Tour bus!Thank you!
Deal! We will be the guides.
Get on!
Frannie, plaese.
Let's go!
It is a big city.
I want to see Lake Michigan.
No problem, Judy!
Stear is so nice.
I like Archie.
Pattie and Annie will be mad.
I always wanted to visit Lake Michigan.
It's spectacular!
It reminds me of....
Lakewood.
We were so happy back then.
Now everything has changed.
Archie's summer is gone.
Stear's water fence is gone.
Anthony's roses.
A blooming rose garden.
The days at Lakewood will never come back.
Sweet memories,
and....
sad memories,
still lie deeply in my heart.
Let's go, Candy!
Frannie
Did you recall the past, too?
What I recall...
is not important.
Frannie has something in her mind,
but she deosn't want to open her heart to us.
That's the Adleys'company.
These too.
The Ardley family has a lot of banks and companies
in Chicago.
The president of the bank
is Elisa's father.
Mr.Leagan?
Look! That trading company is also ours.
What's wrong, Candy?
It opened my eyes.
Grandfather William is amazing.
It's true.
Even me can not believe,
how much fortune and influence Grandfather has.
The Adleys is amazing.
Candy,
you are one of the Adleys, too!
Candy?
Yes.Candy was adopted by the Adleys.
Didn't you know that?
It was before, not anymore.
What are you talking about?
You are still their daughter!
Stop the car!
What happened?
I am going home.
Frannie
Candy, I was wrong about you.
YOu are from a rich family.
Being a nurse is just a hobby to you.
We...No, I am different.
This is my lifelong job,
not a joke.
Me too.
Frannie
Judy, Natalie, Ellie.
Me too.
I want to be on my own,
and distinguish myself from the Adleys.
Candy
I am leaving now.
Wait, Frannie.
Candy, sorry, we are going back, too.
Good-bye.
Sorry.
It's...
It's not a joke to me.
I really...
really want to be a nurse!
We understand, Candy.
But,
you don't need to give up being an Ardley.
Stear, Archie, you don't understand.
Candy
Stear, bring me to the Ardley's.
I thought about bringing you there.
I know I left them, but...
I want to apologize.
And ask them to listen to my reason.
Then I would feel better.
It's the Ardley's front door.
Stop the car!
What's wrong, Candy?
I am a little scared.
What are you talking about? It's your home.
Isn't it, Candy?
No...
Of course you can still go in there,
because you haven't told Grandfather!
Alright.
I am Candy White Ardley.
But I will be Candy White when I come out.
Stear, Archie, welcome back!
The person in the car...
Candy
Elisa
You are here.
Elisa, you are here!
How come you are here, Elisa?
I came to see Grand Aunt Elroy.
Elisa, is the car here?
This guy is here, too?
I was just wondering.
So hard to get rid of.
The orphan from Pony's Home is really something.
Stear, get away!
Grand Aunt Elroy said I could use the car.
Get on, Elisa!
Wait, let me put on some perfume.
I don't like the smell of an orphan.
Let's go!
Crash the car!
I am sorry,
I didn't expect they would be here.
It's really not my day, to see somone I dislike.
Forget about them, Elisa said...
They came to visit Grand Aunt Elroy.
Grand Aunt doesn't feel well?
Not really, just high blood pressure.
She's doing the same as before.
Say high to Grand Aunt Elroy first.
Here
Stear, Archie, I can get in by myself.
Come in.
Long time no see, Grand Aunt Elroy.
You are Candy?
Yes, Grand Aunt.
I heard you left England
and returned to Pony's Home.
Yes, Grand Aunt.
I came to explain this to you.
Look at the way you talk.
You forgot the upper class manner?
Grand Aunt.
This is the way I talk now.
I am studying right now and will become a nurse.
The Adleys has always been the nobles...
Brother,
it's not a good idea
for her to see Grand Aunt.
She is here anyway.
There is no reason not to see Grand Aunt.
Shameless!
It was a mistake to adopt you.
I want to talk to Grandfather William
about this issue.
What?
I wrote a letter about this.
I...
I want to give up being
the foster child of the family.
Give up?
Can I discuss this with Grand Aunt?
Of course not!
I absolutely agree with that!
Grandfather William makes the final decesion.
I can't decide anything.
Where is Grandfather William right now?
I am sorry.
I get a headache by just seeing you, get out!
Please pass on my message to him.
I can't believe this!
You have been making troubles for him.
- Grand Aunt!
- Get out!
Stear, Archie, come here!
Grand Aunt
Here, you alright?
Is this ok?
I don't want to see you, get out!
Grand Aunt Elroy! Getting angry
will higher your blood pressure.
It's you who gave me high blood pressure!
Calm down, Grand Aunt Elroy!
Stear, Archie, I am going outside.
How is Grand Aunt Elroy?
She is calm now.
I am sorry, Candy,
about Grand Aunt Elroy.
Can't she be nicer to people?
Grandfather is not home?
Actually, he has never lived here.
Why did you say he was here?
Actually, Candy...
Annie, we've been waiting for you!
Annie
Candy
-Annie
- Candy
I miss you so much, Candy!
Me, too, Annie.
Driver
I will take Annie home later.
YOu can go now.
It feels like a dream
to see you in Chicago.
Me, too, Annie.
Let's celebrate in downtown!
Good idea!
Stear, Archie,
I am very happy right now, but I can't.
Why not?
I am worried about Grand Aunt Elroy.
She'll be fine, the doctor will be here soon.
Let's wait till the doctor is here.
She fell asleep.
It's really the fever!
An expert is an expert, right, brother?
I want Candy to take care of me
when I get sick.
Grand Aunt Elroy
Elisa, hide!
Are you in there, Grand Aunt Elroy?
I am coming!
What's wrong, Grand Aunt Elroy?
Grand Aunt Elroy
Elisa
You have been taking care of me?
It's very nice of you, Elisa.
It's my pleasure.
Elisa is lying.
It was Candy!
Doesn't matter, Archie.
I don't need people's approval,
it is my job.
Candy
I didn't think you would be so mature.
I feel ashamed.
Please.
Grand Aunt Elroy, what happened?
I had a headache and I fainted.
That's too bad!
What made you so angry?
Forget it.
Was it Candy, Grand Aunt Elroy?
Where did the kid go?
I don't know, I haven't seen her.
Tell her to come back when you find her.
Yes, Grand Aunt Elroy.
Were you taking care of Grand Aunt Elroy?
Yes.
Good job!
I was just doing what I was supposed to do.
Elisa is a good kid.
Liar!
Grand Aunt Elroy, it was...
It was Candy!
Why are you hiding there?
Doctor, Candy is a nurse.
That's what I thought.
Candy is the Adleys'foster child.
I feel much relieved that
there is a nurse in the family.
Unforgivable!
Grand Aunt Elroy!
I am not allowing anyone in the Ardley family
to be a nurse!
Being a nurse is a honorable job.
I don't care if it's honorable or not.
The Adleys'lady
can not do what the common people do.
Grand Aunt Elroy
Is this what you give return
for what she has done?
Stear!
Candy helped you to bring down the fever.
She is the family's foster child,
it is what she is supposed to do.
Grand Aunt Elroy,
can Candy stay over tonight?
Of course not!
Candy and Annie have not spent
time together for a long time.
Please allow them to stay over tonight,
please!
You people talk too much.
Grand Aunt Elroy won't say yes.
Right, Grand Aunt Elroy?
How could I forgive her easily?
Grand Aunt Elroy is very quiet.
Maybe, it is her way of expressing her gratitude.