To ward off the image of Anthony
which burned deeply in Candy's heart.
Terry forced Candy to ride a horse.
It was summer day's afternoon...
the fresh breeze beckoned Candy's heart
and the green forrest was dazzling.
White party for two.
Somehow...
it feels as if we were like this
for a very long time now...
-You're bleeding.
-Huh? When did I...
You must have snagged a branch
when we were riding.
I'm fine, Terry.
I can't just leave it like this.
Terry...
I can't believe that
this Terry and the rude Terry...
from a while ago are the same people.
It's okay now.
It was a bit rude, I don't regret it.
It smells wonderful!
This lake...
Your mother loved this lake
didn't she?
She's on a ship to America right now.
Cut it out, already.
Such a story...
Hey, Candy!
Candy!
It's Annie and the others!
I'm over here!
That's Terry next to Candy...
Looks like it.
Out of all guys, she picks him...
Brother, go faster!
Hurry! I'm telling you!
Nasty people are here.
Hurry, brother!
What's gotten into you, all of a sudden?
I want to see with whom
is Candy hanging around!
-Terry!
-Eliza, look out!
Sit down!
He's hanging around with Candy!
Get me to the beach, brother!
Don't move, dammit!
What are you doing?
Eliza!
Help!
-Help!
-Eliza!
We have to help them!
What should we do, brother?
They didn't keep their boat still
and now they're swimming.
-Let's wait a bit before helping them.
-Alright.
They didn't keep their boat still
and now they're swimming.
-Let's wait a bit before helping them.
-Alright.
But... they need help, Archie!
There is plenty of energy in Eliza!
Terry!
Help me! I'm dying!
-Help me! Terry!
-Don't grab me like this.
Terry saved her.
Hey! Help me too!
Neil, never absent-minded while rowing
you might overturn the boat!
Eliza! Get a hold of yourself!
Maybe she inhaled some water...
Eliza!
Is she okay?
Yeah. But you surprised me...
three guys and none of you can swim!
What?
Both I and Stear can swim!
Oh? So you chickened out?
Eliza wasn't drowning!
She was swimming pretty well!
It's just that we weren't
too sorry for her...
You can swim?
Just a few moments more and
I would've drowned there.
Terry, I owe you my life!
You cowards!
What would you do if I died?
Eliza, dry your hair with this...
Say, Terry, won't you come to the
Ardley's mansion?
I have to thank you for this.
That's so nice, Terry!
Candy, you stay away!
Eliza,
I'm grateful for your invitation...
but my own mansion is close by.
Then, can I come over to your place?
-Eliza!
-But...
There are no servants in my mansion
and I have nothing to treat you with.
Bye.
What a snob...!
I'm going back!
You're going to come along!
You'll be punished for not helping me!
Pick up my stuff and go!
Candy.
You're going to stay away.
Eliza?
Grand aunt Elroy will be sick
if she sees your face!
Eliza! How can you...
You'd just let me die!
I'll tell Aunt about this! Let's go.
Oh, boy.
Candy, don't worry about Eliza.
let's go to the mansion. Okay?
I'll pass.
I'd rather take a nap in the shade.
Annie, go along with others!
But...
You don't need to worry.
Candy!
Candy! Where are you going?
What's gotten into Terry today?
Moreover, he was rude again...
he left without saying anything to me.
Mark!
You have some business with my bro?
It's not that I have some business
with him...
No business with him,
you keep loitering around here...
Don't say such weird things!
Mark, what did you come here for?
I brought some milk and bread
my mom made.
Terry will be glad.
He's probably hungry by now.
-Bye!
-Candy...
Strange.
What's gotten into me?
I'm wandering around
Terry's house without a reason.
Pull yourself together, Candy!
Ow!
Annie, I had no idea
you were this good!
It's because this piano is good...
Why, this is a nice room!
It's like we're in some
snow-covered land.
This room is according to
aunt Elroy's tastes.
That's why we don't think
it's too pretty.
Doesn't matter how white
a room may be...
if a person who lives inside
has a dark soul...
Archie!
What was that dark thing
you mentioned?
N..nothing... you have a
wonderful dress and...!
Really!
It really matches this room!
Thank you.
I just got a permission from aunt Elroy.
A permission for what?
We'll make a party for Terry next Sunday
in order to express my gratitude.
A party?
I'm still alive because of Terry.
Cut that out, already.
Stear,
you disagree with aunt's decisions?
I didn't say that...
In Sunday, we'll be throwing
a white party in this room!
A white party?
That's right!
Your dress, shoes, parasol...
they all need to be white!
It'll look like a nurse party!
Archie and Stear wanted me to ask
you to come to the party!
I'm glad for that, but I think
I'll pass up on this all-in-white party!
Just thinking about
it gives me the willies.
But Terry is going to come, too!
Does it matter?
Terry hates busy, noisy events.
Did he say that he'll be coming?
I...
I'm not going.
...to this white party.
Candy...
Don't worry about me, you two!
Sorry for going without you...
What are you saying!
You two look wonderful in white!
Kurin!
Kurin, you want to see them?
Aren't Annie and Patty pretty?
Now, see you later!
You don't want to be late?
You'll get burnt
if you don't open that parasol!
White party...
when I look at those two
I'm still just a little bit jealous!
Alright! I'll throw my own party!
Candice White's special act!
I haven't done this in a while,
my skills must have gone a bit.
Maybe I put on some weight?
Candy?
Terry!
I'm surprised!
Me too!
I didn't know there were monkeys
in this forest.
You saw me?
What's the matter?
Aren't you going to the white party?
Yes. They don't want me there, anyway.
If you're not going,
I'm not going either.
Really, Terry?
Never spoil that smile on your face.
Say, won't you come to my place?
There are ghosts in my mansion.
I'd like to see those ghosts!
Annie, Patty
you two look gorgeous in white!
You could pass off as twins from now on!
Strange, he's so late...
It's because he's so whimsical.
He's going to come!
He would've informed us otherwise!
Anyway, let's begin.
Hold on a sec.
It's dark!
They've been here since old times.
They look as if they were alive.
Not really. but the truth is
they get scary when ghosts get in them.
No way!
Candy, look! Behind you!
These arms are great when a girl
needs to be embraced.
Terry!
That joke was a bit too much!
Candy, looks like it's going to rain.
There it goes.
It feels like it's suddenly become cold.
-Put this on.
-Thank you.
This is...
A forgotten gown.
It's your mother's ?
She said:
I'd like that freckled girl to have it.
To me...
It's rude! Announcing his arrival
and then not showing up...!
Aunt Elroy is upset too!
He must've caught a cold or something.
That's it! I'm sure it is!
I'm going over to his place!
Come on, during this storm...
But...
You'll go when the rain stops?
White party at the Ardley's .
We're sitting next to this fire
it feels like Christmas.
She said the same thing.
Who?
Your mother said that, I see.
On that day... when it got dark
we spoke...
What did you two talk about?
Nothing special.
You didn't see her for ten years...
We just stood together
near the fireplace until dawn.
She came all the way from America
to see you...
And you two didn't talk at all.
I wasn't the only one
who couldn't speak.
Your mother, too?
While I was sitting with her
next to the fireplace...
I got this warm feeling
as if it were Christmas.
Just by sitting there in silence...
I felt as if our hearts were
being connected.
I accept the love from my mother.
I would've gone crazy.
Spending time with her in silence,
it was such a wonderful feeling.
That's what a real parent is.
That's what a real mother is.
I've never felt this strange before.
What's the matter, Candy?
-I'm just a little jealous.
-Jealous of me?
Because
there isn't such a person for me.
Say, would you care if the two of us
stood by the fireplace till dawn?
Candy.
Eliza?
So that's what you've been up to!
You ambushed Terry while he was
on his way to my party!
That's not true!
Does it matter?
You crook!
Eliza
The way you enter people's homes without
permission will tarnish Ardley's name!
I'll remember this!
-Eliza!
-Let her go.
But she is going to vent on
Annie and Patty...
Are you their guardian?
It's not that...
They aren't children.
But...
Candy is in Terry's mansion?
When you think about it, that's
exactly what I'd expect of her!
It's because Candy was brought up
in Pony's home!
Eliza.
Oh? Come to think of it, you too
came from Pony's home.
Stop that, Eliza!
No, I won't .
Either you all leave now
or I'll ask around about her.
Everyone...
Annie will play the piano for us
at the end of this party.
-Annie.
-Patty...
Now. It's okay.
Hold on. I'm running this party!
We know, Eliza.
At the end of her performance
we'll offer you our greetings.
Patty!
That's right, Candy!
But Patty was there for me.
I see. Both of you have become stronger.
It's because of this summer school!
Right, Annie?
Yes.
Because of summer school?
Living in huge Scottish countryside.
made both the anguish and loneliness
seem like trivial matters.
My heart is jumping like it somehow
became stronger!
Really!
Annie and Patty are laughing,
they had turned lively and strong,
Candy was glad to have come to Scotland
from the bottom of her heart.
She decided that she'll spend
the last few days in summer school.