Freely leaving the contemplation room.
Sister Gray found out about a pet turtle
Patty secretly kept.
While protecting Patty...
Candy managed to upset sister Gray.
Candice White Adley!
you will be confined
to the contemplation room...
You are banned from participating
in the May festival
Sister Gray is so mad...
just what were you two up to?
Sister Margaret...
It was all my fault.
I got Candy in trouble, too...
Patty, don't say that!
I wanted to see the
contemplation rooms someday!
Candy...
This room is Patricia's .
Candice, this one is yours.
Patricia, give me that turtle.
Yuli!
Sister Margaret, leave Yuli to me!
I'm begging you!
I'll write an apology for this...
Make sure that
you won't get into trouble for this!
Therefore...
Please! I'm begging you!
I understand, Candice.
I believe you. I'll let you have Yuli.
Thank you, sister Margaret!
Candy!
Patty! Leave it to me!
That's great, Yuli!
I'm thinking about
asking Mr. Albert to take care of you.
If he received my invitation
to the May festival...
I'm sure he'll come!
And then
I'll ask him to take care of you.
May festival!
Oh crap! I'll be locked up in here
during the whole festival!
You're banned from participating
in May festival!
Mr. Albert will laugh at me
when he hears this.
And grandfather William...
Grandfather enabled me
to study in this school...
I wanted him to see how hard
I'm working on becoming a lady.
When he hears that his foster-daugter
was banned from the festival...
it might startle him
and he could even die...
And when I think of angry aunt Elroy...
You're a shame of the Adley family!
A disgrace!
What should I do?
Yuli!
You're awake!
Patty used to talk to you
whenever she was lonely.
Even though you can't answer
you're a wonderful companion!
It's because you're a living creature!
Good morning, Patricia.
Get out, quickly.
Good morning, Candice!
Good morning, sister Margaret!
You're here to let me out?
I just brought you breakfast.
I spoke to sister Gray about you...
I already said
Patricia only for one night...
and Candice...
until the May festival is over!
I'm sorry, Candy.
It's okay, Patty.
I'm not very lonely in here!
Thank you.
Waltz!
Everyone is practicing
for the May festival.
Yuli! Are you a boy? Or a girl?
Suits me both ways!
Come!
One, two, three...
And turn!
It fell out.
What a piece of junk.
Yuli, looks like we can escape
from the attic!
What a refreshing spring outside!
I'll return before the next patrol.
I have plenty of time!
Candy!
What are you doing, Annie?
Uh... I'm sorry!
You just said " Candy"
haven't you?
Yes...! I wondered
what's going on with her...
She's locked up in the
contemplation room.
She's probably crying her eyes out
right now.
Good for her!
Candy... just how did you
escape from that room?
Instead of Candy
think about the dance practice!
She must be lonely now that her friend
can't watch over her anymore!
Keep an eye on that record player!
Besides, Candy
now that you've escaped...
just where do you plan to go?
Hey, stop!
Mister, let's hurry to the
Blue river zoo!
All the way to Blue river?
You have the money to pay the fare
young lady?
Of course!
Alright then, hop in.
I'm sorry, Mr. Albert, but you'll
have to pay the fare.
Young lady
just what is that stone-thing?
Looks pretty important to you.
That's right!
It's very important to me!
Yuli, you look just like a stone
with your legs hidden inside.
Wow, balloons!
Say, is that a street musician?
Wow, that kid has a huge lollipop!
Young lady, you seem to have been
living in some hellhole till now...
That's right! I was in jail!
Lately I've been hearing about
kid gangs but...
Maybe I let one of them
into my carriage!
She has a cute face, but I don't know
what she could do!
Maybe... If I turn into an empty street...
she'll clobber me with that stone!
-We're here!
-Thank you!
Could you wait a bit?
I'll call my friends
and we'll pay you the fare.
-Friends?
-Yes!
Well then.
N..no! You don't have to!
Don't call your friends
I don't need you to pay the fare!
Yuli, what was that about?
He treated me like that
'cause I'm so cute!
I wonder if I'll find Mr. Albert.
Mr. Albert!
Terry?
Terry is laughing.
He's laughing so heartily!
They must be having fun.
Mr. Albert has the power
to cheer up anyone.
Yuli, since Mr. Albert is
so good with animals
I'm sure he'll be able to
cheer you up, too!
Good day, Mr. Albert.
Candy!
I had no idea that Terry is with you.
Talk about the devil...
Candy, Terry and I
have been talking about you.
So that's why you two were laughing!
No, Terry told me why he calls you
"freckled Tarzan."
So the two of you were
poking fun at me and laughing about it!
You watched us?
Gosh, he's so rude.
By the way, Candy
what's the matter with that turtle?
That's right!
Its name is Yuli!
I'd like to give it to you!
To me?
It's a precious friend of my friend.
Friend's friend?
That's okay.
Welcome, Yuli!
I'm so glad!
Sunglasses, your break is over.
I'm sorry, you two.
I'll be done in two hours; till then
why don't you two have some fun?
Good for you, Yuli!
I forgot something important!
The turtle!
Be a good boy, okay?
You'll take good care of it
won't you?
I had so much to say
once I got the chance see him.
But I can't find any words.
I only hear
the sound of my beating heart.
Let's go out, Candy.
So many people are here.
Families, couples...
Even groups of hikers...
If I could bring the children
from Pony's home...
they would've been so glad!
Terry!
I wonder... whom do we look alike?
Brother and sister?
Or maybe...
Maybe we look like a couple!
That wouldn't be too far off!
Candy!
Something here looks exactly like you.
What is it?
When you make that face,
you resemble them even more.
Instead of Freckled Tarzan...
maybe Freckled Monkey
would suit you better?
Don't you make fun of me!
You're gonna get some!
Terry, you!
Geez, where is he?
I wasn't really going to hurt him.
Candy.
-Terry!
-Wanna share?
Thank you.
I thought you got scared of me
and ran away.
No way.
Alright!
Cute!
By the way
how come you're here today?
I escaped from the contemplation room.
Contemplation room?
You know, last night...
Why, you stubborn old...!
It's not very funny!
Stubborn, you said?
I love this.
Even I wouldn't have said such a thing!
Miss freckles.
And thus, I was banned from
the May festival.
That's my bad luck.
I see, you won't be there.
May festival sounds like a lot of fun!
Many flowers... candy...
and the dance!
Yeah, it really is a lot of fun!
They'll bake a cake this big!
I'm so disappointed.
I even invited Mr. Albert...
How did you meet Mr. Albert?
I met him back in America.
While I was tending horses
in Eliza's house...
one night I went out and he saved me.
Help me!
Somebody!
He always appears to help me
when I'm in trouble.
He's such a good person!
When Anthony died...
he came to console me.
Candy
What do you plan to do after his death?
You want to keep weepy face and hesitant
from now on?
Lakewood was such a wonderful town!
I'm sure...
that Anthony's roses are blooming now.
Anthony?
On that day
she mentioned the same name.
Anthony...
Anthony!
Who is Anthony?
On that day, on the ship...
I thought I'd seen Anthony.
However...
I was completely wrong.
Anthony was a very kind boy
who loved his roses.
Good thing that I'm not like him.
Terry!
He grew roses?
I'm sure he must have been a real wuss.
Terry! That's rude!
Anthony wasn't weak!
He was a strong... masculine...
wonderful person.
I see. And what happened with
you and that rose-kid?
He dumped you in favor of his roses?
What's up with that gaze?
I'm sure he's in America
right now, fawning over his roses.
Anthony is...
dead!
He fell off a horse.
He's dead?
Fell off a horse?
No wonder, that night when I rode...
Candy must be very afraid of horses.
Don't get on that horse!
Stop that horse!
Candy
You liked Anthony that much?
What a pity.
At least, I can pray for his happiness
in the other world.
Terry!
Must you be so rude?
Putting down Anthony
was horrible of you!
-Terry!
-What's with that Anthony...
Those who die don't come back!
Terry is horrible...
Putting down Anthony...
I won't forgive you!
As soon as he speaks up, he finds
the words to hurt one's feelings.
What's the matter, Candy?
Did Terry go back?
Yeah... That punk...
He didn't really look like a punk to me.
Ever since that night when I saved him.
he came to see me from time to time.
He's a punk to me!
You two got into a fight?
Can't help it, then.
Here's Yuli.
Yuli!
Mr. Albert
have you received my invitation?
Yeah, for May festival?
I'll be there for sure.
Thanks.
Maybe I could borrow a new suit
from a friend.
I need to dress up a bit!
Uh, I was banned from the festival.
Banned?
It was because of Yuli. I'm sorry.
No point in going then, I guess...
I'm sorry.
Looks like I made it back before
they found out I was gone.
I thought Mr. Albert would've laughed
after telling him what had happened...
But he looked so disappointed.
Kurin!
Kurin, you've come to see me?
Since Yuli is gone!
I need a companion to talk with.
I'm so glad you're here!
Until now, I've never felt the kind
of loneliness Patty had been facing...
Mr. Albert, Stear and Archie
were always there for me.
And now that I'm completely alone...
Kurin, you are there for me.
That's why... that's why
I'm not lonely, Kurin.
Thank you, Kurin!
Candy was overjoyed
to have Kurin at her side.
And now that
Kurin was next to her
Candy thought that she wouldn't be
so lonely during the May festival.