A pretty, lasso-wielding girl.
America.
Just south of the Michigan lake,
near the small mountain village,
there used to be an old church
called " Pony's home" .
In Pony's home, together with
two caring nuns,
lived children who had nobody
of their own.
They were called Sister Pony
and Sister Lane.
Come on, you don't need
to be afraid of a boogie man!
Snow is all strange to you, right?
Come on, eat up.
Tom!
Sister Lane.
A baby is crying.
Tom was trying to tell us
about the crying baby!
Watch your step!
It's here, sister Pony!
In such a snow...
There is a note attached, too!
I couldn't take care of her anymore,
no matter how much I tried.
Her name is Annie.
Annie?
She smiled.
It's okay, Annie.
Sister Pony, another baby!
Sister Pony, it's here!
My, my, what a lively baby!
Did you find any notes?
Only this doll.
Candy?
Your name is Candy?
So... you are Candy.
And in such a white day...
Because we found her on such a white day,
let her name be Candice White.
Candy the prankster and little Annie!
What's going on?
From that time, exactly six years
have passed.
Years quickly flew by. Annie, Candy
and Tom have already grown this big!
Why doesn't my snowman look anything
like Annie's ?
Candy, it's good.
I'll climb on its head!
Candy, are you okay?
Thank God.
They're coming this way!
-Look out!
-Move it!
My snowman!
Now you've done it!
Tom, wait up!
Candy!
Annie!
Tom, apologize to her!
Candy, it's okay. Candy...
She may be okay with that,
but I'm not. Apologize to her, Tom!
Sorry...
It's springtime.
In the forest, on the hill,
and in the fields - spring is everywhere.
It's springtime for all the
kids and animals, too.
That's terrible.
Must be Candy's doing.
Candy?
I'm here!
Where?
Up here, sister Lane!
They fell from their nest
so I put them back in!
Candy!
It's dangerous, come down quickly.
Okay!
No! Not like that!
Be careful! Come down slowly...!
Candy! Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Candy!!!
Candy.
Why did you do that prank for?
Because...
Candy, did you think about
the poor ducklings?
I did it because I'm sad.
Candy!
Because ducklings that get separated
from their mama are so sad.
For ducklings, there are no kind
people like sister Pony and sister Lane.
And they'd be left alone.
You can go, Candy.
Okay!
Sister Pony, don't you think
we overdid this a bit?
Sister Lane, scolding Candy
was your idea, right?
Well...
Look over there, sister Lane.
-Candy!
-Annie!
My heart is racing as if I were
the one being scolded.
Really.
I must be more careful
from now on.
If I keep doing these things,
your heart will pound,
and I don't want that to happen.
Candy!
How could we ever scold them?
Just look at them.
It's almost as if this
were their last.
What's the matter, sister Pony?
I'm thinking about the day when
they'll be separated from each other.
A day will come when
one of them will get adopted.
Perhaps it won't happen for a while...
No, it could happen 3 days from now.
The 3rd day of Every term,
children from Pony's home
are studying good manners.
The adopters will come to see them.
Every one of them is dreaming about
a happy life with kind adopters.
However,
Candy and Annie don't think that way.
Candy, Annie, stop fooling around!
If you didn't want to leave,
why didn't you say so?
Why are you pretending to be bad?
I am sorry...
Candy, don't you think this was bad?
I want to stay with Annie forever.
You were willing to risk happiness
of other children for your own?
Other children?
They were laughed at because of you.
Everyone?
That's right.
Children from Pony's home are well
known for their good manners,
but this could change if the two
of you keep making trouble.
I'm sorry, sister Pony!
Candy.
Four more years have flown by.
Candy and Annie are celebrating
their tenth birthdays.
Well then, Candy, Annie.
Candy, Annie, congratulations!
Candy, Annie, happy birthday!
Thank you!
Hey, how come Candy and Annie have
a birthday on the same day?
John, you see...
In all, Annie and I were found
together on the same day.
Since our real birthdays are unknown,
that we were born on the day
they found us in the snow.
Hey, I wish they found
me with you, too!
John, you!
Thanks.
Candy! Your new papa and mama
will be mad if you do that!
We'll stay here until we turn into
little old grannies, right, Annie?
Saying such a thing is nice,
right, Tom?
Something happened to him?
Something wonderful.
Once the snow melts, Tom will
be taken away by a wealthy farmer.
Then, Tom gets to have a father
and a mother?
That's right.
They are really wonderful people.
-What is it?
-Candy!
Somebody wants to take this prankster?
They've gotta be some weird-ass people!
Don't be like that, Candy.
I'll get adopted one day, too!
Nobody will take a tomboy like you!
Get him, Candy!
Surrender, Tom.
I'm not gonna lose you...
Candy, stop that!
Tom will be leaving soon, can't
you two get along till the end?
I can't wait to see you go!
And I'll finally be at peace!
Candy, what kind of people
are Tom's new parents?
It doesn't matter at all!
He won't get adopted because Tom
is way too crooked.
Candy!
How can you say that!
Annie?
Why can't you be happy for him?
I'll tell you then;
do you think he'll be happy
if he's taken away from here?
Well...
I like Pony's home. I like Annie.
I don't want to be taken anywhere.
Candy!
I like you too!
What's that sound?
Tom?
Damn.
Candy!
You're never gonna become a cowboy
if you keep throwing like that!
Shut up, I'm doing my best!
If you want,
Candy, the lasso master,
will show you how it's done!
Who needs you... go away!
Let's see what you've got then!
Here you go.
Your aim is off a little bit!
Don't touch that!
This hat was given to me
by my future father.
What's up with this hat?
Shut up!
Now you've done it!
Stop that!
I won't give up to you!
Candy, are you okay?
Tom, when did you become so strong?
I always was.
Then, you were...
I didn't want to hurt
a nice girl like you.
Tom, you fool!
Candy!
I hate you!
Go away to your new father!
Clint, Candy is crying.
I never saw her cry before.
Snow is gone. The day of Tom's
departure is finally here.
Teacher, leave this guy to me!
I'm going to
make a great man out of him!
Thank you very much.
Be good, Tom.
Well then, Tom,
say goodbye to everybody.
Uh... I...
You idiot!
They've been taking care of you
for ten years,
you can't even thank them properly?
Tom, are you okay?
Wait a minute, mister!
Candy!
What?
Tom hasn't gone with you yet!
You've barely known him for one
day, and you've already hit him!
This is Steve's way of doing things.
Ah, so.
Tom, don't go with this ruffian!
What are you saying, Candy?
Tom, once this bad man adopts you
you think you'll be happy?
Sometimes, I get violent too.
Tom
Amazing, with hands this big...
Everyone, look! These are the
hands of my future father.
My hands are someday going
to be this huge, too!
Tom...
Sister Pony, sister Lane,
thank you for everything.
I will work and do my best!
Take care of yourself, Tom.
Send us a letter.
Thank you, everybody!
Take care of yourself.
Goodbye, Annie.
-Tom.
-Bye, Clint.
Candy.
I really wanted you to teach me
how to throw a lasso.
And I wanted to teach you.
Son, let's get on our way!
Coming, Mr. Steve!
You fool.
From now on, call me daddy.
Daddy.
Alright! You're now my son.
Here you go.
-Well then.
-Farewell!
Farewell, Tom!
I never told you this.
The night when two of you
were abandoned in the snow.
It was Tom
who first heard you two crying.
It was Tom who found us...
Annie, shortcut.
-Tom.
-Thank you, Tom!
Farewell, Candy, Annie!
Tom! If somebody beats you,
you must fight back!
Candy! Annie!
Farewell, Tom!
Somehow, he looks like a real father.
What's the matter, Annie?
Annie?
I want them too,
gentle papa and mama...
Annie, face up.
Here's a kiss from mama.
Then... a kiss from papa.
My papa is Annie.
My mama is Candy.
-Annie!
-Candy!
Annie trembled from sorrow
in Candy's arms.
They did'nt know that
the separating day is near.