After refusing by the hospital in Chicargo,
Candy found a job in doctor Mati's hospital.
One day, she went to Seli's invite.
Candy called Seli's name.
Their own love
Nil.
Candy. What a pity
I am not the one you want to see.
I am cheated.
I will be cheated. After I heard Seli
I can't control myself.
Why are you in such bad mood.
Nil, you are too bad, I will go fırst.
Try.
Nil, what do you want?
What?
I just want to talk with you.
You're afraid others talk, so you avoid me.
I said so.
Nonsense.
Everyone will be happy if I love her.
Many ladies love me
that are more noble than you.
But I like you.
Like? Nil like me?
Don't hide it, you like me too.
I like Nil?
Are you shy, don't be afraid
just two of us here.
I said it.
Say.
I hate you. It's not shy, how can I love you.
Hate. Really?
Of couse, you always treat me bad
Now you say you love me.
Nil, get away, I want to go.
Leave me alone, Nil.
Candy, I, I...
Leave me alone.
Baster.
Nil.
Nil, open the door, Nil, open the door.
Candy.
You can't leave before you love me.
Who will love you?
Then, you will stay here always.
Candy, you want to jump?
Candy.
Candy, I will not give up.
It's cold.
No one's here. No car. Where's this place.
Everyone's worrying me. I must be quick.
Stop, please.
Candy.
Mr. Albert.
What's wrong, Candy
I am looking for you for a long time.
Mr. Albert.
Candy, why are you crying.
When I see you, I can't stand it.
Look, you're wet.
I went to the sea to swim.
I buy the skirt for your gift.
For,
for me?
I can earn some money now, you change it.
Thank you.
It's too late, I went to Doctor Mati's.
It said you went on a stranger's
car and went to the sea, I am afraid.
You thought I am kidnapped.
No, even made a mistake, I will not kidnap Candy.
Mr. Albert.
Just a joke.
It suits you.
Thank you.
Everytime, I am in troulbe, you save me.
What's wrong with you, Candy.
Some one cheated me that Seli came here.
But it's Nil.
Nil.
You know him.
No, I have heard about him.
He said he loves me, I am afraid. I hate him.
He's poor. No one can love him.
Am I too direct? But that's the truth.
It must hurt him.
What's wrong, Candy.
I feel it's a hard thing to hate someone.
I can't live with Candy all the time.
Don't tell her I recover my memory.
I still need time.
Nil loves Candy. Candy is popular.
What do you mean, doctor?
Candy is terrible.
What do you mean I am terrible.
Nothing.
Some one will like it.
Enough, enough.
But, will the playboy give up so easily?
If he will.
Doctor.
Candy, work hard today.
Yes, come in.
Good morning. Morning.
Sit down.
Candy, what's the Mr. Albert doing?
What? Animal business.
Really, he like to join the other basters.
No.
Everyone said he let you do the job
but enjoy himself.
No, he has a good job too.
Don't talk nonsense.
Doctor, tis is real, I saw by myself.
They didn't treat you any more?
How.
You just talk like this.
We just do it for Candy.
Yes, I hope she will not be sad.
He just bought car and clothes.
I earn some money.
Can you earn money just by the animal business?
What, Candy?
Doctor, please give me some time
I want to see in the animal institute.
That's the place where Albert works.
Yes.
Ok, go to have a look.
Thank you. Doctor Mati. See you.
Chicargo animal institute, it's here.
But Albert is not here.
No.
Do you know him?-No.
And we have no animal business.
No, no.
What does Mr. Albert do
where does his money come from?
I don't know what he do in the back street.
He lost his memory, maybe used by the bad guys.
Albert didn't work in the animal institute.
There must be some mistake.
Yes, Candy, please believe Albert.
Yes, I belive him.
Go on your work
Candys smile is patient's medicine.
Yes.
That's good, Candy.
Boss, wine.
Young man, stop to drink.
Give me wine.
No, no, you must be mad.
What? Say it again.
Will you pay my money?
You will hurt others for you don't know the pain.
Quiet. What's the light there?
You're Dili.
That's the east, so Julia is the sun.
The bright sun, drive away the moon.
Dili, it's me, Albert.
Albert, I don't know.
We see each other in the zoo.
We are just like brothers.
Stop it, I am not Dili.
Dili.
Don't be close to me.
You can't shoot me, you are falling.
Idiot.
Don't make me as idiot.
I am ashamed with you.
Idiot, I will not save your face.
I won't either.
Baster.
Open your eye, Dili.
Stand up, Dili.
I am not Dili, no, no.
Dili.
Is your friend?
He stays here for two days.
Boss, give me some water.
I prepared for it.
Is that ok, Dili?
Mr. Albert, keep beating me.
Dili.
So, after you leave the theater
you are wandering all the time.
I want to forget it.
It's about Candy.
The stage, life, everything destroyed
So I ran away.
I want to fınd back myself.
Do you fınd it?
No, now I can do nothing.
But, I hope Candy can stay in Chicargo.
I can't.
Dili, don't give up, cheer up.
Mr. Albert, it's too late.
No, you are a genious.
No, that's just the nonsense after drinking.
Dili, are you a man?
Not only you hurt, Candy is also sad.
I know.
You do not know.
Candy tried her best, but you give up.
Dili, come with me.
Look at that.
Candy.
Why is she here?
The hospital in Chicargo refused
to accept her, she didn't give up.
She want to go her own way.
Yes, no matter what, do not give up.
Her own way.
I don't want to leave, if only the time can stop.
Dili.
Don't say a word, just like this.
Dili is crying. Dili.
Departing with a man love me so much.
Candy, please be happy.
Dili, the same to you.
Candy left the hospital.
Dili, it's still time. Go to chase her.
Don't be sad for me.
This is my choice, Mary.
Dili.
Yes, I chose Mary.
I am not regret.
Who's next? Is this you? Come in.
Sister, is this hurt?
No, I am a good nurse.
Albert, I will go to the theater.
I will go my own way.
Dili, go to see Candy fırst.
No, I will go back directly.
See you, Candy.
Candy didn't know Dili is besides
her and went away soon.
There's Candy's smile in the clinic.