Grandfather William in the dream.
Grandfather William!
Candy feels so exciting.
The Grandfather William
who gave her all kinds of happiness...
is now staying in the hospital
where she works.
Grandfather William, It's Candy.
Grandfather William.
Grandfather William, I miss you so much.
It begins with the day
which Ardley family adopted me...
Lakewood, London,
there are memories through my youth.
I betrayed your kindness...
gave up the identity
of the Ardley family.
Grandfather William.
I will help you recovery
as soon as possible.
Grandfather...
If you already forgave me,
I would like to tell you...
It's Candy.
Your adopted daughter Candy.
Allowed me.
Grandfather.
Doctor Frank.
Doctor!
It's the pillow!
You are a fresh man.
Stay calm to do Judgment.
I am sorry!
While Grandfather William
makes a diagnosis...
the curtain...
Yes. No one can enter except me.
Excuse me.
Candy! Time for class.
There are different ways
to take care of baby and adult.
I'll show you today
how to look after a baby.
Grandfather William
is difficult to get along with.
I must open his heart.
Dim-wit.
Candy! A question for you.
Yes!
What am I teaching today? Answer me.
It's...
The lovely baby.
It's not mother's class here.
Sorry!
Candy, what's the age of baby?
It's...
What's the age?
I'm asking you.
Frannie!
Yes.
A baby before two years old.
Good! I have a baby here.
Before you look after a baby,
you must understand that...
A baby is not a little adult.
Headmaster!
What's the matter?
How to take care of a patient...
older than me?
We are talking about baby's caring.
I'd like to know
the caring of elder patient.
Shut up! The study has its priority.
Yes!
What's that attitude?
Mr. William never talks with nurse.
Why?
He only talks with doctor Frank.
He never treats us as people.
The Grandfather...
No,
Mr. William is not that kind of man.
How do you know that?
I know.
A man like that...
would never adopted me as his daughter.
Grandfather William!
He has woken up.
He is as quiet as Anthony.
As if he was thinking all the time.
Grandfather William, I am Candy.
Grandfather,
I will do my best to look after you.
To meet you here...
I'd like to thank you from my heart.
You gave me so many helps. Thank you!
I expected all the time to see you.
Grandfather, are you still angry
for my leaving school?
Get out!
Grandfather!
I never met a nurse so noisy.
Grandfather, won 't you forgive me?
What's matter with you...
keep talking to yourself.
That's because...
I never expect that I can meet you here.
I can 't help that.
Give me a quiet nurse, anyway!
Grandfather,
it's me, don 't you remember?
Stop nonsense...
I am your adopted daughter,
Candice White.
I don 't have a daughter like you.
Candice White Ardley,
have you heard that before?
Ardley? Boring.
Is this man really my grandfather?
Grandfather William!
Don 't call me grandfather!
I am William Markba.
Mr. Markba?
I mistook him for grandfather William.
That's it.
Mr. Markba,
have you heard about William Ardley?
I heard about the Ardley family,
I don 't know any of them.
My family is a prestige family.
As a prestige family,
you should heard about William Ardley?
So, you were adopted by the Ardley's.
To adopt a daughter like you...
The Ardley family is really boring
like the rumor said.
Boring?
Just like you.
Mistook me for somebody,
still noisy like that.
You are the one who is super boring.
How about me?
Your name calls William too,
but you are completely different.
What do you say?
Mr. Markba.
Doctor!
Doctor Frank, quickly!
Stiff the neck again?
Prepare for injection, quick!
Yes!
Let him sleep for a while.
Don 't irritate the patient excessively.
It's all my fault, I am sorry!
Dim-wit!
Don 't you yet admit that
you are a dim-wit?
Yes, I admit that.
Quarrelling with the patient...
there 's no such nurse in the world.
I mistook him for my benefactor.
The name William,
is very common in America.
It's not the reason I mistook him for.
It is said that
he has lands and villas.
It's also common too.
I am sorry!
Anyway, Frannie will return
to look after Mr. Markba.
Was I been dismissed?
Take a day off tomorrow.
Introspect?
Take a walk in the park.
The park?
That place is suitable for the dim-wit.
It is not too bad anyway...
you have worked for a day at least.
I am sorry, Frannie!
Forget it!
I'm happy for grandfather William that
he 's not an odd man like Mr. Markba.
Candy,
are you ready for the practice tomorrow?
I don 't have to ready for anything.
I'm going to the park tomorrow.
I'm not a good nurse, I guess!
How about Terry now?
Does he work hard in the show business?
His mother Eleanor Baker
is a famous actress.
He will do his best to challenge her.
And I...
Have one, Miss nurse.
Do you know me?
No, it's the first time.
How do you know that I am a nurse?
The smell of hospital.
-The smell?
-Joseph hospital, right?
You can smell that too?
No,
It's the largest hospital in the city.
I see.
I have ever stayed in Joseph hospital
for half a year.
Because of illness?
I felt so happy then.
Staying in the hospital make you happy?
The nurses took care of me
like my daughter.
Ignore the patient's bad temper.
Granny?
Do you mind that?
No!
I felt lonely after leaving the hospital.
I miss the nurses everyday.
Are you live alone?
I come to the park everyday
to feed these pigeons.
Nobody cares about me all day.
I'd rather stay in the hospital
than here.
I'd like to fall ill again.
How lonely this granny is!
She had friends
when she was in the hospital.
Mr. Markba must be very lonely.
That's why he dislikes everybody.
Are you leaving?
Yes, I have work to do.
It is sorry to bother you.
No, thank you for your advice.
Be my friend if I fell ill.
Okay!
Candy!
Just in time.
If you have not come back before dark.
I'll send your luggage to Pony's home.
It's you
who 'd like me to go to the park.
A good nurse would never
deal with the headmaster...
it's with patients.
But...
What shall we do?
if Mr. Markba calls you.
You mean grandfather William.
You wished to meet with him, right?
-But...
-Do what you promised.
Look after the patients with your best.
Headmaster,
I'm willing to look after Mr. markba.
People get into the hospital
are all patients, treat them equally.
I'll exchange my shift with Frannie.
That won 't be necessary.
What do you mean?
Doctor Frank told me that
you are a trouble maker.
Doctor Frank?
I already told the headmaster
about everything.
Mr. Markba 's criticism to me,
I'm willing to improve.
Improve it to the next patient.
Is there any chance to allow me
to look after Mr. markba?
I have told the headmaster.
Doctor Frank
is unwilling to change his mind.
I won 't give up.
It's Annie's father?
Mr. Brighton.
-Candy!
-Long time no see.
I was told by Annie 's letter that
you were studying in a nursing school.
What a surprised!
Why are you coming here?
To visit a patient.
I'll show you the way, the ward is here.
It's alright! I know the way.
That way is...
The patient whom I pay a visit
is behind that window.
Mr. Markba?
You know him?
Allow me!
It's alright!
The man is not easy to get along.
You mean... he 's always like that.
Yes! I'm here to bless him.
Bless him recovery as soon as possible.
Does Mr. Markba know that you are here?
No. It's fine to me.
-Are you close to each other?
-No!
We are neighbors around the villa.
He is not good at being close to people,
but I appreciate him very much .
I wish him to fully recover
as soon as possible.
Mr. Brighton,
I will do my best to look after him.
Please take care of him for me.
I can 't do that!
As a headmaster...
I can't change the decision of
the doctor-in-charge.
I'm willing to look after Mr. markba.
Leave this passion to other patients.
Candy, go take care of Mr. Markba.
Is doctor Frank forgive me?
It is Mr. markba 's idea.
I can 't believe this.
I'm going.
Mr. Markba,
sorry about what happened yesterday.
You know Brighton?
You saw everything from the window.
Answer my question.
Yes, he is Annie 's father
whom is my good friend.
What happened to your head?
Stay! If you know Brighton.
Leave! If you don 't know him.
Yes!
Don't move!
I'd like to draw the quilt for you.
Don't be meddlesome, stay where you are.
But, stand like this...
Stay where you are!
Don't move!
But...
Give me a shade from the sunset.
I'll draw the curtain for you.
Through the curtain,
the sunset won 't be able to seen.
Does Mr. markba like the sunset?
I told you before,
I hate the nurse who talks too much.
Yes!
Candy didn 't get angry
for being treated as a curtain.
The look of Mr. markba under the shade.
Same as the look of Terry
who she met first time.