As a result of Eliza's and Neil's
prank
Candy was labeled a thief.
I can't put up with thieves
in Leagan family!
And so they decided to send
Candy to Mexico.
Departure to an unknown country.
Good morning
Caesar, Cleopatra!
I still don't know on which day
will they send me to Mexico.
But I'll take good care of you
until that day, so don't worry.
-Candy!
-Yes
What is it?
You'll be leaving
tomorrow morning. Got it?
In the morning?
You haven't packed up yet
haven't you?
No, not yet...
Then, pack up quickly.
That way you won't be in a hurry.
We're finally parting, Candy.
We'll really miss you!
Don't come back!
Tomorrow morning... to Mexico.
No matter how fast I'm running...
it's much too soon.
Anthony, at least,
I'd like to say goodbye to you.
I'll have to part from these
rose gates, too.
What a wonderful smell!
I won't forget it!
Anthony!
Hey, Anthony!
Hello, Stear, Archie!
Working the garden, as usual?
Anthony, what was the name
of this rose again?
It's a new kind. Can I take one?
I like Candy to have one.
Archie,
you can't take any of these.
I already gave one to Candy.
I see, you already did...
What?!
Anthony, when did you...?
These roses are called
"Sweet Candy" .
"Sweet Candy" ?
I named them after Candy.
-Why, you!
-Don't you joke with us!
No, Kurin! Be quiet!
Stop that!
Aunt!
I have something to say to you.
What happened, aunt?
Listen!
You must not approach Candy.
Why?
That girl stole from the Leagans.
Candy... stole?
Yes.
That's a lie!
That's nonsense!
That's not true!
Are you certain?
There's no way she'd ever do that.
Be quiet!
As a leader of the Ardley family,
this is my decision.
You must not approach her!
I'm ordering you!
Aunt! I won't listen to your
orders anymore!
Hey, Anthony.
Don't say things you don't
know anything about!
Anthony! What's gotten into you?
You've never opposed me before.
It must be that Candy's doing...
No, you're wrong!
It was my own decision.
Aunt, I'm mad!
Oh, my!
I'm going back!
Anthony, you've...
You've angered Aunt over Candy.
I've got to do something...
If I don't prove her innocence...
Anthony
you mustn't anger your aunt.
I'd be content if you just
believed that I'm not a thief.
I'll be heading to Mexico
tomorrow.
I'll write you every day
until I come back.
And I won't forget about
Archie and Stear.
You need to live in harmony
with your aunt.
Farewell!
Candy!
She must have seen everything.
Candy
Miss tomboy!
She's upset because Aunt
said bad things about her.
Candy!
Farewell! Thank you for giving
me these fond memories!
Farewell, Anthony!
This is enough.
This beautiful forest and the lake
They're in my memory now.
Now, let's go, Kurin.
Do you know what's Ardley property
in Mexico alike?
I know a little.
It's a horrible place.
Work is much harder there.
Also, bandits sometimes
attack the property.
It's a horrible place
And they're sending Candy
to such a place...
Madam is so cruel!
The property in Mexico is
such a place...
Sister Pony...
What should I do?
Candy, you're a strong girl who
always cleared the path for herself.
You'll be okay.
No! I don't want to go to Mexico!
Kurin.
-Candy?
-Dorothy!
Everybody is waiting for you.
Come soon.
Waiting for me?
Candy.
I didn't have the power to stop them.
I'm so sorry for that.
Please, forgive me.
It's okay! I'm so happy.
My friends made a farewell party
in my honour!
We prepared this party quietly,
to avoid the madam's attention.
That's why
we did everything in secret.
Eat plenty!
Thank you, Doug.
Thank you, everybody!
Hey, Mary, haven't you promised
that you wouldn't ...
I'm sorry!
Don't cry, everybody!
No matter where I might end up,
I'll be just fine!
It's exactly like mr. Hoittman said!
I'm sure Candy will do just fine!
Candy!
You look so serious...!
Do I?
Candy.
If you're really going to Mexico...
Candy!
I'll never let you go away!
Candy, hang in there!
Do you best, Candy.
Thank you very much!
Good night!
This is... Sweet Candy?
Anthony...
Anthony must have brought them.
What's this note?
Candy. Please forgive aunt Elroy.
I'll do everything
I can for your sake.
You do your best, too!
Anthony!
-Candy is...
-To Mexico?
Aunt! Why didn't you
tell us about this?
You'd make a lot of noise if
I told you.
Of course!
Why are you sending her to
such a faraway place?
Aunt, please!
Reconsider this decision!
I can't do that.
That girl is a thief.
Candy would never do such a thing!
I saw it with my own eyes!
Eliza pulled her family's belongings
from Candy's baggage!
Neil!
Aunt, Candy is not someone who
would steal from other people!
I'm going to prove it!
Hey! Wait, Anthony!
Anthony.
Sorry.
Neil!
Neil, you set up Candy for stealing?
You won't get away!
I'll tell the truth, just stop this!
I was tricked by Candy as well.
She's a natural cheat!
And she's a thief, too!
Neil, enough nonsense!
Mother!
You framed Candy for stealing
and now
she's going to Mexico for that!
Neil, if you don't tell the truth,
it'll hurt you much, much more!
Tell the truth!
Stop!
Will you tell the truth then?
It was your and Eliza's doing,
after all.
You wanted to frame her?
Then, you'll tell the truth to aunt
Elroy first thing in the morning!
Do you swear on the honour
of the Ardley family?
She's supposed to be leaving
in the morning.
We'll see you again tomorrow!
Candy! Wake up, Candy!
They're here to pick you up
Candy.
To pick me up?
Yes. Take your things.
But I was supposed to leave
in the morning...
What? They've already come
to pick her up?
That's right, Brother.
What's the matter, Brother?
Anthony and the others are in for a
big surprise! Can't wait to see them!
The time of my departure
came so soon.
I don't have the time to bid
my farewell to Anthony.
Farewell, Caesar, Cleopatra!
Anthony!
I'm sorry to have woken up
you so early, madam.
I got here sooner than I planned.
It's okay. You were in a hurry.
Yes.
This is Candy.
Look after her.
As you please.
She's little. And that suitcase...
I can't use her if she's just
gonna mope around like that!
Bye, Candy.
Don't come back.
Now.
What's this thing?
It's a raccoon. Take it away, too.
This thing?
Caesar and Cleopatra!
Horses understood that
Candy is going to Mexico!
Mr. Hoittman
I don't want to watch this!
I'm finally leaving Leagan's estate.
I've had many
unpleasant moments here.
But I've also had so many
wonderful times!
Farewell, Dorothy, Doug
Mary, Mr. Hoittman!
I couldn't meet you in the end.
Farewell Archie, Stear...
Anthony.
Neil, I came back like I promised!
Yeah, I waited for you.
I think you turned up a bit late.
Candy is already gone!
What?
She's already far from here!
-What?
Left already? Wasn't she supposed
to leave in the morning?
If you don't believe me, you can
check the barn for yourself.
Anthony!
You're going after her!
But Candy will not come back!
No good!
I can't see them anywhere!
Candy.
I wanted to see you
until the very end.
The sound of bagpipes!
Where...
Where is it coming from?
Anthony, Archie, Stear...
Candy.
Don't cry, Anthony!
Continue playing!
Candy, you're going to Mexico
after all.
If so...
If so...!
Hey, sit still!
You'll make me angry!
Farewell
Anthony, Stear, Archie.
Hailed by the sound of bagpipes
Candy set on a journey to Mexico.