Candy and Terry...
who were both invited to the barn
with a fake letter...
were discovered by sister Gray.
Candice White Ardley!
You have made a very serious offense
Therefore
you are expelled from the school!
Until your family arrives to
pick you up...
you will be confined to the tower!
Terrius G. Grandchester!
You are confined to your room
for a week!
The punishment for Candy and Terry
were indeed quite different.
But Candy wasn't aware of that.
Within the cold, thick walls.
They didn't give me the time
to explain myself.
Everybody acted as if thigs
were crystally clear.
I can still hear Terry's voice.
Terry.
Candy...!
Terry!
Candy!
All of this must have been Eliza's idea.
Why didn't they understand?
It wouldn't have ended like this!
Whatever the reason
you and Terry were doing it!
When I arrived to the barn with sisters
both of you were inside!
Two of them alone!
No wonder they got expelled!
What a disgrace!
Two of them alone!
No wonder they got expelled!
What a disgrace!
No! I got expelled over
such a misunderstanding!
I somehow have to escape from here.
I have to see sister Gray!
Let me out!
Sister Gray.
Why wasn't I expelled from the school?
Terrius...
Weren't you supposed to be confined
to your own room?
Please, answer me!
Get out, now!
Leaving room without permission during
confinement is a violation of rules!
In that case...
how come that I wasn't expelled as well?
Why wasn't I confined
to the school's tower?
Why wasn't I treated the same way
as Candy?
Why is that?
It's because...
the boys and girls are different.
Sister Gray.
If it's because my dad keeps
donating money to the school...
how come you weren't frank about it?
Terrius G. Grandchester!
Take back what you said now!
I haven't taken any donations!
In that case, punish me the same way
you punished Candy!
Sister Gray.
You could examine the incident
more carefully.
That was a ploy!
Somebody wrote fake notes...
in order to lure both of us
into the same place!
Whether it's a ploy or not...
you were found late at night
in the barn!
That's enough.
Moreover
for a young girl to behave like that...
I can't just forgive her!
There is no helping it, then.
If it's come to this...
I'll ask my father to have
Candy's expulsion revoked.
Duke Grandchester?
My dad's influence is quite something
I guess.
Terrius!
If you do this...
you won't only hurt the honour of
this school...
Also hurt the honour of your family!
Just what is honour?
Wha... what?
Duke Grandchester is a honourable man!
He puts up with you
doing whatever you please!
Most importantly...
I am not obliged to obey
Duke Grandchester on such matters!
Now, return to your room!
Terrius G. Grandchester!
Now what...
I even resorted to help from my father
whom I hate so much...
Candy... what can I do to help you?
What can I do?
Candy. What can I do?
I can't do anything but cry now.
I go all weepy as soon as
noone is watching.
They'll inform Grandfather William
about my expulsion...
the man who adopted me
as his foster daughter!
He eagerly wanted me to become a lady!
Grandfather William.
He's going to be crushed.
Poor Candy.
Not only that they expelled her
but they also locked her in the tower.
Everybody was biased against her.
Terrius was only confined to his
room for a week!
Patty, I'm going to inform
Archie and Stear.
I'm sure that those two will get some
good ideas on how we could help Candy.
Annie, if they see you
you could end up like Candy!
I don't care. If they see me, I'll
be expelled together with Candy.
Annie!
Up until now, Candy was always
the one who helped me.
Therefore, this time
it's my turn to help her!
I understand, Annie.
I feel the same way. Let's go together.
Thank you, Patty!
But leaving this room
could pose a problem!
If somebody sees us...
We'll go Candy's way!
Patty, let's tie together these sheets!
Sheets?
We can't jump around Tarzan-style
like Candy...
so we'll use this instead.
Through the yard?
It'll be okay.
I didn't know you were capable of this.
Must be Candy's influence.
Now, let's go.
Annie, am I doing well?
Yes, Patty! Just don't look down!
Of course I won't !
Annie, don't stop... quickly
let me down! I'm scared!
You're already on the ground.
Really!
Archie's and Stear's room is up here!
How do we go inside?
Just like Candy, we climb this tree...
go across that branch, but then
we'll have to jump to the balcony.
Maybe if we threw a stone
at their window...
Stear and Archie will probably notice.
You can't do that!
If the stone bangs up against the glass
others will hear it as well.
Annie, have you ever climbed a tree?
No, but I watched Candy
while she was doing it.
I think I'll do okay.
It's hopeless...
Well, Archie...
I'm thinking about a lie detector.
What do you think?
Lie detector?
Yes. It can tell you
whether one is telling a lie or not!
Sounds fun!
We're still far from the balcony.
I'm afraid!
Jumping down from such a high place...
Would take Candy's skill to do it...
Archie, what was that sound?
Must be Candy!
Oww...
-Annie!
-Patty!
Why are you two here?
Are you okay?
Archie, Candy is in big trouble!
What? Candy?
Now that Candy was expelled
she won't be by my side anymore.
Candy.
What should I do?
Sitting alone and worrying in my room...
it won't do you any good.
Terrius! You bastard!
Archie!
What did you do to Candy?!
Terry, we're wrong about you.
We misjudged you.
You idiot!
Why did you call Candy to the barn?
Calm down, Archie!
What good does it make
if you two fight now?
Don't hold me back, brother!
Candy was expelled
because of this idiot!
Archie,
people from other rooms will notice.
If grandfather William get mad...
disowns Candy and drives her away
from the Ardley family...
Where would she go then?
Disown her?
Candy...
You! Say something!
It wasn't me.
I didn't call Candy to the barn.
I was called by her.
A note?
I'd like to talk to you about some
very important matters.
Tonight at 8 o'clock
I'll be waiting in the barn. Candy.
Candy?
This isn't Candy's handwriting!
Exactly my thoughts.
This handwriting...
Eliza!
Eliza?
She purposely changed her
handwriting a bit but...
I'm sure that
this is Eliza's handwriting!
What a horrible thing!
Well. Let's show this to sister Gray.
If we do that...
Candy might be freed!
-Hardly. Think about it.
-What?
They won't accept it.
Then...
We'll have Eliza admit it herself!
If we do that, sister Gray
will have to accept it.
Calling me to such a place...
Just what do you want from me?
We'd like to speak to you about Candy.
My, weaklings like you
want to speak to me?
It is us who'd like to speak to you!
What is it?
Are you threatening me?
It's not like we are threatening you
Eliza.
We only want a little bit of honesty
from you.
Eliza, you wrote this?
I don't know!
Don't give us that!
We sure that this is your handwriting.
Maybe it was you who wrote that?
Damn it...
I'll get a confession out of you!
You'd hit a lady?
What kind of lady are you?
I'm not going to hit you!
I'm too disgusted to touch that
putrid face of yours!
What horrible words!
Eliza, please! Help Candy!
And this one is going to
try to move me with her tears!
Eliza, if you say the truth...
Candy's expulsion will be revoked!
Hold on a second.
You are saying that it was my fault
that Candy was expelled but...
I don't know anything!
Eliza.
I'll get you to say the truth
even if I have to strangle you!
Archie, don't !
Even if you kill her, you won't
get the truth out of Eliza.
it'd be better to worried about
yourselves than about Candy?
What?
You called me out to this place.
If somebody finds out
how you threatened me...
I wonder what will happen?
Just this time, I'll turn a blind eye.
See you!
Damn! What should we do?
Why didn't I think of
that lie detector before?
Candy went through all of this
just to end up expelled from the school?
Hasn't she made any difference?
No, Candy left something big
after herself.
She helped to build a large, strong and
growing friendship between two people.
Two?
Patty and Annie.
It was Candy who brought them together.
It's all Candy's doing.
Are you fine with Candy no longer
being in this school?
-No, I wasn't saying that.
-Please, calm down.
If you must fight
could you please take it outside?
"Take it outside" , was it?
Aren't you worried about Candy?
How can you be so calm and indifferent!
Calm?
I am anything but calm.
Both of you, please leave!
-You...!
-Archie!
Brother!
Let's go.
Let's leave him alone.
Terrius.
Candy went through a lot.
That's why we are trying to
make her happy.
Terry, don't you feel the same way?
I didn't have it difficult like Candy.
My goodness...
The Candy I know - -
is always cheerful...
And yet, she grew up
knowing she was an orphan.
And what was I doing till now?
Rebelling against my father...
wasting his money...
Duke Grandchester is a honourable man!
He puts up with you
doing whatever you please!
Damn it!
I won't allow anyone to mess with you.
I won't forgive those
who caused you grief!
Now I'm the only one
who can protect Candy.
Nobody but me!
Kurin?
Kurin... where are you?
Where are you? Kurin!
You're underneath this?
Kurin!
Thank you!
Kurin, you got this muddy just to come
over to my place?
Candy.
I will stay here.
Until the morning...
If I was older...
both Candy and I would've been
able to leave this school...
while laughing and saying goodbye
without any regrets.
And then we could live together.
Terry?
Terry, it's you?
Terry!
Terry...!
Candy!
Candy, cheer up!
I will, Terry!
What happened?
You weren't punished?
Punishment, it's a bunch of crap!
Terry, it's you!
Exactly, Candy!
Whatever happens, you shouldn't grieve!
You should laugh cheerfully!
Yeah, I understand!
Thank you, Terry.
I won't cry.
I will laugh cheerfully.
If it weren't for these thick walls...
I would've shown you my smile.
I must decide...
it's for Candy's sake!
I must decide now!
After bringing his decision...
Terry appeared very sad.
However, Candy was in the tower
did not know of this.
The melody which
Terry played on his harmonica...
that gave Candy the strength
and courage to pick herself up.