Candy came back from Frannie's house.
A man was sent in to the hospital.
Candy was shocked.
This patient who just got back
from the Europe war field,
looked just like Mr.Albert.
The man who forgets his past.
Mr.Albert.
Wait!
Don't come over.
He wouldn't stay still.
So we gave him a tranquilizer.
You are responsible for this animal.
Poopet,
be good or you gonna get kicked out.
You are so skinny,
and you are losing your hair.
Doctor Reknapp,
Which ward is this patient going?
Ward number zero.
Ward number zero?
Ward number zero has not sunlight,
and it is small and dirty.
As expected.
Ward number zero is for
criminals and dying people.
He just wouldn't wake up.
That man is Mr.Albert
for sure.
Mr.Alert will not stay
in ward number zero.
Doctor Reknapp.
I know that patient,
his name is Mr.Albert.
You know that patient?
Yes, he is my friend.
Don't send him to ward number zero.
I didn't knew he was your friend.
Albert?
What is his surname?
-Surname?
-Address?
-Address...
-Family?
Why?
What is his surname?
Age?
I don't know,
I just know his name.
Although we know each other
for quite a long time...
We didn't get to know each other
too well...
I can ask Mr.Albert for his
address and family...
That's it Candy, you can go.
That man has already lost his memory.
Lost his memory?
Does Mr.Albert forget everything
about the past?
Unidentified.
Unpaid hospital bills.
He doesn't seemed to be
seriously hurt.
Ward number zero will be fine.
I am doing the best I can do.
Candy.
Candy,
Stay out of this.
Yeah.
Having a student
who knows a criminal,
is a shame for
Merry Jane Nurse School.
Mr.Albert is not a criminal.
He didn't lose his memory.
We will see when he wakes up.
He will be fine when he
sees me and Poopet.
Poopet,
will Mr.Albert forget about you?
He liked you so much,
how would he...
This is a nightmare.
The Mr.Albert I knew...
Mr.Albert.
Poopet, stay in my room.
Have a good rest, ok?
Be good.
Candy,
That patient came from Italy.
Italy?
I heard that the bombing caused
his injury when he was on the train.
He was trying to protect that stinky.
He tried to protect Putin.
That explains why
that stinky wouldn't leave.
Candy, stay out of this.
I heard that
there was a spy on the train.
He claimed that
he has lost his memory.
He must be a spy.
Just happened to be
on the same train.
And you think of
Mr.Albert as a spy!
He is not that type of person!
How unlucky to have someone
like him in this hospital.
He has been murmuring words like
America and Chicago unconsciously.
Unconsciously...
Such wounded
shouldn't not be sent here.
It is not easy for those
hospitals in Italy.
They couldn't do anything for him.
That's why he is here?
He has been murmuring words
such as America and Chicago.
The whole hospital is
is talking about Mr.Albert.
He is not widely welcomed.
Mr.Albert,
Why were you in Italy?
Weren't you in Africa?
You had a small clinic there...
And you were taking of the animals.
You were always so bright...
Full of energy...
Travelling all over,
So free like a wind.
Poopet
Aren't you suppose to be in the room?
You gonna get into troubles
if you keep wandering around.
Poopet,
do you want to see Mr.Albert?
Me too.
Smells moldy.
Mr.Albert,
You became thinner.
Looks so handsome
without sun glasses.
Mr.Albert, please wake up,
I don't want a reunion
with you losing your memory.
Poopet, don't worry.
I will stay by your side
I will protect you.
Mr.Albert,
Are you up?
I hope you can regain conscious.
Is the doctor going to help him?
We just can't leave him
in the room like that.
It hurts.
Nurse, help me.
Stear.
What is wrong?
Nurse,
My leg...
Archie,
My arm...
Annie,
What happened to you all?
How are we going to see you
if we don't pretend to be patients?
Your bandage looks bad.
Brother said this is better.
Yeah, just like a wounded.
Stear, Archie and Annie,
Why do they show up
at such time?
You alright, be careful.
Come with me.
What a helpful young nurse?
So grateful.
That's it!
Welcome!
Candy, did you meet Terry?
Yes, just for a short moment.
Terry left with the train.
The wind connects us together.
Great, Candy.
Why so you seem lifeless
even though you have seen Terry?
Why? Candy.
You looked upset.
We shall go to the yard.
Right.
I wanted to go to the yard.
I have something to show you.
Me?
What is it?
Come! Candy.
Pattie!
Candy!
I miss you, Candy!
I miss you too,
it has been so long, Pattie!
Candy,
I came to Chicago last night
and I couldn't wait to see you.
She wanted to see you so desperately,
she has been bothering me about that.
Now we meet, Pattie.
It has been ages since we
seperated in London.
Candy,
You look very nice in this dress.
Thank you.
You look like you have
put on some weight.
Come on, Pattie.
Take a closer look...
Stear...
This is hospital.
Aren't you guys patients?
Yeah.
America is so peaceful.
There is no war here.
London is pretty bad.
More and more women got on
to the field as medical crews.
Woman goes on to the field?
They volunteered to go on
to the field.
Man should go on to the field
and protect and love their family.
Couples fighting on the field.
How can we stand aside and watch?
Brother,
You look like
you can't wait to go to war.
Pattie, has St.Paul Instituition
changed at all?
It has not changed much.
Principal Grey is just
as strict as he always was.
St.Paul Instituition,
Second Pony Hill,
London City, big roads,
On going cars,
These will change because of war.
I ran away from the instituition
during the May Festival,
to go to the Blue river zoo
and meet up with Mr.Albert.
Yeah, Candy, Yuli is here as well.
I brought it out from the zoo.
Next time I will bring it...
Yuli,
I handed it over to Mr.Albert.
Mr.Albert was very happy.
Candy, what is wrong?
Mr.Albert...
What happened to Mr.Albert?
Mr.Albert is in this hospital.
Is it true? Candy.
Injured? Or sick?
He is not just injured...
Mr.Albert has changed,
He lost his memory.
How could this happen?
Italy's hospital sent him here.
This hospital does not welcome him.
Quiet.
No, he hasn't regained consciousness.
Let me see him Candy.
It is better not to see him
before he reains consciousness.
It just makes us feel bad.
Even worse if I leave
without seeing him.
Please Candy.
This is Mr.Albert's beloved Poopet.
Smells moldy,
such as lousy room.
Is he Mr.Albert?
I didn't have much impression,
but I am sure it's him.
Is he really Mr.Albert?
He is so handsome.
Why is he wearing sun glasses
all day?
Brother, cut it.
Brother.
Unforgivable.
Such a kind man.
Because of the war...
Just tell us
if there is anything we can do.
Please do, Candy.
Thank you.
I will tell you guys if I need help.
We will be back, Candy.
Take care of Mr.Albert.
Good bye, Candy.
Good bye.
Right,
I have to take care of Mr.Albret.
I will swap with the nurse
in charge.
New bed sheet and blanket,
New clothes,
Fruits and juice,
I am sure this would help
Mr.Albert.
You are...
He lost his memory indeed.
He doesn't even know I am Candy.
Mr.Albert.
Sorry, Poopet,
you must be hungry.
Mr.Albert
should eat something too.
Please stay on the bed
as you just woke up.
Where is this place...
America.
Chicago St.Joanna Hospital.
I see, I was sent back here
to America.
Chicago.
America.
Chicao, America.
Mr.Albert.
Don't force yourself
to think things.
Lie down and rest.
Who is Mr.Albert?
Why did you call me that?
Mr.Albert.
If I tell you that
we knew each other now.
It's just going to make you
more confused.
Who is Mr.Albert?
I am sorry,
Albert is my brother's name.
You look just like my brother.
And it's quite hard to call you
without a name.
You don't like it?
That's alright,
It's your brother's name.
But, my name...
My name...
No, I can't remember.
Don't force yourself.
You will start to remember
when you are recovering.
And you will remember your name.
Trust me, I am a
well-known nurse in this hospital
You?
Don't worry,
I will take care of you.
I will keep you company.
Your name is...
I am sorry, I am Candy White.
Just call me Candy.
Miss Candy.
Candy is fine.
Candy.
Yes.
Right, just Candy.
This is how
Mr.Albert always called me.
This is Poopet.
Poopet.
I guess you want a name,
Nice name.
Just wait,
I wish Mr.Albert
can remember everything.
I will take good care of him
until then.
Candy made her decision
deep down her heart.