Tom was adopted by Mr. Steve.
Suddenly,
Pony's home feels lonely.
Take off!
Adventuring together!
John wet his sheets again!
You'd better do that
before going to bed!
I'm sorry.
Why, you!
Annie, can you catch him?
Annie,
Clint wants to eat some dried meat.
Annie, what's wrong?
Do you have a fever?
It's nothing.
But you don't look good.
How nice...
to have a mother and a father.
I got it now, Annie!
You are ill, after all!
It's your spirit that is ill.
Annie!
It's just that I'm a bit lonely.
Annie, that's exactly what I was
trying to say. Leave it to me!
What are you going to do?
Look forward to the tomorow morning!
Annie! Hey, Annie!
Candy!
Why so early?
We are going to cure your spirit!
Now, hurry up and get dressed!
Sister Lane, I'm so sorry...
Looks like we'll have some
great weather today!
Candy, is this okay?
It's okay! Now, let's go!
Sister Pony!
Oh, good morning, Sister Lane.
I've found this note,
Candy and Annie have..
That's Candy's writing, isn't it?
"Sister Pony, Sister Lane, Good morning."
"Annie and I have set on a journey
in order to cure Annie's spirit."
-To cure her spirit, oh my!
-Sister Pony!
"I felt that Annie was a bit
under the weather lately,"
...so that's why I thought
a picnic might cheer her up.
Candy does these things all the time!
"We don't know where we'll go,
but we'll come back before dark."
"Therefore, don't worry."
"We also took some bread, cheese..."
"... and wine that sister Pony
used to drink before going to bed."
Wine? Oh!
Well then, cheers!
Do you think it's okay?
Don't worry! Sister Pony drinks
this stuff every night!
Wonderful!
Feels great!
-Candy has disappeared!
-She'll soon come back.
John, why don't we wait for her in the back?
Help me make some nests for the chicken.
Now, hurry up!
Sister Pony, I'm going to look
for them after all.
Sister Lane, I don't think that
it's a good idea.
Why is that?
In ten years that Candy and Annie
have been here,
...not once have we taken them
to a picnic.
But that's because we had no money.
We had no money,
that should'nt stop them from going.
Sister Lane, don't be so hard on them.
I'm sure they'll have wonderful
memories of this day.
I'm going!
Candy.
Candy?
Candy, where are you?
Candy! I won't forgive you for this!
Annie, let's catch it!
Wait up!
Looks like it's waiting for us!
I've grown so thirsty!
It's cold!
Annie! It feels good!
The stream looks too fast!
I'm afraid.
Leave it to me!
What are you going to do?
Tie this end to that tree over there.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Candy, I'm glad I came.
You don't feel so lonely anymore, right?
Want to go to the other side?
Annie!
Don't let go of the rope!
-Annie!
-Candy!
Candy!
Annie! Don't let go of my hand!
Mr. Brighton, it's girls!
They are going to drown
if we don't help them!
That's terrible!
Both of you,
don't let go of that rope!
There!
I'll help you.
It's okay.
You're safe now.
(you're safe now...)
Lucy, where are the girls?
Mr. Brighton, just look at them!
We look a bit different now!
I prepared something nice for you.
Here, come this way.
Mr. Brighton, now you have
two girls at home!
Two girls...
Smells wonderful!
Candy!
Here, come this way!
How do we eat this stuff?
It's unusual to you?
We eat this for the first time!
Right, Annie?
At Pony's home,
we'd get in a lot of trouble
if we didn't eat properly!
Let's eat!
Tasty!
Candy, don't pig out.
No, as for barbecue, it's okay to eat
any way you like it, since it's so tasty.
It's really tasty!
By the way, what exactly is
Pony's home?
Oh, mister, you don't know?
I don't come very often to this house.
It's a place for children
without parents.
Oh, that's so sad.
But the two of us don't really
look sad, do we?
Well, not really!
Do you know why Annie's and
my birthday are on the same day?
No idea.
You don't really look like twins.
It's because we were found abandoned
on the same day!
Candy!
On the same day!
Huh?
Is something on my face?
Huh? No...
Lucy, bring some lemonade.
Here you go, mr. Brighton!
I wonder if it's for us too!
-Candy!
-But...
Here, it's all for you!
After you eat up, would you
like to ride a horse?
-Sounds like fun!
-But I'm afraid.
Don't worry, our horses are calm.
This horse looks so nice!
Come, your turn.
Here you go.
Go!
We are moving!
Of course you are!
Candy!
This place became lively again
after such a long time!
It's almost as if master's
late daughter came back to life.
You aren't afraid anymore?
No, because I can hold on to you.
-Candy?
-What is it?
Are you sure we aren't dreaming
the same dream?
Because today was like in a dream.
Maybe so.
I've only slept in a crummy
old bed at Pony's home,
the bed here looks like
it was made for a princess!
Well then, Annie.
Candy?
Let's live together with this man.
What do you mean?
He could adopt the two of us
as his daughters!
Annie! How can you say such a thing?
You understand that you can't
stay forever at Pony's home?
No. I don't want that.
Listen to me, Candy.
If we become his daughters,
we could stay together forever.
Annie!
When did you become so selfish?
Like sister Pony was always saying,
abandoning others at any time is wrong!
But I want to stay together with you!
And you'd entrust yourself to some
person you've never met before?
Brightons are good people!
Well then, do as you like!
Yes, I will.
I don't know you anymore!
Candy! Where are you going?
Back to Pony's home!
You can become their daughter,
if you want to!
Wait, Candy!
-I hate you!
-Wait!
I want my papa and mama.
Gentle papa and mama.
John! Where are you?
Teacher, I couldn't find him!
I wonder where'd he go.
Teacher, somebody is coming.
I wonder who it is...
Candy!
What kind of outfit is that?
What happened to Annie?
Annie has...
Candy, John had disappeared.
What happened to him?
He disappeared right after the lunch.
He must have gone looking for you.
John was trying to find us?
-John!
-Candy, where are you going?
John!
You're here, after all.
Candy! You found John.
Be quiet.
-Candy, careful.
-Leave it to me!
That was scary!
John. Wake up, John!
Candy!
Don't give me that,
you got me so worried!
Hold on tightly
until I get us down!
Down from where?
Be careful!
That's Brightons' carriage!
Candy? What happened?
Quickly come down! Or...
-Ouch.
-Candy, are you okay?
Ah! Annie!
What's all this about?
Annie!
You brought Annie back, didn't you?
Miss, Mr. Brighton is very worried.
I'm sorry. Where is Annie?
She'll be staying at the villa tonight.
I came to see if you safely made it back.
Annie won't be coming back?
She reminded him of his late daughter.
Mr. Brighton's ?
I see.
We have plenty of food, go ahead!
Yes, thank you!
Candy's favorite nuts!
Here, Candy.
We should have brought that girl, too.
Lucy, is the stew done yet?
Bring it quickly.
Yes.
Sister Pony,
Mr. Brightons may adopt her tomorrow!
That's right.
Annie probably can't wait, too.
I'm sure she'll be okay,
becoming a daughter of a good family.
Sister Pony, Sister Lane.
Candy?
I hate you all!
Annie.
Candy.
She is pretending to sleep.
She can't sleep either?
It's hard for her.
To sleep without Annie next to her.
for the first time.
Sister Lane, let's call it a day.
Annie!
Candy.
It was John...
Clint!
The storm kept you awake, too?
Annie might not come back.
But I...
Clint?
Annie.
Annie?
-Candy.
-It's really Annie.
I wanted to come back.
All night long.
Candy!
Annie!
I'm so glad. Annie.
I wanted to see you so much, Candy.
I couldn't stop thinking about you,
I came here first thing in the morning.
I, too, thought all night about you.
Candy, about me wanting to become
Brighton's daughter...
Still..?
No.
Really? That's great!
Here.
These are..
I brought them to you,
it's your favorite nuts.
Annie.
Annie! We'll be friends forever!
I'll never let go of you ever again!
That's right!