Candy realized that, it's not easy
to take care of the patients.
The headmaster Merry Jane
who is strong and cordial.
That is a real nurse.
The smiling nurse.
We 'll stop here today.
Observe the rule
while you are practicing.
Yes!
What's wrong with you? Louder!
Distribute the task, Frannie.
You take charge of the special ward,
start from today.
That's great, Frannie, to look after
the patient of special ward.
She 's the top student.
We can 't compare with her.
Quiet!
Miss Shany, I have a question.
What's it? Frannie.
What about the patients
I'm taking care of?
Leave them to Candy!
Leave them to me?
Candy is a fresh man.
It's hard for her to handle that.
Frannie, don't worry. I will do my best.
Candy can 't make it alone.
And...
it's you who helped her all this time.
No problem.
I'll do as what Frannie taught me.
Candy,
do your best while you 're practicing.
Yes, I will.
All by myself.
Sounds like that I'm a nurse already!
Peacock!
Really!
As a fresh man. If she can
take care of those patients...
how embarrassed Frannie will be?
Better than the top student Frannie.
Frannie looked depressed.
I don 't like to be defeated
by a fresh man either.
Take the temperature.
Hello! Dim-wit.
My name is not dim-wit.
I am Candice White Ardley.
I shouldn 't said the word Ardley.
It's unfair to Grandfather William.
What's the matter?
Candice White Ardley.
No, I was wrong.
My name is Candice White.
You can 't even say your name correctly.
What a dim-wit.
Please call me Candy from now on.
But, the dim-wit is more fun.
It's headmaster's fault.
Dim-wit, why are you standing there?
They are making fun of me,
I don 't want to look at them.
Don 't be depressed,
there 's nothing wrong as a dim-wit.
Anthony, Stear and Archie,
they told me that before.
I match with a smiling face.
Yes, just like that!
Keep your face smiling, dim-wit!
They keep calling me dim-wit,
why don 't I accept that?
Alright! You can call me dim-wit.
You must cooperate with me
from now on.
Sure!
It's a deal, dim-wit.
Let's take the temperature now.
Open your mouth, guys!
It's open.
Thank you!
Please!
Finished.
Everyone!
Thank you for your cooperation.
Haven 't you forgot anything?
Dim-wit.
It's all done. Have a nice day, guys.
Good bye.
Do your best, Candy!
Candy?
They called me Candy.
Dim-wit.
Did Pony teach you that
walking like this in the corridor?
No!
It's corridor,
don 't you know that? Dim-wit.
I am sorry!
Behave yourself, dim-wit.
Yes!
All of you...
You 're healthy enough
to leave the hospital.
Dim-wit! Get back to work!
Yes!
The patients are more optimistic
since she 's here.
Will you please help me?
Yes!
The pillow makes me uncomfortable.
I'll handle it.
It's okay now, please!
Thank you!
-Excuse me.
-Yes!
The bandage has been loose,
will you help me?
Gosh! I am not ready for that.
-Will you please?
-Okay.
Am I doing the right thing?
The patient's psychological
is not stable.
Don't make the patient panic.
I should not make her panic...
or she will not trust me afterwards.
Just a moment.
It's...
I am sorry!
Everyone will make a mistake.
No one is born to doing things right.
It's nothing to make a mistake,
you can make it right next time.
I am sorry.
Always keep your smiling.
The patients will get recovery
because of your smile.
Yes!
The patients will get recovery
because of my smile?
They are so kindness.
-Candy!
-Frannie!
Is it a hard work?
Not at all! Patients are
willing to cooperate with me.
I see!
-Candy!
-What's the matter?
Don't please the patient on purpose.
Our patients are talking about
the things you did.
Things I did?
They wish to be taken care by you.
Candy!
Can you look after all the patients?
But... I...
Candy, I am your room mate,
here is my advise.
A good nurse would never
please the patients on purpose.
Yes!
Who 's crying?
Frannie?
Frannie.
What happened? Frannie.
It's nothing.
But, Frannie, Just now...
Mind your own business.
Frannie!
I had told you...
I hate the one who talk too much.
I am sorry!
A tough girl like Frannie shouldn 't cry.
I can't believe this.
What's happened?
Here is the special ward
in which Frannie take care of.
What's the patient looked like?
I am not your servant.
I hate to take care of you.
I neglected my duty,
I'm not a good nurse.
The patient of the special ward
treated her as a servant.
Frannie is a top student,
she can 't bear that.
That's why she cried last night.
Frannie, how is the special ward?
It's easy.
The patient in the special ward
must different from others.
The rich people should be unreasonable,
shouldn 't them?
He is very kindness.
How nice.
I too want to look after the patient
in the special ward.
You can 't.
You are not a top student.
I'm leaving.
Frannie, is he rich?
It is said that
he has some land on the lakeside.
And some villas too.
That's great!
Lakeside? Villa?
same as the Ardley family.
An odd and wordy old man.
Frannie!
-No, he is talkative.
-That's terrible.
However, he is kind to me.
Frannie is truly
good at dealing with the patient.
He asks everybody to
call him Grandfather William.
William?
Grandfather William of Ardley family?
He 's here!
I wanted to see him all the time.
Frannie!
Please, Frannie. Let me take care of him.
I really want to look after him.
Candy!
-You are a fresh man.
-Unreasonable.
Please, Frannie.
You are a fresh man.
How can you look after the patient
in the special ward?
I have to take care of him,
no matter how.
Please! Let me look after him.
Do you covet his money?
No!
Alright.
Let's change our shifts tomorrow.
Frannie!
You must do that carefully.
Yes!
You are filled with confident.
I'll report to the headmaster.
Thank you, Frannie!
At last,
I can meet with the Grandfather William.
The grandfather William
adopted me as his daughter.
The dream finally come true.
-Wait!
-Candy!
Arrogant!
She won 't make it.
Leave it to her without authorization,
you might get trouble.
Don 't worry!
Master William won 't like her.
She will be finished soon.
What?
Leave the special ward to her?
Does the patient trouble you?
No, it's Candy's idea.
You are not that kind of person
who is willing to give up easily.
No, I never give up.
You are the only person
who can take care of that patient.
Candy?
You want to try her?
Yes!
Are you making fun of her?
No!
Frannie, it's still your job.
That dim-wit might mess things up.
She 'll need your help by then.
Yes!
The headmaster promised that?
Thank you!
What is Grandfather William looked like?
an affable face with white beard...
as serious as Aunt Elroy.
Will he be surprised
when we meet each other?
He would be surprised for sure
that I was here.
I left the St. Paul academy
without telling him...
Gosh!! I'm sure to be blamed.
Grandfather,
I'll look after you as an apology.
Please don't blame me.
I can 't wait to see you.
The day
I became the daughter of Ardley family...
I was expecting to meet you gratefully.
The days in Lakewood,
the life in London...
It's you who gave me that.
We are now so close to each other.
You are now In the special ward
with illness.
I would do everything for you.
No! I was overslept.
I was too happy to sleep last night.
Didn 't notice that
Frannie was already get up.
Headmaster Merry Jane!
Good morning! Dim-wit.
It's your cap again.
Good morning!
Where is here? Dim-wit.
Sorry, it's corridor.
So, it's street here...
How can you look after the patient
in a place like that?
Headmaster!
I will not be dim again.
Let me look after Grandfather William.
Please!
You should ready for that...
you would do everything he asked.
He is a patient anyway.
Yes!
Good, go to Doctor Frank.
-He has words to you.
-Yes, I'm going.
Dim-wit, It's corridor here.
What a ...
The headmaster is an odd guy...
so does Grandfather William.
I won 't mind.
I'll do everything he asked.
He must be a kind person
or he won 't adopt me as his daughter.
Excuse me!
I am doctor Frank.
I am Candy, nice to meet you.
This is the nurse's room,
the patient is in the next door.
The special ward
is quite different from other...
The patient needs rest. Be quiet!
I am sorry!
He 's an odd guy...
speak carefully and watch your attitude.
Yes! I will, doctor.
Please! Anyway.
Grandfather is behind this door.
Behind this door...
Grandfather William!
Under my taking care of,
you will be recovery soon enough.
Candy drops her tears.
The sight is dimmer and dimmer
through her tears.