Candy!
Terry!
Their short reunion.
Candy and Terry...
Have sperated again reluctantly.
Miserable Terry
Thank you.
Lets go
The class in the evening
has already started.
Normal bullet wound
Is likely to recover fast if the
bullet has penetrated the body
If the bullet stays in the body
We must perform operation immediately
At this moment
we need to watch out for...
Who let you in?
I am sorry.
I won't accpet any late student
in my class. Get out!
There won't be next time.
Next time?
We are dealing with human lives here!
Who do you think you are!
Get out!
Yes!
I can't do anything.
Teacher Popson was right.
The first aid for bullet wounds.
War is coming.
Is that why
we need to attend this calss?
We have a wounded in the emergency
Tumbled down from the train and
seriously hurt. Please help!
Ready for operation.
Sorry for asking...
Doctor, those trainee nurses...
This is chance for them to learn
Give me two good trainees
Please...
Frannie and Natalie
Assist Doctor Popson
with his operation
Yes!
The rest do some self-study.
What are you doing?
Go get some self-study.
Yes!
Candy!
No, It's Impossible!
I heard that Doctor Popson's patient...
is an actor from the Stellas troupe.
Stellas troupe?
That is Terry's troupe
Judy,
what is the name of the patient?
Oh yes!
He seems to be a famous young actor
Famous young actor...
It cant be...
Candy, where are you going?
Natalie, what happened to you?
Candy,
can you help to look after Natalieb?
She is feeling a bit anaemic.
Natelie, are you alright?
Frannie, the patient...
How do you feel?
Candy.
Don't tell anyone
I fainted in the operation room.
I could not make it.
Is it that serious?
We might lose him.
Candy!
The operation is over.
Wait!
What is the matter with you?
You skipped your night shift and
were late for class.
That is because...
Natalie is not any better.
She faints when she sees blood.
How can she be a nurse?
Sorry
Having students like you
in Merry Jane Nurse School.
Is a shame
Frannie, why did you
vent your anger to Natalie?
Candy don't waste time.
Go fill the name card for the patient.
The name is Terry.
Terry!
I didn't expect to write your name
in situation like this
Terry, I am Candy.
You hear me?
You heard me, right?
Why did you so such stupid thing?
Terry.
Did you jumped off the train for me?
Terry
Elisa!
You 'd better break up.
What do you mean?
The Largon will be responsible for
Terry's expenses
Elisa 's familly?
It is really mean
for those people in the troupe.
They didn't even show up
when Terry is so hurt like this
Terry, don't worry
The troupe is preparing
for the next show.
You don't seem too happy at me
taking care of Terry
Terry should be the one
who is unhappy.
What are you talking about?
You better watch out!
I am Candice White.
Are you looking for me?
Candy
You will report to the
internal medicaine start from tomorrow
But I am a surgery nurse...
What is going on?
You don't need to know the reason.
This is the order from the principal.
Principal?
Elisa
Elisa must be behind this.
Look after with care.
If anything to my Terry...
you will be responsible
Natalie,
Is it alright to cut here?
Ok
Listen!
It is not big deal
to dismiss some trainee nurses.
I understand Ms.Elisa
The other thing...
I will not allow Candy
to go anywhere near the room.
Yes, Miss.Elisa
-So Annoying
-Indeed
Her father is a close friend
of the Mayor.
The principal listens to whatever
the mayor says.
Terry.
We are such close to each other.
Yet I can't take care of you.
Nurse
Me?
Yes, you
Can I help you?
Candy.
Do I know you?
It is me, don't you remember me?
Who are you?
Stear!
Why did you disguise like this?
I don't want Elisa to see me.
She won't come to the
internal department
I am here for Terry...
Terry is staying in this hospital
for the time being.
Yesterday...
Somebody saw Terry in another city.
How is that possible?
Terry fell down from the train...
and stayed in this hospital.
Did you see his face?
That is weird.
I could recall...
His eyes were filled with fear.
Candy, you should look into it.
I will look into it.
It would be fun, if he is not Terry
Because Elisa would be
taking care of a stranger.
Candy, what are you doing there?
This patient is lost.
Hand the case to the doctor.
Nurse,
is it the end of the right lobby?
I got it. Thank you.
Nurse.
Can you change the flowers?
But yesterday's flowers...
Flowers need to be changed everyday.
Terry,
just ask if you need anything.
Oh yeah, the curtain is horrible
Get it changed at once and then...
And, place another bed here tonight.
In this room?
I want to take care of Terry
for twenty-four hour
May I? Terry.
Whatever.
Elisa is staying here tonight?
Candy,
I promise that patient one thing.
He wants to see you
before Elisa shows up.
Me? Did he mention my name?
Yes, Elisa will show up
in the evening.
Thank you. Natalie
Just as expected.
Candy!
Can't you recognise my voice?
Candy.
I am Charlie, Terry's friend
Charlie?
The guy from the wharf.
Wharf?
I remember, Sandra's friend.
Now then you remember.
Charlie, Why?
I had to disguise as Terry
What happened to you?
I escaped from prison.
From where?
A place where people like me
are trapped.
Terry!
Shit!
He is there! Stop right there!
Stop!
When I was sent to this hospital...
I use the name Terry.
Someone will find out sooner or later
I will escape from here
before that happens.
Charlie, this is not right.
Candy, this is a decent hospital.
If only that rich girl is not around.
If Elisa finds out that
you are not Terry...
She won't if I don't speak.
Please leave.
We have nurses to attend to
special ward.
There is no need for family
to be here.
Do you know who I am?
Of course
You are disturbing our nurses.
What did you say?
What is your name?
Frannie Hamilton.
I won't forget you, lets go
Frannie was good.
Candy?
Yes? I am alone here.
He is not Terry.
Candy, isn't this Candy?
The voice... it is somebody else.
He recognised Candy.
-What happened? Charlie.
-Candy!
Someone is in this room.
Who is there? Come out!
Elisa
Candy, who is this guy?
Damn!
Stop it! Charlie
You are Charlie?
I will inform the principal.
Wait! Elisa
Hold on!
You know that fake guy.
He does not really want to be known.
He...
Anyway, he does not have
the same background as we do.
Right? Candy.
Did that fake do anything wrong?
No, he is here because...
Cand, lets make a deal.
Deal?
If you leave Chicago...
I will pretend like
I never seen anything.
Leave Chicago? but the hospital...
Yes, I want you to leave
this hospital
I feel uncomfortable to see you
always around.
Are you serious?
I won't do it
I always wanted to be a nurse...
Whatever...
Think about it before dawn.
Charlie
She might call the police
or something.
She won't. Charlie
Go back to the bed or
your wound will split.
Wait! Candy
Can I trust you?
It is getting interesting.
That fake does not want
the police to know...
Mark, Go to the police station.
Candy, it is late now,
go back to your room.
You don't have to worry about me.
You need to get yourself healed.
You are a nurse now.
I still have a lot to learn.
Candy is a nurse,
Terry is an actor.
Look at me now.
Terry and I have just started.
You can too.
I know what I am suppose to do.
Yes?
That is why I escaped from prison.
What do you want to do?
Join the army.
Army?
Charlie
I think you know that
war has already started in Europeh.
America will join the war
sooner or later.
America?
I will serve my country.
Why?
I have been stealing
since I was young.
I did bad things.
I bullied the weaker.
I am not trying to make up
for what I have done.
I just want to protect
the vulnerable.
I will not let them to sacrifice
for the war.
Charlie, turn yourself in.
Turn myself in? Are you kidding?
I don't know when I will come out
if I am caught this time
I need to go to the army
as soon as possible.
That is him.
-Charlie
-Charlie Sanders
No, get off me!
-Come on
-Charlie
You lied to me!
No, I didn't lie to you.
Candy!
Were you looking for me?
-Come here.
-Yes.
Sign here.
Application to quit from study.
Am I dismissed?
The police have asked for
your assistance.
You might need to leave the
hospital if it gets big.
Leave the hospital?
There are evidences showing that
you have sheltered a criminal.
Elisa, you never keep your words.
Just sign it.
Candy's future is in darkness.
These unexpected incidents
Frustrating journey for
Candy's nurse dream.
Is set to face yet another crisis.