Safex
You are prettier when you're smiling
than when you're crying.
Candy's wondering
Who is the dreamlike young boy?
The image of this young boy,
Candy though as...
The prince came from dreamland.
From today, I'll be a princess?
Sister Pony, Sister Lane,
thank you for everything!
You're going after all, Candy?
I promise Annie and everyone,
I will find my own happiness.
That's why I'll...!
Why so suddenly?
Why don't we make the sad parting
as short as possible?
And, don't tell the little kids that
I'm leaving to Lakewood.
Not going to say farewell to them?
I don't want to say farewell to anyone.
Candy...
Sister Pony?
Though you're a little tomboyish,
you're so cheerful, caring and gentle.
ll give this to you,
the God will always look after you.
Yes.
What is that?
Every child who leave here.
Sister Lane will make her a new pajama.
You never had a new pajama...
Teacher. I'm not crying!
Candy, you're a cheerful, strong girl!
You mustn't cry, even in hardest times!
Patty! From today, entire bed is yours!
All girls who sleep in this bed
will become beautiful like me!
John, stay well!
Don't wetting your bed anymore!
Sam, don't go around bullying girls!
Milly, eat all your veggies!
Thank you, sister Lane.
I'll go while everyone is still asleep.
Sister Pony, Sister Lane, please,
don't wake up for me.
We couldn't sleep, either.
Of all the kids, I think that Candy was
the hardest one to let go of...
She was with us since she was a baby.
That tomboyish girl whom
somebody left at our doorstep.
Farewell.
Candy!
What's the matter, John?
Sister Lane!
Come here!
What happened, John?
Ta-dah! I didn't wet my bed!
That's incredible, John.
Where is Candy?
Candy!
She...
This is the first time
I haven't wet my bed.
Candy is nowhere to be found!
Sister Lane, where is Candy?
Candy?
Candy is...
Don't go out dressed like that!
Come back!
Stop! It's dangerous!
John! Get down.
Look! Candy!
I didn't wet my bed!
It's not fair!
Don't you want to know about this?!
Candy!
Stay well. Find your happiness.
Kurin! It's you.
You came a long way.
I'm sorry, I don't think I can
take you to Lakewood.
Now, go back.
You mustn't follow me!
Aww, come on...
Can't help it, well.
Look, a mountain of carrots!
Now!
I'm too tired for this.
Kurin!
I give up.
Alright. You can come with me.
Kurin!
Excuse me,
can you take me to Lakewood?
Thanks anyway.
Please! No way...
Who... What are you doing?
Hey, Candy!
Tom! It's you.
What do you think of my son?
You've been doing well
since you leave Pony's home.
Now I'm much better with
lasso than you are!
I wonder if it's true!
Tom, why don't you show her?
Come.
Candy, see that tree?
A blind man could see it!
Well, Candy, want to try?
Damn it, this light is deceiving!
Making a excuses,
that's not you, Candy!
Okay, look at this.
That's incredible, Tom!
I thought about your skill,
and practice all the time.
So that's how it was...!
Teacher is pleased!
That's a good one!
So...You're going to
become a princess like Annie.
I'll always stay Candy!
It would be better for you
as an ordinary people like me.
Why?
If you become like Annie,
I wouldn't be able to say hello to you.
Come on,
you can always come to my house.
As soon as
I arrive to Leagans in Lakewood.
Leagan family of Lakewood?
You know them?
I heard about them.
The Leagan family...
A girl like Candy would better
have nothing to do with them.
-Take care, Candy!
-Tom, you too!
Thank you very much!
Candy! Hold on a second.
Candy, It's a big world.
May not all be fun and games,
like in Pony's home.
Life might be hard.
Yet, you must never give up.
I won't .
Try to stay cheerful and tomboyish,
always keep your spirits up.
No matter what happens,
mustn't cry, understand?
Mr. Steve, you talk the same thing
as sister Pony!
Sister Pony?
I see.
Sister Pony said the same thing!
Take care, then! Do your best!
Mr. Steve, you too!
Thanks. See you again!
Farewell.
Candy, farewell!
Farewell!
Oh, no! Tom! Your lasso!
Keep it!
Just in case somebody is mean to you!
Thanks!
Let's go, Kurin.
I wonder what the house look like?
I'm so impatient.
Kurin, let's make a run for it!
What a house!
Just like the house from fairy tale!
I'm sure the Prince is living here!
Kurin, let's go. Excuse me!
You guys!
Now you've done it!
Like this?
It hurts! Stop!
I'm going to pull you down
unless you apologize!
It hurts! I'll fall!
Help me, mohter!
Mother!
What's up with this noise?
What are you doing to my son?
Nice to meet you!
I'm Candy from Pony's home.
This is mistress.
This is miss Eliza.
The young master , Neil.
And.. are there any others?
Only Mr. Leagan.
That's weird, I thought
there was someone else.
The prince...
I mean, the one with bagpipes...
older than Neil...
Don't relate to me so easily!
Mother, has this girl gone crazy?
A prince with bagpipes...
I'm scared!
It's okay, Kurin.
Eliza, you coward!
Now she's talking to me!
listen, Candy.
Relate to Neil as mister.
Eliza as miss.
In this house, the siblings relating
eachother with mister and miss?
Our sibling?! This tramp?
That's a good joke!
Stewart, what have you told Candy?
Yes, I told her that
She'll be the daughter of the Leagans.
So, I'll treat you like a daughter,
and let you go anywhere...
Like...?
However,
Eliza and Neil are not your siblings.
Then I...
You are the playmate of Eliza.
I don't want a playmate!
Your Father's idea.
Stewart, I'm going out.
Prepare the car!
Yes, madam.
Let's go, brother.
How terrible!
Think of her as our sibling!
Kurin,
they don't want to be my sibling.
I still don't have parents.
Even, there is no prince here.
Terrible.
Room is ready.
Hello! I'm Candy!
My name is Dorothy.
-Let's be friends!
-Okay.
Please, come this way.
It's in the attic,
not the prettiest room here...
Go! Jump on Candy's face!
Look out!
Dorothy! Are you okay?
I'm okay!
You two...
What's this?
What are you doing with my pajama?
You call this a pajama?
I thought it was a rag!
Let's see what it can do!
It's a good rag!
Sister Lane made this pajama...
I could wipe my shoes.
What are you doing?!
I won't forgive you!
I won't put up with this anymore!
Somebody come!
Eliza! You're gonna get it, too!
Stop! Please stop!
Help! Somebody!
Stop! What are you doing?
Really. It's not the prettiest room.
But it's my own room,
Kurin? Isn't it nice?
Yes!
Mistress wants to see you.
Must about the incident today.
She'll punish Eliza and Neal.
I'll forgive them
if they want to apologize.
It is you should apologizing!
What?!
Or, you're be out of here tomorrow.
I prefer leaving here
to stay with you horrible people.
What insolence!
Wait!
Darling?
You're Candy, aren't you?
I never thought she would cause
so much trouble.
She is the result of
your whimsical decisions?
Father, Candy is mean to us!
Father, she hurts me!
Neil, aren't you supposed to be
the successor to Leagan family?
But...
I brought Candy here...
because I want you two
to learn something from her.
The old guy seems reasonable.
What do you mean the old guy...
Forget it!
Now, Neil, what was all about?
I was chasing the cat that got away,
the cat jumped on Dorothy
and she fell...
You do it on purpose!
Dorothy was the one in danger.
do you have anything to say?
-Answer me!
-Yes!
It's okay. Candy, forget it.
-Darling!
-I'm going to my study.
Why did he running away?
Mother,
Candy still not apologize to Neil.
That's right!
Candy, apologize to Neil and Eliza.
No way.
You've teamed up with staff
in order to attack Neil!
Absolutely not!
Is that so?
If I can't make you apologize to Neil,
I'll have Dorothy leave instead.
But...
It's not Dorothy's matter.
Dorothy, is this not your matter?
Well then?
Candy, you want Dorothy be fired?
Well then, Candy?
Unless I apologize,
they'll throw Dorothy out.
Well then, Candy?
I'm sorry.
-You said something?
-I didn't hear any of it!
Candy, apologize on your knees.
Apologized should say...
Forgive me, I was wrong.
Louder!
Forgive me, I was wrong!
One more.
Tom and Annie,
we promise eachother to be happy.
I have to do that.
Teacher, I won't cry.
Candy,
you're a cheerful, strong girl!
You mustn't cry,
even in hardest time!
Try to stay cheerful and tomboyish,
always keep your spirits up.
No matter what happens,
mustn't cry.
Understand?
I mustn't cry!
I had promised everybody...
Dorothy?
Thank you very much!
Dorothy, you're unhappy here, right?
Whenever I feel sad...
I'd think of
my little sisters and brothers.
Your brothers and sisters?
I have eight of them!
When I think about them,
the sadness will gone.
Little brothers and sisters...
Really. I feel better somehow!
See!
Kurin, don't blow up the dust.
The prince!
Dorothy, who is he?
I saw him on the premises a few times.
He visits the Leagans?
I'll meet him someday.
He's somebody you know?
Yeah. A little.
Sister Pony, sister Lane,
This is the first time,
I have a room of my own.
I feel so happy now.
You are prettier when you're smiling
than when you're crying.
The dream prince
will soon be next to her.
Think about this,
Her pain and sadness
soon disappeared.