Safex
Annie is gone.
For ten years, they lived together.
Candy stand still
watching Annie's leaving.
You're cute when you smile!
Candy!
Annie!
Annie,
you've come back, right?
Annie.
Candy.
It's a dream.
You were dreaming about Annie?
I dreamt that she came back.
Candy,
I'm sure she'll come back!
Why is that?
Everytime I wet my bed
the dream will came true.
You did it again, John?
I wonder will my dream come true,
just like John said.
What's the matter, Kurin?
Is somebody coming?
Maybe Annie is...
Oh! It's Matthew the mailman.
That's it!
He's carrying a letter from Annie!
Annie's let...
I lose.
Mr. Matthew!
Oh, tomboyish girl from Pony's home!
Say,
have you brought any letters for me?
For you?
A letter from Annie!
I don't know about such a letter.
Kurin, he doesn't know.
All of these letters are for
sister Pony and sister Lane.
Mr. Matthew,
maybe your eyesight is going?
Hey! What are you doing?
I'm gonna check it myself!
Wait!
-Let me help you.
-Me too.
Thanks!
Hey! Return my bag!
Oh! My letters...
-Quickly, catch those goats!
-Okay!
Wait!
Stop that!
(The second day)
Mr. Matthew!
Welcome, Mr. mailman!
Mr. mailman, welcome!
Even you say so,
I don't have letters for Candy.
Mr. Matthew, you've been delivering
mail for thirty years.
What do you want?
In those thirty years,
you must had done some mistake.
I've never done that!
But,
you could be mistaken today!
I can't show you all of my mails
just because you say so!
There's a regulation
protect the mail from anybody.
Regulation?
Hey! Stop that!
Candy! Others too, stop that.
I was just about done!
(The third day)
There's very little mail today.
I didn't have to bring my bag.
Look! I'm not carrying anything.
I guess you're right.
Gotta stick to the regulations.
Annie.
Candy, how long are you going to
keep thinking about Annie?
It doesn't suit you, Candy.
You mean that
Annie didn't thinking about me?
No,
I'm sure she will write you a letter.
But, it's already been two weeks!
If you can believe in her,
you can wait, too.
Kurin, Annie went down that road.
Somebody's coming!
It's okay, Kurin!
Who'd come this late at night?
Mr. mailman, it's late, you got lost?
How come a mailman get lost?
I came to you for a bag.
For me?
Now, open it.
Is it really okay to open it?
Since I came so late,
I'd like to see you open it.
Miss Candy. Annie Brighton.
It's Annie!
A letter from Annie!
Thank you, Mr. Matthew!
Coming so late to deliver this letter.
Come on,
I just went for an evening walk.
The stars are so beautiful.
Mr. Matthew!
If I deliver the letter during the day,
you might burst into tears.
Crying in front of everybody,
you'd probably feel embarassed.
I wouldn't !
I wouldn't cry.
Good night, Candy.
Candy?
That's great, Candy!
Come,
you can read it in our room.
I'll read it here!
In such a dark place?
It'll lighten up
as soon as I start to read!
It's not a problem!
Candy.
To my dear friend Candy.
I'm so happy now.
The big house had swimming pool
and many servants!
My Father and Mother
are very gentle,
living here is almost like in a dream.
I'll soon ask Father and Mother
to let me introduce you to them.
Until then, keep your spirits up!
I'm so glad that Annie is happy!
This is today's mail.
Thank you.
Mail has just arrived.
Come in!
Excuse me.
Miss, mail has arrived for you.
Thank you!
It's from Candy! Hold on, Becky.
You like chocolate, right?
Yes. But...
You don't have to take it.
Madam, excuse me!
Annie, Becky is not your friend.
I understand, Mother.
-From Candy?
-Yes.
Pony's home, Candice White.
Actually, I though about this for days.
What about? Mother.
Before the letters from Candy
came to your hand...
the servents might have seen it.
Right?
Nobody took notice of it yet,
If anyone knew about
the orphanage of Pony's home.
It might hurt you
and the Brighton's namesake.
What would people say
that you were from a dark swamp?
Everybody knows that
you were under my protection.
Be a good girl
and never tell anyone, okay?
Yes.
I had bought something in town.
We'll make a new dress for your party.
What a big one!
A letter from your friend!
From Annie, right? Mr. Matthew.
Hold on, Kurin.
It's not the usual gentle Annie.
I'm sorry, Candy.
I can't write letters to you anymore.
So, this is a last letter to you.
In order to become a true daughter
of the Brighton family,
I have to forget everything
about Pony's home.
Please don't ask me anything.
What's the meaning of this?
Terrible.
To forget everything.
How could she forget
about our friendship?
I can't believe you, Annie.
Everytime I closed my eyes,
I saw your face...
Everytime I closed my ears,
I heard your voice, Annie!
Does it matter
if you're doing so well?!
Does it matter at all?
Who are you?
Whom do I look like?
Your clothes are so weird.
You look like an alien!
An alien?
Because,
you're a guy wearing a skirt.
Even have a flute with a belly.
It's not a skirt. It's " kilt" ;
a Scottish folk costume.
This is a musical instrument,
called " bagpipes" .
Sounds like snails are having a party!
Snail party? That's a good one!
You are prettier when you're smiling
than when you're crying.
You stood there and watched me cry!
Oh, my letter...
Wait!
Got it!
Will you play the music again?
Was I dreaming?
Well, he did look like
a prince from a fairy tale.
You are prettier when you're smiling
than when you're crying.
That's a pretty pendant.
The Prince must have dropped it.
Have you seen someone
carrying a flute with a belly?
-No. Are you from Pony's home?
-Yes
If that's true,
Will you please bring her back?
Ma'am, she is...
I would like to leave her
at Pony's home.
I have too children to care for...
I'd leaving her here
and going off to work.
Candy! Sister Pony is calling you!
Well then, ma'am.
Incredible!
Whose automobile is this?
First automobile visit Pony's home!
It's the same pendant.
That's it! Must be the prince
This is Mr. Stewart
from the Leagan family.
Mr. Stewart would like to invite you
into the Leagan family.
Me?
Leagan family has great reputation
in the town of Lakewood.
Sister.
Isn't Lakewood close to Annie.
Yes, that's correct.
Can I ask you one thing?
Go ahead.
In your family...
is there a young boy
seventeen or eighteen years old?
Yes, The young master.
Sister Pony, I'm off to Lakewood!
I want to be
one of the Leagan family.
Candy!
How come so suddenly...
Please.
Wait up, Candy!
Ma'am!
I made it in time!
From now on,
you'll live in Pony's home.
Uh...
There is one happy girl
who is leaving Pony's home now.
Therefore,
you can take her place now.
Really?
Yes. She just made up her mind.
She is going to be the richest
young lady in Lakewood.
Oh, my...
Her best friend
is just near Lakewood.
Could anyone possibly
be happier than her?
This girl is...
Candice White.
Actually, that's my name.
It's me.
For the prince, for Annie.
From now on,
she will live in happiness.
Tears of joy
kept falling from Candy's face.