Safex
Candy left Merry Jane Nurse School
and headed towards St.Joanna hospital
Everyday she learns to be a
good nurse.
She has been through so much.
And now
One thing that will have a
huge impact on Candy's heart...
is ready to take place.
Assault!
Angels under the shasow of war
Oh my god!
Why? Judy
Nurse troop!
The troops are taking nurses along
to the European war zone.
Europe?
They will pick some nurses
to go with them.
-Who is in?
-How many people?
I am not sure about that.
Could it be the five of us?
I am not ready to
go to the front line.
What should we do?
What is wrong with you guys?
Blanny, aren't you scare?
The decision has not been made,
has it?
You are right...
Don't panic.
Isn't Blanny worried at all?
No way, Blanny must be scared.
Yeah,
She was just pretending to be strong.
Elly is right.
Blanny must be scared.
-Candy!
-Yes!
Take this patient out for a walk.
Yes
I am Marsha, thanks for that
I am Candy White.
Catch you later, Marsha.
Ok.
Candy, please.
Yes.
Let's go.
Did you know supervisor?
I used to be a nurse here.
So you were our senior.
It hasn't changed much.
Why are you staying in
surgical ward?
I am sorry.
That's alright, look!
Prosthesis?
Yes, I have only one leg left now.
I had to blame the war for this.
War?
I went to Europe
along with the army.
Europe?
Yes,
I was attending to the wounded...
But I volunteered to
go to the front line.
So I do not regret.
There are so many wounded and
sick people out there on the field.
Nurses are urgently needed.
Come to think about it...
I am very upset.
I never know...
She would become a disabled.
War is horrible.
Miss.Candy,
it is kind of breezy here,
-let's go back.
-Right.
Nurse troop?
Who will go?
Blanny, you sleeping?
If we got picked...
We need to go on to the field
I won't get to see Terry
for quite a while.
No, maybe I can never see him again.
Nurses are urgently needed.
Isn't Blanny worried at all?
I just can't stay as calm as Blanny.
Shoot! I overslept.
I couldn't sleep for the whole night.
Dim wit!
Headmaster?
As the usual...
You just can't stop running on
the passage even when you are here.
Sorry
Why is headmaster here?
Why?
Didn't principal tell yuo all?
What?
Come with me if you want to know.
-I have class...
-Forget it.
Just come with me quietly
There must be a reason why
headmaster Merry Jane showed up...
Nurse troop
But who will go?
All of us? or...
Come in!
Headmaster!
How is everybody?
Must be about the nurse troop thing
I thought
America wouldn't join the war.
I wouldn't want to be a nurse
if I knew this.
I will quit if they are sending me.
It is just too dangerous to
go to the front line.
Moreover, we are just trainees.
Yeah, we still don't have
enough experience.
I don't want to upset my parents.
Come here, you all.
Yes.
I have met you all just before
you came to this hospital.
I hope you all are good.
I came here for a reason.
Merry Jane Nurse School is under
an order to send a nurse troop.
As expected!
Every famous hospitals and
nursing school in America...
Have already sent people
to the war zone.
St.Joanna hospital is
under an order...
to send five nurses to Italy.
Merry Jane Nurse School
will send one nurse to France.
One?
Any volunteers?
I need one volunteer.
Should I volunteer?
I remember Doctor Mike from
the party is in France as well.
I will leave you here.
Ok.
Maybe we won't see each other again...
we are obliged to help people.
Yes.
Take care! Candy.
You too, Mr.Mike.
We are obliged.
Yes. I shall go to the front line
and help.
But once I go...
I might not be able to see
everyone again.
Archie, Stear...
Annie, Pattie...
Mr.Albert...
And Grandfather William.
But this is what I choose for myself.
This is the road
I should take as a nurse.
Nurses are urgently needed
on the field.
Candy!
Terry!
No.
I will go, I need to do this.
I will go.
Blanny!
Blanny, I will send you.
You all can leave, we need to talk.
Yes!
Blanny was so determined.
Dim wit, what are you doing here?
-Yes!
-Go out.
No more dim.
Yes.
Lucky us!
If Blanny didn't volunteer,
it might be one of us.
If I got picked,
my parents will be upset.
I am thier only daughter.
Blanny was brave.
Yeah, she did it for us.
Didn't care about her family,
and made the decision.
I don't have parents.
But Blanny does.
Why was I hesitating?
Why didn't I volunteer?
Blanny!
How was it?
Nothing.
You are calm.
Good on you!
When are you leaving?
In two days.
Two days?
That is fast!
This just happened too fast.
War will not wait for anyone.
Right...
But the war is worse than expected.
Wounded is increasing.
Many nurses sacrificed themselves.
Blanny,
you are on night shift today.
I will swap with you.
-Why?
-Because...
You are leaving soon.
There must be a lot of things
you need to take care of.
It is fine, you don't need to worry.
I will take care of myself.
I did the right thing.
This is what nurses
are suppose to do.
I don't need to discuss
with my family.
Sister Pony and sister Lane...
If they know that I am gonig to
Europe with the troops,
will they go against it?
I have many people that
I want to meet.
Too many, I am so greedy
Terry...
I wish we could be with each other
for longer.
Not just for short moment.
I have someone that
I can't leave behind.
Blanny has parents.
I will go looking for Blanny.
Why?
This is just something from us.
I can't take this, take it back.
Blanny, Because of you
we don't have to go on to the field.
You don't have to thank me.
I volunteered for this.
What? You are here
to thank me as well?
No, I need to speak to you.
Important things,
just the two of us.
Right, we talk outside,
let's go!
What do you want to say?
I...
Any complaints just bring it.
No, it is not complaints, it is...
What?
I want to join the nurse troop.
Why?
You have parents.
Yes.
Two older brothers,
two younger sisters,
and one younger brother.
Such a big family?
I shold be the one going.
What?
You shouldn't be giong to the
war zone,
I should be the one going.
Candy, what are you talking about?
It has been decided.
Why do you want to go for me?
I am an orphan,
and I have so many people that
I can't leave behind.
You have parents and sibling,
you must be very reluctant
to leave them behind.
Are you serious?
Are you kidding?
My family won't worry about me
even I go to the front line.
My father gets drunk everyday
and quarrels with my mom.
My brother and sister
never give a helping hand to others.
Everybody lives their own lives.
You think a family like that
would care anything about me?
Don't be silly!
And don't worry about me either.
But Blanny...
Go for me?
Just mind your own business.
I told you that I hate people
to intervene my business.
No,
if anything happens to you...
You mean I will die?
I am awared of that
when I volunteered.
This is my decision.
Please don't try to stop me.
Go on to the field bravely,
this makes me feel more like a nurse.
Blanny!
I can't believe
I told her about my family.
I never mentioned this to anyone.
This isn't right!
Blanny was right.
WE can't move on
if we always have family in mind.
Maybe I should just
take care of my own business.
Am I wrong?
This is my decision.
Please don'stop me, Candy.
Blanny,
I thought you were a mean person,
I have a lot to learn from you
as a nurse.
Blanny has got a totally different
personality and thoughts from me.
We grew up from
different backgrounds.
Although I don't have parents,
when I was in Pony's home...
everyone was like a family to me.
Blanny,
maybe we could become good friends,
if only we have more time.
But we will seperate
in two days time.
Take care,
Judy, Natalie and Elly.
Supersivor,
thank you for everything.
Take care Blanny.
-Candy!
-Yes!
Thank you.
Blanny,
I am sorry about last night.
I shouldn't have said those things
but...
Candy, I am not going to die.
Of course, we will have the chance
to be colleagues in the future.
Blanny
I know this is hard,
but you should be going.
Although we didn't get to
understand each other more.
Everyone, take care.
I still admire you, Blanny.
Go!
I just can't make myself to like her.
I can't never be as bright
and honest as her.
You definitely will be a good nurse.
Good bye! Candice White.
Blanny is heading towards the
war zone with the troops.
Although they couldn't be
good friends.
To Candy...
this brief encounter with Blanny,
has motivated Candy.
to follow and strive for
Blanny's example as a nurse.