Safex
In order to meet Terrius
Candy got on to the cart
and headed towards Elmo cinema.
The show is one day away.
Terrius is leaving
Chicago tomorrow.
The shadow under the spotlight
What happened to Candy?
Annie, is she here yet?
Did she have an accident?
Archie, mind your words.
Candy won't be coming.
Elisa, it is you again...
If Candi is smart.
She won't be late.
What do you mean?
Trainee is not suppose to be here.
Candy is still part of The Adley's.
Please take your seat.
We are waiting for our friends.
No entering when show started.
We should go in five minutes prior to the show.
Please take your seat.
Mr.Robert, I can't find Terrius.
Suzanna, I thought you guys were together?
We were, in the rest room.
How irresponsible.
I guess we need to delay the show.
I will look for him.
Do you know where he is?
No
I searched all over except the audience stands.
-I found him.
-Where?
-In audience stands.
-Whereabout?
Third floor right in the middle.
What he thinks he is doing?
No I will look for him.
Please reprimand him.
The show will never start like this.
Terrius, since when you became an audience?
I will show up when I am suppose to
The director is mad.
Mr.Robert
Why are there no audience on third floor?
It is going to be a charity show tonight,
it is only for people with high status.
Can't they come to third floor?
Look
What do you think those people are likely to react
if they know there are seats on third floor?
Terrius, just focus on your job as an performer.
Another slow celebrity.
Candy
I made it.
Sorry I am late
It is ok, the show is delayed.
I wouldn't be able to come in
if it wasn't for the delay.
I was so worried back in the cart.
Candy, hurry, it is going to start.
Hurry, it is going to start.
Candy.
How come you are here?
Stear, Archie
Who let her in?
Candy is adopted by The Adley's.
-Why not?
-Shut up
There is no seat for Candy here.
Big Granny, Candy is Granfather William's...
Candy, lets make this clear
Have you seperated from the Adley's?
Big Granny
These seats are for The Adley's only.
Big Granny, you must let me
attend the show tonight.
My friend is performing tonight.
Friend? Come on
Terry forgot about you.
Stop lying to yourself.
There is something between Terry
and the leading actress.
The leading actress?
Suzanna Marllu, she is so beatiful.
Shut up Elisa
Big Granny please give Candy a seat.
Ok, there are plenty of seats
No No more show for you guys
if you all can't stop talking.
Right, lets go
Ok brother
Forget it, I am out of here.
Candy
The show has began, please take your seats.
The show has started, I need to hurry.
I can't afford to regret.
It was not easy to swap shift with Natalie
Connel and Obani
The King likes the latter more.
Everyone thought so.
Before the King gives away his wealth...
I need to find a seat as soon as possible.
Now, I have important things to say.
Take out the map.
I will split the territory into three
You all don't have to worry...
No I can't see anything here.
Someone will find me sooner or later,
I need to go somewhere else.
Find somewhere else.
The show will not be interrupted.
I really need to find a seat soon.
Authorised personnel only.
Get out
-Excuse me
-Quick
I came for nothing
I might go upstairs
Be happy
You are my smallest daughter.
I will anything just to spoil you.
France territory.
Barlgon's farm
You will get more land than your sister.
How do you intend to thank me? Tell me
I have nothing to say
Nothing to say?
Yes
You get nothing if you have nothing to say
Answer me again
I cannot describe my sorrow
in words.
This place...
There are some audience stands here.
Terry
The one you love
is my most hatred daughter
Forget about her alright?
That daughter brought me shame.
I will grant you my other daughter instead.
Please calm down my Lord.
She was your beloved daughter.
She was your pride and your precious.
She was your most loved princess.
And you are turning your back against her now...
What exactly did she do?
Unless her wrongdoings...
Have exceeded society's acceptance
Otherwise, what you have just said
didn't make any sense
Terry you did it
Feel really good
She is going to make serious mistake.
Unless it is a miracle,
or nobody is going to believe it.
Terry
Are you dreaming?
Young lady with a freckled face.
Freckled face?
What a pity
Such beautiful face under the freckles
You must like your flat nose
Terry
I understand
Just yell Anthony'a name
Please, don't die
Why stop yelling?
Yell!
Why did you stop?
Tery, we meet at last
I am here
Look here Terry
Come Cloudia
Terrius
It was great! Especially the king.
It was excellent.
Great
Terrius, you were the best.
Go to the restroom now.
We will meet Terrius for sure.
Where is Terrius's restroom?
Why are you still here?
I am Mr. Terry's...
Go away, you cant come in here
It won't take a minute
You can wait him at the exit.
He will attend the banquet later.
Thank you.
He will come out in a second.
I want to get his autograph.
So many fans.
I see Terry at last
I want to go talk to him.
Hey! Follow the line
Excuse me, sorry.
Terry is coming out.
Terry
Terry, here.
Terry wait!
Don't board the car
Terry here!
Terry
Suzanna, get on the car.
Terry wait!
Terry you are heading towards me
Didn't you see me? or...
Terry and Suzanna,
Didn't you know?
Was it the pretty lady from just now?
No
Terry,
you didn't pretend not to see me did you
Terry
Terry What is wrong?
Nothing
Great show tonight you did so well
I clearly heard
Candy calling out from the crowd
Hope to see you again, Candy.
Institution in London.
Summer school in Scotland.
You smiling at me.
Where did that smile go?
Terry
We meet at last
What a grand banquet.
Mr.Maymor
It is an honour to be here
Mr.Robert
This banquet is to thank you and your crew.
No
We should toast to Shakespear
You were so outstanding
and the King of France...
Terry?
He has a lot of potential.
Surrounded by the girls, can't even walk.
He still has a lot to learn
What a bright future
I guess he second Robert?
Hope so
Mr. Terry, you are so handsome,
please sign for me.
Me too.
Why am I so unease?
Terry
I can't forget her voice
Come on, it can't be Candy.
Mr. Terry
Please stop by our place
during your stay in Chicago.
I have a huge garden
I am sorry, I have to go.
Elisa
You finally came, so happy.
Why is Elisa here?
Excuse me
Elisa, did you and Terry know each other?
Yeah, we were good friends back in London.
Yeah? Terry
When did you come back?
By yourself?
Answer me, Elisa
Terry, don't do this
Answer me Elisa
Did you come back by yourself?
No, Neo, Stear and Archie,
they are all back.
Stear and Archie
Did you find her? Brother
No
There is no one here
Where could she be? Candy
She might went to the banquet?
Did Candy come back with you guys?
I have no idea what you are talking about?
Liar! Tell me!
I really don't know!
Stop! Terry!
None of your business
Terry, this hankerchief
The crew found it
In the audience stands on the third floor.
Third floor?
Only you and Mr.Robert been there
This belongs to mw when I was in London
I remember...
I use this hankerchief to dress Candy's wound.
Candy She was here!
She was watching me from third floor!
It was Candy, it was her yelling!
Elisa
Candy is in town
Terry Where are you going?
Still so passionate
What has Candy got?
Elisa, Neo where are you?
Where are they?
I am leaving tomorrow morning
Anxious and desperate
Terry is will do anything to find Candy
No I won't give up!
I must see him
It is either tonight or never
Candy made a push to carry on!
Candy!
Candy and Terry
Two of them looking for each other,
with only one kilometre apart.