Safex
The dawn at Mount Rodney.
Mr. Carson' s children...
allowed Candy to stay at the barn
without telling their father.
That night, the youngest child Sussy,
broke out in fever.
Mr. Carson kept shouting that
the doctor will not come.
However, saving patient
is doctor' s responsibility.
Candy believe in that
and went out for the doctor.
It' s over there!
Doctor! Please! Doctor! Open up!
Yes... who is it?
We have an emergency!
The doctor needs to come right now!
Sussy has a terrible fever!
Sam... I' ll wake him up.
Come inside.
Yes.
Okay?
What? An emergency?
Who' s calling?
It' s Mr. Carson' s Sussy...
She is in a fever...
What? Carson?
I can't.
What?
I can't go to his place.
But...
aren't you supposed to be a doctor?
Saving the sick people isn't your job?
I went there in good will
and did an examination.
I won't allowed anyone
called me a murderer...
Please go back.
But...
Doctor, wait!
Doctor! Please!
It won't work, sis!
Sam...
He won't help us, It' s dad' s fault.
Sam!
Ever sice mom died...
He sometimes got drunk
and wandered around doctor' s house.
No!
No matter what happened.
The doctor must save the patient.
My dad thought that
it' s doctor' s fault that mom died!
Doctor!
My wife?
There was nothing I could do...
Why don't you save her?
Murderer!
-Mr. Carson!
-It' s not doctor' s fault!
Get out!
Get the hell out!
After that, dad started drinking
and coming to doctor' s house.
Shit!
You all sided with that doctor...!
My wife... give her back!
Give her back!
I see. That' s why everybody
started avoiding him?
That' s right.
That' s exactly why I can't
just leave Sussy like this!
We must do something...
Lady!
How is Susy' s condition?
She suddenly felt exhausted
and broke out in fever...
That fever appeared
seemed out of the ordinary.
It could be measles.
Measles?
If it' s measles...
We should treat her somehow?
Well...
See? I told you the doctor won't come!
It' s okay. I will help her.
What? You?
You think I' d let you mess aroun
my daughter?
Moreover...
haven't I told you to get lost?
The rash is coming out!
I' m sure it' s measles!
What? Measles?
I've seen it many times in Pony' s home.
-Mr. Carson!
-What?
Hurry and bring some dry clothes
for Sussy to change into.
Are you ordering me?
Sussy' s illness is contagious.
Have Sam and Jeff contracted measles?
We both had it while mom was alive.
Right?
Mom watch all night over us.
I see. And I' ll watch over Sussy.
Thank you, Candy-sis.
Sam, bring some cold water.
Ok!
Jeff, you bring the towels.
Mr.Carson.
Hurry and bring Susy' s clothes.
After that, place Sussy' s bed
in the warmest room.
Alright!
Sussy, hang in there.
Mr. Carson!
Please don't make so much noise.
You' ll upset her.
I' m worried sick...
Why don't you take a nap?
I' ll watch over her.
Please do...
I just can't watch her like this.
-Dad!
-How' s Sussy doing?
Don't worried, go to your bed.
Dad, will she really be okay?
She' ll be okay?
Yes, I think so.
She' s not gonna die.
I remember the time Jimmy had a fever.
I didn't know how to do?
I just panicked.
Candy! it' s alright.
Don't worry
return to your room and go to sleep.
Yes.
Sister Pony and sister Lane
nursed him back to health.
Sussy, I' m sure you' ll be fine.
Instead of your mom
I' ll nurse you back to health.
-Bro, Sussy will get better, right?
-Of course!
Candy-sis is so kind.
Yeah!
She is just like a real sister.
Bro.
It' s Dad.
He' s praying for mom
quickly return from Mount Rodney.
Jeff...
If mom comes back, he wouldn't be
so confused anymore, right?
This guy... when is he going to realize
that mom is died?
Please, save Sussy.
I' m begging you...
give her some strength.
Mom!
Mom...
I' m right here.
Sussy, I' m right here.
Mom.
Sussy.
You' re better.
Candy-mom.
Sussy. Thank goodness, Sussy!
Sussy! What happened?
Dad!
Sussy!
She' s alright.
Thank goodness, Sussy!
Thank goodness.
Sussy.
You' re already awake?
We couldn't sleep because worry.
Bro.
You' re better. Sussy!
That' s great, Sussy.
Thank goodness!
Truly thank goodness.
Huh! A carriage is coming this way.
It' s the doctor.
He must worried about her.
Now he shows up?
You killer. Why are you coming here?
I' m gonna beat you.
-I' m not coming anymore.
-Wait!
Mr. Carson.
Stop that! Dad.
-Wait!
-Stop! Mr. Carson
-Stop!
-Let go of me.
You' re wrong for hating the doctor.
Sussy got well bacause of doctor.
Why do you said it' s his doing?
Doctor' s wife
told us how to treat Sussy.
If she hadn't told us how to do
we might not able to help Sussy.
Mr. Carson. no matter how hard
the doctor might try.
Please try to understand
Doctor, are you here to see Sussy?
That' s exactly why I came.
I couldn't sleep from worry.
This way.
No need to worry anymore.
Thank goodness.
You did well, Candy.
You' re a great nurse.
Me? A nurse?
Sam, stop by at my place
to pick up the medicine.
Okay!
Thank you!
Wow! smells great.
Smells great, right?
Let me see...
Hey, Sam. That' s bad.
That' s bad.
Doesn't matter how good you are
you can't match the taste of my cooking.
You' re a wise guy, aren't you?
Hey, Jeff.
I' m just tasting...
There.
Well?
Tasty.
That' s great.
Sussy was quickly getting better
because of Candy' s care.
There! say Aaah!
Here! Sussy.
A treat for you because
you didn't complain the medicine.
The rash is almost gone.
Sis, you really can make anything.
Thank you, Candy-mom.
Sussy keeps calling you mom.
I don't mind.
But you' re still too young to be a mom.
You better be my bride.
Sam, you...
Bro, you' re sly.
You' re blushing.
I have not felt this good in a while.
Sam, Jeff,
I' m going to climb that tree.
Candy-sis, you can climb the tree?
I' m good at that.
I want to climb it once Sussy get well.
Sis, you' re a tomboy.
A tomboy.
That' s right! Look at me.
Sis, do your best.
Kurin is good, too.
Do your best, Kurin.
I can see the sea.
Kurin, the sea.
America lies across that sea.
America, where Terry is right now.
And my dearest Pony' s home.
It' s going to start snowing soon.
I' d better board a ship before then.
Here.
Here
-Uh... Miss Candy.
-Yes.
-Could you come over for a minute?
-Okay.
I owe you so much
for taking care of Sussy.
This is too little but...
It' s okay, I' m not for the money.
I did this because I like children.
Actually...
I want you to leave.
You' re just at a stopover at my house.
Please, leave before children
start liking you even more.
If you leave before everybody wake up.
Maybe your departure
won't be so hard on them.
It' s exactly like you said.
I' ll leave tomorrow at dawn.
Please take it. Not much
it' s the best I could do.
Really, I' m fine.
I' ll get along somehow.
Sussy, you' ll be just fine.
I' m so glad you got well.
Jeff.
Listen to your brother.
Sam.
With you around, I know that
Sussy and Jeff will be safe.
Stay well.
Farewell... everyone...
Stay well!
Sis.
Sam.
I heard you talking.
I won't hold you back.
Sam.
Sussy and Jeff will be okay
Therefore...
Sis, take care.
Sam.
Farewell.
Sussy, Jeff, Sam.
Everyone, stay well!
Farewell, Mr. Carson.
I wrote you a letter of introduction.
A friend of mine, Juskin.
He' s running a ship company
in Southampton.
Mr. Carson.
His company maybe big enough
you can look for him.
He saved me from slave traders.
Thank you, Mr. Carson.
Farewell, Candy-sis.
Farewell!
Sadness always follows parting people.
However
this sadness doesn't last forever.
Candy cheered up, heading towards
the port of Southampton.