Safex
The lonesome three.
Mr. Albert rescued Candy who fell
down the waterfall and nearly drowned.
He said; whenever you're sad or hurt,
put a letter into a bottle...
and let it flow down this river.
To Candy,
Mr. Albert was a total stranger.
The image of kind,
bearded Mr. Albert
burned itself
deeply into Candy's heart.
At that time
Owing to the hard work of Anthony
a new kind of rose...
began to bloom beautifully
in the Adley' family garden.
Anthony gave Candy's name
to the new rose.
He named it " Sweet Candy" .
Sweet Candy.
It's sweet and pretty just like me,
right, Kurin?
Anthony worked so many years for this,
and finally it bloomed.
Of course, it's the only one
of its kind in the whole world!
Anthony named that rose after Candy...
What happened to him...
to go crazy over that
barn-dwelling girl...
He's not the only one.
Stear, Archie and everyone else
in the house is all " Candy..."
The next thing will be us Leagans
looking up to Candy!
To such a girl?
I'm not going to put up with that!
Do something, Brother!
And I will.
Have any good ideas?
I'm thinking about poisoning.
Candy?!
Stupid, not her.
Not her?
I'll poison horses in the barn.
If you don't spread the dough
like this
you can't make a tasty pie.
That's right.
It's the hard part of the lesson!
Brother, do it now!
Candy is in the kitchen!
Alright.
I'll let horses drink a bit of this.
Won't it kill them?
It'll get them pretty sick!
Now, eat up, Caesar!
That's ...
Something must have happened.
Neil!
Neil, what's wrong!
Hang in there, Neil!
Eliza, calm down, it's me, Candy!
What happened?
Somebody! Somebody come!
Brother was...!
Neil, pull yourself together!
Neil!
-Miss Eliza! What happened?
-Miss! What's wrong?
Brother was...!
-Mr. Neil!
-Great.
Quickly!
Mr. Neil!
Don't worry.
He's just unconscious.
Mr. Neil?
Just who did this to you?
It was Candy! She did it!
Eliza?
Candy did this?
But this is...
Candy wanted to give this
to the horses!
Eliza! Don't tell such nonsense!
You're calling this nonsense?
When Brother tried to stop her,
she hit him!
What a violent person!
I'm shocked!
But... Neil was already on the
ground when I came in here!
You're calling Miss Eliza a liar now?
I saw everything.
A tall man fleeing from the barn!
That's right, Candy.
Blame others again!
I'm telling the truth!
You saw it, too!
I saw nobody
running from the barn!
This swelling is turning into
a nasty eyepatch.
Candy did it.
This is a pretty nasty wound.
Such a tiny girl would hardly...
Hoittman!
Are you calling Miss a liar?
Uh, no! I wasn't really...
Anyway, let's carry Mr. Neil
to his room.
-Yes.
-Now, hurry up!
-It hurts!
-Poor boy!
Who would be so horrible
to such a gentle child?
Brother, hang in there!
Get well quickly, Mr. Neil.
-It hurts me, mama!
-My poor boy...
"Get well quickly" , huh?
And he just got an eyepatch.
It seems that he doesn't know that
one can't fight without getting hurt.
That's right! I was hurt in fights
so many times ever since I was a kid.
Doug, Dorothy
Do you think that I did that?
If it wasn't you
maybe it was God's doing!
God's doing?
A divine punishment!
Candy! Get in here!
Yes.
Poor girl.
She's gonna get chewed out again.
Candy.
Let's hear the truth
from Neil himself.
We'll know for sure once
he tells us.
-It hurts!
-My poor boy!
Well? Who hit you then? Okay?
You only need to tell me that.
It was...
Brother, Candy did it!
Wait!
Neil!
He's " mister Neil" to you!
Mr. Neil. You're a man, right?
Are you saying that you,
as a man...
allowed yourself to be punched
and hurt by a girl?
If that's true
you're not much of a man!
If that's true, wouldn't that be a
disgrace to the Leagan family?
Candy!
Are you threatening him?
I just want Neil.. no, Mr. Neil
to tell us the truth.
Tell me now.
Don't concern yourself
with what Candy said.
Tell me the truth, Neil!
The truth.
Brother!
Neil!
It was... Candy did it!
Neil, I saw everthing.
The fleeing dark shadow.
A tall man with long hair...
Then, it was...!
So that's how it was.
What?
What's up with that happy face?
I'll go look for the man
who punched Neil!
Candy!
I'm sure it was Mr. Albert.
If I put this letter into a bottle
and let it flow downstream...
It will reach mr. Albert.
Candy, If something happens to you...
you can write me a letter.
Put it in a bottle and
allow southern winds to take it.
Your note will surely reach me.
Thank you, Mr. Albert!
The southern wind is blowing.
Please... reach Mr. Albert.
Kurin, where are you going?
It's dangerous!
That's right
If I wished upon this bottle,
I could at least follow it a little.
We can't follow it from here on.
Can't help it then.
I'd better head back.
The moonlight is disappearing.
It's dark! What will I do?
Good morning. Candy!
Mr. Albert!
I got your note. Anyway
let's go to my place.
Yes.
You're living in such a place...?
Mr. Albert, is this your house?
-Something like that.
-It's pretty!
Hey, wait a minute.
You need to take a test
before you can enter this house!
A test?
You'll know in a moment.
Hey! We have a guest!
So many!
Kurin, they're your friends!
It tickles!
They're cute!
You're a good boy.
Alright, you've passed!
And with a maximum score, too!
Are you living alone
in such a big house?
They are my family.
And there are many of them.
It was you who punched Neil, right?
That's right.
He was going to poison
innocent animals, and for what?
However, I'm afraid that I put you in
a lot of trouble by doing that.
Neil and Eliza were trying to
set me up on purpose.
I was going to talk to them.
But I didn't .
Why?
They were gradually turning you
into a leper of the Leagan family.
I don't care!
I wasn't going to forgive them
anyway!
But...
And those two, they wanted
to have me kicked out all along.
Do you have a place to stay?
Let me stay here, please!
I'm good at everything,
and I can even make a pie!
And I can look after the animals!
Candy.
These animals know how to find
food for themselves.
They had to learn that, or they would
be in trouble when they're alone.
Is it okay for people to be alone, too?
I like being alone.
I thought so ever since I was little.
You, too?
Yes. I'm a lone tramp.
Then, this house...?
Probably some rich man's villa.
Okay
I'm like that, too!
Alone and homeless!
What are you so happy about, then?
Because...
it's been a while since I've met a
lonely person just like me.
I see. So that's it!
What's going on?
It seems that it's time for me
to say goodbye to you!
This way!
Where are you going, Mr. Albert?
I'm going to help my animals
escape to a safe place.
I'll go with you!
Candy, you stay here
and hold them off.
But...
They won't do anything bad to you.
Candy, I'll see you soon, for sure.
Stay happy.
Hang in there. Don't give up!
Mr. Albert!
Well then.
Get out! Slowly!
Are they going after him because
he did something wrong?
Get out or we'll shoot you!
It's not a joke, don't shoot!
A little girl!
-Are you alone?
-As you can see!
Where is that man?
He ran away hours ago!
Isn't he a friend of yours?
Not really.
Hey, we'll going to look for him
around the estate.
And how did you get inside
the estate?
Through that entrance.
Damn...
-Here is Adley family property!
-Adley family?
Anyway, you'll have to come
with us.
Why are you guys looking for
that man, anyway?
Because he was trespassing.
What? Only because of that?
What do you mean?
We are supposed to shoot
all trespassers on this estate.
Anthony!
Candy!
Mr. Anthony!
This girl is an acquaintance of yours?
Yes. She's my friend, Candice.
Oh... alright then!
-So good!
-I'm sorry for that.
My fault.
No, not at all.
Candy, you don't have to return
to Leagans anymore.
What do you mean, Anthony?
The three of us had
a wonderful discussion.
A wonderful discussion?
If you come, I'll show you.
-Candy? In the Adley family?
-Yes, aunt.
Anyway, even though she's a girl,
Candy is violent, rude...
-Archie!
-It's okay!
And though she's a servant,
She's hardly worthy
of the Adley family!
Anthony, you too?
I've heard a lot about Candy's
bad behavior.
But...!
If this continues
She might bring bad reputation
to the family!
Thus, great aunt Elroy
Our idea was to have you
educate Candy from now on!
Me?
There is nobody else that could
educate Candy!
Why, maybe so...
If you can turn Candy into
a beautiful lady...
people will look up to you even more!
And you came all the way just to...
Then, are you okay with Candy
being taken in by this house?
I will be a stern teacher to her!
-We did it!
-Congratulations, Candy!
Aunt Elroy?
Eliza!
Don't let yourself be fooled, aunt.
What do you mean?
Eliza!
She's the one who snuck into the
mansion with some bum.
I'm sure you will dearly regret this
decision.
With a bum?
I heard this from the guards.
Candy! Is this true?
It's true that
I snuck into the mansion...
but that person wasn't a bum!
That's right! Mr. Albert is Candy's ...
Anthony!
This conversation never happened.
-Grand aunt!
-Please reconsider this!
I don't want to deal with
such a filthy girl.
Eliza... just how far will she go?
It's okay, Anthony.
As long as you and the others
live in this place.
I'll be happy.
Candy...
A man who lived alone in that mansion
went on a journey today.
Things were similar with me.
Candy...
It's the same with me, too.
Anthony?
My late mama made this rose garden.
So that's why Anthony likes roses.
Mama loved roses very much.
I too... love roses!
Candy... want to ride?
Yes!
Let's run, Candy!
-Okay.
-Hold on tightly!
Run!
We won't give in to loneliness!
We won't give up!
Candy, relax...
Just don't fall from my arms!
It's okay.
I'm holding on tightly!
Anthony...
Hear the sound of my heart.
It's so... so loud!
This wind against my face...
Anthony, I'm hearing your voice
with the wind!
Candy!
I love you!
Anthony!
I wish the two of us
could become the wind...
going somewhere far away.
I wish this path
would extend to eternity.
This is what Candy wished for.
In Anthony's arms,
forever.