Safex
Terry.
Suzanna played as Juliet.
She saved Terrius but needed to
have her right leg amputated.
Meanwhile,
Candy headed towards
principal's villa.
And met this actress, Karen.
Two of them didn't know anything
about Suzanna's accident.
An invitation with an one way ticket.
-I am back.
-You are back.
Principal's reply.
How is principal?
Very good.
Good.
How is Florida?
It's a beautiful place.
Summer all year.
Is there anything else, Dr. Reknapp?
You rushing home?
You are having your leave now,
there is nothing else.
Take a good rest.
Thank you, See you later.
Present for those
who lost their memory?
Yes.
No, and Dr. Reknapp.
Please take it.
Good bye.
I have only one.
I am back, Mr. Thomas.
Welcome.
-You become darker.
-Hey!
Stop staring at me.
Here, present.
Thanks, I will take it.
Where is Mr.Albert?
He is in his room.
He seemed lonly
when you were not around.
Was he?
Cheer him up.
What is Mr.Albert doing?
Come in.
Does Miss Candy live here?
Yes, she is away on a trip.
Candy, it's you.
Welcome, Candy.
I am back, Mr.Albert.
Candy,
There is a letter for you.
You don't need me to tell you
who it is, right?
Must be from Terry.
-Orange...
-Present for you
Forget it.
It's an invitation card from Terry.
If Mr.Albert is recovering well,
I hope you could come.
Leave everything behind.
Just like old time
when we were in St.Paul Instituition.
Invitation, one way ticket.
Terry,
Mr.Albert,
Terry invites me to Broadway.
That's great.
Candy, don't worry about me,
go happily.
Thank you, Mr.Albert.
Suzanna Marlu.
Sorry, but Mrs.Marlu
refused to see you.
I am very sorry.
Could you hand this to her.
Excuse me...
He is here everyday,
so sorry for him.
Mrs.Marlu wouldn't even
take any flowers.
Visit? Go back,
I don't want to see you.
I will not forgive you.
Suzanna sacrificed her future for you.
I hate you.
Calm down Mrs.Marlu.
That's an accident,
it has nothing to do with Terry.
No, he killed my daughter.
He needs to be responsible.
Give me back my child.
How can she go on to a stage
with only one leg?
She wanted to be an actress
since she was little.
Suzanna,
If only I could swap with you.
I really hope I could
Suzanna, are you ok now?
What do you have in mind?
And on that ship...
You saw Terry for the first time,
He held you,
you two staring each other,
Come on, Mr.Albert,
I have heard it too many times,
I could even memorised it.
Candy, don't be mad.
I am willing to listen
no matter how many times.
Thank you, Mr.Albert.
I am so happy.
Always so childish.
The face behind the mist looked
really like Anthony.
Did I ever mention about
Anthony?
He is your first love.
No,
My first love was at six.
The prince on the hill.
First love at six.
That's pretty early.
The prince on the hill.
Anthony,
And then Terry.
No, Terry is different.
We will meet again.
One day.
We will.
Even Mr.Albert lost his memory.
We still reunited.
Mr.Albert,
it's so good to be alive.
Why do you say that?
Come
Even seperated,
we still have a lot of good memory.
Think about the past.
Terry in the Blue River Zoo.
Terry's smile
under the spring sunshine.
And make up party.
First kiss.
We missed each other so many times
since we left school.
This is time
I am sure I can see Terry.
I can't wait to go to Broadway.
Candy,
How many eggs you want?
Shoot!
Lights higher, good.
Ropes tight, good.
Background more to the right,
good.
More, good.
That's so cruel.
The rehearsal continues even
Suzanna had her accident.
Terry.
Karen Clairs will be
palying Juliet from now on.
Get along well.
Nice meeting you, Terry.
I can do better than Suzanna.
Nice meeting you, Karen.
Captain Robert only cares about
the performances on stage.
This is reality.
But I just can't leave Suzanna behind.
You 're going to Broadway
tomorrow.
I need to get something first.
Be careful.
Candy, don't get too excited.
Heading to Broadway tomorrow.
The first train.
Candy didn't see us, Brother.
Forget it.
Why is she so happy?
Of course, Archie.
Yeah,
Candy is going to see Terry.
Miss, you dropped ten dollars.
Really?
Hello, Candy.
Having a good mood huh.
You guys!
When did you follow me?
You were so excited
and you didn't see us at all.
We want to have a farewell dinner
with you.
Sorry,
I was going to get something.
Hop on.
We are going with you, Candy.
Thanks.
Candy,
we can help you with the dinner.
Lucky.
Are you sure? Can you cook
something that is edible?
How rude.
Yeah, I will buy Terry a scarf.
Candy,
you should buy that in New York.
Yeah,
the taste is better over there.
Right.
Beautiful roses.
I will get some for Teey.
Candy, do you have any idea
how far is Broadway?
The flowers are going to die.
Yeah.
Here comes the ice cream.
Hey Stear.
It's going to melt
before it reaches Terry.
Candy, we gonna eat it now.
Stop thinking about Terry.
Come, the ice cream tastes
a lot better in winter.
Strawberries flavor is delicious.
I want a cap as well.
Are you serious? Elisa.
Candy.
How uneducated.
Eating ice cream on the street.
I would rather be uneducated.
And eat ice cream on the street.
This is so good.
Elisa, you want some?
Don't be as bad as Candy.
Let's go Brother.
Candy, I am going to Broadway
to watch shows.
You know who is the main cast?
Is Terry,
I will have some chat with him.
You should go back and
get your bandages done.
Candy, why don't you tell Elisa
that you are going to Broadway.
Yeah.
That's alright.
Elisa likes to tease me.
I don't want to disappoint her...
Mrs. Marlu is not here.
Do you want to
go straight to the ward?
Upstairs, turn right. NO.12
Thank you.
Come in.
Terry.
Suzanna.
You come here every day.
I knew.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
How is rehearsal?
I heard Karen got the role.
She must be very happy.
She always wanted this role.
The show is coming real soon.
She is coming, isn't she?
She?
Candice White.
Yeah, Candy is coming.
I don't want to cause
any misunderstanding.
It's over between you and her.
Look how I have become
because of you.
You are responsible to take care of me
for the rest of my life.
Just kidding, Terry.
I won't force you.
Suzanna,
It's not your fault.
I don't hate you at all.
Terry,
Don't bother,
concentrate on your performance.
She...
You should go out with her.
Please, leave me alone.
Don't come again, Terry.
I will see you tomorrow.
Suzanna.
Mr.Albert.
Candy is leaving for Broadway,
we will look after you every day.
It's good.
The food is wonderful.
Stear, what is up?
Nothing.
For after meal entertainment,
please enjoy my accordion show.
Brother,
We are going to
have some digestion problems.
What are you talking about?
Archie.
Get ready to see this.
Poopet knows how to dance!
Come, Candy, let's dance.
Candy didn't know anything
about Suzanna's suffering.
She is going to meet up with Terry.
Candy's heart
is filled with excitement.