Safex
The barn princess.
Candy's heart was overwhelmed with
happiness on her first party.
She was even able to dance with
Anthony, whom she likes very much.
But then, Neil and Eliza tried
to abduct Candy.
To bring a servant to a party...
Madam Leagan is such a gentle person.
Even though
everybody was saying that,
deep inside
they were condemning the idea.
...and it was such a wonderful party.
I'm so sorry that I can't show you
just how beautiful my party dress was.
At least,
I can show you this drawing.
-It's so pretty.
-She looks like a princess!
I want to see the real one!
That's right. I'm sure you'll
see it one day.
Candy really became a princess
in the Leagan family.
Yes.
Candy, you are not a part
of the Leagan family!
-I understand.
-If you understand,
what were you doing at the party?
You were snobbish as if you
were one of us!
Uh, I was just trying to be
my usual self...
And then you go around
stealing boys from other people!
My bed!
Candy, from today,
you'll be changing your room!
Changing...?
You want me to sleep
in the garden?
In the barn.
Candy,
that place suits you perfectly!
It's a wonderful place for your
head to cool off!
When he finds out that
you're living in the barn,
Anthony will stop seeing you.
I'm leaving now.
Stewart, prepare the car!
At least, try to get along
with the horses.
Anthony...
he's not such a person.
They threw me out from the
attic and into the barn...?
I thought that it would be
much worse...
Let's get along!
You guys thought that since I'm
here now, you would have to go?
Don't worry, I'll be your friend.
Kurin, what happened?
What are you saying?
Anthony!
Kurin!
Hey, Candy!
Eliza and Neal have gone out...
That's exactly why I came.
Because both of them are gone.
I thought you'd be going
out with them.
I...
That's right. They are not being
nice to you, both of them.
Mr. Anthony, these are all.
So many?
I'll help you carry them.
-You?
-I'm strong enough!
Are you okay, Candy?
Candy,
carry them towards the gate.
It wasn't my intention
to go this way...
Candy, are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Are you hurt?
They are so filthy, aren't they?
I'm sorry for letting you do
all this work.
I'll handle the rest.
Anthony must have been startled
seeing my rough hands.
When he finds out that
you're living in the barn,
Anthony will stop seeing you.
Move it, it's dangerous!
This car doesn't have any brakes!
Stay clear!
Boy, watch out!
That was dangerous.
Boy!
What will I do now?
I ran him over with my car!
He's dead.
I'm so hungry...
Madam was so horrible to you.
Making such a sweet girl
take care of the horses.
It's okay with me.
I really like animals!
It's Stear's car!
Hey, Candy!
I brought a guest of yours!
My guest?
Candy!
John?
John, did you come here all alone?
Of course I did!
Candy!
Don't tell me you went
without telling sister Pony...
Of course I did!
-What?
-Candy,
John came here because he
wanted to see your beautiful dress.
-John...
-If I were his age,
I'd never have the courage
to do such a thing.
I'd get caught, probably.
Stear, don't praise him for
doing this!
Hey, I barely managed to stop!
I can't stop this car
once it starts moving!
I'm sure everybody is
worried sick about you.
I'll go back as soon
as I see your dress!
That must be the window
of your room, right?
That's not it...
Can I see it?
Come to the barn for a minute...
I don't care about the horses!
I want to see Candy's room!
John...
Welcome back, miss Candy!
Dorothy!
Wow, you called Candy " miss" !
Wonderful!
Such a sweet young lad,
isn't he?
It's the first time
someone called me a lad...
Welcome to our household.
Well now, this way!
-Dorothy...
-Leave this to me.
Wow, is this Candy's room?
Looks like it's made for a princess!
I'm not sure it's okay
to go into Eliza's room...
She won't be back before evening.
John, don't open that wardrobe!
Why not? It's yours!
Are all of these your dresses?
-Yes.
-Candy,
show me the dress which
you wore at the party!
But...
And in return...
It's a sheet, isn't it?
It's okay, just take this end!
Ta-dah! Look at this
There are no pee stains on it!
Really! John, you stopped
wetting your bed!
That's right!
John, I'll show you my dress
if you came all the way here
just to show me your sheet!
Okay then!
-Wonderful!
-It is, John.
Don't look at me like that!
I'll remember it well,
and I'll tell everyone at the
Pony's home about how it looks!
John!
-Miss!
-Move it!
Why are you blocking my way?
Eliza!
So that's how it is.
Candy?
Candy,
what's the meaning of this?
-Who is she?
-Eliza.
Candy's sister, right?
Sister?!
Candy, who is this filthy runt?
He's John.
Came to see me from Pony's home.
He's all filthy,
just what I expected!
And what is this old rag
supposed to be?
Dorothy! Throw it out!
This is my sheet!
You call this a sheet?
Weren't you supposed to be
in the barn, Candy?
-What?!
-Stop it!
Dorothy, disinfect this room
immediately.
Candy, take this filthy
runt to the barn where it belongs.
-Eliza!
-Mother, Candy has...
Candy, you have a guest.
I have...?
Greet her immediately.
Mother, what about the dress?
Eliza, keep quiet.
Candy,
you look just like an adult!
Sister Lane!
Candy,
John ran away from home.
John!
-Good day.
-John!
I knew I'd find you here!
Mother, you'd let Candy tarnish
my room with her presence?
Until those two return
I don't want that!
Barn is enough for Candy!
Eliza
Candy left Pony's home in order to
become your playmate.
If that woman finds out that
Candy is now sleeping in the barn...
It's because Candy was so rude,
so what?
Anyway, do as I said.
Mother!
It's for the sake of Leagan family!
I'd like both of you to be
grateful to me!
You ran away,
why do you want us
to be grateful about?
That's right!
Everyone was worried about you.
But sister Lane
kept worrying about Candy!
John.
Candy,
and you wanted to see sister Lane?
Yes. I wanted to see her.
I ran away from Pony's home,
causing you two to meet!
Kurin!
You look well too, Kurin!
Candy, is it okay for me to
play with Kurin here?
Yes.
Wait up, Kurin!
What a huge garden!
I could get lost in here!
Wait up, Kurin!
I'll go back if you disappear!
What? It's a barn, isn't it?
I know what horses look alike.
A bed!
Somebody is sleeping
with the horses.
Candy's pajama!
Candy sleeps in such a place!?
You saw it, didn't you?
Candy!
Aren't you a princess?
I'm a princess.
-But then...!
-John,
I'll be fine as long as my spirit
doesn't give in to the real princess.
Candy,
why weren't you telling us...
John
You're a man, aren't you?
Yeah, I was born as one.
In that case,
you can keep a secret.
You want me to lie to teachers?
You can do it.
Thanks to John, all three of us
are sleeping in the same room.
He's not saying anything...
Looks like he's already asleep.
Candy, now I can be at peace.
I'm sure sister Pony
will be glad, too.
Tell her that Candy is very happy.
Sister Lane, Candy is...!
John, weren't you asleep?
Candy!
You're a man!
Since John isn't wetting his bed
anymore,
he might start to oversleep
regularly...
Thank you for your hospitality.
Sorry for the trouble.
No. Boy,
if you want to see Candy
again, you can stop by.
Don't worry about Candy.
Yes, thank you very much.
Please make use of my car.
I couldn't accept that...!
Candy, won't you come with them
till halfway?
Yes.
Candy!
-A friend?
-Stear and Archie.
Mr. driver, please stop the car!
How do you do!
The three of us,
though Anthony isn't here,
we'll keep an eye on Candy.
I'd like to talk to Candy in
private for a moment.
Okay?
You're friends, why not.
What did you want to talk about?
Candy, don't let yourself be broken.
Sister Lane.
Actually, my idea was to take
you back to Pony's home.
You knew, didn't you?
Candy...
People's mouths can lie,
but their hands don't .
As soon as I saw your hands,
I knew what you've been through.
Then, these hands...
But...
I'm not going to take you back.
I now know that you have so many
friends at Leagan's household.
A cook, the old gardener,
and the handmaid...
There are so many people
who love you.
When did you see them?
Oh well... Those two,
they are your friends, too?
Candy, putting on a pretty dress
and living in a beautiful room...
does not amount to true happiness.
True happiness is
all the warm hearts of your friends.
I think that, too.
Your teacher thinks that you are much
happier than Eliza.
I am happy.
Now your teacher can peacefully
return to Pony's home!
Hang in there, Candy!
If they're mean to you,
I'll keep coming all the time!
The three of us will watch over
Candy, so she'll be okay.
Thank you!
John, come to see me again!
You too!
Farewell!
She is such a gentle teacher.
She is almost like my mama.
You're a bit too tomboyish
to be her daughter...
Candy, did something
happen to Anthony?
To Anthony?
He was acting weird since yesterday.
My hands.
Hands?
Anthony was startled
when he saw these hands.
Hey, Candy!
Anthony!
I'm sorry for yesterday.
Allowing you to carry
such heavy bags...
I haven't realized they're
making you do this all the time.
Here.
It's from my own garden.
I'll give you a much prettier
rose for your birthday.
Thank you...
But my real birthday...
Alright! Next time we meet,
let's make it your birthday.
Anthony!
Okay? Next time we meet,
it's your birthday.
Candy's spirit full of happiness,
as if a rose blooming in her heart.
She thought that this is the hapiness
sister Lane told her about.