Safex
Because of Anthony's kind heart
Candy's heart
was full of happiness
A small ribbon connecting hearts.
Good morning,
Caesar, Cleopatra.
I'll make you two pretty!
You're up early, Candy!
Good morning,
Mr. Hoittman.
Something good happened?
Can you tell?
People wake up early and all by
themselves when they're happy.
In that case, something good
happened to you, too?
I woke up early
because I'm the gardener.
I always have to wake up this early
to work in the garden.
But this time I want to see
our important guest.
Guest?
I think, mr. Brighton...
Mr. Brighton?
Something like that.
Say, Mr. Hoittman,
Mr. Brighton will not be
arriving alone?
Dunno.
Haven't seen him for years,
but probably, his daughter...
Oh, I have a few things to do.
Annie is coming.
If mr. Brighton is arriving,
then Annie will come too.
Kurin!
Kurin
It's not because you overslept!
Annie is coming!
Annie from Pony's home!
I thought I'd meet her someday,
but to meet her so soon...
Annie.
Ever since we were little,
I though of her as my sister.
When she was taken away
by Brightons,
I cried and cried.
I've never been as sad
as I was on that day.
And Annie is coming now,
Kurin!
Annie is coming!
Did you call me?
What do you mean?
Don't you know how you're
supposed to enter the room?
Uh... you requested?
Make horses more presentable.
Our guest will be riding
one of them.
The guest will...?
Her name is Annie Brighton,
from...
I'm right on it!
What's up with her?
Seems happy.
She won't notice
what we've prepared for her.
Well, well,
isn't this Madam Brighton.
-Now, Annie.
-Yes.
Annie!
She is so pretty!
She looks like a princess!
My, my,
you've become a fine lady.
So pretty.
It's been such a long time,
madam Leagan!
Really, it was.
Candy.
Farewell, Candy.
I want to forget everything
about Pony's home.
That's why I haven't sent
you any letters since then.
Annie.
Kurin, don't !
Somebody!
Kurin!
-Candy!
-Yes!
Don't do that, Kurin!
Welcome.
-Annie, are you okay?
I'm sorry about this.
Candy!
What would you do if something
happened to our important guest?
Yes, but Kurin was...
Just take it away!
Hold on, madam.
Do you have a single room?
She requires my constant attention.
But madam, I'll make sure to scold
Candy because of this!
No, there's no need to do that.
Yes.
I was so surprised to see you here!
We haven't heard from each other
in a while.
Candy, it was you that vexed
the raccoon upon Annie?
Uh...
I understand how you might feel
but...
Annie is now a daughter
of the Brightons.
Suppose the Leagans find out that
you two were living in Pony's home.
the one who would suffer the most
would be Annie.
Candy
If you really like Annie,
let this remain a secret.
Okay? Understood?
Anyway, Neil and Eliza are happy
that you brought Annie along!
Oh, really?
Annie is the only daughter of
the Brighton family, am I right?
Annie, aren't you feeling well?
No, she's always like this.
Maybe she could try to be a bit
more like Eliza.
I'm just trying to look
like you, Mother!
Candy.
Kurin, sometimes people...
shouldn't meet each other,
though they might want to.
But it's okay.
Later on, Annie
will come to the barn.
And then... for sure.
Neil!
What are you doing here?
Mind your own business!
Aren't you hiding something?
Shut up!
Show me! If something happens in here,
it would be my fault!
That's ..!
A broken spur?
What were you doing with this piece
of junk?
Give it!
But... I've never rode a horse before!
It's okay! Right, brother?
Yeah. Our Cleopatra is very calm.
Riding her is easy.
I'm afraid!
Annie, please ride the horse.
That's right. A lady should
br fond of horse riding.
Now, let's go!
I'll borrow you my riding clothes.
It's Annie!
Kurin, you mustn't bother Annie.
Look, isn't she such a calm horse?
Yes.
There is nothing to be afraid of.
Now, put your foot here.
It's okay, put your foot here.
Come on!
Cleopatra, you need to be
very careful today!
Candy. I'm sorry.
See! It's nothing to be afraid of!
Okay, now look at this.
It's so high up in the saddle, right?
It'll be okay if you hang on tightly.
What's the matter?
Neil!
Annie! Don't let go!
Candy!
Candy, help me!
Annie! Hold on!
Candy!
What? A girl was riding that horse?
Get away! Another one!
A girl was riding this one, too?
What's up with that?
Annie, hang in there.
I'm coming now.
As soon as Annie climbed
on the horse,
Candy scratched its rear with this.
Right, Eliza?
Yes, that's right.
And we couldn't stop her.
Madam
I failed to keep my eyes on Candy.
This wouldn't have happened
otherwise.
That's right,
it was all Candy's doing!
Right, brother?
That's right. She becomes violent
if you don't keep an eye on her.
Annie..
if something happens to her...
Annie...
I must help her somehow!
Help me!
Annie, hang in there!
Annie, I'm coming now!
Hang in there!
Cleopatra!
Stop, Cleopatra!
Be a good girl, Cleopatra!
Stop.
Good girl. Calm down.
Annie?
Annie, it's okay now!
You're scared, aren't you?
Candy.
You're okay, thank god.
What a horrible thing to do.
Neil will hear from me
when we come back!
Annie, why are you so quiet?
You haven't said a thing
all day long.
It's okay, nobody is watching.
Are you pretending not to know
me in front of everybody?
Annie, haven't we seen each
other in a while?
You know, Sister Lane and
John came the other day.
John!
Please... stop telling me
about Pony's home.
Annie?
I forgot everybody.
Annie.
Forgive me, Candy.
Don't make me go through
this anymore.
I had to forget everything.
Annie,
you've forgo sisters, me and everybody?
I didn't want to! I had to!
I'm a daughter of the Brightons.
I have to do this in order to
protect my happiness.
As mother was always saying;
Annie, we took you because
you're a wonderful girl,
and you'll be happy
once you become one of us.
I'm worried about one thing, however.
If someone learns of
your past in Pony's home,
you won't be able to
make your way in high society.
I do'nt understand.
What does it matter to the society if
you don't have a mother or a father?
Don't say anything else, Candy!
I can't help it. Not anymore.
Kurin... they wouldn't even
let me see Kurin!
He looked forward so much
to meet me...
He was so happy to see me!
I wasn't even able to show
my grief!
Miss Annie!
It's the car from the estate.
Miss Annie, are you alright?
Good thing that you're not hurt.
Don't worry,
she was only scared a little.
Candy, madam is angry and
wants to see you!
Why me?
Candy. Are you saying that it was Neil's
fault that the horse went on a rampage?
That's right.
Neil scratched Cleopatra's rear
with a broken spur and...
That's enough!
Are you trying to
accuse others of your own doing?
That's exactly what Neil was doing!
Please, call Neil!
You've got some nerve for a servant!
I'll bring him myself then!
Stop right there!
Candy!
What's up with that face?
And you call yourself a man?
What are you doing?
I'm not angry because you tried
to tack your crime onto me!
It hurts! Let me go!
If I hadn't catched up to her,
she would've fallen off and
would've been hurt badly!
What's this, how come you are
worried so much about Annie?
Annie is...!
Annie? What's up with her?
Miss Annie
is a very important guest!
Don't you ever approach her again if
you'll do something like that again!
Who are you to tell me what to do?
-Why, you!
-Stop that!
Neil, if you do something to Annie
again, I won't forgive you!
It hurts! Mother!
What's this!
-Stewart! Quickly, get Neal...
-Yes, madam.
Candy, don't do that!
Neil, that's a promise!
I understand.
Candy, we will have you expelled
from this household.
I don't remember you mentioning
anything about that.
There are plenty of servants
that can replace you.
But...!
I'm sure I heard that from Annie,
as well.
Why?
I'm supposed to...
Annie?
But...!
But it wasn't Neil's fault,
wasn't it?
-Well, Annie?
-I...
She will...
Quickly, say it!
Uh...
Annie, what's the matter?
Mother!
Madam,
can we somehow bring this
issue to an end?
It was most fortunate that
Annie was not hurt in the accident.
I don't think so.
Candy put our important guest
in great danger.
But wasn't Candy the one
who stopped the horse?
But, madam...
We'll do it this way, then.
If Candy apologizes,
we'll call this over.
If that's what madam wants...
Well then, Candy?
Why do I have to...
Okay? Next time we meet,
it's your birthday.
If I leave this house now,
I'll never see Anthony again.
And I'll get sister Pony
and sister Lane very worried.
Okay, Candy?
You won't get her to apologize
so easily, she's not obedient!
Yes. But it's a compromise.
I'm sorry.
It is.. It is alright.
What does it matter if I
apologized to her?
I know it was hard on her, too.
Candy.
It's alright, Kurin.
Annie is going back where
we can't reach her.
Come see us again.
Yes, certainly.
We've had a pleasant time.
Well then, till next time.
Annie is going back!
Candy, I'm sorry.
Annie
Farewell. Take care of yourself.
Candy.
It was hard on you,
wasn't it, Candy?
I came to apologize to you.
I saw everything.
Everybody was telling lies,
but these eyes saw it all.
But I let you down as a friend.
I was too afraid to defend you.
Gardeners like me aren't supposed
to be curious.
It's okay, mr. Hoittman.
I wasn't crying because of that.
Today I lost someone who was
like a sister to me.
It's Annie, right?
No. Annie is still your friend!
In that moment,
when she was about to fall off
the horse, just what was she saying?
Candy!
Annie was calling my name!
That's right.
Not her mother or father.
Instead she called your name.
In such times, people call out the
people whom they like the most.
Annie?
Annie!
Ribbon.
It's Annie's ribbon.
She must have left it
behind on purpose.
Just like mr. Hoittman said.
Annie!
We'll be friends forever, right?
That small ribbon
Connected Candy and
Annie's hearts together again.
Even though bad things do happen,
a greater good might come out of it.
To be continued...