Safex
For Candy,the animal doctor Sha
was not a murderer at all.
In order to catch Sha,
Keli knows,the two security comes
she went to the parking lot.
There's another murderer.
Candy,Candy.
What,Keli,don't frighten me.
Sha,now go.
What's wrong?
Candy,Ma,he...
It's worse again?
I can't see.
I will change now.
Ma.
Where is he,he's not well enough.
Candy.
What about Inspector's home?
There.
I went there.
In the street.
Ma,Ma,Ma.
Too bad. Inspector must be very angry.
But it's not your fault.
But I didn't pay attention to it.
What's wrong,Keli?
Where?
It's Ma.
Ma.
Where did he go?
Strange. What does he bite?
That's sister's brooch.
Doctor Keli's?
Send to me on my birthday.
Where did you find it?
Perhaps sister went here last night.
Do you know where sister is?
Go first.
Sister.
Doctor Keli.
Do you pitch it here?
It's sliding here. If she fell down,he will die.
Be careful,Candy.
That's all right,I am used to it.
Sister.
It seems he find it.
Doctor Keli.
Sister,sister,it's me.
Candy,sister she...
Just lose concisiousness.
Sister,it's me,Sha.
Bring her to the clinic.
Ok,I will carry her.
Is that ok,Sha?
That's all right.
Ma,ask someone for help.
Don't stay there.
Hurry,go to find Candy and Ma.
They ran away.
Idiot. They didn't take their luggage.
Inspector.
Ma.
Where do you go? What's this hat is?
Wait. Ma. Where do you go?
Doctor Keli.
Everyone,help.
Be careful,careful.
That's too bad. Mud in the whole body.
Who will help her to change.
Wait.
I will change it.
Can't we help Doctor Keli?
She always take care of us,we must thank her.
Yes,yes.
Thank you.
In fact,Doctor Keli is a woman.
Candy,he's a woman?
Yes.
She's my sister.
Your sister?
So everybody out,including Sha.
Sorry,Candy.
Give it to me.
You frightened me.
I said why there's such a beautiful boy.
Bian,you didn't know it?
I am not confident with me anymore.
But,the woman doctor is better.
If only I am hurt.
It's no use to pretend to be ill.
That boy.
Doctor Keli,it's me,Candy.
Candy.
Sha,doctor she...
Sister.
Sha.
Sister,I made you worry.
The inspector will come.
I want to let Sha know,so I...
How did he know here?
Don't let he catch you.
I can't run away. First,there's no way back.
Go to the policce station.
Inspector.
What's the matter,Candy?
What?
Don't be silly.
You know,the doctor is the murderer's sisiter.
And you hide the fact from me.
Inspector.
Don't look down upon me.
Can you be quicker?
The road is very sliding.
Don't worry. There's no way back.
Come,go.
Wait,inspector,please.
Don't send Sha to the security.
Too noisy. Let go. After we know
he's a murderer,we can't let it go.
Sha,Sha.
Doctor Keli.
Sha.
Sister.
Doctor.
Sir,please help us.
You,go to work.
Doctor Keli.
Let me be caught but not Sha.
Please.
Please save her brother,please.
I want to help too.
How can the security come and catch no one?
Please help to hide Sha.
You are lazy again.
Inspector.
Enough. You all shut up.
Go away.
Inspector,the security will be here.
What can we do?
Then,the inspector want to...
Hurry,work,work,work.
Magu,food,food.
Lunch?
Yes,made something Keli and Sha like the most.
I know,sir.
The food for them two.
Yes,Candy.
Doctor Keli,inspector will let Sha run away.
But the security will be here soon.
Doctor Keli will be right soon.
Hey,when will he come?
What? That's the end of the road.
That's all right.
Together,push.
Hurry,we will do it again.
Look out,it will hit it.
We made it. Brother,it needs time.
What?
No,it's not big enough.
So,that's it.
Ok,make more dynamite.
I am afraid it will fall down.
How about carve?
We must do something.
Who's that? Maybe the security?
Candy.
I will help you.
Is Doctor Keli Ok?
Wait for the recovery.
I will borrow it.
Look.
That's right.
I didn't expect to do this here.
Sir,it will be right soon.
Wait,look at this.
This is the tree bark.
I don't know who throw it down.
Why like this?
It seems they know we will go.
Hurry.
Hurry up.
We made it.
Made it?
We can go through.
That's good. Thank you.
It's inspector.
Hurry up.
It's Doctor Keli and Sha.
Mr. Boru is my good friend. He will make it.
Thank you.
He will go to the police station by himself.
Candy,thank you for your help.
No,I should say so.
See you. Candy.
How will you die?
Dorucky is here.
Hurry.
Yes. Thank you all.
We just make the road. Be careful.
Thank you. Bye,doctor Keli,good bye,Sha.
Where's the clinic?
There.
Is Candy in?
Tiantian?
No,Candy.
It seems no one there.
Miss.
What's up,Security?
Are you Candy.
Yes.
How can they ask you to dig the hole?
There's not enough people.
Go to insepct it.
I will borrow your light.
It's inspector.
I do every thing I can.
There's no way here?
Yes,there's one month to be there.
No special place.
Look in another place.
I am hurt.
It's hard for me to be here.
Not nothing.
Please.
Only one nurse? This coffee?
Candy,what's wrong with Magu?
She's not well.
She must think three years before.
Yes.
What did she do?
She's a murderer.
Long time no see,Magu.
She's not that kind of person.
Mother is good person.
Yes,yes,good person.
Though she killed the bad guy
but she killed person.
Magu,Maliu who wanted to beat the baby?
Beat the baby?
It's too noisy,she said.
We all think you didn't kill anyone.
I just want to push him away.
It's not your fault.
Mother.
Maliu,I have something important to do.
I want to go to.
You can't go.
Maliu,mother.
Mother,mother.
Maliu.
Sha and Magu are good people.
They see the carriage,and said to themselves.