Safex
Candy lost her confidence
in being a nurse.
Headmaster Merry Jane
suggested her to take a vacation.
Pony's home in Candy's hometown
is welcoming her with passion.
Lovely bride.
Mina, you need to know
how to climb a tree to be our friend.
Push it up.
You wanna give up?
Jimmy, stop teasing it.
We are trying to teach it
how to climb a tree.
Don't force it, take it easy.
Let me help.
Mina, don't be afraid of height.
Come on, get up.
Is somebody here, Kurin?
Where?
Mr.Mathew.
Mr.Mathew?
Mina.
It's so heavy! Move away!
Mr.Mathew.
Candy!
I was wondering who it was!
Nice to see you.
It's been a long time.
You've grown up, Candy.
Got a boyfriend?
Come on, Mr.Mathew!
Climbing is not as easy
when you get older.
Let me see....
Wait a minute!
-Is that....
-Tom's here!
That super cowboy.
Hello, Candy.
Thank you for coming to Pony's home
to see me.
No, I didn't know you were here.
Why did you come here, Tom?
I came for Mr.Mathew.
There are no letters for you today.
No, I need Sister Pony's letters.
This?
Yes, please give it to me.
No, it's Sister Pony's letter.
Tom, Why do you want
to take Sister Pony's letter?
This is from my father.
Right, the sender is Mr.Steave.
Mr.Mathew, please!
Give the letter back to me!
Sorry, I can't do it.
I see, Tom.
Will your father's letter put
Sister Pony in a difficult situation?
Please, Mr.Mathew.
Tom,
it is my job to deliver the letter.
I know, but...
You must have said something bad.
Like, Tom peed in his bed.
Candy, I am 1 7 years old.
Sorry.
Please, Mr.Mathew!
Even the son
can not take his father's letter.
That doesn't harm!
Not this one.
Tom. Isn't this Tom?
It's been a long time. You look good.
Sister Pony.
Let Sister Pony decide.
Tom wants to take your letter.
Sister Pony.
No, this is my letter.
Sister.
I'll hand it over to you now.
-Thank you very much.
-Goodbye, Tom!
Thank you very much.
Promise me, Sister Pony.
Keep a secret for what's in the letter.
Ok,
I promise you I'll keep the secret.
Sister Pony, I won't tell anyone.
No, Candy.
I am going back to the room
to read the letter.
You can go back now.
Too worried to go home?
Nosy.
What are we gonna do?
What happened, Sister Pony?
Sister Lane, look at this letter!
But, this is for Sister Pony.
That's ok. Look!
Alright.
Tom...
How is it?
They seem to be surprised.
No! Jimmy!
Come on.
I said, ''No!''
Alright.
I won't peek.
Tom is afraid
everyone would know about it.
Don't do this. It's mean.
Why don't you let us know?
Yeah,
you are just like those grownups.
What can't you tell us?
It's not your business.
Tom.
Sister Pony.
Tom, I can not keep the promise.
Sister.
Can we read the letter now?
Yes.
Sister does not keep his words.
No, this letter is not just for me.
It is for everyone.
Let me summerize it.
Tom is getting engaged.
The banquet is at noon.
Tom is getting engaged?
Tom, is that true?
What does engaged mean?
To have a lifelong mate.
-A lifelong mate for Tom?
-Quiet!
There is more.
We sincerely invite Sister Pony and
Sister Lane to join the banquet.
And welcome
all the children to join as well.
Please must show.
-Congratulations, Tom!
-Congratulations, Big Brother!
Listen...
Congratulations!
What's wrong, Cassie?
Sister, can kids be engaged?
Cassie, Tom is not a kid.
He is seventeen.
I can't believe Tom is getting engaged.
Listen to me. Sister.
So, this is your father's decesion?
Father and his friend's decesion.
Why didn't you say ''No. ''at the time?
Of course I wanted to say ''No. ''
But,
Father already had a deal with someone.
I knew you liked Diana!
So I made a decesion by myself.
Congratulations!
Father decided by himself.
Her name is Diana?
What is she like?
I don't want to say bad things
about people.
What can we do now, Sister Pony?
It is tough.
-Sister Pony.
-Candy.
Sister, let me talk to Mr.Steave.
Candy.
Sorry, I listened to your conversation.
Candy,
are you really going to my home?
Yes. I want to let Mr.Steave
know how you really feel.
That's great!
Father is going to listen to you!
Wait, Sister Pony!
Candy, go ahead.
It's not the wedding yet.
You can also visit the Steave's Farm.
Is it really a good idea, Sister Pony?
It's not good for us to say something.
Candy is not a child anymore.
Ok.
We have always been
the trouble makers since little.
We grew up together.
But, my father is very stubborn.
No matter how studdorn he is, it is
not right to force you to get married.
You must have someone you like.
That's why
you care about this thing so much.
Tom.
I do have someone I like.
But, we parted for our own dreams.
There are many things that I want to do.
I don't want to get married so early.
Hurry!
Tom is back!
Diana, the groom is back!
I am back.
You are back.
Welcome back, honey.
Welcome, Candy.
Hello, Mr.Steave.
I am Diana.
Thank you for caring about Tom.
Nice to meet you.
Tom, she is the bride?
Yes, that's her.
Here, Candy, come on in.
Honey, give me the hat.
Enough!
Being shy in front of the guest?
Diana.
Come on, let's get ready to eat.
I expect it to taste good.
Are you alright, Diana?
Why didn't you ask me to help?
Anything wrong?
Nothing, Diana is acting stupid.
Go back to the seat. You are the guest.
Yes.
Tom and Diana are more than just a few
years apart, just like me and my wife.
You got married at a young age,
too?
No. I am 29, and my wife is 1 9.
I want to wait till I am 29, too.
That's ok. Reserve for the future.
The earlier the better. Right,Diana?
This... I...
I like it to be earlier, too.
Tom, what a lovely bride.
Candy.
Diana, give me Father's red wine.
Candy, try to convince Father now.
Mr.Steave,
the reason I am today is....
I understand.
To congratulate on Tom's engagement.
Candy, we had a deal.
Ouch! The bride is so lovely....
You are so mean, Candy!
Tom, stop talking in private.
If you are a man,
say out loud for what you want to say.
Then I am going to say it.
That's a man!
Father,
I don't want to be engaged with Diana.
Every man has to get married.
Father,
Diana is not who I truely like.
Is there someone better than Diana?
Candy.
Tom.
You...
Diana.
Tom, you are an idiot!
Wait, Diana!
Why did you say that?
Sorry. If I hadn't said it like this,
Father wouldn't have listened to me.
Is it also ok to hurt Diana?
I made a mistake.
The kids are in sleep.
Thanks a lot.
Candy hasn't come back yet?
I hope she can change Mr.Steave's mind.
Father.
Candy.
What happened?
Who did you fight with? Father.
I was not fighting with anyone,
I was beaten by Diana's father.
Diana's father?
I went to cancel the engagement.
Father, aren't you mad at me?
I have always wanted you to marry Candy.
You misunderstood, Father.
You are being shy again.
I gave up on the relationship.
She was adopted by the Adleys,
and studied abroad.
Our family will never catch up on
her family with a farm like this.
Mr.Steave, you misunderstood.
I did.
Father.
Come on, let's celebrate!
Great!
There will still be a banquet.
Tom and Candy's banquet, of course.
Wait a minute, Mr.Steave.
Calm down, Father!
I am happy for you two.
Honey, you are back.
I wanted it to be earlier, too.
It's all my fault.
Come in.
Where is Mr.Steave?
Drunk, and sleeping now.
What should we do, Tom?
Don't worry about the banquet.
The invitations?
Father wanted me to send them out,
but I hid them somewhere.
And Sister Pony's letter?
Father missed that one,
and sent it out seperately.
So you were trying to catch it
before it arrived.
Candy, sorry for the trouble.
I am ok.
Will Mr.Steave be mad at you?
The worst is to be punished,
and I am ready for that.
Good night, Candy.
Good night.
Mr.Steave,are you still feeling sick
from last night's drinking?
The chest.
The chest?
That's alright.
It will get better in a coupld days.
But, chest pain is not a small thing.
Sorry, I feel better now.
Should we wake Tom up?
Wait, Candy,
I have soemthing to say to you.
But, you need to rest.
I often forget things.
Often? Did Tom know about it?
I don't want him to be worried.
But, you are father and son.
Candy, I know
there's not much time left for me.
You know? Did you see a doctor?
I know about my body
better than anyone else.
Nonsense!
Candy, please take care of Tom.
I don't want to!
Candy.
You thought that you were going to die.
so you were anxious to get Tom married.
I wanted to have a daughter-in-law
before I die.
How do you know you are going to die,
if you don't go see a doctor?
What do doctors know.
Don't look down on doctors.
In order to save people's lives,
do you know how hard,
doctors and nurses try?
Candy!
I am sorry if I offended you.
I am currently
studying in a nursing school.
You?
Tom sees you as his real father.
For Tom's sake,
please come to the hospital with me.
Tom.
What are you doing, Tom?
Father is an idiot!
I am your father.
I won't be happy just because
you let me take over the farm.
What I care is Father's health.
Tom.
If you leave me,
I'll become an orphan again.
The person I like is not Diana or Candy.
It's Father!
Idiot! A man does not cry.
Mr.Steave,
go to the hospital to check your body.
Go!
I don't care if he wants it or not.
That's great!
Be good friends of Tom's forever.
Ok.
I am coming.
You are good, Candy!
Diana,
do I smell like the hospital?
No.
Making a wreath for Tom.
The medicine smell on the body
is gradually getting away.
It is the first time
that Candy feels lonely...
since she came to the nursing school.
She is eager to go back to the hospital
for a path of her own.