Safex
Dr. Reknapp learned that...
Candy moved out of the dormitory
and lived with Mr.Albert.
He wanted Candy to move back,
or she had to quit her job right away.
She had to choose one.
Far from reach but near at hand.
I am back, Mr.Alert.
Candy, welcome back.
Why are you wearing the apron?
-How does it look?
-Very pretty.
Try my cooking today.
I can't do it.
Mr.Albert finally got happier,
I can't leave him like this.
Candy,
what did Dr. Reknapp see you for?
You saw that?
Seems like you were being blamed
for something.
He was just nagging.
It smells good.
And feels good.
Don't wake Candy up, wait...
It looks so familiar.
I have seen it before.
When was that?
I can't remember.
Mr.Albert wants to regain
his memory.
I should stay with him.
Good morning, Candy.
Good morning, I overslept.
I gotta go to the hospital soon.
Candy, aren't you having
the night shift today?
Sleep more.
There is something in the hospital.
For Mr.Albert's sake,
I can't quit the job in the hospital.
I am going to beg Dr. Reknapp.
Gotta go now.
Did Mr.Albert
find out that I was fired?
I don't want to repeat what I say.
As soon as Mr.Albert regain his memory,
I'll move back to the dormitory.
So...
Look at this.
This is...
A previous army nurse
of Blanny's, Catherine.
Catherine?
She sleeps in the tent everyday.
-Dr. Reknapp.
-Candy.
The nurse I want
must be as good as Catherine.
Don't come to work anymore.
What I did might be wrong,
but I can't quit my job
as a nurse easily.
A cleaning lady?
Ok.
You are...
I am new today.
Candy.
I already fired you.
I know,
but I'm not a nurse now.
I am a new cleaning lady.
A cleaning lady?
Let me clean the table for you.
Don't try to buy me.
Cleaning is my job.
Who hired you?
The administrator.
Senior Nurse,
call the administrator here.
Dr. Reknapp, we just got informed that
Catherine...
Catherine?
She was killed in Italy.
She died?
Liar! I just received her letter
this morning.
Catherine died...
I just received her letter...
-She is not 20 yet.
-It's true.
Candy, your uniform...
I was fired.
Because of Mr.Albert?
Candy, why didn't you
discuss this with us first?
Why?
I didn't want to bother you sisters.
Candy, the elder sisters
don't just tease the younger sisters.
Let's go to Dr. Reknapp.
I...
Let's solve this with Dr. Reknapp.
Everyone go together.
No! It's out of the question.
What I decided will not change.
Even if it's wrong?
-Right.
-It's nonsense!
Too much!
Go back on duty!
Dr. Reknapp,
we reviewed Candy's behavior...
Now is not a good time to punish her.
Mr.Albert is not the only patient.
Teresa.
The reason I insisted on doing this
was because of Catherine's death.
We, too.
Catherine risked her life in the war,
to save people's lives
regardless of their identity.
And she sacrificed her life.
Catherine was risking her life
on the battlefield.
But now we are abandoning
Mr.Albert in the rear.
How would she feel about that?
Please don't fire Candy.
Would Catherine agree with you?
Yes.
Why are you so sure?
Catherine and us are all nurses.
Candy is a nurse, too.
Hope Catherine is like you.
Can Candy be back to her work?
It's not me.
It's Catherine.
Thank you.
It's great, Candy!
Thank you everybody.
You should thank Catherine.
Catherine, we never met before,
but you helped me.
I can only express my thankfulness
in front of the photo.
You were the army nurse,
willing to sacrifice your life.
The war in Europe must be intense.
Blanny, wish you safe and well.
You have to come back alive
and yell to me.
Candy, you don't have to do
the night shifts anymore.
Why? I...
You have to take care of Mr.Albert
during the night.
Dr. Reknapp said,
''if problems arise... ''
He can come back to the hospital
for treatment.
Dr. Reknapp...
Mr.Albert should feel relieved now.
Right! Let me scare him.
Gentlly...
He's not home.
Mr.Albert.
Mr.Albert, Poopet.
Is it possible that
he thinks I am fired by the hospital?
There's no message.
Mr.Albert didn't want to
get me involved.
It took him a long time
to start getting well...
Someone is waiting for me
to go home.
That feeling made me so happy
everyday.
Mr.Albert.
Your smile was nice and warm.
We finally got together.
Why did you leave me?
I didn't notice.
I thought he was in the room.
Thanks.
Come, cheap stuff!
On sale today.
You will regret if you don't come!
Hurry!
Mr.Albert
doesn't like noisy places.
What were you trying to do?
-Aren't you handing it over?
-Arrogant guy!
Speak!
I already apologized.
This voice...
Who do you think I am?
I am Neil from the Adley family.
So what?
How dare you touch me?
You will regret it.
You drove to give us a trouble.
I drove..
Why did you get a flat tire?
A child from a rich family.
Leave me alone!
Let me teach you a lesson!
Stop!
Candy.
Why is it a woman?
Three people teasing one.
Shut up!
You want to be beaten?
Don't tease a man, let go!
This woman really needs a lesson.
She doesn't want to live anymore.
Let me kill you with my fist!
How could you hit a woman?
Bitch!
Neil, run!
It should be safe here.
I won't thank you for this.
Mind your own business.
A hopeless guy.
Never worked out for a long time.
Why did she save me?
Didn't she hate me?
She forgot about what happened before
and helped me out of the trouble.
Nosy.
I can't thank her.
She wanted to help me herself.
Can't find Mr.Albert everywhere.
The light in the room...
Mr.Albert.
What a noisy girl!
Welcome back, Candy.
Mr.Albert,
where have you been?
I have been looking for you.
Sorry.
I went to work part-time.
Work part-time?
You knew I was fired.
No.
The money wasn't much,
but I shall be on my own.
What for?
You should stay home and rest.
No, a little movement
is good for memory.
And it can distract my attention,
too.
Candy, why do you look so tired?
This is because...
You didn't go to fight, did you?
Just like Terry.
Terry? Fight?
Mr.Albert, you remember that?
Mr.Albert.
It's not me.
Didn't you mention that to me
before?
-Seems like it.
-Candy.
Don't be upset.
It seems like that I am the one
who lost the memory.
Who is the patient now?
Mr.Albert is getting better
little by little.
Go take a shower now.
I was like a fool,
looking for you here and there.
No.
I shouldn't have sneaked out.
Mr.Albert, you won't go out
by yourself, will you?
You are having a good appetite,
Candy.
I was doing some activity.
No, it was because of work.
I should begin to work, too.
I will give you a suit
for broadway.
Does Mr.Albert want to go along?
Seeing Terry
may bring back some memory.
No, maybe next time.
I don't want to get between you two.
Mr.Albert...
If that's the dawn of the east,
then Juliet is the sun.
No.
The audience in the back
will not hear me.
For Candy,
I got to practice harder.
The beautiful sun, rise up!
Suzanna.
Terry, your voice is loud enough.
Sorry.
Please don't bother me practicing.
Even though I don't know
who that person is.
You are not performing
to the audience.
What?
The woman in Chicago
is your real audience.
What do you want to say,
Suzanna?
I heard you reserved
the best seat of this show.
Is that person Candy?
Please get out.
Terry, don't invite her.
Don't let Candy come to Broadway.
I don't understand.
Please, don't invite Candy.
Who are you to say something
like this?
Terry, I like you, I love you.
I don't want to lose you.
Terry.
Candy dreamed about Terry
calling her name.
But she couldn't move at all.
Chicago and New York
are thousands of kilos away.