Safex
Since they were set up by the family of Elisa,
Candy and Annie
had to sleep in the tree house.
They were immersed in the memory of Pony's Home.
Actually, they could feel more happiness
when nobody bothers them.
A dangerous garden party.
The sun is out already.
We were chatting too late last night.
Let's get up now or Stear will tease us.
What a wonderful feeling!
Good morning, Mr.Bird.
Candy, it's not good!
What's wrong, Annie?
The rope ladder is gone!
Candy is frightened.
Let me see, Brother!
It's great!
It must be those two!
Candy, what should we do?
Don't be afraid, Annie.
I am so scared.
Good morning, lazy bone.
Stear
Archie
What's wrong, Annie?
The rope ladder is gone.
It must be Elisa and those people.
Maybe
Don't worry.
I was ready for this since I was a child.
Look up.
This tree house is very well equipped.
Elisa, there is another rope ladder
in the tree house.
How come?
It didn't work out again.
Don't be too happy. I won't let you go so easily.
It feels so exciting to live in the tree house.
Today is the last day.
Do we have to go back
to the hospital tonight, Candy?
Brother, don't feel so sad.
We will have more chances in the future.
That's true.
Candy can visit with Annie
whenever she has a vacation.
Thank you, Archie.
Let's go to the lake after we eat.
I have a new invention.
And we can swim, too.
But, I don't have a swimsuit.
Candy, you can borrow mine.
That's perfect!I am going!
There is a lake in the woods.
Hold on, Candy, hide!
Grand Aunt Elroy?
What happened, Brother?
The thing Grand Aunt Elroy sat on,
was my invention.
It's broken.
What's thing, Stear?
Listen, everyone.
This is a...bed in the water.
A bed in the water?
This box is transparent and is made
out of artificial fiber.
A person can lie inside and sink into the lake.
There is a tube for breathing,
and there is a periscope, too.
It seems like your new invention is vanished.
What did you say, Archie?
Stear, don't get mad. I would like to try.
Ok.
I'll make a double bed next time.
Let's have a party! How is that?
Agreed!
Forget it.
Elisa
Four of you
can come to my dinner party.
A dinner party?
Yes, I invited many friends.
Grand Aunt Elroy agreed with it.
What trick are you playing, Elisa?
Don't come if you don't want to.
I was just being nice.
Wait, Elisa!
- We are happy to go!
- Candy
A part of only four people is not fun.
I'll be waiting for you, hurry up!
Candy
We don't know
what Elisa really wants.
We are about to leave.
Elisa won't do anything to us.
Candy, I'll go with you.
Let me lend you my formal dress.
Thank you, Annie.
Let's go change our clothes.
Which one suits you best?
My clothes are gone!
They're gone?
Would it be...
They must be worried to death.
Aren't they going to come?
Candy always wants to do things well,
she will come.
That's right, shameless people.
Everyone, this is Candy and Annie.
I am Candy, nice to meet you!
I am Annie.
Candy, Annie, didn't
I tell you this is a dinner party?
It's rude to dress like this.
I see what's going on.
Elisa, forgive them.
How would an orphan from Pony's Home
have a formal dress to wear?
I...
Annie, keep our dignity.
Welcome, everybody.
Stear, Archie.
Don't feel restrained
in a Adley's party.
I think so, too!
You are...
He is my cousin.
I am Mike. I am on vacation right now,
so I come to join this party.
A soldier from the French war zone?
Mike is an army doctor.
He is not a real doctor yet.
We have an immature nurse here, too.
Mr.Mike.
That Miss.Candy?
You?
Yes
She is a foster child of the Adleys,
and not attending her duties.
That is aweful.
That's not aweful, that's good!
We need more nurses.
It must a tough job serving at the frontline.
I am going back to the battlefield right
after the vacation.
The battlefield?
Mike, don't talk about the war.Let's dance.
Elisa, give Annie back her clothes.
They are in the room on the top floor,
help yourself.
The room on the top floor?
Here!
We found them.
Open the door!
Be quiet!
You are Neal, why did you close the door?
Candy, don't you like to take a risk?
The door is closed, use the rope.
The rope?
Go cry there!
It's so high.
But, I can't lose.
Watch me.
Ok.
Isn't that Candy?
Candy
Why is Candy on the top floor?
Evereyone, look!
Is this what an Adley's lady should be doing?
Undisciplined.
So behined.
She's almost like a monkey, shame on her!
How would Elisa have a relative like this?
Candy
You must have never seen
a woman like this, right, Mike?
Why is she like this?
She is always like this.
Liar! It must be a trick you
are playing, am I right?
I don't know anything.
Brother, we can't let Grand Aunt Elroy see this.
Ok, let me take care of that.
Candy, slowly.
Archie told me to go down fast. Ok!
It's not like that, Candy.
Throw down the suitcase.
I can't just stand here.
Leave her alone, Mike.
You are so heartless.
What is that noise outside?
Nothing, Grand Aunt Elroy.
Then why is it so noisy?
The sunset is too beautiful,
and everyone is too excited.
The sunset here truely is beautiful.
You are right, Grand Aunt Elroy.
Are you ok?
Yes.
Ok, let me come help you.
Ok.
Nothing now.
Thanks.
Candy, cherish your life.
There are people dying
in the battlefield everyday.
Sorry.
There are still many important things
for us to work on together.
Yes.
Come on, let's go down.
It's pissing me off!
Damn! I have tried everything.
Brother.
Candy's heart is going away with Mike.
We can't do anything, Archie.
Mike is truely outstanding.
Mr.Mike.
A telegram from France.
What?
Everybody,
I am very glad to join this party.
I have to go back to the battlefield right now.
The battlefield?
There are many patients waiting
for me to go back.
There are many young people like us
in the battlefield.
Some died, some seriously wounded.
I have to go back to the hospital, too.
I'll give you a ride.
Thanks a lot.
Candy
There are many patients waiting for me.
See you again, Annie!
Archie, Stear.
Thanks for your hosting.
Bye, Candy.
Elisa, Bye.
- Let's go, Candy.
-Alright.
Mike.
Can we just waste our lives with
no goals everyday?
Are you scared in the battlefield?
Of course! But, those soldiers
are even more scared than I am.
Let's say good-bye here.
Alright.
Maybe we won't be able to see each other again.
We medical people must fulfill our jobs.
Take care, Candy!
You, too!
Bye, Candy!
Bye, Mr.Mike!
Good-bye!
Mr.Mike,
I will be an outstanding nurse.
This young man Mike,
firmly strengthened Candy's dream
of becoming a real nurse.