Safex
Candy made a mistake.
That's the doctor in the set.
And that's a woman.
A clinic need no angle
All right.
Thank you.
Don't wake him up yet.
Yes.
During this time,treat me as a man.
It needs the man here.
But,the good one is dead.
Yes,dead.
You can drink all night.
Yes,yes.
Be quiet.
Miss,you will do here?
Drink away from here.
This is the clinic.
Miss,we drink for some dead one.
Who ?
Who is dead jus now?
Bian,he's just be taken here.
He's alive.
Really?
The operation just finished.
Yes.
Is this ok like this?
No,he lost too much blood.
The doctor seems better than the idiot.
And the nurse is good too.
Be quiet. The patient is here.
The doctor says the same.
How can you be naked before a lady.
Wait.
Let go.
Listen,give it to Bian.
This.
What to say.
We made a mistake. We thought he's dead.
That.
That's too bad.
It seems an audition.
I am hungry.
Come in.
Doctor,nice to meet you. My name's Magu.
I am Keli.
I don't know whether it's good for the doctor.
It seems delicious.
Nurse's food is in another room.
Sorry,please take it here.
But...
Two is better than one.
Maliu,take the nurse food here.
Yes.
Thank you.
That's quite different.
Please enjoy yourself.
Wait,don't you like it?
From tomorrow on,mine is just the same as Candy.
No,I...
But,the doctor...
I have my way.
Yes.
And just call me doctor.
Yes,doctor,doctor.
Let's start.
Ok.
Here.
I am ok.
That's ok. Are you hungry?
I am sorry.
This is not the hospital. Only two of us.
It's not like the doctor and the nurse.
Sometimes,I will be the nurse
and you will be the doctor.
Ok.
Come on.
What? Just a nurse,eat like a doctor.
Yes,Inspector.
Don't joke. The
doctor demand it.
Yes,just for a short time.
What about it,inspect?
Do as she said. For a long time
she can't stand it.
This bad nurse.
Candy,I will do it myself.
But you just finished the operation.
The same to Candy.
I am ok,the coat hang here.
That,I...
The rewarding.
You know it.
Yes.
Quite like me.
En.
Look at the name.
Keli,20 years old.
That's my brother.
He's doctor's brother.
He's gentle,not like a murderer at all.
But,why?
He likes animal. He was the animal doctor.
But,then,the place he worked...
Sha,it's yours.
But,it's not payday today.
This is the last day.
It's not same as our contract.
Just fired.
I know.
Where do you go?
I will report you cheat me here.
You want to threaten me?
I find you cheat me.
Wait.
How can I let you go to the inspector.
Do you want to fight?
Dead.
From then on,he becomes a murderer.
So,I don't know where he is now.
Perhaps,he will come here.
So you come here.
I want he go to the police station
Or,it's more serious.
Doctor,I will ask for him.
Perhaps someone knows him.
Sorry,miss.
You will be well soon.
Feed by others. That's the baby time.
Miss,miss,the patient. Open the door.
I am coming,please be quiet.
Please,miss.
Are you ill?
All of us.
All of you.
Look,help me.
Wait,please stand one by one.
I am first,help me.
What's wrong?
From yesterday,my stomock ache.
The same to me.
Me too. Open your mouth.
Nothing special.
You mean I pretend it?
I didn't say it.
Don't you believe the doctor.
But...
Be quiet. The patient is sleeping I nthe room.
Mis,you mean we pretend to be ill?
No.
Doctor,please say your symptom.
Candy,Candy.
What the illness?
The doctor can't speak the truth.
Is that bad?
It's the acute brain death.
What's that?
For simple,there's sore in the brain.
Brain,sore.
Don't worry,just do an operation.
Cut,my brain?
The doctor must see
the other patient,I will cut it.
Don't joke. That's my brain.
Who's next?
I am better.
The idiot is there.
What are you doing here.
Don't fool them.
No,Candy wants to cut for me.
Doctor,don't be too good to the nurse.
Though you are the inspector,don't be so rude.
Tiantian.
Malu.
Morning,you are Malu,right?
Eat the breakfast.
Thank you. I am Candy.
Tiantian.
Candy.
No Candy,but Tiantian.
I mixed it too.
It's Tiantian.
Don't worry.
Candy is good here.
It seems she's a good doctor.
Who's doctor Keli?
The new doctor of the Candy Clinic.
May I see it?
Keli,is that Keli?
Do you know each other?
I know my student in the college.
A very good doctor.
It didn't mention it's a man
or a woman in the letter.
I thought it's a man.
If it's a woman,it will mention it.
Where's the Keli you know?
I don't know. Her brother has some problem.
Anti,write to Candy.
I think it's a man.
Really? I think it's a woman.
He just follow us here.
Did Anne know him?
What's the matter?
Do you know doctor Martine?
Not very much.
So you didn't hear about Doctor Keli?
Just heard about it.
Where is the man?
Excuse me,who are you?
I. Are you Doctor Keli's brother?
Wait.
Anti.
He ran away.
It no need to run away.
He thought we'll notify the police.
After ten days,the bandage can remove.
Thank you. Thanks for the doctor.
Letter.
From my friend in Chicargo.
My brother is in Chicargo.
Must be in Chicargo.
Candy.
Yes.
You are much better. Can you stay for a weeK?
Go to Chicargo?
I want to find my brother.
I will take care of the clinic.
I will talk it to Meilu.
I hope no cute patient.
Will that be ok if I leave for a week?
Please. There's no patient yet.
Thank you.
You must come back.
I decide to come back.
There's some doctor will not be back.
Please be careful.
Thank you.
Yes.
Be careful.
Patient.
Come quickly.
Yes.
The terrible thing.
Come,quickly,quickly.
In the carve.
There.
No one's here?
I am the nurse. He's there?
Mr. Meilu.
I am the patient.
Any patient drink?
He hates the nurse.
Do you cheat me?
I don't want you to go out.
Why?
After you came here,we are very slow.
What? Someone hurts the fingers,
or strike,they all went to the clinic.
Is that my fault?
I think so.
That's my job.
If they go to the clinicd during the work
the work can't be done probably.
Sir,no matter how small the wound it,
it could be terrible ill.
I don't want to be treated by a nurse
Go back or not?
Not go back.
I must stay here for duty.
That's ok.
What do you want?
I can only do this.
No one can hear you in the carve.
Candy's heart seems freeze.