Safex
Aboard the ship heading to England
Candy met a young man
who reminded her of late Anthony.
That young man, who turned out to be
a son of an eminent nobleman,
arrived to London and unexpectedly
appeared before Candy.
And so...
Candy went through the gates
of the strictest school in England
The St. Paul Academy.
Pony's hill in prison.
I'm Candice White Adley.
Welcome. I'm the school director
sister Gray.
I'm sister Margaret.
Now, come here.
Yes.
Miss Adley, take off that fur.
Uh, no, I've caught a cold during
the trip to England.
Compared to America, this place
is much colder! And...
Adley, I have a question for you.
Yes.
What did you come here for?
Of course... to study.. and to
become a prominent lady.
And yet, you did not come here
as soon as your ship landed ashore.
Instead, you went on a carefree
sightseeing tour of London.
I'm sorry.
Do you understand?
Once you become a student of
St. Paul academy...
you are to obey my orders.
Sister Margaret!
-Now.
-No...
I'll take it off myself.
The school will store it for you.
No need to!
You have no need for such a gaudy
fur collar while studying.
Hand it over!
While you're on the premises...
you must obey
director's and guard's orders.
Adley!
Hand it over!
Oh! God...
Now.
It's heavy.
They're popular in America right now...
because they're so warm and...
What's the matter?
Kurin!
Kurin, quickly, hide somewhere!
Director!
Are you okay?
What did you do just now?
You brought a wild animal
onto the school premises!
Uh, he's completely tame...
and he's been with me for...
Enough of that!
This is not a zoo!
Sister Margaret.
Immediately catch that animal.
Yes, director!
-I'll help her!
-Wait.
You will stay here.
It's obvious that I need to explain
the school's teaching methods to you.
Brother, will Candy be okay?
Kurin is the problem.
I hope he didn't go crazy.
There! It went that way!
Hey, is something going on?
There is a raccoon on the
school premises.
Aren't wild raccoons extinct in England?
Brother
it seems they saw through the play.
I'd go over to help her, but...
we aren't supposed to go
anywhere near girls' ward.
So you're saying that
you couldn't find it?
Yes. It probably hid in the forest.
Therefore, the staff and the students...
probably don't have to worry about
being attacked, right?
Kurin would never attack a human!
Be quiet!
Sister Margaret, show Candice White
the way to her room.
As you wish.
Let's go.
Where is Kurin hiding?
-What are you doing?
-Nothing
Uh, I thought, what a wonderful
school building.
Candice White; speaking in the
corridors is forbidden.
Yes!
This is your room.
Immediately start preparing
for tommorrow's lecture.
We've gathered all the books
you'll be studying from. Understood?
My head is hurting
after just looking at them!
Just prayers and lectures...
But it seems like this is a good place.
That's right, I'd better look for Kurin!
Kurin?
Kurin, where are you?
Maybe it's Kurin!
How do you do?
My name is Patricia O'Brien.
If you'd like, you can call me Patty.
I'm next.
Next?
Oh, you're in the next room.
I'm Candice White.
But everyone calls me Candy.
Well, come in!
Excuse me for my intrusion.
You're sounding so formal...
Well, Candy?
How do you like your room?
-Hey, Patty!
-Yes?
You know raccoons, right?
I know.
These animals are related to pandas
and are native to Americas.
You sound like an encyclopedia!
So, what about raccoons?
Maybe you saw one.
Yes, I did.
Where?
-In the books.
-Books?
In an encyclopedia about animals
of the world!
Come on...
I saw a real one in a zoo
when I was a little girl.
Alright...
That's right! Maybe he
went to Archie's place!
-Say, Patty...
-Huh?
Where is boys' ward?
Just what did you say?
Boys' ward! Let's go over there!
What?!
Patty, why are you so startled?
Girls going over to boys' ward...
Come on!
There is someone who is
almost a family to me in boys' ward!
They are great people!
I'll introduce them to you.
N..no, I'm fine.
I'll concentrate on my studies...
You don't have to get involved...
Anyway, where is boys' ward...
Ssssh! Your voice is too loud!
You have to stop speaking like that.
It's a nuisance to others.
What, only because of that?
This bell signals free time.
Free time?
Let's go.
We're not supposed to be
in our rooms during our free time.
Huh? It's not really free time then!
It's okay, just come.
This is the library.
I already have enough books in my room.
Maybe Kurin went to hide in here.
Kurin...!
What's the matter?
I'm just looking for something.
Candy!
Let's go.
This is the lounge.
A lounge is a place where one can speak
right?
Nothing is going on... everyone
looks as though they're dead!
Ssshh! It's a speaking room, but
you mustn't speak in a loud voice!
Speaking room?
Otherwise, you could bother others!
They look as if they're telling
secrets to each other...
Huh? Candy?
What a pleasant surprise.
Hello.
So Eliza is your friend!
Yeah, I sort of know her.
Candy, allow me to introduce
you to everyone.
Eliza...
This is Candice White from America.
She is better known as
the barn princess.
Eliza...!
Barn...?
Even though it turned out that she
is now a member of the Adley family,
when she first arrived, she worked as
a dogsbody in our stables!
It's true, Candy!
-She was a dogsbody...?
-Why is she here then?
That's right!
Won't you tell them how
you been dumped at the orphanage?
Moreover, you're a murderer!
Murderer?
It was you who killed Anthony!
Eliza, what are you saying?
If it weren't for you...
that thing would never have happened
to Anthony!
Eliza, do you really believe in that?
Of course!
Now, let's go, Patty!
Leave her alone.
Who'd think that I would find
Eliza in this school...
And Kurin went away somewhere.
Yeah, who's that?
Patty! Come in!
No, I'll stay here.
Can I help you somehow?
Sister said that we will be wearing
white skirts for the morning prayer.
White skirt?
That's all. Good night.
Good night.
White skirt for the morning prayer...
-Teacher!
-Candice, you can't do this.
Your window is open.
Close it and go to sleep.
Curtains, too.
I understand, sister Margaret.
I left this opened because Kurin might
have entered during the night but...
Moreover
how did they know about this?
Of course. They're much stricter
than I thought.
I completely overslept!
Patty!
Everybody is in the chapel already.
Everybody is wearing black clothes.
Sister said that we will be wearing
white skirts for the morning prayer.
What's with that outfit?
Maybe she's on her way to the stables!
Patty!
Candy, I'm sorry.
Candy!
What's the matter
standing out like that?
White looks good... but today,
black is better after all.
I'm going to change!
-Director!
-Candice White.
Are you aware that black outfit
is required for the morning prayer?
Yes... I'm sorry.
I got it wrong.
But I can change quickly!
There's no time.
Take a seat.
Yes.
Terrius G. Grandchester!
If you're late, it would be better
to stay out.
Anyway, sit down.
What's so funny?
Nothing really.
It's just that when I see
everyone praying like this...
They look so calm and polite
on the surface...
but deep inside, I wonder
what are they really thinking about!
-Terrius, ge - -
-Was it " Get out" ?
Yeah, alright, you don't have to say it.
I can do that myself.
I didn't come here to pray, however.
What did you come for, then?
To take a nap.
-God...
-Forgive him.
This place is usually so quiet.
Unfortunately, that's not the case now.
Hey, you're gonna tell me when
everyone leaves, okay?
Well then
my earnest ladies and gentlemen!
Nice meeting you.
Wait!
Oh, I know.
I am to come to
your office after this?
If that's what you want
I can keep you company.
Well then.
Lord have mercy on him!
Say, who was he?
He's a son of Duke Grandchester
Terrius G. Grandchester.
He's a nobleman?
It seems that he came here
just to upset the teachers.
Be quiet!
You must not allow such
trivial things to distract you.
Due to the circumstances, our regular
praying won't be enough.
So we'll double our time
for prayer today.
My legs are killing me...
Tell us more!
Terry breaks all the rules
but he never gets in trouble!
He rarely attends
but his grades are good!
Terrius.
That was close!
Let the sleeping dogs lie.
Terrius.
When I first saw you,
you were crying.
But in the next moment
you were laughing at my freckles.
I have no idea which one is real you.
Terry!
Uh...
Director wants to see you!
Annoying old crone.
Maybe he forgot me?
He's making fun of me!
Oh no, the class is starting!
Nobody is here.
In which classroom is today's lecture?
To Candy.
The next lecture is held
at the northern building, room 1 4.
Somebody wrote me this note!
Uh, where is the northern building?
That way.
Thank you!
Why does it have to be this far?
There it is!
Sorry I'm late...
Eliza and the others got me again.
What's up with this school?
That's it!
Why did they say that this school
would've made me a prominent lady?
I'd only become an unpleasant
cold person!
Orphan! Dogsbody!
The academy's orders are final.
The best school in England
what a joke!
Kurin!
Where were you?
You had me worried!
Kurin!
Wait up!
Kurin, what are you trying to tell me?
Kurin, please, don't leave me alone!
Kurin, wait!
Kurin!
Kurin, you fool.
It looks just like Pony's hill.
Kurin!
Alright, I'll try, too.
Kurin, so this is your home?
I see you've prepared yourself
a lot of food.
I see. So you've already arranged
your life in this place.
Moreover, you've given me a place
where I can get rid of my sorrow.
Kurin, I'm going to do my best, too.
And someday, I'm going to show you
the place where I'm living now.
I will come to this place
if I become lonely.
Candy cried out to the now distant
sister Pony and sister Lane.
Instead of answering...
the image of their smiling faces
surfaced in Candy's heart.