Safex
Candy saw the vision of
Anthony riding a horse.
It turned out that
Candy mistook Terry for Anthony.
Terry carried unconscious Candy
to the nurse's room.
A treasure which caused anger.
I'd like to thank Terry
for what he did but...
I have no idea where to find him...
Kurin is probably
tired of waiting for me!
There she goes!
My sister told me...
Candy keeps sneaking around alone...
She must done something bad
and she's keeping it a secret!
If that's true...
this could become interesting!
There she is!
Alright. Let's follow her and find
out what's she been up to!
Neil!
Terry!
You wimps
want to find out a girl's secret?
Secret? Candy's secret?
This has nothing to do with you!
Move!
Why don't you try to move me yourself?
Shit!
Get him!
What's the matter?
Get up!
I'll remember this!
The leaves have already grown this big.
The other Pony's hill is getting greener
isn't it, Kurin?
May...
the time when this refreshing breeze
blows over the actual Pony's hill, as well.
Sister Pony!
sister Lane! What's the matter?
You don't usually get this upset.
I'm sorry!
It's because we received letters
from Annie and Candy!
From both of them?! Hurry!
Let's read them!
It seems that Candy is doing so well!
Annie, too.
I'm glad that Annie stopped hiding the
fact that she was raised in Pony's home.
Probably with Candy's help.
Candy was always the one who kept
giving her strength and happiness.
That's right. And to us, as well.
I'd like Candy to become even happier.
That's right, sister Lane.
Candy sounded so excited in her letter.
She said
"I'm going to be even happier now."
The letters which both Annie and I sent
must have arrived by now.
Candy!
Candy, where are you?
It's Patty.
Kurin, hide!
Patty, I'm here!
So this is where you were, Candy!
That's right!
-I'm jealous of you.
-How come?
It's because you can easily
handle anything on your own.
-Candy?
-What is it?
Candy, are you ever lonely?
Of course!
When I'm lonely, I come to this place!
-Here?
-Yes!
This place looks
exactly like my Pony's hill,
there's my father-tree to whom
I could tell him everything!
Your father-tree?
Yes. And this tree looks just like
my father-tree.
That's how I came to call this place
"The other Pony's hill" .
The other Pony's hill?
Yeah!
If you ever get lonely...
you can climb this tree and
it'll listen to anything you said!
So that was Candy's secret?
I, too, have a secret.
Patty, you?
Yeah! My secret treasure!
-A treasure?
-That's right.
Candy, you forget your loneliness
by coming here...
and I forget my loneliness
by keeping my treasure with me.
So, what is your treasure?
Instead of telling
I'll show it to you later!
I've never shown it
to anybody before!
I wonder what it is!
It's beginning!
Everyone, be quiet!
Now, everyone...
I'd like to inform you about
the May festival.
May festival?
Sister, when is it?
Who will be flower-girls?
Be quiet. You should know that...
this school organizes festivals
in May and October.
-It's the first time for you, right?
-Yes.
It's the only entertaining event
in this school!
It'll be the most splendid
fun day in a whole year!
The flower-girls this year...
all girls born in May
will get that privilege.
Maria... Mauren... Sylvia...
My birthday is in May, as well.
It was Anthony's decision.
It's from my own garden.
I'll give you a much prettier
rose for your birthday.
Thank you...
But my real birthday...
Alright! Next time we meet
let's make it your birthday.
Anthony.
Okay? Next time we meet,
it's your birthday.
And... on that day in May...
It's blooming!
The new rose is blooming!
Beautiful!
This is a new rose, right?
How do you call it?
Sweet Candy.
Sweet Candy?
I will give it to you as a present.
And today is your new birthday.
Thank you, Anthony.
Candy!
Did you hear?
Your name was called as well!
Me, too?
So beautiful!
You're lucky to have been born in May!
Flower-girls
can wear beautiful costumes!
May festival is something wonderful!
Cars decorated with flowers...
carrying many flower-girls
will parade alongside lined up boys!
Everybody will be looking at them!
And in the evening
at the dance party...
you'll be free to pick a partner!
Partner?
I'm so jealous because you have
a wonderful boyfriend...
You have Stear and Archie
and I'm always alone.
Archie has Annie, but Stear...
Patty,
I'll ask Stear to be your partner!
Stear...?
But... to become my partner...
Don't worry! I'll ask him in your place!
Really? Thank you, Candy!
But what about your partner?
My partner?
No! Just what was I thinking?
There's no way that Terry would go out
to dance in such a loud, busy place!
What's the matter, Candy?
It's nothing!
I'll find a suitable partner,
don't worry!
That's right! If you find someone...
you don't need to hide him from others!
I'll invite my grandmother Marsha
to the dance!
Patty, we can invite someone?
Yes. We can invite as many friends
as we want!
Really?
If I could, I would've invited
sister Pony, sister Lane...
and all the children from Pony's home.
But... it's impossible.
That's right! I'll invite Mr. Albert!
And grandfather William!
Patty, see you later!
What are you up to?
I'll send invitations to my friends!
You're so fast!
I'd better send those invitations
as soon as possible!
See you!
Grandfather William...
who watches over me and
wants me to become a lady...
My kind patron, grandfather William.
Also, I'll invite Mr. Albert!
What's going on with Terry?
I need to thank him for saving me.
Just a moment, Candy!
I want to have a word with you.
Can't it wait?
I need to go somewhere.
You're going to Stear and Archie
in boys' ward?
No, I'm not!
I'm going to a beautiful place
you know nothing about!
What's up with that, you liar.
-Are you calling me a liar?
-Yes, I am.
An orphane from Pony's home,
how you know your birthday?
That's right. Maybe you won't be a
flower-girl, after all?
Haven't you two
seen the school's name register?
It clearly says that
my birthday is in May!
You can't know that for sure!
Oh, you two are jealous because
you didn't get to become flower-girls!
If you want to become flower-girls
so much
I can ask sisters
to let you two join us!
I'm sure you'd look lovely!
I'm looking forward to May festival!
And I need to hurry!
Excuse me!
What a piece of work!
It's gone into her head!
Just where is Candy rushing off to?
I'm sure she's up to something.
Very well.
Is this deep enough?
It's enough.
That Terry guy is going to regret
for beating us up.
We'll teach him.
Maybe I'll find Terry
at top the other Pony's hill?
Kurin didn't come out to see me.
Somebody is nearby.
If Terry isn't here...
How long is she going to
keep wandering around?
The only place I haven't checked yet
is the barn.
Terry's coat!
He must be somewhere around here!
Eliza?
So it was Eliza who kept
following me the whole time?
I'd better watch my back.
I can't meet Terry now.
Avoid the trouble.
But if Terry is nearby
I could thank him now!
Ah...! Thank you for saving me!
Thanks you from my bottom of my heart!
Don't yell like that, silly.
She thanks me from the bottom
of her heart? Candy.
What was that?! That idiot!
I followed her around all this time
just to see her yell like that?!
Somebody!
Help me!
You held your nose up while walking
and just look where it landed you!
Who is that? Don't talk nonsense!
Quickly, let me out!
You're never humble, even
when you're in such a position!
Shut up!
Quickly, let me out!
I'm not touching the worst punk
in school.
I'll get my hands filthy!
Oh! It doesn't bother me!
You just stay there all night.
People rarely go this way.
Give me your hand...
You're heavy!
You're not hurt, aren't you?
Princess, you're safe now.
Filthy!
So it was you who dug this hole?
What a way to thank me!
See, that's a terrible false accusation!
Who dug it up then?
You know that coward, Neil Leagan?
Neil is completely unlike you!
Both are quick to blame others,
I didn't expect anything else.
Terrius. That punk!
And yet, he acted like a gentleman...
You're not hurt, aren't you?
I still feel it...
Princess, you're safe now.
It is said that he's a nobleman
who lives in a big castle.
A nobleman...
there aren't any in America.
I wouldn't mind dancing with him
at the May festival.
Say, Candy...
As I promised, I'll show you
my secret treasure!
Well, Patty? What is your treasure?
Let me give you a hint.
You see, I'm an only child.
As far as my memory goes
my parents were always away or busy.
I had noone but little birds and dogs
to talk to.
And then they sent me
to this boarding school.
At first I was unbearably lonely!
My treasure is something that
helped me through all loneliness.
I only want to show it to you!
Patty,
I'll be waiting for you in my room!
The light is on
in Stear and Archie's room.
There is light in Terry's room, too!
Unusual things happen, I guess.
May festival.
Archie and Annie.
Stear and Patty!
And I...
Patricia O'Brien!
I'm sorry, sister!
Patty!
Forgive me!
When did you get that thing?
Get rid of it! Immediately!
Patty!
Candy!
I wanted to...
I wanted to show Yuli to you!
I just wanted you
to meet my friend Yuli!
Patty.
Faint-hearted Patty against the rules
by doing something like this.
It takes more than ordinary courage
to do this.
Patricia O'Brien!
You always were an eminent student.
Get rid of that turtle, spend a day
in the contemplation room.
If you do that, you will be excused.
I could never leave Yuli!
Sister Gray...
Yuli is just like me...
weak... cowardly... exactly like me!
Get rid of it!
forgive me, Yuli!
Please, don't make me leave him...
Everyone, return to your rooms!
It's almost lights-out time!
Sister Gray, do you insist on
getting rid of the turtle?
Of course!
Animals are banned by regulations!
Not to mention that
it's a hideous turtle!
It may seem filthy to you,
to Patty, it's a precious pet!
Candy!
Why don't you listen to her reasons
for having it?
Regulations...
That's why this school is so cold!
Anything else to say?
Even though this creature
was created by God...
you don't have any affection towards it?
One who doesn't love animals,
doesn't love humans as well!
Just where would she throw away Yuli?
There is no food or water around here!
-You want it to simply die?
-Yuli...
Regulations are regulations.
I make sure that nobody
goes against those regulations...
and I intend to keep doing that way.
Patricia, get rid of it!
Why, you stubborn old...!
Candice White Adley!
You will be confined to the
contemplation room...
You are banned from participating
in the May festival
I can't go to the May festival.
And I already invited
grandfather William.
Mr. Albert is coming, too.
I finally invited them!
Quickly, apologize!
Candy, apologize!
I wonder will sister Gray forgive me
if I apologize now.
If I apologize now... now!
No, I haven't said anything wrong.
God loves animals the same way
He loves humans.
Sister Gray.
Am I going to hear your apology?
No. I won't apologize.
However, it's true that
you're a stubborn inflexible person..
I really meant that.
-Oh, no!
-Very well!
Both of you are confined
to the contemplation rooms!
Patricia only for one night...
and Candice...
until the May festival is over!
You understand?
Candy finally
managed to upset sister Gray.