Safex
Sneak in cargo vessel,
Candy and Cookie heading to America.
They've been found by the sailors.
Captain Niven told them that...
they' ll be sent back to England
next morning.
The other shore of sea storms.
It' s about morning.
Once,
the ships appear over the horizons.
I will be sent back to England.
Sorry! Kurin.
I thought that
we can return to home peacefully.
-Candy!
-What' s matter? Cookie.
Ship' s arrived.
I can see nothing.
I can see that.
Nothing can escaped
from the sailor's eyes.
It' s true.
The ship' s coming, Cookie.
We still have 30 minutes, wait here.
Where are you going? Cookie.
No way! what do you want?
Please!
I would like to return to England,
let Candy go to America.
No way!
Candy must return to America.
Captain.
Boat ready!
Good! Wait for the captain' s indicate.
Wait! Captain.
Let Candy return to America.
No way!
Wait!
How many times you want me to say?
Heartless Octopuses!
The captain is a fool!
Stop that! Cookie.
But...
-Viva.
-Yes
Grasp this boy.
It' s captain' s order.
Sorry, Cookie. It' s captain' s order.
What do you do? Release me!
Beat him well!
Stop!
Slander the captain.
Send them to that ship!
Candy! Your baggage.
Thanks.
Let' s go!
Take care of yourself.
Damn it! Beat me like a kid!
Everyone! Sorry to bother you!
Take care!
Take passenger boat next time.
Captain Niven. Good bye!
You don't have to say good bye
to this kind of man.
Are the punishments not enough?
I will definitely back again.
I will hide carefully,
smuggling to America.
Shut your mouth up and get on the boat!
Come! Candy.
Watch your foots.
Captain Niven! urgent telegrams.
Urgent telegrams?
Sorry we don't have unbrella, Kurin.
Don't blame us!
I wish I was in charge.
Unfortunately,
It' s captain to take charge of.
Stop talking like that, row quickly!
Elder brothers!
I have a friend on that ship.
You can asking him for help!
Thank you!
Now what?
Bro! The ship...
What' s matter?
The Sea Gull...
-Brother!
-Cookie!
You can read the flag signal?
Mission stop!
Whole members return to on board!
Return to on board?
What' s matter?
I have a little dizzy.
You bastard! Uncomfortable?
Mr. Viva.
Let me help you!
Sorry! Please!
Captain Niven.
Thank you!
I was wrong about you!
Don't misunderstand.
It' s because of violent storm alert.
A storm?
Just a small storm.
Even you' re smuggle,
I still have to save your lives.
The storm is coming.
All engines!
Can I help you?
It' s dangerous here.
Where are other people?
Where is Viva?
I go find him.
Are you okay? Mr. Viva.
Candy!
When you were in the cabin.
Do you hear the rat?
No.
The footsteps of rats?
Think well!
It' s relation to life and death.
I really didn't hear anything.
Is that true?
It' s over!
What do you mean?
Before the ship is sinking,
the rats would leave first.
Disgusting...
The ship' s sinking? How could she?
Cookie, is Mr. Viva saying the true?
Rats have the instinct of foreknowledge.
There' s no rats on a sinking ship.
I see.
I' ll help them.
I' m going too.
Move fast!
The scattering goods
might cause dangerous.
Watch out!
I came for help!
Back to your room,
Children should not playing around here!
I am no children, Watch!
Danger! Cookie!
Cookie!
Is he all right?
life is no danger, bone fracture only.
In case hurt the nerve,
he might paralyze forever.
Captain, please.
What' s matter?
The water is soaking in.
What?
I have to help Cookie.
When I was a child,
in the Pony' s home...
That' s it.
Appreciate you, Kurin.
Painful? Cookie.
Cookie, do you know who I am?
I am Candy, do you know that?
Don't move!
Your foot is broken.
Go away!
Cookie.
damn it!
You feel painful? Cookie.
I don't care about the pain.
My leg... my leg is broken.
How can I become a sailor?
Cookie, whem I was a child,
I saw someone broke his leg...
That will be recover soon.
That guy' s nerves didn't break.
Your nerves is not sure...
Damn it! Sank this ship!
Why you say so? Cookie.
Go out!
You have to calm down, Cookie.
It' s not sure that
if your nerves broke or not?
Is that so?
My foot has already been abolished.
Candy! Someone got hurt, quick!
Okay!
Seasick again?
Hurt!
I' ll wrap up for you, Stand it.
Thank you, Candy.
It' s nothing.
you are going well.
you must be a good nurse.
Here, keep on working.
The water has come in.
Don't be stunned, quickly,
or we will have trouble.
Kurin, you' re here.
Mr. Viva.
Candy, storm finally passed by.
Are you still seasick?
I' m Exhausted.
Yes,
everybody' s busy over the night.
Okay!
This is my unique cooking.
Candy!
Sorry! Without your permission.
Never mind.
Will you taste it for me?
How can they eat this kind of things?
So awful?
Just the opposite.
It' s so delicious, both I
and the captain have never took before.
Whom you learn from?
It' s Sister Pony.
Sister Pony?
She brought me up,
just like my mother.
Someone made this kind of soup,
must be a very gentle person.
The soup?
You can find out a person's natural
instinct in the material.
Smell so good, what' s that?
Thay already smell that.
Here! Candy' s special.
That' s great!
One more!
Viva, how about the seasick?
I' m okay now!
Cookie needs a bowl of soup.
Cookie.
He' s not here. Where is he?
The harmonica that Terry gave him.
Cookie.
Kurin, go notify everyone.
Wait! Cookie.
Release me.
Can't be a sailor, I would rather die.
Nobody say that you can't be a sailor.
I have already can't be a sailor.
Cookie, how can you be so weak?
You can't understand my feeling.
You don't understand
the pain of can't be a sailor.
Somebody!
Captain.
Coward.
Cookie,
you are not qualifed to be a sailor.
Yes, my body already disabled.
It' s because of your cowardice.
The man shrinks back of trouble,
can't be a sailor.
There' s no place to hide on a boat.
I didn't escape from the storm.
In the voyage of life.
There are wind and waves at any time.
Meet the setback and want to die
How many lives do you have?
Right? Cookie.
Captain Niven have contact America
by radio.
You can go to the hospital of America.
Captain.
Cookie, do your best!
Make your dream come true.
Candy!
We will help you, Cookie.
Yes, we will.
Come, Cookie, you need sleep.
Cheer up! Cookie.
Captain.
What happened to the ship
that going back to England?
I was told that she' s okay.
That' s great!
Cookie wants to be a sailor.
Terrius wants to be an actor.
I want to try my own ability...
to return to America.
I can't be defeated by
Terrius and Cookie.
What happened?
Candy! The port.
America! My home town.
Cookie.
We have already arrived America.
Really?
Mr. Viva, please take care of Cookie.
-Okay!
-thank you!
Finally...
Finally arrived.
Sister Pony, Sister lane, Terrius.
Important people in my life.
You are all in front of me.
Endless voyage has ended.
America at this moment...
launch her hands
to greet Candy' s return.