Safex
Candy spent a great time
on her vacation at Pony's Home.
She came back to Joseph Hospital
with determination,
and returned to her busy life again.
The young lady at Special-Care ward.
A very comfortable day.
Candy,
are you done cleaning for Room 1 1?
Yes, I am. Doctor Frank.
Bring the medicine
to Room 5 and Room 8.
Also, room 6 needs a sheet change.
Three thirty-minute drops for Room 3.
Yes, sir!
And....
Two-hour nap for Room 5.
Understood! Are these all?
Dim-wit finally grew up!
Did the vacation work?
Like Blanny?
-Dim-wit!
-Yes!
Scared me.
You are so mean!
Hey everyone, this is the hospital,
keep quiet!
Or get out!
Candy, keep the patients quiet!
Yes.
Blanny,
Pattie and Stear all wear glasses.
You are the coldest.
Dim-wit!
I won't be stupid again.
for what?
Headmaster!
What are you talking about? Dim-wit,
Your letter.
Your time to take a break.
Yes.
From Stear and Archie.
Candy, May is here,
and your birthday is coming.
Here is a birthday card for you.
It's so pretty! Archie did it!
I' ve been so busy that I almost forgot.
May is my birthday!
Anthony grew a new kind of rose for me,
Sweet Candy.
The anniversary of the St. Paul Academy.
Terry.
The first kiss.
Terry... I try not to think of him.
I remember his face
whenever people mention about London.
Where is he right now?
Terry.
Is that...
It's coming.
Help!
What happened?
Are you alright?
All gone.
Aren't you Stear?
Candy.
Found you!
I didn't expect to see you so soon!
Brother's inventions
always get us in trouble.
Candy.
Archie.
Is this real? Candy, the white angel!
Stear and Archie never change.
There are talks
about the wars in Europe.
Grand Aunt Elroy
wants us to go back to America.
Annie, Neal, Ellisa,
everyone is back!
And Annie...
I can breathe the air much better
outside of St. Paul Academy!
I was not learning much, and trying
to stay there was not helping at all.
Emergency! I gotta go!
Candy, see you later!
Archie, Stear, thank you!
I had a great time today.
Do your best, Candy!
See you again soon!
I'm late! I'm in trouble!
Dim-wit.
Headmaster.
Candy, please take care of the patient
in the Special-Care ward.
Yes.
Special-Care ward? What kind of patient?
Just came in. Her name is Caroline.
That little girl... What's her problem?
I heard it's Colic.
Nothing unusual though.
She'll remain in the hospital
temperalily. Please help her.
Yes.
Special-Care ward....
Mr.Markba was once there, too!
Why?
I always believed....
As long as I did everything
to take care of you well,
you would be fine.
Mr.Markba.
Special-Care ward was a sad memory.
Why did they put me here again?
Headmaster Merry Jane
did this on purpose.
She wanted me to get over my sorrow.
Listen! Sobbing and crying all day
for a patient,
Being a nurse
is not a right thing for you!
It is a nurse's job
to deal with seperation and death.
Right!
I'll try my best to help the patients!
You are in charge of Caroline?
Yes.
I am the practice nurse, Candice White.
Please call me Candy.
Practice nurse?
Please don't be worried,
I'll take care of her.
It is annoying....
What can a practice nurse decide?
You can talk to me for any problems.
Listen! She has to practice the piano.
The piano? Is practicing the piano
a bigger deal than being sick?
It's not your business.
You don't understand
how much work I spent on her.
Madam wants Miss Caroline
to be the best pianoist.
- Do you understand?
- That's right.
Caroline is gifted.
Brilliant! Like a genius.
Terrible! I had an appointment
with the piano teacher!
I have to go back
to discuss the matter with her.
You! Take good care of her!
Yes.
God! I can't believe
there is a mother like this!
Such a nice day!
why didn't anyone open the window?
Mother.
You are awake.
- Where is Mother?
-Just went back.
I am Candy, and I am assigned to
take care of you. Let us be friends!
No, you need to rest.
I feel better now.
It feels so comfortable!
Can I take a walk in the garden?
I don't understand.
Doctor Frank, how do you think?
I have no idea, either.
Nothing unusual, with no pain, either.
Let's keep an eye on it.
Candy, bring her to the garden.
Candy!
Candy, get ready!
Let's go!
- It's stuck, Candy!
- Ok.
You are amazing, Candy.
You gotta learn how to climb the tree.
See!
Thanks, Candy.
Candy.
Yes?
Is it scary in the tree?
Not at all.
It feels very comfortable. It lets you
forget all the worry and trouble.
You wanna try it?
I can't!
It's ok.
let me help you, give me the hand!
Come on!
Why did you stop?
- Miss.
- What?
How was it? Feels good, right?
Caroline.
Letting a patient climb the tree.
What's going on here?
I made her do it.
For what?
Just trying it. Everything is fine,
don't worry about it.
Just trying it? Caroline is a girl.
How can a girl climb a tree?
We will take care of the patients.
Ok, I understand.
There are things more important for
Caroline than climbing a tree.
Sorry.
Why did Headmaster say
you let her climb the tree?
Your mistake is my responsibility.
Dim-wit.
Candy, you didn't get fired, did you?
No, I am fine. Headmaster
took the responsibility for me.
Her heart is actually much gentler
than what she looks like.
That's perfect!
Come in. Slowly.
Mother.
Hello.
What's going on with the piano thing?
She can climb a tree,
of course she can practice the piano.
The teacher is here.
Nonsense! This is the hospital!
Nonsense? Climbing a tree is nonsense.
Miss Caroline,
let's practice the listening first.
Miss Caroline.
Caroline.
My stomach hurts!
- Caroline.
- It hurts!
It's all your fault
to let her climb the tree!
Doctor Frank.
We can stop her pain temperarily.
How about the piano?
Of course not!
What does a practice nurse know?
Of course a practice nurse knows
this kind of thing!
Shut your mouth, Candy!
Today she needs to be observed.
Maybe tomorrow.
Headmaster, is it really a good idea?
I can't do anything. It's our fault.
Sorry.
Good morning, Caroline,
how are you feeling?
You are here already?
Stop pretending you don't know.
What do you mean?
You know what I am talking about.
Look at this yourself.
The strings are broken.
I want to see the headmaster.
Any proof that Candy was here early?
Who else would it be?
Not me.
First, you were against the piano
to be moved in.
I am still against it, and....
Headmaster, I request someone else
to take care of Caroline.
Do it right away!
Ok, I'll do it right away.
Headmaster!
Don't talk!
It's not fair! It wasn't me!
Who broke the strings then?
Why did Caroline
suddenly have a stomachache?
Come in. Slowly.
Right!
When Caroline saw the piano,
her face became all pale.
She had a stomachache
as soon as the piano teacher came.
The piano must have something to do
with Caroline's illness.
Stear once said...
I can breathe the air much better
outside of St. Paul Academy!
I was not learning much, and
staying there was not helping at all.
Maybe it's...
It is Caroline.
Liar!
Caroline wouldn't do anything like this!
The answer is obvious.
Caroline has some psychological issues.
Psychological?
Forcing her to practice the piano
which she hates.
The piano she hates?
The piano was her favorate thing.
No matter how much she liked it,
if she was forced to practice it everyday.
No one would take it.
That's right. It is exactly
what your daughter's problem is.
Her unconscious resistance
caused the stomachache.
How come
Caroline didn't tell me anything?
She always listened to me since
she was a kid. She never resisted me.
She is a good kid.
She never says anything
because she is afraid to say it.
Move the piano away right now!
I can't believe it.
She is such a good kid.
How did a replaced nurse
come to Caroline's room?
Isn't it weird?
That's because Caroline...
Candy, get out.
- But...
- Get out!
Headmaster, it must be her!
No, it's impossible.
Then, Headmaster.
let me hide in Caroline's room tonight,
ok?
The piano is still in the room.
Caroline won't be able to sleep again
tonight.
Poor Caroline.
Caroline.
It truely is her.
At least, hide the piano.
Caroline.
Poor Caroline, I am sorry.
Mother is wrong.
Sorry I let you suffer so much.
Miss Candy.
Caroline has been out of the hospital
for 3 weeks.
Today, it is the first time that
she wants to play the piano herself.
The melody is fascinating.
I am wrong.
From now on, I'll let Caroline
do everything she wishes.
It's all because of you!
That is great!
Dim-wit did an amazing job!
Caroline and her mother
regain health because of this.
It is true that.
Candy is growing up,
and it is inspiring.
Candy successfully helped
Caroline and her mother.
She is now so happy to be a nurse!