Safex
Candy, who was encouraged
by Mr. Albert's kind words,
realized that she can't spend
her entire life crying over Anthony.
Instead, Candy decided that she is
going to stay at Pony's home...
and take care of the children
just like sister Pony and sister Lane.
Setting out on a voyage towards hope.
Huh? The bell?
Something happened?
Sister Pony, why is the bell ringing?
Candy, you don't know, too?
Then it must be one of the kids
pulling pranks again.
Stop!
Boss!
Stop ringing the bell for fun!
It wasn't for fun!
Why did you ring then?
It's the birthday of teacher Candy!
-Is that right, everyone?
-Yeah!
Teacher Candy?
Candy said that she'd stay here
forever and take care of us!
That's why we called her Teacher!
Candy?
Actually, I wanted to tell you
about that...
because I want to become
your helper.
I want to take care of the children!
Candy.
I have confidence in myself.
It's okay, sister Lane, sister Pony?
Yeah...
Sister Lane?
I welcome that but...
Now, Jimmy, feel free to ring the bell!
Okay!
Anthony, Stear, Archie...
and Mr. Albert!
I'll work hard to be a good teacher
like sister Pony and sister Lane are!
-Boss!
-Candy!
Attention!
At ease!
Hear me, from now on I'll be
taking care of you!
You need to listen to what I tell you!
Do you understand?
Yes!
Now, let's tell this to Mr. Cartwright!
I see. So you've decided to
become a teacher in Pony's home.
Yes.
I'm sorry that you didn't want to
become my daughter.
But since Pony's home is so close
it's almost as if we're living together!
That's true, too.
Please accept my decision.
I welcome that.
That's right, I'm going
to give you a nice present!
-Present?
-Come here.
I'll give you that calf.
You're cute!
Once it gets big,
you'll have plenty of milk.
We could start with this one, steadily
buying more cows as we go along...
If you do that, your farm could
become larger than mine!
Thank you very much
Mr. Cartwright!
That car...
It's the Adley family's car!
They still haven't gone to England!
Stear, Arch...
George?
I've come to pick you up
Miss Candice.
To pick me up?
You're taking me back to Adley house?
Candy.
Sister Pony, sister Lane...
I'll stay here forever!
I don't want to go anywhere!
Candy...
-Boss...
-Candy.
I want to stay here forever!
You agree with that?
Sister Pony?
Sister Lane?
Now, everyone, let's go outside.
Mr. George, I'll leave so you can
talk to Candy in private.
Now, now, let's go.
Please, let's sit down.
Miss Candice.
I'm fine.
An order from Mr. William.
You are to come with me.
No! I've left the Adley house!
I'm not his daughter anymore!
You decided that on your own accord.
Formally, you're still an Adley.
An Adley...
Please don't forget that.
No! I don't want to go!
Back to Lakewood, which is
full of sad memories of Anthony...
I don't want to go!
You won't be going back to Lakewood.
Madam Elroy returned to her
former residence in Chicago.
In Chicago?
Miss Candy
Mr. William ordered you to
attend school in London.
London?
Across the ocean?
But... Aunt Elroy must have
opposed his decision!
Actually, Madam Elroy
did oppose him at first. However...
I see. I can't oppose William's orders.
Instead, I'll have
Candy strictly lectured
so that she would become a lady
worthy of Adley family!
I understand.
I don't want to go!
How can he keep ordering me around...
If that's what he wants of me, he should
have come to say it personally!
Candy!
Come with Mr. George!
Sister Lane!
To be able to study abroad...
such a blissful opportunity
doesn't come often!
But...
Candy, sister Lane and I
are thinking the same.
Sister Pony!
Miss Candy
Mr. William didn't mean any harm.
It's for your own sake...
Jimmy!
She doesn't want to go!
Didn't you hear what she said?
It's all for your sake.
Boss, don't go anywhere!
Candy stays right here!
-Go back!
-We won't let you have her!
Yes, I'm not going!
I'm living here!
Candy, just what do you plan on
doing, supposing you stay here?
I can take care of the children!
Candy, a good caretaker isn't someone
who just watches over children.
Then, are you saying that I
still can't be a real caretaker?
You would have to study a lot more
if you want to become a caretaker!
That's horrible!
You two are trying to throw me out!
Candy!
No! I don't want to go!
Boss!
-Candy!
-Wait!
Everyone, please understand.
We are like mothers to you and Candy.
Do you think that parents can be calm
to give away one of their own?
It's very hard on us, too.
But, if she leaves to study abroad,
it's better for her in the long run.
Candy and Jimmy are...!
-Candy!
-Jimmy!
I thought that Sister Pony and
sister Lane wouldn't let me go.
It's cold! So unfair!
I wanted to stay with you, boss!
Thank you, Jimmy.
Let's take shelter somewhere...
That's right...
who knows when it'll stop...
You still feel sad, don't you?
I feel cold...
There's a big tree this way.
Hold out until we get there.
We can dry from rain here...
-I'm cold...
-Try hugging Kurin!
Kurin, come.
It seems that
nobody is worried about us...
I don't want them to worry!
They hurt you, so what do they care?
-Candy!
-Jimmy!
Miss Candy!
-Candy!
-Jimmy!
Miss Candy!
What's the matter, Jimmy?
I'm cold...
I think the rain got me there...
Why didn't you tell sooner?
You're burning!
Boss, I'm cold!
Jimmy, hang in there!
I'll take you back to Pony's home!
No, you mustn't return now!
They'll take you away!
Jimmy! Hang in there...
-Candy!
-Jimmy!
-Mr. George
could you please take Jimmy
back to Pony's home?
-As you wish.
-Jimmy!
Jimmy, don't die!
-Candy!
-Don't die!
You can't do anything
without studying!
If you stay like this
you can't take care of the children!
Candy, now
let's go to Pony's home.
Yes.
Forgive me, Jimmy.
It's my fault that
such a thing happened...
Candy, please move a bit.
Candy, step outside a bit.
But...
It's okay. We can handle it.
Okay?
God, please... help Jimmy!
Candy!
Huh? When did I go to bed...?
Someone must have brought me here.
Teacher...
He's asleep. Let's be quiet.
Sorry! Uh, is he...
The fever is gone. He's alright.
Sister Pony, sister Lane...
you two were awake the whole time?
Yes.
I want to take care of the children...
But when Jimmy got sick...
I couldn't do anything.
You can't do anything
without studying!
If you stay like this,
you can't take care of the children!
Even now
I feel the pain of that moment...
Just what was I thinking back then?
In order to make my own stance
I involved Jimmy in the process.
Candy, a good caretaker isn't someone
who just watches over children.
I'm beginning to understand
what sister Pony said back then.
I'm no match for them!
Candy, so you've decided
to go to London?
Yes. I'll study very, very hard
to become a splendid person!
In that case, we will be most happy
see you off on your way.
Teacher?
You traitor!
Jimmy!
Liar! You promised you wouldn't go
no matter what happens!
Jimmy!
You're not the boss anymore!
Jimmy, wait!
Jimmy!
Jimmy, open! Jimmy!
Don't speak to me anymore!
Go wherever you want to!
Jimmy!
Get out of here! Now!
Jimmy.
Damn it!
Damn!
I'm sorry, we've just become friends.
Okay, everyone? Take good care
of this calf!
Okay! Leave it to us!
Candy. Take care of yourself.
I will.
Candy, don't worry about Jimmy.
I'm sure he'll understand someday.
Yes.
Well then, Miss Candy.
Farewell, Candy!
Boss.
Farewell!
Farewell, Candy!
Sister Pony, sister Lane!
Farewell!
Farewell, Candy!
Farewell, Candy.
Hang in there.
Learn a lot, Candy.
It seems that I won't be
seeing Pony's hill for a while.
Boss...
Mr. Cartwright!
What's the matter?
Your horses...
Which is the fastest one?
My horse over there is pretty fast...
I'll borrow it for a minute!
Boss!
George, please stop the car.
It seems as if...
somebody were calling me.
It could be Jimmy...
What happened?
Nothing.
Boss!
When I grow up, I'll...
Pony's home will always be
your homeland!
Miss Candy,
it's very cold on the deck.
Please go to your room.
Thank you, George.
By giving kids a ride in your car
you've made them so happy!
You know
they never rode in a car before!
They are good kids, aren't they?
Yes, kids from Pony's home...
Jimmy, please understand.
Mr. Cartwright, I'm sorry.
I had to leave so suddenly,
without saying farewell to you.
But I'll write you a letter instead!
You kind, smiling people...
who gave me all these
wonderful memories; farewell!
I'll come back as a better person!
To Candy,
it was a departure to a new life.