Safex
You must be happy, Candy,
or I will not forgive you.
The same to Taris.
In order to forget Taris,
Candy decided to go to the moving hospital
in the mountain area.
The cross in the Bony hill.
Chicago is far far away.
Good bye, Mr. Albert, Alqi and Annie.
There're many people waiting
for me in the mountain area.
I am sorry.
Miss, may I sit with you?
It's very dangerous to take a train.
Dangerous. Be careful.
Nonsense.
It's all my grandson taught me.
I can't stand it.
Don't cry. Be serious.
Dangerous. Go away.
Are you all right, Granny?
It's terrible. So I hate to take a train.
Go away.
Go away. Don't be on my way.
Shut up.
We came to this land first.
What? Are you against to develop the rail way?
Wait, you can beat me
But who will take care of the cow?
The passengers must be tired.
Sorry, we need 15 minutes.
If it's ok
please get down the train for a while.
It's not good to the health for sitting to long.
Tom, aren't you Tom?
Candy, it's you.
I don't know you are here.
Are those your cows which block the train?
We will move.
You are wonderful to take care of so many cows.
I have a helper.
Mina.
It's cold.
I went to the Boni's house
and Mina helps me for the cow.
Boni's House?
Candy will go back to the Boni's House.
No.
How to take the train?
Run the cow away.
Mina, it's your turn. Take it easy.
The set of the rail way in Gulei town?
Please don't go there, Candy.
That's the hell.
Hell?
The life is very hard in the mountain area.
There're many gangsters there.
That's good.
Don't be joking.
I persuade you to come back.
Tom, I made up my mind.
I have heard about it. So I must go there.
This is my first duty.
A lot of patients are waint for you.
Candy.
Take on the train. We will start soon.
Tom, it's nice to meet you here.
Please give me regard to sister Rainen.
Tell them, I will try my best.
Candy, in fact...
What?
I can't tell you about the dean.
What's wrong with her?
She's ill.
Ill?
She's old.
Is she in hospital now?
What's wrong with her?
Yes, it must be the hight blood pressure.
Before I get out, she's ill
The doctor suggest her to take rest.
That's too bad about the high blood pressure.
She's old now, so it's dangerous.
Why do you hide this from me?
I don't know.
That's too bad. The patients
in Gulei are waiting for me.
But I am worried about dean too.
How long is here from Boni's House?
For the quick horse
you can get there before dard.
Go to my field to change the horse first.
You two, we will start.
Let's go.
What about your job?
It will be ok if I get there later.
Ok, let's get the luggage.
America is small
I didn't expect to see friend here.
Granny, take care.
Thank you for your friend let me have rest.
See you.
Get on.
Don't be so serious.
Ok, Candy?
The Dean see my growing, I can't hide from her.
That's right, we didn't change a bit.
But, we are growing up.
And dean is old.
I can't imagine she will leave us.
Candy, we must take care of her.
I will work hard.
Take it easy.
Thank you.
I will go to see her tomorrow.
It's so good to meet Tom.
Or I will not know the dean is ill.
She's gone away.
Hurry up, it's very near.
It didn't change a bit here.
Boni.
Dean Boni sleeps here forver.
Why?
Dean Boni.
Mother.
Candy, is that you?
Sister Rainen.
Dean Boni.
What's wrong, Candy.
Why was she dead?
Nonsense. Candy.
Why didn't you inform me.
I am sorry to Dean Boni.
Nonsense.
Why didn't you inform me.
Candy, calm down.
How can I calm down.
That's a corss.
Sorry, dean Boni's still alive.
That's Boby's joke.
Boby?
The new come boy. A little strange.
He will make the tome
for others while he's unhappy.
So it is.
He want to scold Boni's House.
Look, the word is wrong.
I will not forgive him to joke like this.
Candy, wait for me.
Candy, you come back.
Where's Boby?
In his room.
Thank you.
Are you Boby?
Yes.
You should not make this joke.
What do you want?
I will give you a lesson.
How.
Stand up.
No.
Stand up, Boby.
You're nasty.
What are you doing.
Boni is our mother.
I don't allow you to scold her.
How dare you to beat me?
Wait and see.
Stop. You didn't come back for a long time.
Boby, stop.
God, you are hurt.
Nurse still needs to cure.
You are still so rushing, Candy.
You always make us afraid.
But, Boby is too much.
It's really strange to make
tome for the alive people.
Why don't you blame him?
When he comes here, he can't read.
So old.
His father is the native He drinks
all day and forbbide him to go to school.
Are those words beautiful in the cross?
The others always laugh at him for he can't read.
What's this?
Boby, what are you doing?
Jim's cross.
Jim makes me a fool.
Boby, no name, whose cross is this?
That's right.
Boby's practicing the handwriting.
He can write now.
So you are not angry at all.
When he's angry
he will write down the other's name.
Sometimes, he will write the wrong word.
Candy, why did you come back by horse?
I neally forget the most important thing.
Are you better now?
Open your mouth.
Hurry.
What's wrong, Candy.
Just do as she said.
The throat is ok. Put out your toungue.
Candy.
Like this?
The liver is ok too. The pulse.
Put your toungue in your mouth.
I din't put out my toungue for a long time.
The pulse is ok too.
Excuse, is this ok for you
to take off the clothes?
You want me naked?
Candy, what do you want to do?
Don't be shy. I am a nurse.
Why do you check for me?
Boni is ill.
Who told you?
Tom.
You saw Tom?
Did he cheat me?
No, Candy.
Why did he say I am ill.
That's too much.
Why did Tom cheat me?
No, Candy. We must thank him.
He said so to let you and me meet.
I agree.
That's right.
Dean, Sister Rainen, I must thank Tom's lie.
Sister Rainen, take out.
Yes.
The dean helps to search for you.
What's this?
Taris.
He's a famous actor now.
Dean is his fan.
Candy?
Sorry.
Candy, what's wrong with Taris?
We broke up.
You are so sad.
No, it's a long time before.
Kaline.
I will leave.
Kaline find any girl friend?
I miss you so much.
It seems Candy is not happy at all.
Yes, Tom said I am ill
He must find there's something wrong with Candy.
She can't fool Tom with the happy appearance.
Is everyone here?
Let's start.
Candy, Boby is not here.
Oh.
I will look for him.
It's done.
Why are you here now.
Candy.
Make cross againe
Who are you scold ing this time?
Look.
Sister sleeps here forver.
Mine?
Yes.
Thank you for you making it for me.
My name is Candy.
That's too complicated.
Your word is just like the printing.
You are welcome.
No, I want you to help me.
Help you?
Who is in the firewood room?
Boby, are you making cross?
It's brand.
Gulei clinic.
Sister asked me to help her.
Yes, I will start out tomorrow morning.
There's no brand in the mountain area.
We are not worried about the brand.
Candy, please don't leave for Gulei town.
Yes, I have heard the local people said,
that's a terrbile place, especially for a girl.
I know, I make up my mind.
Candy.
Are you for Taris?
No, it's none of his business.
I am sent there by the
Chicargo Saint George Hospital.
Candy.
You're poor, Candy.
Dean, Sister Rainen.
Dean cried too.
Sister Rainen teared for me.
Thank you very much.
They need a nurse. So I will go.
Because I am a nurse.
I have many friend went to the European battle.
It's nothing for me.
I know.
We think too much.
But, it must be very hard, Candy.
No, you work harder than me.
Are we hard.
Take care of the children.
No, the children is the bless of the God.
Boby, what's wrong.
Sorry.
Boby,
I scold you, I...
Boby, we didn't hurt for this.
You will be a good person in the future.
Candy will be a good mother and wife.
Yes.
Dean.
The cold wind blows in the old school.
Candy was very warm in her heart.
After breaking up with Taris,
the coldness in her heart went far far away.