Safex
Candy tried her best to stop Maliu cry.
The young Magu was a murderer.
Maliu didn't know what's happened.
The special menu.
Mother. Maliu.
I have important thing to do.
Work.
Maliu's mother cooks very well.
Many people want her to cook for them.
Will she come back?
Of course. How long will I sleep
then mother will be back.
Two days.
They want to hire her.
If I sleep for these days?
One more day.
Then she will come back.
I am silly,I can't count.
Maliu,be a good boy. Mother will be back soon.
En.
Maliu,Maliu.
Where's Maliu?
She's ill,Maliu,Maliu.
I will be a good kid.
I will help you too.
Miss,please sit down.
I have heard you catch the murderer?
Thanks to you.
And Candy was caught too.
Inspector.
You didn't catch her?
Candy hid the murderer.
It's a good crime,isn't it?
No one knows
Magu is a murderer.
Sha is the real murderer.
No,it's Magu,a female.
Why,wait,I will get the exhibit.
Where's the letter?
What do you do,Ilasha,Anti?
I want to borrow a chess.
I didn't hide anything.
Wait,hurt.
Let me see,it's the letter mailed from Candy.
It must be then...
It seems you went to the police station.
Leave me alone.
You are ashamed to cry so loud.
He want to steal the letter.
What can I do?
Let me know all you tricks.
I have finished it.
If it's for mother,it will be quicker.
Keli,thank you.
Candy wants to say something.
Sir,yes.
Keli,play with Maliu.
In fact,
you want to bright Maliu to the street,do you?
If not find someone to replace Magu
we will starve.
Take it to the office.
It will be arranged.
What will you do to Maliu?
Mother was like that.
She can't stay here for long.
Move her to other place.
Sir.
I will take Magu's place.
Candy said for the food. Yes.
Of course,I will be a good nurse too.
Don't joking. I am seriouse.
So,let Maliu stay here.
Do you cook before? Of course.
I am the genious.
You just cooked for two or three people.
No,ten.
But,here's more than 100.
Leave it to me. I think you know,
more people do not matter at all.
Though you said so
you will find 1 10 is different.
If some's here.
Tiantian,the pot is hot.
Put it in first.
I will help too.
No,you will cut yourself.
I am frighten you.
I am hurngry. Isn't it ready yet?
What about food.
Don't make us hungry.
Sorry,wait a little more.
Candy is cooking.
If there's anything wrong...
I am the nurse,it doesn't matter.
Today we will have
the corn soup.
Don't push. Stand one by one.
I want a big bowl.
It's full.
Please,I want a big bowl.
Please. The same.
Good. Good.
Candy,hurry up.
What's wrong?
What's this,it's not enough.
Be quiet,it's just before the lunch,isn't it?
You will serve the dinner now?
Sorry,that's all.
We have bread.
Yes,please stand it first.
Change it.
I know it's burnt. But that's delicious too.
No,it's quite different.
I forget.
God,I said don't make fuss.
Sorry,I will be good tomorrow.
No?
Candy,health is important for them.
They work in the dark everyday.
They only have pleasure during the dinner.
If you feed them with fodder
what will they think?
Do you think this is good?
Yes,Candy,do you have parents?
No. So do I. But I have later.
Inspector.
So,he's the big boss here.
You are a good nurse too.
Maliu will be good too.
Even without parents,she will be good.
But,is this all right to bring
Maliu to the street?
Yes,Maliu,Candy.
Are you hungry?
I didn't have supper yet.
Wait,I will cook something for you.
Be well,Maliu.
So is the inspector.
Bye,bye.
Candy,see you. See you,inspector.
It's really quick.
Maliu,are you happy to the street?
Yes,because mother is there.
But,want to see mother.
Eat delicious food with mother.
It's rabbit. Just like mother.
Yes,Uncle,hurry,hurry.
I can't say anything else.
The contact car isn't here yet.
Candy.
No,it's cold. Wait in the waiting room.
What about it?
It should be here three hours before.
I don't know. The train won't come here.
It won't take Maliu away.
Do you want to go back?
It's not joke.
So,it will be a big problem for inspector.
Inspector.
First,it's bad without food and fire.
It's train. The train's coming.
It's sound.
It's true.
Gulei town,the last stop.
Is there any one taking the train?
The young woman.
Young woman. Anne,Candy,that's good.
Anne,Anti.
Candy,I didn't see you for a long time.
So,Ilasha gives my letter to the police.
So,perhaps,because Candy hide the murderer.
And she's caught.
Yes,I am worried. So I came here.
Sha's all right.
But,Maliu's mother was caught.
Do you want to see your mother?
Yes,much quicker than we go back.
We will talk to them.
Ilasha made it. Candy.
How can we stop to let Maliu to the street?
Leave the food to us.
So it is.
But I am confident for cooking for 1 10 people.
Besides,the Adura's Home in Chicargo,
if you do not go back soon,then...
Don't worry about it.
Rocky will ski in the hill.
Do it,Candy.
If so,thank you.
I can't compare with Candy.
Maliu went back to the street,
and she still can't see her mother.
No,I want to go.
Mother will come back to me,let's wait.
Candy's lie.
Maliu's a good child.
Maliu get down the train. No,don't.
Maliu,perhaps mother is in front of here. Mother?
If we miss her,it's not so good.
Follow me,let's go back.
Really,will you be back?
Yes,do as Candy said.
Why not do as my command?
But...
They are good at cooking.
Don't be rude.
What's good at cooking?
Don't be like that.
Anne will not disabey the family work.
Yes,mine is good too.
What? Mine is too.
Are you a man?
Yes. Yours are like a puppet.
Go back,back.
What?
Do you judge a man by hand and face?
Yes.
What?
After all,will we use it or not...
Please,inspector.
Give you one more change.
If you make strange things,
throw you to the valley.
Candy.
Come to see the bread.
Anti peel the potato,
cut the radish,it's really good.
Anti,so,
I can't compare with Candy.
I am really worse.
Candy,is that burnt?
I hope we can eat supper tonight.
It's terrible only having soup.
I am hungry.
What?
You work so hard everyday.
Miss.
Candy,don't you stand on quene?
We work all day,and now we need to stand?
I am really sorry.
Please,try it.
This is good. Is this ok?
Inspector's.
Now,come here.
No,that's ok.
Inspector.
You eat too.
So,I make it.
For the first time,I see them eat so happily.
The leave can't be eaten.
Idiot,that's the decoration.
It's like what my wife made.
Aren't you single?
No,if my wife's here,
The set with happy mood.
Maliu wanted to go to the street.
No one find it.