Safex
The dance where I met him.
The day for the party
is finally here.
However, Candy had no dress for
the party.
However, since she was invited
Candy decided to go to the party
dressed as she was,
even though she was well aware that
her dress was hardly appropriate.
How is she not embarassed of being seen
wearing that thing at the party?
Does it matter?
She didn't want your dress, anyway.
Maybe so.
I want to meet Anthony!
Tell me, what will Anthony
think about this dress?
My, my, if he's anything like you,
he won't get his eyes off you.
Is it wrong? I like him!
The boy whom Eliza likes
is called Anthony?
I wonder what he's like.
-Candy.
-Yes?
Listen.
The grand aunt Elroy of the Adley
family is extremely insistent on courtesy.
If you somehow stand out during the party,
we will send you back immediately.
Yes
This road...!
This road... it leads to the rose gates!
The place where I met the Prince...
The rose gates are open now!
The gates which were always closed!
Wow, wonderful!
This residesnce looks like a castle!
I don't belong in this place, at all.
And besides, I...
Hello, Candy!
Hey, miss tomboy!
Stear and Archie!
I knew you would come!
You too?
You invited her as well?
Great minds think alike!
Welcome.
Grand aunt Elroy is waiting for you.
Thanks.
Where is Anthony?
Over there.
Is that so? Anthony?
Eliza, don't run.
-Welcome, Candy!
-We've been waiting for you.
What's the matter, Candy?
-I...
-It's not like you!
We'll escort you.
Give me your hand!
Stear and Archie don't seem to mind
the way I'm dressed...
I'm glad I came, after all!
That's the spirit.
You're cute when you smile!
The Prince!
I thought I might happen to meet him
but...
to really meet him...
I didn't think I'd see you here!
We thought you'd come by later.
Anthony? What are you doing?
Anthony?!
This person is...
My prince is...
Anthony whom Eliza likes...
This can't be...
My name is Anthony.
Anthony Brown.
I'm Candice White.
She is our servant.
That's not true!
I came to the Leagan family
as Eliza's playmate.
At first, yes.
But now you're my servant.
If I knew you're
in the Leagan family,
I'd invite you over, too.
Sorry! We did that before you!
Really?
Since she was officially invited,
she is a guest just like
Eliza and everyone else!
Thank you.
Anthony,
how come you know Candy?
I don't ... I saw her at the rose gates
a few days back.
That's not true!
We met much earlier,
haven't we?
At the Pony's hill.
Party is about to begin.
Please gather inside before dinner.
To all members of the Adley family;
welcome.
That person is grand aunt Elroy?
She is scary.
I decided to move to this estate
in order to live with my grandchildren,
with whom I spent very little time so far.
I would like to give my best regards
to my three sweet grandchildren.
Where are they?
Some grandchildren I have!
All of us, who are living in in this
estate, and grandfather William's ...
Candy!
I promised that I'll escort you.
Archie...
What's with that suit?
Everyone's suits are too formal.
Don't tell me you did this for me...
I didn't . Come with me!
Anyway, you wouldn't be able to hide
if you were wearing a lady's dress!
This is great!
Won't you eat, too?
There's no stopping great aunt Elroy
once she starts rambling!
Archie!
Who laughed?
It was me.
Candy!
Who is that girl?
Aunt Elroy, I am very sorry.
She is one of our servants.
And what is a servant doing in here?
We brought that girl along because
Stear and Archie officially invited her.
My grandchildren?
In that case, why did you allow her
to come in such casual clothes?
...just what were they thinking...
...they don't know the party dress code...
Only you are standing out. Here,
look around.
There is nobody else dressed that way.
That's not true, aunt.
You two!
Aunt, we are sorry.
The girl was laughing at me!
Archie, your face...!
Don't be so careless!
Aunt, try to be more relaxed!
Well then, I propose a toast to
health of our grand aunt!
Cheers!
I surrender to you guys!
We'll continue later on.
Now, the dinner.
The Leagans were ridiculed
because of her!
I won't forgive her.
Where'd she go, anyway?
Thank you. You all changed
your clothes because of me.
We're the ones to apologize!
We invited you
without much thought.
No, I really appreciate it!
It looks almost as if
we are in a castle.
It's almost as if I were dreaming.
What are we going to do?
Tell her? Anthony?
-Maybe.
-What?
-What is it?
-You know...
there is a scary room in this house!
With ghosts and all?
Yes.
At night, there are ghosts in there.
The ghosts of the Adley warriors.
When the southern clock tower
strikes ten...
...the light goes on in an empty room!
With a top hat and a black mantle,
he goes around for a walk.
"I won't let you go." , " Nobody out."
That's right.
The ghost's footsteps keep
echoing in the hallway...
...tap...tap...tap...
You're lying, aren't you?
Sorry!
Candy, I'm really sorry.
Cheer up,
the dance is about to begin.
I'd like to talk to you and Anthony.
-What about?
-Come to my room.
We'll be back soon, then.
If she shows up at the dance
wearing that,
everybody will laugh at us Leagans.
Let's throw her out of this place.
You can't do that while Stear and
Archie are following her.
However, I have a good idea.
Here it is!
-Archie...
-that's ...
Of course,
since I knew she'd be coming,
I bought this for Candy!
Then,
why didn't you show it sooner?
I wanted everyone to be surprised,
when she stands out at the party!
Candy?
My head hurts.
Won't you prepare a bed for me
in the bedroom?
Yes, okay!
It's the last room on the third floor!
I'll bring eliza in a minute.
I understand!
The last room on the third floor...?
Wearing a top hat and a black mantle...
Hey, they're just puppets!
But they look just like real people!
A whole line of Adleys...
...they said, ancient warriors, huh?
But I don't like this.
That must be it!
That room.
Eliza!
I'll let you out an hour later!
So stay quiet until I let you out!
Open up! Let me out!
And watch out for ghosts!
Look at this.
I guess... this one is for Candy, too?
That's right.
Brothers think alike, right?
I'm sorry, but that dress
is way too big for Candy!
No way...?
You'd better leave
these things to Archie!
I knew her exact sizes the
moment I saw her!
Archie, I can't let you be the
only one to give nice things to Candy!
Come on, don't fight.
Why don't you try
to join two dresses together?
Okay, that way, I could still
give my dress to Candy.
Okay! In that case,
leave the rest to me!
If you really can do that, then let
me be the one to tell it to Candy.
See you!
Eliza!
Anthony!
Where is Candy?
I don't know.
The dance is about to begin,
won't you dance with me?
Where'd she go...?
Don't mind Candy!
She is here for the first time, so...
she might have gotten lost.
I'll look for her!
He's not gonna find her!
Help me!
I think I heard a sound
coming from here...
The dance begun already.
Where did she go?
Let me out!
Somebody let me out!
Anthony! Dance with me!
Hey, Archie!
Are you done already?
Dance will be over
before you get this done!
Now we wouldn't want that to happen!
The clock...
That's ...the southern tower!
"When the southern clock tower
strikes ten..."
It's ten'o 'clock.
"the light goes on in an empty room!"
"With a top hat and a black mantle,
he goes around for a walk."
Somebody! Help me!
A ghost!
Candy?
Anthony?
Anthony!
What are you doing in such a place?
When the clock struck ten - -
...it started to pace around!
Just what are you talking about?
About a ghost!
But that's just a story.
The dance is beginning.
Found her.
Where were you?
I found her wandering on the third floor.
Now, Candy, put this on!
Wow, it's beautiful!
Is this... for me?
These are mother's memento.
I'll borrow them to you,
please take them.
Candy!
How did she come out?
It's wonderful. Am I dreaming?
If it's a dream,
I never want to wake up.
Candy, it's not a dream.
It's true? It's really true, isn't it?
Anthony, I wanted to ask you before
but...
What was it?
Do you know about Pony's hill?
Pony's hill?
I don't know
But...
It's my turn now!
I wonder why Anthony said that
he doesn't know about Pony's hill.
But I don't care. It's not going
to change my Prince in any way.
I'm sorry!
You were better
while you danced with Anthony!
Don't complain!
It's my turn now!
To bring a servant to a party...
Madam Leagan is
such a gentle person.
Darling, have you heard what
everybody was saying?
Candy made us look caring.
No. Even though
everybody was saying that,
deep inside
they were condemning the idea.
What we brought with ourselves
is this pure girl.
And even the great aunt is
looking at her like that.
In any case, this can't go on
for too long.
Archie's lucid expression...
...and the mischievous spark in
Stear's eyes...
But...
when I'm dancing with Anthony,
I remember the light breeze
from the hill.
The breeze that grew so much gentler
from the time when I met the Prince.
I can forgive Neil and Eliza.
Sister Pony, sister Lane!
I'm so happy right now!
This was Candy's first party.