Safex
After losing Terry,
Mr. Albert becomes the
only support Candy has.
At this time, Mr. Albert
bumped into a car accident.
Slight memories.
Bad news!
Candy!
She's not home?
What should I do? Candy?
Candy!
Poopet, you're so annoying!
Candy, bad news, your brother...
My brother?
Is she talking about Mr. Albert?
Mr. Albert's out buying things.
He hasn't come back yet.
I am coming!
What's the matter?
Candy!
What's wrong?
Your brother was bumped by a car!
He's in Happy Clinic right now.
How's he?
I'm not sure.
You'd better hurry up taking a look.
Mr. Albert had a car accident.
Why?
After Terry had gone,
Stear left us.
Now it's Mr. Albert...
Here?
Human, dogs, and cats
are all welcome.
Why did they send him here?
Come on in!
Push harder! The door is broken.
Ok.
Where's Mr. Albert?
Is that this patient's name?
Yes.
He's taking a rest there.
Mr. Albert...
Is he dead?
Open your eyes! Mr.Albert!
What happened, Mr.Albert?
Hey, slow down.
Why didn't Mr. Albert answer me?
Calm down, drink some coffee.
I don't need that.
His wound is not that bad.
Not that bad?
That's right.
Getting wounded is always a
serious deal. Aren't you a doctor?
Yes, I am.
Better than I imagine.
You're such a lousy docter!
How can a doctor examine his patient
by imagination?
Lousy docter.
Mean girl with sloppy pajamas.
At least I'm wearing clothes.
I wear that because
I caught a bad cold.
That's not gonna work.
You're having a fever!
I am Ok. Mr. Albert
is more important than me.
I've already checked his situation.
Before his memories recovered,
I can't give you specific answers.
His head is injured.
His head?
Mr. Albert has already
lost his memories.
Now his head got a injury as well.
It's good.
For what?
He might recover his memories
because of this injury.
Do you think
he'll get his memories back?
How do I explain that?
There's not much equipment here
in my clinic.
I hope he won't get worse
than now.
Who sent him here?
Who did this?
Calm down, girl.
It was a passer-by.
You are so energetic.
I guess the cold can't get you down.
Have this medicine.
No!
Ok, then
we'll just wait for him to wake.
Just Take a rest.
Let's play games.
This... That...No!
The Nine Circles?
Is he really a doctor?
Put it inside here...
Open your eyes, Mr. Albert.
You're not staying here.
I'm gonna take you to the hospital.
Isn't that me?
Poopet is on my shoulder.
Train? Where is it going?
Poopet, Where are you going?
Poopet!
Alright.
What happened?
Mr. Albert...
Who's this girl?
This girl...
Candy.
Don't move.
Lie down slowly.
Slow down.
He's not like a lousy doctor.
Where am I?
Italy?
Here's Chicago. Mr. Albert.
Chicago?
Chicago? Right.
Candy, aren't you having a fever?
Don't worry.
I'll take a look at him.
Head problem is very important.
In the head, we have brains,
nerves for sight and smell,
pituitary, protein, amino acids,
fatty acids, and collagen.
Its structure is very complicated
and indispensable.
I can't judge him by his look!
How do you feel?
I believe your thoughts are in disorder.
It would take a while,
then you can get your memories back.
Is that true?
The lousy doctor would not lie.
Sorry... I was so rude.
I believe in Doctor.
-Call me Margin
-My name's Candy.
And actually I am a nurse.
You have patients
in such a short time.
Let him get some rest today
and come back tomorrow.
Thank you.
That's great. Mr. Albert.
Do you still remember
the first time we met?
There were so many animals
around us.
After I remember everything,
what would happen then?
I am so worried.
Who in the fact am I?
What did I do for a living?
If I recall my past...
Can I still be with Candy?
Are you feeling cold, Candy?
Here. dress it up.
But what about you?
You can't catch a cold right now.
Thank you. Mr. Albert.
That's warm.
Let's go home for dinner!
Good morning!
Good morning, Candy.
Are you going to work?
Goodbye!
Goodbye.
Take care!
It's really hard to forget
things about Terry.
I believe Candy would be alright.
We'll see her smile soon.
Terry!
Stellas troupe.
Romeo and Juliet.
New Actor Terry Glanchester
had a great success.
Terry, congratulations!
Thank you.
What's that attitude!
I can't forget it.
Madam, allow me to give you a hand,
please.
-That's so kind of you!
-My pleasure.
Stop!
I'm gonna read the stories.
Let's start.
Did Mr. Albert
go to Dr. Margin?
I wish he could remember all
as soon as possible.
But...
Will Mr. Albert
start traveling around again?
He'll bring Poopet and his backpack
then leave here.
After he recovers,
Mr. Albert will be definitely leaving.
I would be alone again.
Alone.
I am not afraid of lonely.
I have lots of stuff to do.
There's no time for me
to think too much.
Head nurse,
is there anything I can help?
Aren't you going to rest?
You 've been busy from morning.
No. I want to keep myself busy.
Please take care of the patient
in Room NO.25.
Ok.
I am on my way.
Dr. Reknapp, this way.
Thank you.
Is Candy Ok?
She said she 'd like to be busier.
What will I do in the lunch break?
I wanna get more work for that.
Trees in severe winter
are waiting for spring to come.
I am here for healing my pain.
But,
why can't I pull myself together?
No, I can't be brought down.
Who can't be brought down?
When were you guys coming?
You're too concentrated.
We called your name but no response.
I was daydreaming!
You look so happy.
Are there any good mews?
We got a leeter for you!
Is it from Stear?
It must be nice to stay in France.
He's got time for letters.
Did Stear write that?
Dear Pattie,
I am on the ship to France.
It's really tiring on the boat.
We have to clean up,
wash clothes, and also cook.
Life in the army, it's totally
different from what I thought.
Maybe It's the peace you want.
When you get the letter,
I will be one of the
France Air Force.
Stear, you...
This is the letter for you.
I'll read it!
Welcome back, Candy.
It must be very good that
Terry and you finally meet again.
Candy, this news...
What's wrong, Candy?
I can't hide it anymore.
I broke up with Terry.
Terry is gone.
Candy...
Don't say anything, please...
Don't mention him again.
So, you're doing that
because of Terry...
Candy, I've thought...
When you fainted on the train,
you must be so upset.
But I have no idea.
I didn't pay attention about you
because of Stear...
I believe...
It's enough that I had liked him.
Besides,
he's got Suzanna with him.
I should forget all the things
about him,
and stick on my dream
to be a good nurse.
Lunchtime is over, I got to go.
Pattie, don't forget to say hi for me
when you write back to Stear.
Goodbye!
Stear and Pattie.
Annie and Archie.
It is the fate
brought them toghther.
Don't you worry about me.
Candy.
Come to my room.
Yes.
I want to send you
to the moving hospital.
The moving hospital?
That's right. It's the hospital to
support developing the railways.
When the railway
develops to the inland,
the hospital would be
moving with the construction.
When will this project be over?
I'm not sure. I guess it'll
wait for the railway project finished.
I hope you can complete
this mission.
Is this fine with you?
About being the nurse with the army,
I hesitated.
But Blanny said yes
without a second word.
If I accepted it at that time.
I would not have broken up
with Terry.
This place is full of sad memories.
I'm going to leave them behind.
I'll go. Dr. Reknapp.
You accept that job.
Candy, don't worry about me.
Dr. Margin
would take good care of me.
He's a nice guy.
Candy, the problem is you.
Me?
You can't get over Terry.
That's why you hesitate.
If you're in this mood...
Then don't go.
Mr. Albert?
You can't take good care of
patients when you're absent-minded.
Can you? Candy.
Mr. Albert, I...
Candy understands
Mr. Albert's words.
For completing the mission
of nursing.
She made up her mind
dedicating herself to patients.
I'll go.
Candy makes that a promise
in her heart.