Safex
Anthony decided to take Candy
to his own home...
in order to save her from the
torment of the Leagan family.
However, Eliza managed to
ruin his efforts.
Springtime wind on
the big tree.
In that moment
Mr. Leagan, who was absent
for a lenghty period of time,
finally returned to his estate.
Welcome back.
Hello. Ruth
you're the same as always.
Yes.
What happened to Candy?
Why are you wearing that apron?
Darling, I want to talk about
that in private.
What? Candy has...?
She's violent, selfish and
totally unmanageable!
Unless we get rid of that girl,
she will bring shame to our family!
Right, Brother?
I can't put up with it anymore!
Call her to my study!
Yes!
She's finally gonna get some!
Pack my suitcases... Am I fired?
It's your day off!
Day off? But...
Everybody needs a day off
once in a while.
I thought you might want to
visit your Pony's home, Candy.
Then...!
I want you to get your
stamina back.
I will.
My dear Pony's hill.
The engine sounds good today!
It's been running for ten minutes
already and hasn't blown out yet.
Candy?
Candy!
Damn!
What? Candy has..?
That's right!
Why didn't you go after them,
brother?
You know that my car tends to
break down at important times!
Hey, Anthony! Candy has...!
I came to tell you good news.
Anthony
what happened to Candy?
Mr. Leagan returned today,
so Candy will be okay from now on.
Where was she going, Anthony?
On a refreshing journey.
Mr. Matthew!
Mr. Matthew, hello!
Candy!
You can drop me off here, Mr. Steyn!
I'll walk the rest.
Thank you very much.
Candy!
Why did you return?
Uh, well...
You think they kicked
me out, right?
Uh, no... Am I wrong?
It hasn't changed at all!
It's so beautiful.
I'm back. At the Pony's home.
And the Pony's hill.
I'm home!
I'm home!!
It's Candy's voice!
Candy?
And Kurrin too.
I'm back, everyone!
Candy!
John, Sam, Milly!
Candy! Sister Pony, it's Candy!
Don't tell me that Candy...
Don't worry, Candy just came
back for the holidays.
My! Candy!
Alright, I'll be on my way.
Uh, Mr. Matthew,
are there any letters?
You mustn't forget about
all those important letters!
Today I have no mail
for Pony's home.
Well then, excuse me.
Candy, I'm sure he came just
to see you off.
That's it.
Thank you, Mr. Matthew!
It's so nice,
being in Pony's home.
It feels like my home, after all.
Sister Pony, sister Lane,
I'm back.
Welcome back, Candy.
Let's play! Okay!
Everybody, let's climb a tree!
Don't do that, Candy!
"To be cut down."
This is...
They plan to relocate that tree.
That's impossible!
We were against it, but...
this land is
Mr. Cartwright's property.
Mr. Cartwright is rich and
he wants that tree.
If that tree disappears from
Pony's home...
My memories of that tree
come all the way to the beginning.
When I fell from it while
rescuing little birds...
When I watched my friend
Annie leave...
I was on that tree.
I will beg mr. Cartwright.
Mr. Cartwright is in a
foreign country right now.
I won't be able to wait for
him until he comes back!
And this matter is urgent.
Teacher!
Big trouble! The tree is...!
This is bad!
John, gather everybody!
Ok.
Candy!
Don't do anything violent!
You! What are you doing?
Climb it!
Hey! Don't climb up there!
Stop it!
You're gonna fall!
Stop that!
Hey, stop it!
Hey! Come down!
What are you doing? Come down!
Candy!
Don't do anything stupid!
It's them who are stupid!
Shut up! I'm gonna get you for this!
It's Mr. Flanneman!
Mr. Flanneman!
What's all this fuss about?
As you can see,
these kids are opposing us.
This is our tree!
We're not gonna give it to anyone!
-You won't take it!
-It's not yours!
This tree was bought by
Mr. Flanneman! Get down now!
You idiot!
What are you loitering about?
Move it!
Alright!
One, two, three...
Algight, I'm gonna get naughty!
Hey! This is my tree!
If you don't get down,
I'm gonna drag you down myself!
Everybody, come down!
Mr. Flanneman,
please don't do anything to children!
Candy, come down!
I won't give up so easily!
Alright then! I'm good at
climbing trees, too!
I got you now.
It's pointless!
If you come any closer,
I'm going to jump down!
Oh, you're a lively young lady.
Well, I'll have a smoke.
I'm Flanneman.
President of the
Washington-based company.
Though you're a president
of the company,
you have no right to take our tree!
Actually,
my hobby is tree-climbing.
Ever since I was a little boy,
I've had a keen eye for good trees.
I've gathered trees good for climbing
from all over the world in my garden.
I've been making all of my business
decisions while sitting atop a tree.
If you already have so many trees,
you don't have to take this one, too!
No, I was charmed by this tree.
It's shape is great,
it's good for climbing,
it's a best tree in America!
This tree is beautiful
because it's growing on this hill.
If you take it to your garden,
it will lose its charm!
Are you saying that it will
lose its character?
And besides, the tree will dry out
before you get it to your garden!
Don't worry. I hauled trees from
even further places.
Anyway, we are strongly
against this!
That's right!
We're against this!
Shut up!
Be quiet!
If you won't let me move this tree...
then I'll have to come from
Washington just to climb it.
Really, Mr. Flanneman?
And I guess I'll have to build
myself a villa, right there.
You'd tear down Pony's home...?
You can choose;
either we move this tree,
or we tear down that building.
Candy, let's give up on that tree.
Like mr. Flanneman said...
once a man wishes for something,
he will do anything
in his power to obtain it.
The tree is crying.
It doesn't want to go anywhere.
You, too, like Pony's home?
You want to stay here forever?
A dry leaf.
That's it! I have a good idea!
Candy!
Good morning, sister Lane!
What are you doing, Candy?
Making dry leaves!
Just a little bit more!
Do your best!
Okay!
What?
The tree is beginning to dry?
Yes. As you can see...
What? Move it!
Now you did it! You damaged its
roots while digging that trench!
If you take it like this,
it'll dry out soon!
Please wait, sister Pony!
We'll make God angry if
we keep quiet about this!
Even God
occasionally turns a blind eye!
Let's give up on this tree.
Mr. Flanneman!
Climbing dry trees isn't my hobby.
Stop working!
Mr. Flanneman, banzai!
Banzai!
I'm so sorry that
the tree began to dry.
Mr. Flanneman, there are
so many good trees elsewhere!
No. I'll never find a tree
like that again.
It's starting to rain, isn't it.
Candy!
Big trouble! If it rains...
What's the problem?
No, Mr. Flanneman,
if you don't head back soon,
you'll get wet!
I came with a car.
But I don't have an umbrella!
I'll stay here until the rain stops.
Mr. Flanneman!
What's the matter?
The tree...!
What?
Wait, Mr. Flanneman!
-Please wait!
-Don't touch me!
This is paint!
I was tricked!
Deceived by such a child!
Get to work!
-Begin!
-Yes!
Mr. Flanneman...
Candy! Do you think
I'd let myself be fooled by you?
Please stop! I'll apologize for
trying to deceive you...
-but please...
-I refuse!
No point in trying to stop me now!
No! You won't take my dad!
Patty! You're just...
Patty!
You were there all along?
I won't let you take my dad!
Dad? This tree?
That's right.
Mr. Flanneman
This tree is our venerable father.
There are two gentle mothers
in Pony's home
-Candy...
-But there is no father.
When we see
those two strong branches
We imagine that
they are our father's arms.
So.. this tree is here
instead of our real fathers.
That's right!
That's enough!
I give up. Candy,
I'll stop the works.
Mr. Flanneman!
Thank you!
Thank you, Mr. Flanneman!
If I took the father
away from so many kids,
God would have damned me
for sure!
Thank you very much,
Mr. Flanneman.
I'll come from time to time
in order to climb this tree!
We'll be waiting for you.
Thank you.
Candy, let's race to the top of the
tree again some time!
I won't lose!
I won't lose too!
Farewell, Mr. Flanneman!
Farewell!
Refreshing wind
blew over Pony's hill...
as if it were bringing springtime
from some faraway place.