Safex
A midnight picnic.
With the ending of an
exciting May festival.
Blue skies reigned over the London.
marking the beginning of the summer.
Students have also changed into
their lighter clothes...
following the arrival of summertime.
Students are very exciting
looking forward the summer vacations.
Summer vacation? That's so nice...
Say, Candy... I discussed with Patty
about this...
how about we all go to Scotland
for a summer vacation?
Scotland?
Yes. To a summer school in Scotland.
Summer school? Sounds fun.
Let's go together!
Scotland? Doesn't sound too bad.
Candice White Adley?
Candice! What kind of pose is that?
Yes!
A lady doesn't behave so immodestly
in front of other people!
Eating and lying on the ground!
I'm sorry.
This school takes pride in educated
finest young gentlemen and ladies!
And yet, what were you doing just now?
-But...
-You understand?
Make sure that this doesn't repeat.
They'll never make a lady out of her.
Oh well, I did it again!
I suck at this!
I think I'll give up on this.
Going to summer school?
It's a school,
so sisters will be going with us?
I want the freedom to do whatever I want
during the summer vacation!
That's it! If I go back to America...
Pony's home.
And after that... Anthony's grave.
I'm going back to America
during the summer vacation!
Candy!
What's going on?
Terry is fighting?
Candy, Annie!
Archie is fighting...!
-Then, Terry is fighting...
-with Archie!
Say that again!
Don't freak out over me
badmouthing America!
America is my homeland!
I won't forgive those
who badmouth my country!
It's a homeland to you, but
it's a worthless country to me!
To me, it's a worst country!
Say that again!
Stop that, Terry, Archie!
Take this, Terry!
Stop that, Archie!
Please!
Can't help this.
They would've done it sooner or later.
Stop that, the pair of you!
The troublemakers are here.
Let's part our ways for now.
Wait up, Terrius.
Why, we were just joking around.
That's not what I saw.
Who pulled the first punch?
Well, Archie was the first.
Is that true, Archibald Cornwell?
Yes.
Archibald Cornwell...
you will be confined to a
contemplation room in the northern wing.
Archie!
You'd lock up Archie
without hearing his explanation?
Be quiet.
Whatever the reason, we won't tolerate
such violence in a school for gentlemen!
Don't knock!
I'm sorry!
Strange... I'm sure I heard a knock...
Annie, what's that basket for?
Uh... there are sweets
books and food inside...
Annie, don't say that you want to
go to a picnic with me?
But...
But there is only about 500 meters
from here to the contemplation room
-And you even brought sweets?
-But... this is...
Let's get rid of that basket.
No!
If someone sees you carrying this
you'll get in trouble!
I wanted to take this to Archie...
Give it to him?
Gosh, I'm so dense...
Alright. Let's take the basket to him.
It's your turn now, Annie!
I'm afraid, Candy!
Listen, close your eyes and
think of Archie's face.
Now, you'd better close your eyes.
Hold on to this rope!
Don't open your eyes!
Do your best.
Strange...
Kurin, are we alone?
Annie, let me carry the basket for you.
I'm fine! It's not so heavy when I think
of Archie in the contemplation room!
If you really want that.
-Let's hurry.
-Wait!
Kurin, take a look around the
northern wing.
-Annie, let's rest a bit.
-But...
If they find us here
nobody will know our real plan.
Therefore, relax.
Stars are beautiful.
A midnight picnic...
I remember, Candy!
Come to think of it, remember the time
when the two of us went to a picnic?
We stole sister Pony's wine...
took the food...
it was so much fun!
That's right, I remember.
-Here you go!
-Can we eat this?
-It's for Archie...
-There is enough for everybody!
-What's this?
-It's a blanket.
Archie might be cold at night...
What's this pattern?
It's called tartan check.
They've been making it
in Scotland since old times.
Tartan check?
Come to think of it...
The Prince on the hill...
Anthony, Stear and Archie...
they all wore kilts with this pattern.
Are you sure that this Summer school
is really in Scotland?
Scotland is a country of tartan check
and bagpipes.
Annie, I'll go to Summer school.
Really, Candy?
I want to see Scotland with my own eyes.
The place where Prince on the hill
and Anthony lived...
Scotland.
Kurin!
Archie is in the contemplation room?
Candice, open up!
Open up, Candice! Are you in there?
If you don't open, I'll enter myself.
Candice?
I suspected something was up.
He's up there?
-Now...
-Candy, I'm afraid!
It's okay! You won't fall
if you come down slowly.
But I...
Just a little bit more!
Do your best, Annie!
Now, come down.
Thanks, Candy.
Now, let's go.
Candy!
Annie, we're almost there.
Hurry up!
Archie, are you there?
Candy!
Archie!
Annie is with you?
What are you doing here,
in the dead of the night?
Don't be so rude...
two girls risked their lives for you!
Right, Annie?
Archie... I was so worried...
Silly, I'm doing just fine in here!
We thought you'd feel down, right?
-I'm so glad...
-Candy
they locked me up in here, but
I don't think that I did anything wrong.
I'm gonna get that Terry next time!
Settle the score?
I'm gonna challenge him to a duel!
Duel?
Stop those horrible things!
What's the matter, Kurin?
Oh no, somebody is coming this way.
Annie, hurry and give the box to Archie.
Archie, catch this!
We brought this for you.
Thanks!
-Archie...!
-Annie!
Poor Archie.
I'll come to you again!
Annie, if we don't hurry...
Farewell, Archie!
Annie.
Listen up, Kurin!
Show Annie the other way out of here.
Candy, what about you?
I'll do something to buy you time.
Now, go!
Candy.
Kurin, take care of Annie!
Candice!
Good evening.
Candice White Adley
Where were you going this late at night?
Uh, when I can't fall asleep
I go for a night stroll...
Are you making fun of Director?
You went to the contemplation rooms
right?
Yes, something like that...
Sister Chrisse
escort Candice back to her room.
I'm going to check the
contemplation rooms.
Yes.
Uh, just a second...
Tommorrow we'll decide upon
Candice's punishment.
Annie... did you manage to escape?
It's impossible.
Climbing this by myself...
Patty!
Hurry!
Thank you, Patty!
Is Candy with you?
Candice White Adley!
Your right for summer vacation
is revoked.
As a disciplinary action
you will remain alone in the ward.
But...!
You're supposed to be a lady!
How could you sneaking into the boy's
contemplation room?
But... Archie is my relative.
That's not an excuse!
They canceled your summer vacation.
I'll go over to the Director!
She doesn't have an ear for reason.
No, not that!
I'll ask her to cancel my
summer vacation as well.
Annie!
You always kept pulling me
out of troubles.
But from now on, I want to start taking
responsibility for my own actions.
Annie, Eliza and the others
are eavesdropping.
There's still about a week
before summer vacation!
It'll work out somehow!
It's easy to say that, I don't think
that the director would change her mind.
Whatever I say, it'll do no good.
What should I do now?
Terry!
So rude, just appearing like that
above my head!
You too
I don't want anyone to bother me
when I want to be alone.
This time, you came to regret
your stubbornness.
You already know?
That you won't be going on a
summer vacation.
Just when I started to think
you're kind...
If you kindly ask me on your knees
something good might come out of it.
Who are you to say that?
After all, it's your fault that
Archie lock in the contemplation room!
That's why I said
I'd do something about it.
I'd rather die than
beg you on my knees!
That's Freckled Tarzan.
It's the dining hall lady.
What's the matter?
Miss, it's nothing.
It's a letter from my son.
He turned eight this year.
He lives in Scotland.
Why did you tear his letter then?
He thought I'd be coming home
during the summer vacation.
But my holidays have been canceled.
It's my only holiday
throughout the year.
He'll be impatiently waiting for me...
My sweet son, with chestnut-colored hair
and wide eyes.
He and his grandfather will be
waiting for my return.
Why were your holidays canceled?
One student will remain in school
so I have to take care after him.
That's me! Because of me...
Lady!
It's alright. It's our job, after all.
I've even troubled the old lady
with my actions.
Stear!
Candy.
Have you seen Terry?
What? There's no way that he'd show up
for the morning prayer.
Please, when you see him, tell him
that I'll beg him on my knees.
You're going to beg him?
What are you doing, Candice?
Please do that, Stear!
What was that?
Brother, maybe your hearing is going?
But Candy really said that!
You think that Candy would've begged
that guy on her knees?
That can't be! You must be mistaken!
That's right. It is a mistake.
I never said that.
Terry!
That Freckled Tarzan was mistaken
if she thought that.
But.. that's what she said!
And to relay the message to you!
What?
To relay the mesage to me?
Enter!
You called, Director?
I voided the revocation of
your summer vacation.
Really? But why so suddenly?
I did it on my own discretion.
Then, I don't have to stay in the ward?
Yes. However...
you are obliged to enroll
in the Summer school in Scotland.
-Yes. I understand!
-You may go.
Director... I'm very sorry for
causing this much trouble.
I realized that...
I need to think of people
whom I hurt for my own benefit!
Who are you talking about?
I'll be careful from now on!
Lady!
Miss. I'll be going back to Scotland
after all!
I got a job in the mansion of
Duke Grandchester in Scotland.
Duke Grandchester?
That's Terry's father!
I'll see my son for the first time
in over a year...
I need to let him know that...
It was Terry!
Terry came to help us!
Candy.
I'm jealous of you and Archie.
You beg me on your knees
for the sake of an old dining lady.
When I badmouthed Archie's homeland
he burst out in passionate honesty.
Terry. Thank you.
You really are kind.
Aren't you feeling lonely by yourself?
Terry, let's go together.
To Scotland, a country of
tartan check and bagpipes.
Inside her heart, Candy cried out
her thoughts to Terry.
However, she couldn't turn
those thoughts into words.