Safex
Somebody has used the name 'Terry'
and stayed in the hospital
where Candy was working.
It turned out to be bad boy Charlie.
Moreover,
Charlie is escape from the prison.
The police is looking for him all over.
The flowers in heart
Candy, you lied to me!
Quiet!
Charlie, I didn't do it.
I didn't call the police.
You don't have to explain.
I was so stupid to trust you.
Charlie.
What has Candy done?
She was covering for Charlie.
Candy already knew
his true identity
She just can't keep herself away
from troubles, can she!
Doctor Popson.
Where are you taking the patient?
To the hospital in youth hospital.
You will need my permission
if you want to move the patient.
But, this young man is a criminal...
If we stop his current treatment...
it will leave him a scar on his face.
The principal has given his permission.
This has nothing to do
with permission.
This is to do with 'look'.
Unless...
You are bringing him to a
better doctor than me.
But Doctor Popson
Isn't he going to influence
the others...
if you leave him
with normal patients?
Doctor Popson,
I will take care of Charlie.
Right, I will convince the principal.
Yes!
Great! Charlie.
Sorry to get you involved in this.
It is ok, you can blame me.
But you need to thank Doctor Popson.
Stop acting cool.
It makes me a gangster
by having a scar on my face.
Charlie, you...
Although I am a bad guy...
I will never hate anyone.
Me too.
I will never frame anyone.
So who called the police?
The police was after me,
only you knew about it.
Oh yeah, thinking backwards...
Elisa!
She didn't keep her words, Elisa.
Elisa, are you look for me?
I thought you are fired,
why are you still here?
Why should I get fired?
You were sheltering a criminal,
there are evidences.
Elisa, you called the police.
This is an obligation
for a good citizen.
But we had a deal.
Sometimes I lie.
You know, you are sick.
You seem to know me very well.
Bye, I am still working here.
Candy!
Why do I come to hospital today?
The invoice from the hospital?
Yeah, the fee that
young gangster owed.
You want me to pay for that?
Yeah.
I thought he was Terry.
Although The Adley's is rich...
they are stupid enough
to pay for that young gangster.
But the bill...
If you don't pay for it...
I will go straight to Pony's home.
Pony's home?
Isn't principal your family?
Wait! I will pay
Please give me some time.
Right, bye.
Don't forget!
How am I going to pay for
that amount of money?
Candy!
Qucik, that patient...
Charlie?
What are you doing?
Stop! No violence!
Carlie! What are you doing?
You messed up all this, Candy.
You and that lousy doctor,
stop helping me.
Helping someone like me is going to
get yourself into troubles.
Doctor Popson!
Candy, get ready for treatment.
Yes.
None of your business! move!
Increase the dose.
We should get rid of people like this...
as soon as possible to
stay away from trouble
I don't need you to reprimand me.
That hurts, be careful!
How do I raise so much money?
I can't get any other job.
Charlie again?
He just slept.
What was that sound...
Why?
Nothing, nurse, I need a glass...
I come to help.
I am sorry.
I am better now,
trying to for some other jobs to do.
Did auntie make all these flowers?
Yeah.
They are good for shop decoration
and stage play.
Stage play?
Mr. Terry I am a reporter.
I am not good enough for interview.
Wait!
Someone pretended to be you
because you are famous.
Pretend to be me?
Yeah, you didn't know?
That man was hurt
and was sent to Chicago's hospital
Chicago's hospital.
It might be the one
Candy is working in?
Why?
Excuse me... I am sorry.
Can you please tell in more details?
I should be the one
asking you for details.
What is going on?
Shoot! I had to rush for the
morning news.
Please, tell me what is going on.
This flower...
Might appear on Terry's stage.
Failed again.
Auntie has got a different one
You are up, Charlie.
Can nurse in this hospital
have part time jobs?
It is so boring to face you
everyday like this.
Why do you need money?
Money? No.
Do I have something to do with it?
Is there any nurse
who pay for their patients??
Don't do it in front of me.
Candy.
Who knows you wouldn't go wild if
no one is watching you?
I told you not to do it.
You promise me you would
stay on the bed?
Right.
Can I trust you on this?
I said I won't betray anyone.
I will do it in my room.
Good.night.
Quiet, this is hospital.
Uncle, are you from this hospital?
Yes.
I am looking for a nurse
her name is Candy.
My sister told me if
I need any money...
I can look for Candy.
Elisa?
You owed her a lot of money.
Give me some more time.
I will go for a walk now.
To Pony's home.
Wait! Neil.
No more delay.
Give me another month.
Do you know how many days
are there in a month?
One week.
I don't have time.
I need soome money, Grand Aunt Elroy
doesn't know about it
Come back in two days time.
Two days?
Two days.
Neil.
I will be waiting.
Charlie,
time to take your temperature.
You haven't had
your temperatuer taken.
Who is that guy?
The one who drove here
to look for you.
Neil, Elisa's brother
I am getting it.
Charlie.
That Neil asked you for money.
It has nothing to do with money.
If Neil and Elisa are family...
Candy, those money...
It is not for hospital!
You just said it yourself.
What she thinks she is doing?
She just put me in special ward.
Charlie, no!
Damn!
No matter how good I am...
I still can't make that much money.
Charlie, where are you going?
Move! don't disturb me.
Charlie.
Where are you going with the knife?
Get lost! Candy.
My god, are you going for Elisa?
I will teach them both a lesson.
Charlie, if you do this...
I have recovered but still have to
go back to the prison.
You promise me
you would stay there for good?
I can't forgive those two people.
Don't do it,
your sin will grow deeper.
Move! Candy.
Charlie you fool!
Candy!
Go ahead, I won't stop you.
I said
I never hated anyone before.
Actually, I have hated someone.
My mother.
My mother worked very hard
just to raise me.
At day time she will work in the factory
and she will work part ime at night.
Then, I became a gangster.
I had a fight with my mother
and I left the house.
That is why you won't let me
do any handwork.
You will remind me of my mother.
What about your mother now?
Still working.
Yeah?
She must be doing better than me.
How about your mother?
When I was little
my family discarded me.
Really?
But I am not lonely.
I have many people caring for me
So I am not lonely.
I slowly understand.
What?
Why Terry likes you.
Just this bit of money.
Neil will come today to get the money.
Candy, you got an express
Me?
Looks like it is from a gentleman.
Thank you, Blanny.
It is from Terry.
Candy
I am on a show tour here in
Mississippi coast's St. Louis town.
Reporters have told me
about Charlie.
Charlie is my important friend.
He helped me a lot when I was young.
No matter what he has done,
I still trust he is a good lad.
It is destiny that brought you two
to mee each other.
Please look after him for me
with the cheque attached.
Don't tell Charlie about this
He will not accept this.
So much money.
I miss you so much.
The show is busy here, I barely
have time to stop by to see you.
I am really sorry that
I can't meet you on this
Terry.
If there is any money left,
buy some strawberries drinks
for Charlie.
He likes only strawberry drink.
Strawberry drink?
The invoice is settled.
Charlie must be happy
to see strawberry drink.
Charlie, I got a present for you.
Charlie...
Natalie, you seen Charlie?
He has been moved to the hospita
in youth prison already.
I permitted it.
He has recovered.
Doctor Popson...
Patients checking in or out,
will be my call,
I don't have to inform any nurse.
Yes.
Thank you for your care.
Candy!
Regardless of types of patients,
as long as they come to the hospital
They have the right
to receive good treatments.
Charlie must be happy.
He will be happy after
he got out from the prison I guess.
Quick! Candy.
The next patient is here.
Charlie made this.
Although Charlie didn't tell me...
Surely he did help his mother
with the handwork.
He thanked me and Doctor Popson.
That is why
he left these two flowers.
Charlie!
Nice job
This is from Charlie's heart.
I have healed his wounded face,
You have comforted his painful heart.
Docotor,
do you like strawberry drink?
My favourite when I was young.
No!
This is how we drink it.
Right, cheers!
Warm wind breezes into the room
in the summer evening.
Candy and Doctor Popson
enjoying the strawberry drinks.
The cold and freezy drinks,
sparkling like
Charlie's revitalised heart.
Entering the mouth fresh and cool.