Safex
Annie keeps sending letters to Archie
every week.
Candy was surprised
when she found out that.
When Annie left, with whom
she lived since her earliest days
Candy felt very lonely.
A wonderful Sunday.
I see, yes, I think that as well!
Patty, what's going on?
everybody seems so happy.
Fifth Sunday is drawing near.
You mean, Fifth Sunday?
It's a time when students are allowed
to leave the school premises.
-So they'll let us outside?
-Yes.
Wow, I'll stretch my wings!
I didn't mean that literally...
Have I said something wrong?
Fifth Sunday?
So they're doing this
only a few times a year.
As expected from St. Paul academy
they're so shrewd.
Kurin!
Good news, Kurin!
I'll be allowed to go out
for a whole day on the next Sunday!
I guess I'll go sightseeing with
Stear and Archie.
Tower bridge...
St. Paul's cathedral...
That's right!
We might ride a boat on Thames!
Thus, the eagerly awaited
Fifth Sunday finally arrived.
-Mother!
-Father!
The air outside feels so good!
Mr. Alistear! Mr. Archibald!
Brother, it's that carriage!
So nice from them
to send a carriage for us.
This way!
I'm sorry
but could you wait a little?
We're waiting for Candy.
Everyone is already waiting for you.
That's our Candy, she's a fast one!
Please.
-Neil?
-Eliza!
You look surprised.
Grand aunt Elroy
is waiting in the hotel.
Where is Candy?
-Hurry! Go!
-As you wish.
Hey, but Candy isn't ...
Took me some time to dress up!
Teacher, I'm off!
Where are you going, Candice?
"where am I going" ...
you must be kidding me!
Even though I'm a freshman,
I know about a Fifth Sunday...
Candice, regulations don't allow us
to let you leave.
Regulations...?
Even though
today is the Fifth Sunday...
unless your parents or relatives
give us permission to let you go...
we can't let you leave the premises.
But...
Now, return to your room.
Prepare for tomorrow's lecture.
Teacher...!
I thought this was going all too well...
Kurin, no good.
The yard...
That's right! In that case,
I'll go to the other Pony's hill!
I'll feel better over there.
Wait up, Kurin!
If this were the real Pony's hill...
and if I were together with Annie...
just how happy would we be?
What's the matter, Kurin?
Fire! Hurry, water...!
You are...
What's up with all the panic?
Terrius... you...
you're smoking here...
You look envious, Miss Stutter.
If you want some, I'll let you have one.
You must be kidding me!
Don't make that face!
Your freckles really stand out that way!
You know, when your nose moves
your freckles move as well.
I don't want you to speak that way
about my freckles!
Why do you break the rules, anyway?
Oh, since you don't like being called
after your freckles...
maybe you're a Tarzan-girl.
What's a Tarzan-girl?
In the darkness
throwing a white rope...
and swiftly, escaping like an animal...
And, holding onto the end of the rope...
dashing from girls' ward
over to boys' ward!
He was watching me.
When I was going to Archie's room...
Hmmmh,
Lady Freckles or Tarzan-girl...
Both of them fit you well.
How about freckled Tarzan?
What's that?
It's your name.
My name is Candice White Adley!
Don't forget that name!
Alright? It's Candice White Adley!
Okay.
Heard you the first time.
Freckled Tarzan.
Hey, your freckles stand out
when you're angry.
By the way, why are you here?
It's Fifth Sunday.
And why are you here?
When everybody leaves,
the school becomes so peaceful.
You weirdo.
That's right, this place is the other
Pony's hill, my special place!
Don't just barge in and smoke in here!
Other Pony's hill?
You look well, everyone.
Welcome to London, grand Aunt.
Did you have a pleasant journey?
It was pleasant.
I brought you these presents
from America.
-Neil, Eliza.
-Thank you!
I'm glad, Grand Aunt.
These are for Stear and Archie.
Why are you two looking at me like that?
Aunt Elroy
Just why did you separate Candy
from the rest of us?
Candy is also a member
of the Adley family.
Only by name.
Eliza, you keep quiet.
We are speaking with Aunt!
I decide
whether I will invite Candy or not.
Therefore, why didn't you invite her?
Archie, I didn't come to England
just to have something ruin my mood.
Come in!
A guest.
Let her enter.
Maybe it's Candy.
Please.
Annie?
My, Annie Brighton.
It's been a long time.
Now, join us.
Excuse the intrusion.
I and that Terrius are the only two
left in this big school.
I guess everybody is having
so much fun right now.
Maybe there are more students
who stayed in the school?
Maybe...
Nobody is in here!
Candice, open up!
Teacher!
Hurry up, Candice!
You are free to go out
hurry and prepare yourself.
A carriage is here to pick you up.
To pick me up?
It means that I can go?
Now, hurry. It's impolite
to keep someone waiting.
Yes! I'll go right now!
But... I wonder
just who came to pick me up.
-From America...
-Stop!
Teacher, let me look forward to this
until I leave the premises!
Candice!
You'd spoil the surprise
if you told me now!
I wonder who came from America
to pick me up...
Sister Pony, sister Lane
Tom... or maybe...
-Candice, hurry up!
-Okay!
I'm really going this time, Kurin.
What's the matter?
Hello, Candy!
Mr. Brighton!
Mr. Brighton is a man who
took Annie from Pony's home...
becoming her father.
Now, come on.
Annie... Annie is here as well?
Well then, take care.
Annie!
Annie is in the hotel.
She is waiting for me in the hotel?
Meeting Annie in London...
It's a dream come true!
Candy...
That's the London Bridge.
Annie and I used to sing about it
ever since we were little.
"London bridge is falling down
falling down..."
That is the Tower Bridge, right?
It's rising!
Take a good look!
I bet you've never seen
a bridge like that one, Kurin!
Candy, where do you want to go?
Of course, to the hotel where Annie is!
The Adleys are in the hotel, too.
Then, grand aunt Elroy...
So that's the reason I wasn't invited.
It's fine with me...
My wife doesn't want anyone know that
you and Annie were raised in Pony's home.
I'll give up on seeing Annie then.
Thank you. To make up for this
today I'll take you anywhere you like.
I want to visit some
wide and open place!
Such a place?
I want to scream out loud!
Very well.
-To Epsom!
-Yes!
Horse racing...
This is a wide, open place
where you can yell all you'd like...
Moreover, there is a racing horse
which came all the way from America.
A horse from America?
Yes... it'll compete in the next race
its name is " Pony flash" ...
Pony flash?
"from Steve's farm in America..."
It's Tom's horse!
You know him?
Yes, he was in Pony's home with me.
Oh, that's nice.
Mr. Brighton, so where is that horse?
That must be it, mr. Brighton!
Tom must have worked hard
about this horse...
Go, Pony flash!
Terrius?
You've mixed up some names.
This horse is called " Royal king"
and it's going to win the next race.
Mr. Brighton...
Pony flash is over there.
So that's Pony flash...
It looks exactly like you.
It's got freckles all over!
What? Does that matter, as long as
it's faster than the others?
Alright. Wanna bet?
Bet?
If that clumsy horse
takes a third or better place...
I won't call you by your freckles
anymore.
I'll call you Candice White Adley.
Well then?
Really?
However, if that horse takes a
fourth place or worse...
you'll become my slave.
A slave?
That's right.
If I want to smoke
you'll light my cigarette.
If I get thirsty
you'll make me some tea.
Who'd do that...!
That's right...
I wonder if that horse
can finish the race at all.
I'll bet you!
That's the spirit! Well then!
You didn't introduce him to me
Candy?
He isn't a person worthy
of an introduction!
They've started.
Pony flash!
It seems that Pony flash
has trouble keeping up.
Go, Pony flash!
Poor thing.
Pony! Tom in America
is rooting for you!
Ow! Pony flash!
It's catching up! Go, pony!
But it's still last...
Pony! Tom's friend is rooting for you!
Pony!
Go, Pony! Go!!
No good.
I lose.
Can I start by polishing your shoes?
Looking from my seat
your horse came in third.
But...
Well, time to part our ways.
Terry...
That's too bad.
Another five meters and our horse
would've finished third.
Thank you, Mr. Brighton!
I haven't screamed my lungs out
for such a long time!
Me, too!
When I scream my lungs out...
all those unpleasant and sad things
I kept inside seem to fly away from me!
Candy.
And it's all thanks to you
Mr. Brighton!
So pretty!
St. Paul's cathedral is all in red!
Candy, your face also looks red.
Mr. Brighton, you too...
and Kurin, as well!
Candy, from time to time,
I start thinking ...
how would have changed
if we adopted you instead of Annie.
Mr. Brighton?
No... Annie is a good girl.
So calm, pure...
That's right! Unlike me
she is so much more...
The reason I met up with you
today...
is because I want you to
take care of Annie.
Annie?
Annie is going to transfer
to your school.
To St. Paul academy?
Thus, my wife and Annie went to
Adleys' place to greet them.
However, I came to see you.
Me?
The one who cares and worries
the most about Annie...
the one I can rely on, is you, Candy.
But if someone finds out about
Annie and I, Annie will...
That's the problem.
It's a selfish favor to ask
I'd like you to take care of Annie,
because that's something you always did.
You don't want that, Candy?
No, it's just...
I'm a little jealous of Annie.
How come?
It's because she has such a kind father.
Mr. Brighton, I'll do all I can.
Thank you, Candy.
Kurin, Annie is coming to
St. Paul academy.
Though not immediately
I'm sure that one day...
we'll be good friends just like
we were back in Pony's home.
Seeing Mr. Brighton's strong posture...
Candy remembered the big tree back
at Pony's home...
the tree that ever so gently
watched over Annie...
making Candy feel very envious.