Safex
Nil pretends to be Seli
and lied to Candy to the valle.
But Candy ran away.
Then, the real Seli saw Candy went her own way,
he went back to the theater.
The man left
Candy, I didn't tell you, I have my memory again.
I have my memory
I can't make any trouble for you again.
Thank you very much.
Do you want to say good bye to Candy, go.
Gubei, it's early, let me sleep.
Good bye, Candy.
An clear morning, good morning, little bird.
Come on, today.
Mr. Albert is up.
Even prepared the breakfýrst.
It's the letter.
Mr. Albert, Mr. Albert.
Mr. Albert.
He went here early in the morning
I didn't have enough sleep.
Where did he go?
What, travel?
Yes, thanks for you caring.
But, Albert.
Doctor, please take care of Candy.
Albert.
It seems the car's waiting for him.
Car?
I only saw two men,
that's the neighbor said,
he talked with unknown man in the back street.
Maybe he.
Kidnapped by the basters?
Impossible.
I will go to look for him.
Mr. Albert, where is he?
I don't think it's trouble to look after him.
He's he, he doesn't have to leave.
He said this to me before.
Candy, it's good to shar things.
I want to do this, to share the
happiness and sadness with you.
Mr. Albert.
Ok, Candy.
Why do you forget the engage?
Mr. Albert, you can go to me
if you have any trouble?
It's only me now.
Mother, do you know Candy work in the clinic?
What, I forbid any one to accept her.
But she has job now.
Did Nil know it?
Of course.
That's too bad.
Mother, drive her away
Or who knows what will brother do.
He's attracted by Candy.
Do you have any other way?
Cheat the prince to drive her out the city.
If the prince found it...
But he's bad ill, he will not fýnd it.
Mother, Lord Oraba hates Candy too
he will help us.
No, you can't do this.
Brother.
Do you hear what we talk?
I heard it. Mother, I am serious.
Nil.
Brothe, do you knw what are you talking about?
I really love Candy.
Brother, I feel hasted
why hear you call her name.
No matter what, I will marry her.
Mother.
We didn't fýnd Mr. Albert.
Boni's Home, it's very alike.
Patty.
He's shaking. Pray for Stia. I know you.
Mr. Albert is not here, I am worried too.
And he went to the war.
Candy.
Patty.
Candy, I am nervous
It's just the same everywhere.
Don't worry, what happened.
Stia sent a strange letter, I can't sit quietly.
May I see it?
Patty, I want to talk about my good friend Domi.
Come back.
It's Domi's plane.
Domi, Domi.
Domi.
Domi, cheer up.
No, everyone's dead, Stia.
I, lover...
Don't make your lover sad.
Domi, Domi, Domi.
Is that the fact, is that the war?
Human's life...
Laugh in the morning,
why is like this, Domi?
Will the next be Stia?
Patty, don't worry. He will not die.
Stia,don't make Patty sad.
Yes, give you a good thing.
Happy box, it's made by Stia.
Stia.
Yes, he made it.
He said thoe who hear the
tone will gain happiness.
It's really good.
Patty can gain happiness.
Thank you, Candy.
Stia.
There's command to attack.
It comes at last.
The sky is just like always.
The only difference is that
there will be war soon.
Though it's nervous, but the heart is calm.
Why?
It will be well.
Domi, Domi, I will attack now.
The sky you protect so much
let me help you to protect it.
Stia, don't die, protect your girl friend.
Patty, Patty.
What's wrong, Patty, why don't you look at me?
It's the enemy's plane.
Patty, how long will you hear?
But...
If hearing too much about it
you will be too happier.
Candy is right.
Idiot, you shoot beveled.
Ah, Domi.
No, I can't shoot.
Domi, I am sorry, I can't realize our engage.
Patty, Candy.
Good bye, Patty, Candy.
Ah, music...
Patty.
The God is gazing us in the heaven.
He's guiding us, and the sold is going to sleep.
Amen.
Stia.
The gentle Stia.
The tyre fell again.
Candy, jump.
I felt it.
I didn't expect this is
the last time to see Stia.
This is the special music box.
What?
Candy, open it and hear it
you will have hapiness.
Thank you, Stia.
Take care, Candy.
Patty.
I will ask someone to fýx it, the music is good.
See you, Candy, Ani, and Aqi.
The warmest place in Florida
it can dry your tear.
Thank you, Candy.
Though we depart, we are still friends.
Yes, Ani.
Patty, be happy.
It's ok with it.
Patty will get on the car.
Granny, please take care of Patty.
Yes, Pattty's parents go there too.
Good bye, Candy.
Godd bye, Patty.
Godd bye, Aqi, Ani.
Candy prayed the Stia's music box sounding again,
and those who hear it will be happy.