Safex
Tiny suffers from hemophilia
depressed all day.
With Candy' s help,
she' s getting optimistic gradually.
The sound of walking
which strengthen one' s mind.
What are they doing?
Please!
-Be careful.
-Yes, I' ll be fine.
Sister Pony, sister Lane.
Candy!
Where did Jimmy go
in the early morning?
Mr. Cartwright's pasture.
Jimmy works in the pasture,
don't you know that?
Jimmy works
for the children of Pony' s home.
For the children?
Yes. Exchange the milk
of the pasture with the work.
It' s Jimmy's idea.
The milk we drink every morning ...
Yes, It' s Jimmy's contributions.
I don't know that.
Sister Pony, sister Lane,
can I go with him?
Mr. Cartwright must be very happy.
Look! Sister Pony.
Jimmy!
Well.
Okay!
Jimmy.
Boss. Candy boss.
Wait for me! Jimmy!
I' ll go with you.
Candy boss became a snowman.
Bad-mannered.
You want to go too? Kurin.
I've no idea that...
you go to work
to exchange the milk every day.
While everybody is sleeping.
Since you' re not at home,
I am the boss here.
I should take care of everybody.
Jimmy has grown up.
Pull over!
Why?
I' d like to take a look.
I remember that...
We went to Mr. Cartwright's pasture
on Christmas Eve,
After that,
you went to London in spring.
Time passed swiftly.
You got heavy from England.
What do you mean? Jimmy.
Nothing!
I didn't said that you' re fat.
You...
Need some help? Boss.
Don't be silly, I don't need help.
Help! Jimmy.
You are doing well.
Of course, I practice seriously
while you' re leaving.
What have you learnt in London?
Don't let the tree catch a cold,
Mr. Cartwright.
Candy!
Long time no see, Mr. Cartwright.
I miss you so much, Candy.
What's the matter? Mr. Cartwright.
I needed to be looked after
more than the tree.
Mr. Cartwright, I am sorry.
Leaving for London without telling you.
No, you are home now!
Mr. Cartwright.
Elder person is apt to shed the tears,
in the house.
I have something to tell you.
Mr. Cartwright.
What do you want to say?
Take a look.
Hold! Just a moment!
Watch this!
It' s cool! Jimmy.
It' s perfect!
Something about Jimmy?
Jimmy' s wearing my used gun belt.
I gave him on purpose.
I hope that
he would inherits this pasture someday.
Does Jimmy know this?
-No!
-Why?
I'm afraid to be refused,
just like you did before.
Mr. Cartwright.
Mr. Cartwright,
I' m sure that Jimmy will take it.
I hope so!
Jimmy' s going to be
Mr. Cartwright's inheritor!
What a good news.
That's great! Jimmy.
Candy, will you tell Jimmy for me?
It' s my pleasure.
Thanks!
It' s a present for Candy' s return.
Thank you! Mr. Cartwright.
Give my regards to
Sister Pony, sister Lane.
-Okay!
-Good bye!
- Be careful!
-Yes!
-Jimmy...
-What's the matter? Boss.
What do you think of Mr. Cartwright?
He is a good man.
Have you ever thought of that
you might be his inheritor?
-I've never thought of that.
-Is that so?
But, I will not accept that.
Why? Jimmy.
Candy boss has come back now,
I will stay with you.
Jimmy!
Everybody, milk' s coming.
Welcome back! Jimmy, Candy.
Boss, they looked so happy,
that' s enough.
Jimmy has grown up for sure!
He' ll be happy
if he can stay with Mr. Cartwright.
Sister Pony and sister Lane
will agree with that for sure.
Is Mr. Cartwright ask for that?
How nice! Sister Pony.
But Jimmy...
Don't worry, we' ll deal with him.
No, I' m not going anywhere.
Jimmy!
I want to stay with Candy boss.
take care of everybody.
Jimmy!
Damm it!
Does not boss need me anymore?
It' s not true!
Boss!
We should not force him.
Stop the topic for a while.
Jimmy!
Jimmy, Mr. Cartwright is...
Isn't that a pistol?
It' s cowboy' s hand-carry.
I hate that!
Jimmy!
Jimmy wants to stay with me.
As long as I am not here,
he will go to the pasture.
But, Where am I going?
There' s no direction.
Jimmy should have his own happiness.
Tom! That' s it.
He was adopted by Mr. Steave
in the same way.
As an elder, Tom will persuades him.
Jimmy will accept that for sure.
Good morning, Jimmy.
Good morning.
Look! Jimmy.
It' s...
I did it for you last night.
Boss?
Put it on.
That' s great!
You looked so cool! Mr. Cowboy.
Don't try to bribe me with this.
Jimmy!
I won't be fooled, I don't want it.
I have no intention of bribing you.
Really?
Candy is not a stingy guy.
Boss, I am willing to accept.
Thank you!
-Let' s go to the pasture.
-Okay!
It is nice, Jimmy
Your posture is sheer
The Candy boss did it for me
You... cowboy taking charge
of the whole locality
Quite right
Why to bully racoons?
Where is Mr. Cartwright?
He has got cold and had a rest
Candy
No way, lie down
Do not you like seeing a doctor?
You are even more affective
than the doctor
How is Jim's meaning?
Don't move!
You catch a cold and cure first
Have a fever as expected
You' re good at Looking after patients.
No! there' re lot of things to learn.
I' ll deal with Jimmy.
Why don't you take some sleep.
I' m so useless, compared with her.
It' s like this, take a look.
Candy did that for him last night.
Candy' s working so hard just like us.
I hope so!
The happiness of others
is more important than her' s.
Jimmy!
Boss!
Where are you going?
Tom's pasture, Please!
Okay!
It' s been a long time...
to visit Tom's pasture.
You were here before going to London.
Are you going to leave again?
Of course not.
Excuse me, is Tom at home?
Tom!
Candy, What a surprise!
Tom.
Jimmy,
it' s a good thing to Inherit a pasture.
I am happy for everything I have here.
The pasture is going to be changed.
It' s a great moment.
The era of the pistol will be over.
The era of riding horse
will be changed too.
The pasture needs to be modernized.
You should know that...
A man should take the challenging work.
Tom looks so excited.
He already found his own way
with fully confidence.
I am so ashamed, Tom works so hard.
I went to England for studying,
still can't find my own direction.
Boss, you looked so listless?
Jimmy!
Boss!
Jimmy, don't take me as the model,
you should learn from Tom.
-Candy!
-I' m back.
Candy,
go take care of Mr. Cartwright at once.
What happened? Sister Pony.
Mr. Cartwright has a high fever,
sister Lane is there already.
Jimmy!
Please, Candy!
Doctor!
It' s Okay! Just a cold.
Nothing serious!
Don't let him worry too much.
It is Candy
who advised him to take a rest.
It is also you
who advised him to send for a doctor.
I' ll leave everything to you, Candy.
Yes!
Thank you, Jimmy!
Jimmy!
-Mr. Cartwright!
-Jimmy!
Thank you!
Mr. Cartwright.
Candy!
You must take a rest.
I was just away...
I am sorry!
You should lie in bed having a rest,
be good!
Soup!
Boss. Candy boss!
Don't worry!
I will stay with Mr. Cratwright
and look after him forever.
Jimmy!
Mr. Albert, Terry, Tom,
and Jimmy.
You had found your own way already.
The sound of walking
which strengthen one' s mind.
Walk into Candy' s heart.