Safex
Two people of secret navigation.
With the help of captain Justin,
Candy sneak into the cabin successfully.
Taking the loved pet,
she took the Sea-gull leave England.
We can breathe now!
Kurin, cheer up!
Be quiet! Are you a stowaway?
If I got caught,
they' ll send me back to England.
Calm down!
You will be found.
This sound is Familiar with.
The cry of coons? You...
Cookie! You' re Cookie.
Hi!
Don't frighten me!
I was frighten too.
We' ll be found so loudly.
Do you slip away in stealthily too?
You can say that!
That' s great! It' s so dark here.
We must take low voice in here.
If the sailor found us,
we' ll be in trouble.
You know lot about the ship.
I want to be a sailor.
You do have courage,
a little girl dares to run a blockade.
I must return to America.
Are your parents all in America?
No, my parents all passed away.
Me too.
Thanks!
My father was a sailor as well.
I have resolved to be a sailor
since childhood.
The way he speaks is really like Terry.
After my mother' s dead...
In order to be a sailor,
I had been smuggled many times.
It' s not your first time?
Right! Probably ten times.
So many...
But, I never succeeded,
Always been caught.
What would happened If we got caught?
Hang punishment or repatriate.
Hang punishment?
Someone' s coming!
How about it? Any damage?
Ok!
Check carefully!
If the rope is broken, we' ll be trouble.
Strange!
Check-off!
My heart almost stopped!
How can you reach to America like that?
You' re young but brave.
I' m 15 already!
Me too.
I thought that you are younger than I.
Looks not like 15, that' s a trouble.
The companies of the ship here
don't hire the children to be a sailor.
That' s why you want to go to America?
If I were in America,
they' ll hire me to be a sailor for sure.
What happened?
Say ''hello'' to another ships.
The conversation is so simple.
The decks are definitely very noisy.
It' s so dark inside
If isn't cookie at my side...
I' m hungry!
How can you useless?
I' m hungry too.
Candy,
I go to find food in storeroom.
Is it all right?
It is dinner time now!
Becareful!
Wait and look!
Behavior yourself!
Excused me to coming late.
What' s in your pocket?
Take it out!
Where did you get the apple?
An old trick!
It' s captain' s dessert.
You lie.
Only me and the chef
have the key of storerooms.
-Right?
-Yes.
Viva, did you stole the key?
No, I found it in the cabin just now.
Really?
Yes.
Go search!
Let' s go!
The storeroom is locked.
Cookie!
No!
Damm it! Slipped up again!
Get him!
Stop!
Cookie has been found.
What are you doing? Release me!
Release me!
I want to be a sailor.
The Children couldn't be a sailor.
Well-behaved your hands for capture.
I would rather die than give up.
Let go of me!
I like to rescue Cookie,
but I' m afraid of being found.
Stop the ship!
I must go to America.
Everybody!
Throw Cookie into the sea.
Throw Cookie into the sea?
Let go of me!
Stop it!
Help!
Cookie, how you feel?
Is the brain sober?
He looks like a baggage!
Step aside!
Cookie!
You' re...
Don't just stand there,
he' ll be drowned.
Cookie!
Candy!
Do your best!
Cookie! Swim back to England!
How cruel are you! rescue him quick!
He is very good at swimming.
Do you best! Cookie.
Cookie!
Help!
My foot has pulled a muscle.
He' s in trouble!
Back!
There' s no time,
Cookie may cause heart paralysis.
Heart paralysis?
Go save him now!
-Do your best!
-Hurry up!
Give me a rope.
Rope.
Cheer up! Hold me tight!
I have not practised for a long time.
Set!
Miss, You are good.
Stop nonsense, just help me.
Grasp it! Pull...
Almost there!
Hold there.
Cookie!
Why you want to hurt him?
We' er just kidding.
Cookie,
I' m Candy, can you hear me?
Take him to the bed,
go find some blankets.
Do as doctor said.
Don't be rude! He is not the luggage.
Easy!
Brother!
What?
I was wondering that
who is that young lady?
You don't know her?
Could be the daughter of captain?
Captain do has a daughter alright,
but...
You over there!
Give me some warm milk.
Just like captain!
You' re back, Cookie.
Don't worry, you will be warm up soon!
Candy, how can you come out?
You' re an illegal immigrant.
I forgot that!
Hide from quickly.
Where Can I hide from?
Hot milk is coming!
-Candy!
-Lie down...
Cookie, You are a victim.
Keep pretending...
You can't die! Cookie!
Take more blankets here!
Was it so bad? lady.
Lady?
We wouldn't do that
if we know that he is your friend.
If Cookie lose his life,
you' ll probably get hanged.
Hanged?
I told you before,
the ship needs a doctor.
Isn't that the owner's responsibility?
Quiet! Everyone...
Leave it to me! I am a nurse.
That would be great!
Are you a nurse?
The captain' s daughter
is a gentle nurse.
Captain' s daughter?
That' s why they didn't stop me.
The captain will find that
sooner or later.
Is there anything to eat?
A dying patient can eat?
The easily digestible food
and some fruits.
Right away!
Leave everything to me,
please go back to your room.
Sorry to trouble you, lady!
Daughter?
Your lovely daughter.
You want to see her here?
No! Just do your job.
Daughter...
Delicious!
So delicious!
We will make it this time.
The captain...
It' s been here already,
how can he took us back to England?
We' re now
in the middle of Atlantic Ocean.
And, there' s tsunami around here.
You know that too?
I am good at smuggling.
I am captain Neiben.
I am Candy.
Take your meals and get some sleep.
Thank you very much!
Tomorrow morning,
you' ll going back to England.
Captain, it' s middle of Atlantic Ocean,
you want us to go back to England?
There' s ship back to England at dawn.
She' ll take you back.
Captain!
Please wait!
I' m sorry that
we sneak into your ship.
Please don't send us back,
I must return to America.
Captain,
I will become a sailor in America.
Is your name Candy?
Is there anyone helped you?
Who is the guy who helped you?
Tell me the truth.
Nobody!
This isn't the general passenger liner.
There is no lunch eaten free,
everyone on the ship must work.
Anyone gains without pains,
I detest this kind of people.
Captain!
You' ll be send to another room.
Please wait!
The room is so rotten.
It' s better than the cargo cabin.
The captain is so stubborn.
What the captain said is right.
Candy!
In order to go back to America,
I sneak into this ship.
It' s because
we can't find a job on the ship.
I don't understand your situation,
I never request anyone to help me.
What shoule we do? Candy.
We will be sent back to England
tomorrow morning.
It' s all captain's fault.
Eleanor Baker.
The picture of Terry' s mother.
How' s Terry doing in America?
Do you know her?
Eleanor Baker,
hottest actress in America.
I saw her before, the eyes...
You really did.
Eleanor Baker is Terry' s mother.
The expression in her eyes...
The image here, it' s so Familiar.
Yes, The Michigan lake.
Sister Pony, sister Lane
I will be sent back to England
in the morning.
I' m sorry, Candy.
It' s not your fault.
I play worse than Terry.
The ship advances in the ocean.
Candy prays that...
may the sun will never rise.