Safex
One night...
wounded Terry mistook Candy's room
for his own, and barged inside.
Candy snuck out into the town where
she happened upon Mr. Albert.
When Candy came to visit
Mr. Albert in his zoo...
she found that Terry was there as well.
Terry came to express his gratitude to
Mr. Albert for saving him in a fight.
And thus, Candy saw the cheerful
Terry's side for the first time.
The secret of Terrius.
First time I met Terry, we were
on a ship heading to London.
He's crying?
Which is the real Terry?
I've never met someone
who hid his true feelings like that.
It's him!
Brother, Candy noticed!
Quickly, get that cushion!
The mat would be better
than a cushion, right?
Archie, help me out!
That's a good idea!
Huh? The beacon light went out.
Is that their room?
Stear? Archie?
Where are you?
I guess I'm in the wrong room.
Huh?
This is...
This is Eleanor Baker.
The famous American Broadway actress.
"Drop dead!"
Just what is this?
To my son Terrius
With all of my love.
Eleanor Baker.
To my son Terrius...
I see. This must be Terry's room.
But... the beautiful Eleanor Baker...
who signed this is Terry's mother?
Candy!
Terry!
What are you doing in here?
I...
I... I went into this room by mistake.
Listen! Don't tell anybody about this.
If you do, I'll tear you to pieces!
Terry...
Please, go back.
Terry... I'm sorry.
I won't tell anybody. I promise.
Go back!
Candy!
I'm here!
What are you doing there?
I'll come over!
Move a bit!
If you're gonna fall like that,
why don't you fall on the mat?
You look worried
ever since you came here.
So you were at that nobleman's room?
Yes. That's right.
-And... he wasn't there?
-Yeah, he wasn't .
Thank heavens!
If he found you in his room...
all three of us would've been punished!
Archie, Terry is not a snitch!
How can you be sure of that?
The point is that he...
Now, now. He didn't see her
so what's the point in fighting then?
By the way, Candy, take a look at this.
See!
But Stear, I'm sorry for
what happened the other day.
I broke your invention.
Nah, I simplified the controls
on this model...
so it'll be okay.
Geez, brother, you build
all kinds of stuff for Candy.
Archie, don't embarrass me.
I did it again.
I suck at this!
Eleanor Baker?
You said Eleanor Baker?
Brother, the photo fell off from
the flip side of the mat.
Flip side of the mat?
Yes. Sisters won't be able
to find them there.
Take a look, Candy!
Incredible, isn't it?
-We have even more!
-Yeah!
I had no idea that the two of you
had such a hobby.
One can't be a real man
unless he's a fan of hers!
We are both into collecting
publicity photographs.
We did a great job hiding these things
away from grand aunt Elroy.
We went all around the town
so aunt Elroy wouldn't notice.
We spent all of our money
on these pictures!
Candy, you're a fan of hers too?
Huh? Well...
There are many more in this box!
We can give you some if you'd like.
You can put them under your pillow
and watch them at night.
Maybe she'll come into your dreams!
Aah, look at this!
It's from her earlier days in Broadway!
Take a look at this!
She has a lovely birthmark!
So similar.
I can recognize
Terry in all of these pictures.
Those eyes... her mouth...
That's right!
When I first met him...
he must have been returning from
a visit to his mother.
But why was he crying?
Maybe he didn't see her?
Heh?
Didn't see... whom?
No...
I meant, this beautiful woman!
Of course
she's the great Eleanor Baker!
We can't get anywhere near her!
So this great actress is Terry's mother.
Anthony?
Anthony is smiling.
He's gently looking and smiling.
I thought we left all Anthony's pictures
back in America.
How did it end up in here?
Say, can I take it?
Candy, you don't have any pictures
of Anthony?
Yes.
It's all coming back to me
Sweet Candy...
The smell of roses...
It's almost May.
The time when Sweet Candy blossoms.
And it'll be my birthday.
Anthony.
It's almost ten o'clock.
I'd better head back!
You'll come to see us again
won't you?
Yeah!
Next time, I'll show you an
even better invention!
Okay!
So much happened today
the time passed in a moment!
Candy, now!
Thank you, Stear.
-Good night, Candy.
-Good night!
Next time, let's have a good chat
and some tea!
Okay.
Don't mope around like that, you two!
Cheer up!
Good night!
"Cheer up" , she said?
We felt down because of
what happened to her.
That's Candy's strong point.
So Candy still hasn't forgotten
about Anthony?
How could she?
We haven't forgotten, too.
Terry's room is in dark.
What happened after the incident?
Why haven't I destroyed that picture
sooner?
Went into her face... I insulted her...
What for?
Listen! Don't tell anybody about this.
If you do, I'll tear you to pieces!
I had no right to attack her.
I couldn't have destroyed the picture
until now.
I hate the way I feel!
Mr. Terrius!
Mrs. Eleanor, Mr. Terrius is...
Terry!
You've grown so big.
Now, don't just stand there, come on in.
Would you like something warm?
Mama.
Terry.
My dear Terry.
However, you can't live here anymore.
We must keep the secret that
you're my son.
Terry, don't misunderstand me!
I still love you!
Terry!
Wait, Terry!
You're a son of the Grandchester family!
Promise me!
Don't tell anyone that you're my son!
...Don't tell anyone!
Don't tell anyone!!
Why did I go to America?
What have I sought in that woman?
What?
Was it just to see her?
What was I expecting to find in her?
But to see her... What a joke.
Even though I already knew the outcome.
Also, at that time...
I first met Candy.
She was such a strange one.
With her help, I was able to get my mind
off the insignificant things.
And yet...
Oh? You're here?
I thought you wouldn't be coming back.
since you left at your own whim.
I knew it, the blood of that woman
is cursed.
The blood of that vulgar woman
from America...
Lady Grandchester!
If you keep standing there...
I'm going to turn that ugly pork-face
of yours into something even uglier!
Pork-face...?
What insolence!
It would've been better
if you didn't come back at all!
Now, please get out.
Terrius, I'll see to it that you don't
become a successor of the Grandchesters.
Darling! Get rid of Terrius!
Darling!
He's causing shame to the
Grandchester family!
Did you ever think of these children?
Enough of that, already...
Duke Grandchester...
Why don't you speak up?
Why don't you say anything?
If you loved that woman in America...
if you really were in love with her...
That boy gives me such a headache!
Shit!
Everyone, go to hell!
Every single one of you!
Go to hell!
The cross sister Pony gave me
Prince's pendant...
and the picture of Anthony!
Those are my three treasures!
They bring so many memories to me!
But on that day...
We shouldn't have gone on a fox hunt...
Anthony!
Don't ride the horse!
Don't get on that horse!
Look out, Anthony!
Anthony!
Candy?
Candy!
You are...?
Pull yourself together!
Anthony...
Terrius!
What happened?
Candice!
She fell down the emergency stairs.
Anyway, I must inform sister Gray.
Anthony...
Anthony?
She said the same thing before.
These tears...
just for whom are they?
Candice caused trouble again?
I didn't get too many details
from Terrius.
Where is Terrius?
He's waiting in the nurse's office.
He's gone!
He escaped through that window!
Don't worry.
Sister Gray is good at treating wounds.
Ow!
Director!
It's just a bruise.
You really cause trouble
in the dead of night!
Just what where you doing out there?
Uh, I was sound asleep
after the lights-out
but then I dreamt about
many little chicks!
So you dreamt about birds?
No, I became an angel in my dream!
I had such a beautiful body
it was so nice...
And then you fell down the
emergency stairs.
Was it because you wanted
Terrius to carry you back inside?
Terrius?
Terrius carried me...?
Are you saying that
you didn't know that?
I... lost my consciousness.
Very well! Candice White Adley!
Yes!
We'll tie you to the bed if this repeats!
Good night!
Yes... sister Gray.
Candice.
I'll walk you to your room.
-Can you walk?
-Yes!
Terry carried me to the nurse's room.
I imagined it was Anthony
but in reality, it was Terry.
What's the matter, Candice?
No... it's nothing.
-Let's hurry.
-Yes!
Kurin was watching me from outside.
Maybe he is together with Terry?
She just lost her consciousness
after that fall.
Good going there, freckled Tarzan.
Anthony...
Anthony?
Just who is he?
I thought that it was Anthony's hand
that touched my face but...
it was Terry's .
Terry's hand felt so warm.
Candy thought that Terry's true heart
must feel warm as well.