Safex
With nothing to do with Candy's caring.
Mr.Markba said goodbye to the world
when sleeping.
A white rose in memory.
Mr.Markba.
It was only yesterday that
I was by his bedside.
We were going to bring the sandwiches,
after his recovery,
to the secret lake with Mina.
We had the deal.
Mr.Markba.
Candy,you are here?
To help clean the room.
Clean the room?
There's gonna be a new patient tomorrow.
This special-care ward?
This time,
it should be less difficult to deal with.
Martly, Mr.Markba
was not difficult to deal with.
He was a gentle grandfather.
Mr.Markba,
so fast... so sudden....
Like in deep sleep,
to a faraway place,
to be with Anthony.
The flowers only bloom after they die.
They die so that
they can dance with the wind.
And live in people's hearts forever.
When Anthony died,
Mr.Albert once said...
Don't be sad for his death,
but be happy
for the chance to meet each other.
I could let go of Anthony's death.
But why can't I do the same,
for Mr.Markba?
Why do people suddenly die?
Why should there
be death and seperation?
I don't want to see people die anymore.
That's enough, Candy.
Sobbing and crying all day,
for a patient.
Blanny.
Candy, do you really think
being a nurse is a right thing for you?
-Me?
-Yes.
There are two kinds of patients.'
those who recover, and those who die.
For a patient who already died, you...
Blanny.
A nurse can't cry?
Can't be sad?
I wouldn't cry, for anyone.
What is she?
A nurse?
Nurse.
Too tight?
Can't move.
Oh no! Sorry.
Please take it after the meals.
Nurse, this medicine is for children.
Sorry, I made a mistake.
Dim-wit.
I am sorry.
Listen!
Sobbing and crying all day,
for a patient,
is not what a nurse should do!
Yes.
Mr.Markba was already announced
incurable, when he was sent in here.
You knew he was gonna die?
He was lucky.
Died peacefully, without pain.
You suffer, because
it is your first time to lose a patient.
It is what every nurse will go through.
Seperation and death.
What is gone is already gone,
but you can always look ahead.
There will be more than just one.
Being depressed all day,
for a patient's death,
is distracting for other patients.
Got it, dim-wit?
Yes.
Then, go back to Pony's home.
Headmaster!
Go home and think about what I said.
Headmaster,
am I really not good enough for a nurse?
I want you to take a vacation.
A vacation?
Pony will be worried
if you don't go back.
Headmaster.
Go home, if you understand what I said.
You did well, dim-wit.
Yes, thank you!
Headmaster Merry Jane is a nice person,
even though she nags a lot.
That's so cute.
Before I go back to Pony's home.
Go to Mr.Markba's house to see Mina.
Let's go!
Move that chair to the carriage over there.
The one in the front?
Calm down.
Mr. Woldo.
Somebody
come to teach this dog a lesson.
No, Mina, be good!
No, go back!
Mr. Woldo.
Get that dog!
Mina, be good!
Mina!
Stop! Get that dog out of here!
Mina, no!
Shoot it!
Is this from Mr.Markba's house?
What's happening?
Here you are again.
I am a nurse, let me do it.
Thank you.
This is not a gun shot.
Mina did it.
Mina did it?
The master said, all his properties
would be donated to the charity.
That stupid dog
keeps getting in the way.
Mina wants to
protect Mr.Markba's property.
That supid dog better dies.
That shot...
They are trying to kill Mina.
Mina?
Mina!
You haven't treated me.
Just a small wound.
Where did it go?
That dog is good.
Mina must be alive.
Where are you, Mina?
Come out!
Mina!
So cute.
Where are you, Mina?
Is it...
Mina!
Here you are!
That's great, you are not hurt!
Mina.
Mr.Markba...
can't take you here to go fishing again.
Mina, I'll be Mr.Markba for you.
I will protect you.
It's morning.
I fell asleep here last night.
Thank you, Mina.
You were protecting me with your body.
After Mr.Markba died,
I had a hard time
falling alseep at night.
Still looking for Mina?
Calm down, Mina.
We are not bad guys.
Don't be mad, Mina.
Somebody is hunting.
Mina, let's get out of here
as soon as possible.
Mina,
I am bringing you back to Pony's home.
They have a lot of children there.
Weird.
Shouldn't there be a road ahead of us?
We should be there soon.
Let's ask somebody there.
Sweet Candy?
Why are they here?
Anthony's Sweet Candy.
The flowers bloomed.
New roses bloomed.
So beautiful!
It must be a new breed, right?
What is it called?
Sweet Candy.
-Sweet Candy?
-My gift for you.
Today is your birthday.
Thank you, Anthony.
Sweet Candy bloomed.
Whose home is it?
Miss Candy.
Aren't you Miss Candy from the Largons?
Mr.Hurman. You are Mr.Hurman.
These Little Candies....
Yes, Mr.Anthony's babies.
I want to let more people
see this kind of rose.
I miss it so much.
Miss candy hasn't changed at all.
Don't call me Miss Candy.
I am a practice nurse now.
What did the Adleys say?
Is Mr.Hurman working here?
Yes, I am a gardener here.
The master here likes roses very much.
Must be a gentle person.
Like Anthony.
It's that dog again.
Come in, the master is almost awake.
Mina, let's go!
Master?
It's you?
You hid the dog. Get off!
-Don't kill Mina.
-Master!
It hurt me like this.
I can't forgive it.
Mina was just trying to
protect Mr.Markba's property.
Get off! Can't you understand?
I am gonna kill this dog!
Get off!
Mina. No!
Let me go! Get it away from here!
Mr.Hurman.
Miss Candy, go.
Mina, that's enough!
Come here.
Hurman, why didn't you shoot?
Master, if we shoot here,
Sweet Candy will cry.
The roses?
This is Miss Candy.
Candy?
Mr.Anthony named the roses after her name
before he died.
After your name?
If you really like roses,
please forgive Mina.
Master.
Thank you!
Mina, Anthony saved your life.
Mr.Anthony's heart...
is still
living in the white rose garden.
Thank you.
Kurin, I'm back!
Kurin. A new friend. Its name is Mina.
Come here.
Mina is too big! Kurin is frightened!
Be good friends.
Boss.
Jimmy.
Welcome back, Boss.
I am back, Jimmy.
Candy is back, really?
Where is Candy?
Candy!
Candy! Where are you?
Sister Pony, I'm back!
Candy!
Did I change, sister?
Naughty girl is always naughty.
And Jimmy,too!
Sister Pony, this is Mina.
Can we keep it in Pony's home?
It's too big.
Its master died,
so it's all by itself now.
I will take care of the spending
each month.
I'll help too, Boss.
No problem, come down!
Ok, Mina, let's go down.
They are my followers.
That's right. We can help you up,
but you need to go down by yourself.
What's wrong, Mina?
Are you afraid, Mina?
Sister Pony, we are coming down!
Please catch us.
No!
Candy. Come on.
Mina, you are too heavy.
I know all your things.
Candy, come down!
OK, I am coming!
Great!
You are back, hoyden.
No wonder you are the boss.
You are so cool!
Mina is back to normal, too.
Come, Kurin.
The sad feeling in Candy's heart
is gradually going away.
Thanks for Headmaster's thoughtfulness.