Safex
Instead of staying in St. Paul academy
and becoming a lady on the surface.
Candy decided that she would rather leave
in order to find her own path in life.
And...
After asking director Gray to amend
Eliza' s week-long room confinement.
Next morning
Candy quickly left the school.
Long way to the port.
Grandfather William.
Thank you for adopting me.
Today, I' m renouncing the adoption
by the Adley family.
I realized that up till now
I've been relying too much
on the Adley family.
From now on...
I want to find my own path
with my own strength.
Please, forgive me
for failing to become a lady.
I will never, ever forget
Grandfather' s kindness.
Let' s go! Kurin.
Eliza Leagan.
I' m amending your punishment
you will partcipate in classes again.
The letter I secrectly sent to
Duke Grandchester got work.
Eliza Leagan.
You might be fond of sending letters
that meant to trouble other people.
But, doing so is not a good thing.
Be careful from now on.
This is...
The letter I sent to Duke Grandchester.
Sister Gray.
Sister Margaret, what happened?
Barging in without knocking...
Excuse my rudeness, sister.
Candice White Adley...
Something happened to Candice?
She left school.
Candy has...
Sister, we received her letters, too.
Calm down!
Don't make this much noise.
-Sister Gray!
-Annie?
-You are here about Candy, too?
-Yes.
Sister Gray
we' d like to offer our help.
What would you do?
What do you mean?
Of course, we' d bring Candy back.
Why would you do such a thing?
She left on her own will
she doesn't want to be brought back.
Eliza, you...
Sister Gray, anyway
we should take a look around the school.
-Now, let' s go!
-We' ll go together.
Wait!
Sister Gray, Candy needs to be Expelled.
Sister Gray, I' m sure that
Candy went after Terry.
You are wrong.
Candice left me a letter, as well...
Good thing that I made these sandwiches
secrectly last night, Kurin.
What' s the matter?
Calm down. Stop...!
What' s the matter? Are you hurt?
No, I' m fine. Sorry.
You' ll catch a cold like that,
You' d better change quickly.
I' m sorry for boarding your carriage
without asking...
It' s okay! hurry!
Thank you. I am Candy.
I am Arnold.
Nice to meet you.
-Hurry up, brother.
-Okay!
-How cute!
-Hurry up!
Now, go!
By the way, Candy
You still havn't told me
where you' re heading to?
Oh! I havn't mentioned that?
I' m going to the port and board a ship.
The port? I can take you halfway.
are you okay with that?
Yes, Mr. Arnold
I would appreciate that.
We made in time.
Candy...!
What' s going on?
Sorry Sir.
Candice White Adley?
I don't remember
seeing that in the register.
Candy is nowhere to be found.
Maybe she is hiding somewhere?
Sister Margret, I owe you so much.
Please forgive me
for leaving without seeing you.
Stear, Archie, I' m sorry
for leaving out of my own accord.
Annie, Patty, I left quietly
to avoid the sadness for departure.
Candy...
I' m sure we' ll see each other again.
That' s why...
I' m not going to bid you farewell.
Huh? Where are we?
You woke up?
How far it is to Southampton port?
Huh?
you meant to the Southampton?
Yes.
We are going in the opposite direction.
I thought you' re going to the Dover.
Can I travel to America from Dover?
No! You can only go to America
from Southampton
Then, if I hurry now...
You' re in such a hurry?
Well, it' s not that I' m in a hurry.
It' s almost night now.
If you are not in such a hurry,
you can stay overnight at my place.
We' re almost there.
Pinky! Attaboy!
I' ll stay at home tonight.
Mr. Arnold, you' re a shepherd?
Yes, Pinky look!
What a cute guest we have.
Nice to meet you Pinky.
This is Kurin.
Kurin, what' s the matter?
Pinky...
Candy, why don't you come in?
Come, Pinky, Kurin.
Leaves are falling...
I wonder what' s Candy doing now.
-Annie, are you okay?
-Yeah!
You havn't knitted anything for a while.
Patty, and you keep staring
at the same page...
Candy, you parted from us
with such a short letter.
Annie, we should become stronger
from now on.
We shouldn't give Candy a reason
to worry about us.
Yes, Candy hates crybabies.
That' s right.
Kurin! You still have a lot to learn.
Oh! A sheep went astray again.
Leave it to me.
Thank you.
I' m better at these things
than at being a lady.
I haven't felt so alive for a long time.
You make it sound like
you' re asleep for a long time.
Yeah! I felt as if I were asleep
ever since I arrived England.
And today, I finally woke up.
I' m going to begin anew.
Really, Candy, you look like
escaped from a long torment.
Your eyes are all glittery.
I' m so glad I escaped.
Miss Candice left this letter
for Mr. William?
Yes, I' m very sorry for this.
No, it' s not your fault.
Miss Candice wrote that in the letter.
I' m worried about one thing, however.
Miss Candice took off
with almost no money.
-Money?
-Just in case...
I personally brought this...
So Candice went on a journey
with no money.
Farewell, Mr. Arnold, Pinky.
Stay well, Candy.
Kurin, it' s only you and me now.
Our new beginning.
Let' s go! Kurin.
It' s raining, Kurin, hurry.
Kurin, I' m hungry. I' ll buy some food.
Welcome! How can I help you?
Can I get something to eat
for 10 shillings?
10 shillings?
You can't buy much for 10 shillings.
I know. Give me the cheapest bread then.
Alright!
Here! You can take this.
Really? It looks so big...
-It' s okay, take it.
-Thank you.
Kurin, I' m sorry.
I' ll find a proper job tomorrow.
Please bear it for tonight.
I won't give up, Terry.
I' ll have a job in that town.
Let' s go! Kurin.
No, I don't need any help.
As you can see
I can manage everything on my own.
That' s right, you need a job...
We don't hire woman.
This is terrible, I' m broke
couldn't find a job, I' m hungry.
Are we going to sleep out again?
Kurin, you are hunry too?
Alright! I' ll keep looking for a job.
Bed and breakfast.
Maybe I could work at this inn.
Welcome.
Uh...
What is it?
Uh! Would you let me work here
just for one night?
Let me work...
Looks like you have a reason.
Do you have working experience?
Yes, I used to work in kitchen.
Just for one night...
Please.
You won't earn a lot.
I' m willing to work for a meal alone.
Well, let' s see what you can do.
Come.
Thank goodness.
Are you okay?
I' m fine.
While working in Eliza' s kitchen.
I didn't know that
I would use these experiences.
-Are you done?
-Yes.
Well, I made you a meal.
Thank you.
Kurin, you...
Please...
Have mercy...
We don't have anything, get out.
Something to eat...
I told you, we don't have anything.
Have mercy...
See, this girl worked hard for it.
You have to work for people
to have something return.
Have mercy...
Thank you, kind lady.
Thank you, Miss.
Aren't you dumb one.
I thought you were hungry.
-Yeah!
-Why' d you do that?
I felt sorry for him...
What will you do now?
Please let me work more.
You' re quite something...
Okay, eat all you want.
Listen. I don't know your circumstance.
But, I want you to know that
living alone is hard.
-Don't take it too lightly.
-Yes.
If you understood me, eat up.
I' ll let you stay here for tonight.
But, I don't have money...
It' s okay, you' re not staying long,
anyway.
I...
Now... if you cried for this,
what would happen from now on?
Yes...
Terry, Mr. Albert.
I finally started treading my own path.
I felt so much
since I left St. Paul academy.
The landlady has a big mouth
but she is a good person.
Good night, everyone.
Good morning.
Oh! You' re up already?
I wanted tp bake some bread.
You can bake bread?
Yes, a cook taught me before.
You' re quite something.
It' s good.
You' re quite something, Candy.
I' m glad you like it.
Thank you for waiting.
Candy, the stew is done.
Yes.
Really, she is a good girl.
Cheerful, hard-working...
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
You helped me so much.
You really have to go?
Yes, I plan on working and saving money
to go to the Southampton.
Here, don't mind.
Just to cover your expenses.
But, you don't have to.
It' s your salary for baking the bread.
Take it.
Thank you.
Take care.
I will.
Farewell, stay well.
Farewell.
Candy wasn't sure that
if she can go back to Pony' s home?
But, she couldn't turn back anymore.
She keep forward, never looking back.