Safex
Eliza's trap.
Summer vacation spent in Scotland
left Candy with many memories.
And it was Terry who stood out the most
in those memories.
After returning to London...
the town, school and everything else
looked gray to Candy.
A punk.
I'm never going to see him again
after that!
I hate him!
Uh... Candy?
Aww, when did you...?
We kept knocking but
there was no answer...
Sorry...!
Candy, is something troubling you?
Troubling me?
Not at all!
But ever since we returned from Scotland
Candy, you've been acting strange.
Right, Patty?
I'm just playing around!
That's right!
I was about to write a letter.
A letter?
To Grandfather William.
It's not like he's going to reply,
anyway!
Let's see... Thank you very much
for the fun summer vacation...
Even Stear and Archie got a nice tan!
Now my freckles stand out even more.
New semester begins tomorrow...?
I'm going to live by the rulebook again.
In order to tighten your loose spirits
after the summer vacation...
Double the time of today's holy mass.
Quiet!
Oh, boy. From today, we're back
to our lives by the rulebook.
Terry isn't here.
Is he still playing around in Scotland?
Candice White Adley!
What are you looking at?
Yes!
The dazzling summer sky of Scotland
was a bit too much.
Ever since I came back to this school,
everything seems so dark.
Excuse me. Miss, are you alright?
Yes, I'm fine!
Could this be Grandfather William...?
Uh... excuse me but...
are you Terry's ... no, I mean
Terrius's father?
That's correct.
I'm Eliza Leagan
a very good friend of Terry's ...
My, my.
-Uh...
-Sorry...
I'm here to have a word with Director.
Well then, it was nice to meet you.
Please!
Uh, I...
Well then.
So that man was Terry's father?
Just what business
does he have in this school?
My, my, isn't this Duke Grandchester.
Welcome.
Take this.
I'm grateful for your usual
contribution for education...
Is my son doing well?
Y...yes. Lately he's been doing a little
too well.
Actually,
I'd like to speak to him in private.
Very well. I'll call him immediately.
No, you don't have to.
I'll go over to him.
Terrius.
I'd like to talk to you.
Sit down.
I received a letter from Eleanor.
She wrote about how she wants
you to live at her place.
You still want to see that woman?
"That woman?"
That's my mother!
Moreover, she is someone
you used to love before!
That's history!
You are a Grandchester.
I'd like you to think more of your duty.
I see. Were you guided by that honour
when you parted from Eleanor Baker?
Shut up!
You will never see Eleanor again!
If you still choose to,
I will disown you!
She thinks about me
so much more than my father.
I won't follow in my father's footsteps.
If I lead myself by the fabled honour
of the Grandchester family.
what is going to become of her?
I'll never become the kind of person
my father is!
Candy, it's here! A letter!
It's from Grandfather William, right?
It's finally here!
Here you go.
Thanks. Huh?
It's from mr. Albert!
from Africa.
See you.
Thank you, Patty!
Africa?
Dear Candy,
I'm in Africa right now.
I wanted to bid you farewell
when I was leaving London but...
you already went to Summer school
in Scotland.
There are many wild animals living here!
I noticed how these wild animals...
are so much livelier than
those entrapped in zoos.
It's best when animals and people
live naturally.
The same way you are living naturally
am I right?
What's the meaning of this?
Also, send my regards to Terry
he is also loves to live in naturally.
I'm working in a small hospital
taking care of people.
Two or three years... no,
you can come to visit me here forever.
Africa...?
Let's see, London is here...
he sure did come a long way...
I finally got to see you
and you went away again.
Is this mr. Albert's way of life?
Hi.
Don't get too familiar.
I don't intend to forgive you yet!
And I don't intend to apologize.
You're rude!
If you keep making those faces
you'll end up looking like sister Gray.
Just to make it clear,
I'm not here to see you.
Here.
It's from mr. Albert!
I thought you might want to read it
since he wrote so much about you!
Africa...
What a pity, I counted on him...
You counted on him to rescue you
when you pick a fight again?
If I was driven out of the house...
I wanted to ask him
to let me be his assistant.
Terry, something to do with
your father came to see you?
Maybe.
Does this have anything to do
with your real mother?
Concentrate on your studies!
You're making fun of me again!
Finally, you're back to your usual self.
But...
you only speak these rude things.
Anyway, can I take it easy
reading the letter?
Feel free to.
It's regrettable, but I feel completely
relaxed when I'm next to Terry.
I thought things were like this...
Candy is...
Candy is going after Terry...
I'll show you!
Hello! It's been a while
since last time we were out!
Let's go!
Lady, suddenly jumping in front of me
like this is dangerous!
Terry, I'd like to give you a word
of warning.
Can't we leave this for some other time?
My horse wants to run.
I know that girl very well.
What?
I'm talking about Candy.
So you want to hear.
You look like you
can't wait to get it out.
You see, that girl was our servant.
-She was very good being what she was!
-And?
She caught the eye of grandfather William
who adopted her into the Adley family.
And?
But that girl is actually a thief!
She took mama's necklace
and my jewelery.
Even now, you can never be sure
what she is thinking about!
She gets violent as soon as
you give her a mean look...
she even hurt Neil!
If you keep hanging around
such a girl...
you could tarnish the reputation
of the Grandchester family!
Thank you for your warning.
In return, I'd like you to warn Candy
about me.
Terry likes to smoke and drink
during the holy mass.
He doesn't even know the number
of fights he's been into...
but probably tens of thousands.
His dad's dough bought him a place
in this school...
but in reality
he's just a good-for-nothing bum.
Terry!
Tell her that if she hooks up with
such a guy...
the reputation of the Adleys
could be tarnished.
Wait up, Terry!
Eliza, you should look yourself
in the mirror now.
Because you'd see the archetype
of an insane, badmouthing woman.
Go!
He made fun of me...
He insulted me from that horse...
He carried Candy on that horse!
I won't forgive you!
Africa is amazing.
Candy.
What is it, Patty?
Just a sec.
Say, Patty, where are we going?
I'm sorry
but I was too afraid to go alone!
-Afriaid?
-This way.
Nobody is watching us?
A letter?
Who are you going to send it to?
It's our post.
Our post?
So that is post?
Got it!
I'd like my letter to arrive safely, too!
Say, Patty... who sent you this letter?
Stear did.
So you and Stear are using
that tree to exchange letters?
-Patty, you're going at it!
-Aww, come on!
Patty, a patrol.
Wow, I'm jealous!
You're exchanging letters every day!
I had no idea that Patty and Stear
have become such close friends!
Not like that, we're just consulting
each other about our daily events.
Come to think of it
even though it's the same school...
boys and girls meet
only during the prayer' time.
You'll excuse me now.
There is still some time before
sisters go on patrol!
No, I want to write a reply!
But you just sent one!
But... good night!
I can't believe that this Stear guy
is writing all those letters!
I'm better with inventions than
I'm with letters...
Brother!
Sorry... I hit you?
Huh? It's a different kind of envelope.
Candy!
I'm here, Patty!
Candy, I found this in my secret post!
Okay, you don't have to make me read
Stear's letters...
When I opened it
it was addressed to you!
To me?
I'd like to talk to you about some
very important matters.
Tonight at 8 o'clock, I'll be waiting
in the barn. Terrius.
Once you read this letter
destroy it immediately.
Thank you, Patty!
Candy...
Terry must heard about this from Stear,
and he tried to reach me.
But those important matters...
what is it about?
An important discussion.
What's the meaning of that?
Maybe he's leaving to America
in order to live with his real mother?
Terry!
I'm right here!
Where are you, Terry?
Now that was scary.
Why did you call me out here
at this hour?
It was you who called me, right?
What?
You put the note underneath the door
of my room.
I also got a letter that mentioned
an important discussion...
Did you bring that letter?
It said that I should destroy it
immediately after reading.
It's the same idea.
Just what are you two doing?!
Are you trying to ruin the reputation
of this school?!
That's not true, sister Gray!
Eliza!
You...!
Looks like the rumours were true.
The two of you really are seeing
each other in this barn.
You liar! Eliza!
Eliza! I couldn't despise you
more than I do now.
Oh, I just came here to see whether
the rumours were true or not.
This is a ploy!
Candice White Adley!
You are expelled from the school!
Expelled?
Until your family arrives to
pick you up...
you will be confined to the tower!
Take her away!
Please wait, director Gray!
Please listen to me!
What are you doing?
Please wait!
-Terry!
-Candy!
Terry...!
Candy!
Terrius G. Grandchester!
You are confined to your room
for a week!
She and I did the same thing,
so why wasn't I expelled?
Knowing you, I have more sympathy
for actions from your behalf.
That's right! During the time
in Summer school in Scotland...
She was persistently all over him!
Eliza! Bitches like you...
Terrius! I won't tolerate violence
right in front of me!
Let me out!
I was framed by Eliza!
Please hear me, director Gray!
Grandfather William... you...
you would've believed me
would you?
Candy cried loudly.
She shouted loudly.
She felt as if she was being engulfed
by the silent darkness.