Safex
In order to learn the nursing techniques for
the surgical department,
Candy, Blanny and the group are going to
ake off for St.Joanna Hospital in Chicago.
The day has come.
Heading to the hospital in a big city
will be farther away from Pony's Home.
Sister Pony and Sister Lane,
you must be happy for me.
Candy, take care of yourself. Go!
Stear, Archie and Annie.
They are all in Chicago.
I am going to Chicago.
They must be very surprised.
Candy.
Candy, can you turn off the light?
The time has passed.
Sorry, I'll turn off the light now.
Blanny, you are not going to write a letter home?
To tell them what?
That I am one of the five chosen people,
so please be happy for me?
Or should I tell them that
it feels lonely to leave here?
I hate being sensitive.
I only hope to become an
outstanding nurse as soon as possible.
Good night.
Rest early.
We have patients to take care of tomorrow.
Yes.
Blanny
why don't you want to open your heart?
We will study together in the future.
Blanny, we are so nervous.
You are gonna help us in Chicago, alright?
You, too! Please.
So cold.
Blanny works hard and has good grades.
We need her.
St.Joanna Hospital in Chicago
is our headquarters.
They have a lot of outstanding people there.
Country nurses like us
will be looked down.
Someone has got the biggest problem.
Candy?
Blanny and her are enemies.
Good morning.
Today is the last day.
Let's not get too closed to Candy.
It's not good if Blanny gets mad.
Good morning.
Good morning, Candy!
Good morning, Miss Betty!
Candy, good morning!
Good morning, Miss Molly!
Is Aunt better?
That's great!
She can leave the hospital soon.
Candy, sorry for the trouble. Thank you!
Candy, good morning!
Good morning, Miss Tera, Miss Ruth!
Everybody is so nice today.
We won't see you anymore.
You are going to the hospital in Chicago
aren't you?
I....
You don't need to hide anything. We've all heard.
You can't hide anything in the hospital.
Sorry,
I didn't mean to hide things from you.
I just couldn't say it.
I know. We don't want to leave you, either.
Candy, look at these flowers.
We planted them together last year.
We don't want you to leave.
- Silly girl.
- Yes.
Go!
We will pray for you.
Right!
Yes, thank you.
No.
I can't cry.
It's better not to tell the kids.
I am afraid they can't take it.
Good morning.
Good morning, Candy! I finished my breakfast.
You are so good!
Candy, I went to the restroom by myself.
You are great!
Principal will be so happy about this.
Candy, we don't need to take shots today, right?
Right.
Let me tell you a story.
But, you promise me to take the medicine on time.
Sister Candy, we always take
the medicine on time.
Good kids.
These children are so cute.
I am going to leave them today.
I can not say it.
Sister Candy.
What's wrong? Your face looks weird.
Nothing.
Dangerous.
My face looks so obvious.
Gotta be careful!
Blanny.
Candy.
Did you tell them there will be
a new nurse tomorrow?
No, not yet.
Why not?
The words just couldn't come out.
But, before we leave....
Forget it.I'll say it for you.
Blanny, no!
Attention!
Everybody, from tomorrow,
the nurse for this room will be changed.
Today is Candy's last day.
Please cooperate.
Why?
Candy is going to study
in the hospital in Chicago.
- Blanny!
- Chicago?
She is going to leave this hospital?
I will be back soon.
Candy, don't mislead the patients.
But....
Everyone, listen.
If we want to be the real nurses,
we need to gain more knowledge.
Understand?
Blanny.
Sorry, I didn't tell you.
everyone, talk!
That's too much.
Blanny is too much.
Good morning.
You are going to abandon us.
Candy is the devil.
Silly girl, Blanny told us.
Sorry, please let me explain....
I don't want to see you anymore, get out!
Candy.
To make the children sad is unforgivable.
That was dangerous, silly girl.
I am sorry.
What's your attitude?
good-bye!
You are too much, Blanny.
Candy,
stop acting.
Acting?
Right. You were trying to hide it from us.
It made the patients upset.
After you leave,do you think the patients
will ever trust other nurses?
It's not like that.
Nursing is a team work.
No matter who takes over,
the most important thing is
to help the patients receive the treatment.
Although they are always against each other,
they both will be good nurses.
Blanny is right.
I only thought about how would the patients feel,
but forgot about my teammates.
Treatment can not rely on just one person.
It takes the cooperation between
the doctors and the nurses.
A letter for me?
I am sorry.
It's my fault.
I should tell everyone
that I am going to Chicago.
Let's have a farewell party for Sister Candy!
- Right!
-Agreed!
I am going to notify other rooms'patients.
Good idea, right, everyone?
Yes, let's do it!
Decided.
We grownups can not cry first.
That's right!
Candy has always been encouraging us.
This time we'll encourage her.
Let's notify other rooms.
We are coming.
Principal.
Ready?
Follow me.
Natalie and others are over there.
Pricipal told us to gather here.
What's going on here?
This is the meeting room.
There won't be anything good happening
in the last test before we leave.
Go in.
Come, Blanny.
Ready.
This is....
Still not know?
The patients want to thank you.
Sister Candy, go!
Be an outstanding nurse!
I will work hard with everybody.
Blanny, you take care!
Thanks.
Sister Candy, thanks for taking care of me.
I have always been self-centered, sorry.
No, you are a good kid.
Hope you get well soon,
and become an useful person.
- Sister Judy.
- Thanks.
Thanks.
Sister Blanny, thank you for taking care of me.
Blanny.
Everyone, please circle around the table.
Principal, we are leaving.
Everyone study hard.
Take care, Principal.
Candy.
Remember not to get silly again.
Yes.
Time to go.
- Mark, to the station.
- Yes, sir!
Good-bye! Take care!
Good-bye!
Silly girl is gone
the hospital will be very quiet.
Good-bye!
Chicago.
The hospital is on a busy street. It's so good!
It's great!
Come on.
The hospital is so big.
The number of patients in Josep Hospital
can not compare to this one.
Get away!
Smells like medicine.
ouch!
Sorry, nurse.
Sorry,
the kid's hand was burned.
It hurts!
Excuse me....
Fill out the forms. Take turns.
But, it's bleeding....
It's ok, press the wound, you won't die.
That's mean!
I can't treat you personally,
it has to follow the rules.
Why not treat him first?
He is hurting so much.
His problem is not as severe.
But....
There are people waiting to be seen.
Candy made a trouble again.
She should mind her own business.
Isn't it the nurses'responsibility
to prevent patients from feeling anxious?
Who are you people?
Practice nurses from Merry Jane Nursing School.
Merry Jane? Shut up!
If you are busy, we can help him.
That's arrogant of you.
How did Headmaster Merry Jane teach you?
Principal wouldn't allow you to do so.
Candy, let me help you.
Blanny.
Natalie, help me bring my purse here.
Children, please come close.
Go ahead and listen.
- That's amazing.
- Thank you for the help.
Children, look at sister!
Alcohol!
Listen, it will hurt a little bit.
You can stand it. You are a man, right?
Good.
Amazing.
Ok.
Ok, it doesn't hurt anymore, right?
Thank you!
Line up to see the doctor later.
That's ok.
The doctor will do the same thing.
You did it very well.
Headmaster Merry Jane taught you well.
St. Joanna Hospital is the biggest
multi-division hospital in Chicago.
They have a lot of patients.
Expecially the surgical department
that you are in charge of.
This is your room.
Judy, Natalie and Ellie
stay in this room.
Candy and Blanny stay in another one.
Excuse me,
why should I be in the same room with Candy?
Headmaster Merry Jane requested it.
I see...
Take good rest today
you will have a lot to do later.
Yes.
If it was allowed,Candy wouldn't
want to share a room with Blanny, either.
However,
the cooperation a while ago just revealed that
Blanny is a helper who is much needed here.