Safex
The spring is coming...
Candy's leaving for the
Merry Jane Nursing School.
Kurin and The children of Pony's home
went to the station to see her off.
The granny in the street.
What a city!
It's four hours from Pony's home.
Why drive arbitrarily?
Fortunately, my reflection nerve
is still good
So lucky! My dress is still clean.
It is not lucky at all!
Look! It's all your fault.
It was the driver's fault.
Granny, Look out!
That's close.
Are you alright? Granny.
I'm almost done. It's all your fault.
What?
Excuse me!
This...
I forgot that, Thanks!
Granny!
Just a moment.
Excuse me!
Granny!
Where are you going?
The Joseph hospital over there.
Joseph hospital?
The hospital is around the school.
Granny, I'll escort you to there.
Mind your own business.
But... I'm going to the nurse school.
The nurse school?
What you go there for?
What I go for?
To become a nurse, of course!
Become a nurse? You talk too much.
What a strange granny!
But there 's no one helps her...
Yes. let's go!
Why does the family let her out alone?
I have no family.
I am sorry,
your hearing is excellent.
My mouth is more excellent.
I knew that already!
So, you 're came from the Pony's home?
It's not easy to become a nurse.
I knew that!
You know that?
The nurse needs to look after patients.
There are troublesome patients,
sometimes.
She 's talking about herself.
We are here!
Joseph hospital.
Merry Jane Nursing School.
They are in the same location.
Granny, I'll go to the school.
Take care!
Leave the patients aside.
What a strange granny!
I'm here now!
It feels like the hospital,
it's nurse school alright!
A pure white world, fantastic!
They must be the students.
White uniform. Feels so good.
How I looked like in that dress?
Excuse me.
Yes!
Patients must not come in here.
No, I am not the patient.
I have an appointment
with the headmaster.
The information desk is over there.
The information desk?
I didn 't notice that.
We might be good friends someday.
How do you do?
She looked cool, but very efficient.
Are you Candice White?
The headmaster said that
she will be here in an hour.
An hour later?
Why don 't you leave the luggage here...
look around the city for an hour.
It sounds strange.
After entering the school,
I might have no time to look around.
It's a good chance.
Where are you going?
Granny!
I'm free for an hour.
You can stay with me! Come!
You told me that you live alone.
I have been alone all the time.
So does sister Pony
and headmaster Merry Jane.
The headmaster is an odd person.
It is not like that.
Headmaster Merry Jane
takes care of the patients.
She is a great woman.
Maybe...
So does sister Pony.
She gave up everything for us.
So does sister Lane,
they are all great women.
It did again.
What's wrong with you?
You kept away from that last time.
If I did that, what will you do?
Don 't worry!
my reflection nerve is normal.
How unreasonable she is.
Are you mad at me?
No!
I see. That's good!
You can not be a good nurse,
if you lose your temper easily.
Here is the park of the city.
A good place for a walk.
I need a rest over there.
-Keep it for me.
-Yes!
Clean the bench for me.
Okay!
-But...
-Your handkerchief, of course.
I should not told her that
I want to be a nurse!
Sit down, please.
you 've done that before I complained,
that's good.
She complains about everything.
As a nurse, I have to
deal with all kinds of patients.
Stand it!
I'm hungry!
I'm hungry too.
Just a moment, I'll buy you some food.
He 'll catch a cold sleeping here.
You can have it for a while.
A hamburger for you.
Here!
Did you wash your hands?
It's not sanitary.
Go wash them over there.
Yes!
It's cold!
She complained everything,
but reasonable.
Sorry to kept you waiting!
It is alright now!
-Here!
-Thank you!
The milk.
Where is your lunch?
-It's alright!
-Aren 't you hungry?
No, I can buy only one bottle.
And, you give it to me...
Please!
But, you 'll be in trouble...
In what trouble?
You see...
The Merry Jane nursing school...
They have an entrance examination.
Examination?
Without the examination, how to
know that if you 're qualified or not?
It sounds reasonable,
but I never heard of that before.
Extremely difficult examination.
Extremely difficult?
That should be done.
It's related to one 's live.
I'm finished,
I'm not good at examination.
What's the matter?
Nothing,
there 's no examination for me.
Sister Pony and the headmaster
are good friends.
I have a Recommendation
from sister Pony.
That won 't help you!
You have no idea about that school,
it's extremely strict.
Even the daughter of president
was rejected by them.
I see!
What should I do? If they refused me.
I've no money to go back.
You don 't want to eat?
I will take it.
The destiny is in your own hands.
It's an hour already.
No!
I should go home now, where is my muffler?
The muffler... the man over there...
He is gone!
What happened to my muffler?
There 's a man sleep on the bench...
Dim-wit! What's up to you?
I am sorry!
I will have it back for sure.
Where you lived?
Take it to the hospital,
I'll get it later.
As you wish!
Where is that man?
I can find him nowhere.
Compensate her a new muffler.
No! The interview with headmaster.
I forgot everything
while looking for the muffler.
What's matter with you?
I am sorry!
The headmaster is waiting for an hour.
An hour?
She must be mad, What should I do?
This way, please.
At last!
My foot is killing me!
Bestir yourself,
Candy. don 't be useless.
It's okay!
Here we are!
Thank you.
The last course, go!
Come in.
Uh... I'm sorry for being late.
I'm Candice White,
recommended by sister Pony.
Granny!
I am the headmaster here!
Headmaster?
I am dying...
Dim-wit!
Was that Pony teach you?
I am sorry!
-Candice White.
-Yes!
I give you the permission
to enter the Merry Jane nursing school.
How about the examination?
You have already passed.
You mistook me as a patient.
It's a good chance for test
if you are a good nurse or not.
That means...
Kindness is the most important thing
that the nurse must has.
Never discriminate against the old man.
But, your mind is not clear enough.
The nurse must judge accurately.
Yes!
Make things clear!
It's Blanny!
The histories of the patient
of the special ward.
-Come in!
-Excuse me.
It's you...
Do you know her?
-No!
-It's...
We met each other just now.
That's good.
Blanny, a new schoolmate.
Candice White.
Show her the campus.
Candice, Blanny is an elder,
Learn from her.
Yes!
That's horrible!
Is she always so fierce?
That's right!
Her name sounds so lovely,
in fact...
The granny...
Uh...
I was recommended by sister Pony.
She is round and fat,
the headmaster looks so skinny.
Here is the classroom.
It's different from St. Paul academy.
The laboratory.
The library.
So excellent!
This is our room.
We are the room mate! Nice to meet you!
Here is your desk and bed.
Yes!
The uniform is in the closet
next to desk.
This school
is different from other school.
We practice and study in the hospital.
There are lots of patients around,
do everything carefully.
-Excuse me...
-What's the matter?
-Nothing!
-Don 't bother me...
for nothing.
As a room mate, I have a request...
I hate the one who talk too much.
Over!
So efficient.
She 's not a bad guy anyway!
Mind my own business.
It's beautiful.
It's Candy's first step
of becoming a nurse.
I must do my best!
Candy encouraged herself in the heart.