Safex
Jimmy was persuaded by Candy...
to become Mr. Cartwright's inheritor.
It seems that
Candy has found her own direction.
The sound of leaving
is now echo in her heart.
The sob underneath the snow.
-Doctor Lenard.
-Hello Candy.
How is Mr. Cartwright?
I've just fiinished the diagnosis,
he's about to fully recovered.
That's great.
Candy, I've something to deal with you.
With me?
You did a good job, while you were
looking after Mr. Cartwright.
Would you like to help me?
-Help you?
-Yes.
My wife is my nurse,
she has to returns to her family.
Will you help me for one week?
There 's a salary, of course!
A salary for me?
The milk
for the children of Pony's home...
Jimmy works for Mr. Cartwright
every day.
I can't stand by and do nothing.
I have to prove my own ability.
Will you? Candy.
I love to. doctor Lenard.
Have you promised?
I need a confiirm from
sister Pony and sister Lane.
Let me go with you.
Looking after the patients
is a good thing. I agree with that.
Do your best, Candy!
Thank you.
Sister Pony, sister Lane.
Vow!
Candy serve as my nurse and assistant.
Yes, doctor.
The first patient is over there.
How you feel today?
Doctor, It's almost fully recover.
Healthier than a young man.
This is ...
She serves as my assistant from today.
I'm Candy. Nice to meet you.
Let us start the diagnosis.
Candy, the suitcase.
Oh no! I left it on the carriage.
I am sorry, just a moment.
Is that ok? Doctor.
Causing the patient's uneasiness,
I've failed.
You won 't need me anymore.
Really? What a good news.
You can walk like a child. Don't worry!
Don't push yourself too hard these days.
Thank you!
Watch your own body.
Take care of yourself.
Do your best, Miss.
Doctor, welcome back.
Sorry to keep you waitting,
let's start the diagnosis.
Who is that girl?
Put this on, Candy.
Candy, give me a cup of coffee.
Come at once, doctor.
First patient, please.
Please, doctor.
The doctor's work is very hard.
It hurts! a bit lighter.
Doctor, the coffee.
Don 't give me the coffee now!
Give me a hand now!
Yes!
-Harder!
-Yes!
Look! This will hurt you a bit.
Please stand!
-Harder!
-Yes!
OK, It's done.
-Next patient.
-Yes!
Next patient, please!
-Next.
-Yes!
What's the matter with you?
That's it!
Good idea, Candy! Keep on!
It's fiinished at last.
Is it always like this every day?
It's your fiirst day, are you tired?
No!
There are patients in town,
is it fiine with you?
In town?
You need to go out for diagnosis?
We are out of doctors and nurses.
Nurses?
The doctors have very urgent demand
to the nurses.
It's a job with future.
Ajob with future?
You help me a lot.
Do I really help?
Certainly!
You helped that child, didn 't you?
No, I only try to comfort the patients.
That's it.
Candy, may I have that cup of coffee?
But... it's already cold by now.
Doesn't matter, I'll take it.
The street is crowded.
There are diseases of civilization
in the city.
diseases of civilization?
People get more poverty
from the disease of civilization.
It's same when conversely.
He got the disease of richness.
Disease of richness?
Yes, the disease of richness.
What you said is very unkind, doctor.
I'm telling the truth.
You don 't like walking,
taking the car or carriage only.
Enjoy the delicacies that made you fat.
Your heart is now overloaded.
So I ask you to help.
-Join in me the lunch.
-It is unnecessary.
Doctor, do you have a meal today?
WE had not yet, right? Candy.
Let me manage that,
Please make yourself at home.
As you wish!
Candy,
Put the breads into the suitcase.
-Hurry up.
-Yes!
Doctor Lenard,
what would you do with these breads?
Candy!
People get more poverty
from the disease of civilization.
Yes,
and also the disease of richness.
That's right, on the other hand,
it produced the poverty too.
These breads are prescriptions.
Doctor Lenard!
There are presents for everybody.
Doctor Lenard.
Well, Candy, take the breads out.
Everybody, lines up.
Will you give me the present?
That's right, everyone has their share.
-Here.
-Thanks.
Here.
To make you recovery...
I'll do the injection for you today.
-Just a moment, doctor.
-What's the matter?
The injection is expensive,
we have no money.
He can make the money back
after recovery.
Don 't worry about that!
Doctor!
Doctor Lenard.
Make yourself recovery
as soon as possible.
Thank you!
Strange! This is...
The patient's message?
The baby is going to be born,
please! Woody.
The woodcutter, Woody?
It's snowing in the mountain.
Doctor Lenard, what should we do?
I have to go there, of course.
You can 't take the risk,
wait here for me.
Please take me with you.
No way,
It's dangerous in the mountain.
It's same to the doctor.
I am a doctor,
It is my work to rescue people.
I am a nurse,
I have to fiinish my work.
Candy, you will be a good nurse someday.
Yes!
The doctor adheres to his own faith.
Even take his life in his hands.
He is a brave man.
I left the St. Paul academy
to fiind my own direction.
Go through all kinds of difficulty.
I still can't fiind my own direction yet.
I'm sleepy.
Candy, Don 't sleep.
Candy, wake up!
Okay!
Candy, be as a competent nurse.
Candy,
have you heard about Miss Nightingale?
Only the name.
Nightingale is a British women,
with kindness and capability.
It was the war of Crimea.
She went to the front with water.
Both the enemy and British soldier.
She looked after the wounded heartedly.
After the war.
She graduated from the nursing school.
She established the open ward.
Nursing school, open ward.
There 's such a remarkable women
in the world.
Therefore,
you must not surrender to the storm.
Yes!
The road is obstructed. By foot!
Do your best!
It's snowing out there,
will the doctor come?
God!
Doctor.
-Doctor!
-Sorry, I am late.
It's born.
Come! Candy, embrace the new life.
Yes!
Show him to the father.
It's my...
-It is a boy.
-Thank God!
Congratulations! Mr. Woody.
Thank you!
I am so happy, so moved.
People's life is precious.
It's our honor to participate in it.
Very...
Candy, do you try to melt the snow
with those tears?
I just can't help that.
Let's go!
Candy, doctor Lenard have told us
about everything you did.
You 're doing well, Candy!
Doctor Lenard praises you very much.
No, I have lot of things to learn yet.
I told sister Lane once...
You work so hard just like us.
Candy, you told us before that you want
to take care of the children like us.
Sister Pony, sister Lane.
What's the matter? Candy!
I have found my own direction.
I want to be a nurse.
-Nurse?
-Yes!
Candy, It's not easy to be a nurse.
I know! So I need your help!
I have found my own way!
Marry Jane Nurse Training School.
You can part study there.
Candy,
if you really made your decision...
I'll write you a Recommendation
when spring comes...
The headmaster is an old friend of mine.
Marry Jane Nurse Training School.
I can 't wait to be there.
Candy is now expecting for the spring.