Safex
A Good-bye from the carriage.
That wonderful day spent
at the Brighton's house...
turned into a wonderful
memory for Candy and Annie.
Candy and Annie felt almost as if
gentle Mr. Brighton were their father.
The stick is this long,
the meat and vegetables grill together.
Then you eat it?
Yes. Right there on the grass!
It's so tasty!
You don't understand, right?
Uh...
What is it, John?
Is it okay to eat the bones, too?
After you fry the meat and vegetables.
I can't believe this.
Brightons are rich people!
Then, you got to eat all you could?
Of course!
-Incredible!
-So tasty!
What's up with you guys?
You got to eat all you wanted!
I'm jealous!
At least, you have your dreams..
Candy!
Brightons ...
Annie!
Brightons have come to visit us!
Really!
-Mr. Brighton!
-Candy!
Good day!
Good day. You look well, Candy.
I'm sorry that
I leave without telling anyone.
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
Hey guys, this is uncle barbecue.
Candy! You're being rude!
That's okay.
I came today as uncle barbecue.
Clark!
Right away. Sir.
You came to make a barbecue for us?
-That's right.
-Really?
-Candy!
-Wonderful!
Everyone, let's help them!
Uncle, let me help!
Alright then,
take these bricks to the garden.
They're having so much fun!
Thank you very much, Mr. Brighton.
Nothing, barbecue is just an excuse.
No! Actually...
John! It's not done yet!
You'll get yourself burned.
Can I eat five of them?
Of course, eat all you want.
We brought a lot of meat and vegetables.
Here, it's done!
It's hot!
Here, Milly.
Candy.
What is it?
Why did Mr. Brighton come here?
What do you mean?
To make a barbecue for us.
It's not just that.
What else could it be?
Maybe...
Maybe he came to take away one of us.
No way!
No, it must be it.
The barbecue party is over.
You know...
I'm worried just a little bit.
What about?
Like you said,
Mr. Brighton might adopt a daughter,
From one of us.
I don't know what to do.
Candy!
Sister Pony is calling you.
Come on!
Geez, she's gonna preach again.
I wonder what I did wrong today.
See you.
Come in.
What's up with that knock?
I tried to have fun
before you chew me out!
We're not going to scold you today.
Don't tell me
you're going to praise me.
Candy.
What do you think of Mr. Brighton?
He's a rich gentleman. I guess so-so.
What do you mean " so-so" ?
Well, what would you say
if he wish to adopt you?
Mr. Brighton? adopt me?
It's Candy...
Candy! We are serious.
But, why would he want to
adopt a tomboy like me.
That can't be true.
Yes. It's true that
you're difficult to live with...
But he said that
he saw a gentle soul inside of you.
I... I am not gentle.
That's right, he's never seen the
kind of gentleness that you have.
That's exactly what
Mr. Brighton likes about you.
Sister Lane and I of course
will be lonely after you're gone...
It's about time
to start thinking your own happiness.
My own happiness?
Is somebody there?
Annie!
Candy. you should go...
be his daughter...
Annie. You heard everything?
Silly.
You think I'd leave you so easily?
You want your papa and mama,
don't you?
Annie.
We made the promise before.
But...
Annie!
"You must obey what I said!"
Candy!
Thank you.
laid so many eggs today.
There she is!
What's up, everybody?
John. wet the bed again?
Why do you want to know?
It was that bad?
And what if I ate from the barbecue?
You wouldn't eat if you knew, right?
I wouldn't eat for sure!
Hold on, what are you talking about?
You are leaving, Candy!
-John!
-Candy, are you leaving?
Are you really
going to Mr. Brighton's ?
Don't go!
I don't want you to go!
Wait a minute, guys!
Everybody is crying.
My tears are running as well.
You won't be the only one
feeling lonely after Candy is gone.
Ever since she was a baby,
Candy lived with sister Pony and I.
But, we mustn't stand in her way,
even though it brings grief to us.
If you really like her,
you must not cry while she is leaving.
Understand?
Next sunday,
Mr. Brighton will come with his wife.
I hope that
you won't be impolite to them.
Sister Pony?
What is it, Annie?
I was wrong!
I was too selfish,
I should feel happy for Candy!
Annie!
Annie, where are we going?
Come this way!
Candy. teach me how to climb a tree!
To climb a tree...
Annie, aren't you afraid of heights?
No, I'm not.
But...
Why do you suddenly
want to climb a tree?
If I climb this tree,
I could see you off...
As you leave to Mr. Brighton's house.
Annie!
Don't look at me like that!
I'm not leaving.
They won't take me away!
Candy!
Annie, I just thought a good idea.
She's tomboyish,
but she's gentle inside the body.
I've never heard of such a girl.
She has a lot going for it.
I'm sure you will like her.
I can't wait to see.
Here they come! They're early!
I must hurry.
John!
Did you wet again?
Great! Move aside.
I'm sorry.
You did great, John!
Candy always gets mad...
Mr. Brighton, welcome!
We've been expecting you!
Where is Candy?
She must have overslept...
I'd like to take her to my mansion
before the sunset.
Is that so...
Where is she?
That huge-tempered tomboy?
Good morning, Mr. Brighton!
This is my wife, Jane.
A hard working girl.
No, these are my sheets.
Your sheets?
I am happy to go with you,
but this sort of thing happened.
You wet the bed every day?
Yeah, every day since I was a baby.
Darling?
Uh... Mr. Brighton?
Oh, Annie!
The tea is done, please join us inside.
Thank you. You are...
I'm Annie.
Annie? That's a lovely name.
Thank you very much.
Darling, let's go.
Looks good, Annie!
Candy doesn't have that habit,
right? sister Pony
Then, must her little play...
I don't like the way she pulled it off.
Oh, my!
If she staged this bedwetting
because she doesn't like us...
We'll do her a favor
and won't take her with us.
There is no point in taking her
along if she doesn't want that.
Hey, Jane.
We won't take her then,
let her continue living here.
Right? darling
Madam!
Perfect, perfect, absolutely perfect!
Annie, good news!
Candy!
Now we won't have to be separated!
Will you regret for this?
Why would you regret?
I am going to stay with Annie.
Annie?
I wonder if my mama looks like her.
Darling.
That girl looks like a nice one.
What did you talk about?
What happened?
Candy.
The Brightons want adopt me...
as their daughter.
Annie? Stupid.
They first refuse me,
and this time they fixate on you.
If you turn them down,
they will take Milly with them.
No!
Brighton's wife
has specifically asked for me.
Impossible!
Candy!
You don't have to comply.
You can turn them down.
It had been arranged.
Of course,
you will turn them down, right?
I'm sorry, Candy!
Annie. You...
...want to leave?
Forgive me, Candy!
I want my papa and mama.
I want to live with
my gentle papa and mama!
Me too.
But, I won't leave you.
What?
Candy!
Annie, you idiot!
You are not my friend anymore!
I hate you!
I hate Annie. ldiot.
Annie, you idiot! I hate you!
Annie idiot.
Candy.
Annie?
I'm sorry, Candy.
You stood in the rain,
all this time...
I cried together with you.
With me? barefooted?
Things have changed.
We will have to part our ways.
Candy!
We had to apart someday.
Will you forgive me, Candy?
Annie,
you chose your own happiness.
What should I do?
Annie, leave.
Go and be happy.
Candy.
Would you rather throw away
this chance for happiness?
Candy.
Annie.
Candy, take care of Kurin.
Why don't you bring him along?
Brighton's wife hates animals.
I see. There's no trouble to me.
Come, Kurin!
-Incredible!
-She looks like a princess!
Don't get yourself dirty!
You look wonderful, Annie!
Sister Pony, Sister Lane,
thank you for everything!
Be happy, alright?
Thank you.
Take care about Kurin, okay?
He though you'll be back.
Be good, Kurin.
Annie, you'll get your clothes dirty.
Yes!
Everyone.
Annie, banzai!
Candy.
Farewell.
Candy!
Let's go, Annie.
Farewell, Annie!
Farewell!
Farewell, Candy!
Candy!
Annie, with whom she lived
for ten years, is now gone.
Annie's departure broke Candy's heart.
Farewell, Annie.
Farewell, Candy.
Farewell.