Safex
Candy thought this patient
was grandfather William.
And she came across weird Mr. Markba.
But
Candy still treat this weird old man...
as grandfather William
and take care of him.
Where is she?
How to open Mr. Markba's heart?
Mr. Cartwright,
Sister Grey,
The headmadter here Merry Jane,
I met a lot of stubborn people before.
Mr. Markba is different to them.
I am losing my confidence.
Beautiful.
Do not pick up flowers.
No one is watching.
-Mom!
-Yes?
That nurse
pick the flower without permission.
Nurse?
I did not see anything.
She did pluck the flower.
Nurse?
Did she eat it?
He is still sleeping
So peaceful when sleeping
but became so restless when he got up.
Maybe the room is too dull.
Smells good.
Decorate with some flowers.
What is with the flowers?
Mr. Markba, you are up?
I don't like flowers, take them away.
How can someone dislikes flowers?
What are you murmuring?
Sorry!
I am here to say hello to you.
I will look after Mr. Markba for Blanny.
Candy is at your service.
Candy?
Cute name but not the face.
You are right.
What are you laughing at?
Take the flowers away.
What a miserable hospital?
That nurse before
looked like a snow woman.
Snow womanl? Blanny?
Here comes the freckled stupid.
Freckled stupid?
I must stay calm.
What is so funny? Freckled stupid.
I have been tolerating.
Don's waste it,
bring it back to the hostel.
I am thirsty.
Coming.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What is this?
Tea.
I am hungry.
You said you were thirsty.
I changed my mind.
I need to bear with this.
Sorry!
Give me the food.
Yes! Please wait.
Freckled stupid.
Sorry to keep you waiting,
here is the cookies.
You fool, listen...
when I am thirsty and hungry...
bring me the fruits.
Yes!
-Please!
-No I am hungry.
I want some tea.
-Coming.
-I want some juice.
-Please.
-Coffee.
I will get some juice.
Not this one.
-Quick!
-Yes!
I am so tired, what a stubborn old man.
I wonder how Blanny tolerated this.
Candy, shouldn't you be
doing your homework for tomorrow.
I need a rest.
That is so slack of you.
Snow woman! what a description.
Candy, what are you laughing at?
Nothing, I will start preparing.
Blanny,
isn't this the test for wounds?
-Yes!
-It is internal medicine tomorrow.
I am doing this for the future.
What do you mean?
It is going to need a lot of nurse
once the war starts.
War?
It has been pretty peacful.
Do you think it has been peaceful?
Blanny,
where do you think war will start?
-Europe.
-How about England?
Of course!
Annie is in England,
war is going to start soon.
That means
I won't be able to write to Annie.
Candy, Please don't disturb me,
I need to study.
Sorry!
War...
Is Mr. Markba sleeping?
Come to think about it,
I am the same as Mr. Markba.
There is no one that I can talk to.
I miss Annie,
I have so much to talk to Pattie.
Yes! I can talk to Mr. Markba.
None of your business, freckled stupid.
Sorry!
I thought you were
looking for someone to talk to.
So I volunteered.
I don't want to see stupid nurse.
You will be fired you if you keep talking.
Yes! Sorry to disturb you.
Poor Mr. Markba!
He does not want to see anyone.
Headmaster Merry Jane.
Follow me to my room.
What is now? Freckled stupid.
Does headmaster know about it?
Doctor Frank has told me.
Headmaster
Please allow me to look after Mr. Markba.
-No one says you are fired.
-But...
Since you started to look after...
Mr. Markba has been quite pleasing.
-Really?
-It is too early to be happy.
Doctor Frank said that...
It is nice to have someone
so hardowrking like you.
Having you staying by the side
there might be some surprising progress.
It was impossible to convince him.
Is that a compliment?
Think about it yourself.
Keep it up.
Yes!
-Oh! There is a letter for you.
-For me?
I think it was from London.
It was from Annie.
-You can read it.
-Yes.
See you!
-Door closed!
-Oh! no.
Candy, it is nice to receive your letter,
we are relieved.
Everyone is discussing.
Brother, let me see it.
Me too...
Everyone is so eager to see your letter.
I can almost memorize everything.
Since you left...
Archie wears the same fashionable
costume everyday.
Everyone seems alright
after receiving your letter.
Candy, we didn't expect that
you are going to be a nurse.
Nothing has changed in ST. Paul Academy.
Since you left,
it has been so quiet here.
Everyone is lifeless.
The school rules became stricter.
but the point is...
we still seem to hear your laughter
in school.
Looking forward to see you
in the white dress.
Archie Regards.
Candy, it is really excellent of you
to go back to America by yourself.
Pattie!
Few days ago.
Stear and I went to the zoo to see Yuli.
It seemed to be surprised.
Because I have a boyfriend
right next to me.
I want to get married with Stear.
I am sure of that!
Pattie looked so happy.
I am glad that they are happy.
They didn't mention any war
Blanny is having too much thoughts.
Annie's letter,
it is in the same envelope as Pattie's.
Annie.
Archie, Stear and Pattie,
they always come up with good news.
But, my letter is different from theirs.
I have to tell you the truth.
Is Germany starting war?
Is there any news from America?
I heard that Europe is ready for war.
Relax,
it is not as easy as you thought.
I had bad feeling about this before.
It is getting worse lately.
Pattie, wake up.
Pattie.
Please, wake up.
Annie, what is the matter?
Pattie, did you hear gun shots?
Gun shots?
Has the war begin?
Stear told me
that was just night rehearsal.
Why do we need rehearsal?
Is there any war coming?
Annie, Archie and Stear
don't think there will be any war.
Candy, I am scared.
I want to go back to America.
I miss you so much Candy.
I miss you too, Annie.
Mr.Marka?
I sm sorry that I was not by his side.
I...
Calm down now, don't panic.
Now, ready for injection.
Mina
Mina?
Whose name was Mr.Markba calling?
Mina.
How is it going?
Not good, tonight will be crucial.
Tonight will be crucial?
Look, pulse check every ten minutes.
Keep me informed.
Doctor, please save Mr. Markba.
Candy!
Mina, come and see me.
Mr.Markba.
Mina, I want to see you.
How is the situation?
-Still in a coma.
-Yeah?
I want to go back to the hostel.
Ok, go ahead.
-You want to looking for Mina?
-Yes!
Maybe his daughter or granddaughter.
But do you know where are they?
Mr.Markba's family
should know about it.
-Headmaster Merry Jane.
-Yes?
Whom does the patient want to see,
is nothing to do with the nurse.
Blanny!
Candy,
the most important thing now is...
to save Mr.Markba.
Blanny is right.
Headmaster.
But,
that is normally what nurse assumes.
You are still not qualified as nurses.
So I can go?
I allow you to take hospital's cart.
Thank you.
Headmaster!
You need to remember that doctor
and medicine are not the only cure.
Please hurry!
God!
I pray for Mr.Markba's safety
before he finds Mina.
Get ready for intraarterial injection.
Mr.Markba has his family to remember,
he is not lonely.
I wish Mina is right here.
Seems to be the Adley's in Lakewood.
It is so remoted.
Does Mr.Markba really live here?
Anybody home?
Looks like no one is home.
What is the matter at this time?
Are you Ms.Mina?
Mina?
Sorry, Is Mina home?
Yes, What is the matter?
I am a nurse from Joseph Hospital,
I come to pick up Ms.Mina.
-Mina?
-Yes!
Mr.Markba calls out Mina's name.
-Master?
-Yes.
He does not seem too good
I want them to meet each other.
She is sleeping in the yard,
go see her yourself.
Please... the yard?
The yard... here?
Strange! I can only see a dog sleeping.
Do u know Mina?
Do you know where is Ms.Mina?
Ms.Mina?
This dog... No!
Mina.
Are you Mina?
No, Mina!
The Mina
that Mr.Markba was talking about.
Turns out to be this big dog.
Candy is amazed!