Safex
Without his memory back,
Mr.Albert left with no trace.
Candy is very worried about this.
Before the memory is back,
the two people had a deal
not to part again.
A little castle in the city.
What kind of room do you want?
A quiet one.
It's ok if it's a little noisy,
as long as it's cheap.
The room doesn't have to be big.
No way!
But...
I would like to rent a place
like this, too.
How can you treat your customer
like this?
What kind of customer are you?
Have no money
but want to rent a good house.
Welcome.
Would you like to rent a house?
Please have a seat.
No money, no service.
What kind of attitude is this?
Candy.
Must be turned down again.
We will find one today.
Chicago is a big city.
Don't worry, Mr.Albert.
I will find a house.
For rent.
It's so quiet here.
-But...
-Wait for me.
It's been empty for a while,
it's a little dirty.
Excuse me...
You don't like it?
You brought me here...
Does that mean
I can rent the house from you?
You don't want to?
I want to.
This is the kitchen.
And the bathroom.
The bedroom is here.
There is one more room there.
Great!
Are you happy with this place?
Yes.
But, as I said before...
The rent is settled.
You won't be able to pay any extra.
Thank you!
Mr.Albert.
We got the house!
You are not living alone?
I'll live with him.
-Are you siblings?
-We are friends.
Friends? You...
He is my patient.
A patient causes too much trouble.
No.He just lost his memory.
He can't even remember
his own name.
I am so envious of him.
Mr. Thomas.
I wish I could forget about the past,
too.
Including you wanted to
rent the house
Aren't you letting me?
You are not siblings,
and not couples.
How embarrassing!
You misunderstood,
Mr.Albert and I...
Go back.
I was having sympathy
with your situation.
Tired, Candy?
No. You are the one to be tired.
You are not recovered yet.
No, you made me feel better.
Especially the mood.
Are you hungry, Mr.Albert?
You should be back to the hospital.
I have to get you settled first.
It's strange.
What is it?
I have been thinking...
Wandering in the streets
would make most people anxious.
But I feel optimistic.
Maybe you are right.
I am used to living outside,
under the stars.
Right, Mr.Albert.
You like the nature and animals.
Often spend the night outside.
Let's spend the night
in the park tonight.
No, Candy!
Looking at the stars in the sky,
may help you remember something.
Gentleman.
Dating with the lady?
Stop! He is my patient.
Patient?
Are you joking with me?
Take out your money!
Too bad, I have nothing.
Bastard!
Damn!
So great!
I remember when Mr.Albert
was in London...
Terry was drunk and
got into trouble.
Mr.Albert saved him once.
Mr.Albert,
do you remember Terry?
Terry.
Yes, Terry.
Remember anything?
Run!
Don't go!
He is remembering something!
Are you kidding?
I will give you something in return.
Let's run!
Terry.
Yes!
Terry often visited you in the zoo.
No, I can't remember anything.
Take it easy, Mr.Albert.
Candy.
Stear, Archie.
We have been looking for you.
We found a good house, Candy!
Really?
Come, get on!
Thanks.
We're here.
Second floor.
Archie, here...
The landlord turned you down?
We then found this house.
Mr. Thomas.
He lost his memory in Italy.
I couldn't say no to you.
My daughter married an Italian.
I am worried about the war
in Europe.
Your daughter...
Hope she will be fine and safe.
Here is the key.
Thank you, Mr. Thomas.
Archie, is it alright?
Are all the luggages here?
Can your car load a lot?
Brother would have had problem
carrying them anyway.
What are you talking about,
Archie?
Candy,
Dr. Reknapp is looking for you.
Thanks.
You are moving out of the dormitory?
Yes, the Senior Nurse has agreed.
Are you moving in with patient
from Room Zero?
You want to take care of him,
that's your freedom.
But it's a different matter
if you live with him.
It might distract other nurses.
If I tell the truth...
He won't let me take crae of
Mr.Albert.
Answer me, Candy!
We are not living together.
I lied to the doctor.
because I want Mr.Albert
to be recovered.
Welcome, Candy.
It's all cleaned up.
Thank you for doing this.
It looks like a different house.
Annie and Archie helped a lot.
Thank you, Annie!
You're welcome.
Candy, leave it to the guys.
Let's go prepare for the dinner.
Ok, watch me do the show.
Candy, you are cooking?
Don't worry,
I have the medicine ready.
You are really a nurse.
Tying the vegetable is harder than
wrapping a bandage.
You are trying too hard.
I'll go boil the water.
Candy.
Maybe I am too nosy.
This thing,
you'd better not tell Terry.
Why?
If I were Terry,
I would be upset.
Because
I live with Mr.Albert?
Mr. Thomas and Dr. Reknapp
also think so.
People might take it wrong easily.
Thank you for your advice,
Annie.
Then, Terry...
I don't want to lie to him.
Candy.
Telling the truth is the only way
to avoid misunderstanding.
Besides, I don't want to
hide anything from Terry.
Yes, you are right.
I am too nosy.
It's good that you reminded me,
otherwise I'd tried to
hide this thing from Terry.
Oh! No!
Miss Susana.
Nice to see you.
You come to see Terry?
He is not up yet.
Let me wake him up.
No, Aunt, I'll go wake him up.
Alright, please give this letter to him.
Candy White.
That woman in Chicago.
The door is not locked.
Good morning, Terry.
Susana, what are you here for?
We can go to the rehearsal together.
Susana,
I am not in kindergarten.
Terry.
You don't have to pick me up,
I can go by myself.
You go first.
Terry.
If the person standing here was her...
your attitude
would be completely different.
I am going first.
I am back.
Welcome.
I'll make dinner right now.
There was an emergency patient...
Mr.Albert, this...
I didn't have anything to do,
so I tried to cook something.
And the dishes all got done.
You always do things alone.
When you were cooking,
did you remember anything?
It's ok, Mr.Albert.
The detail things in daily life
can help you with your memory.
I feel the puzzle in my heart
is gradually getting away.
Don't you have this kind of feeling
in the hospital?
Let's eat! Go wash your hands first.
Ok.
Mr.Albert.
There is no reply of the letter.
There isn't?
Candy,
are you waiting for Terry's letter?
Terry?
You remember Terry?
No.
You often mention this name.
I...
The poster for the show this time.
So pretty.
There is a month before the show.
Everyone,
try your best to complete the show.
Go!Terry!
Terry.
I play Romeo.
What would Candy think about that?
He must been
still thinking about that woman.
The practice starts at one o'clock
in the afternoon.
I want to give Candy a ticket.
And the train ticket to New York.
One way. I don't want her to go back.
Susana.
Terry, the rehearsal you just did...
I think the time for staring
with tender and love should be longer.
You came to see me for this?
No.
There must be something else.
I wanted to tear it off.
Tear it off?
But,
I can not bear to see you sad.
Take it back.
This is from Candy.
Sorry.
Susana.
-Thank you for doing this.
-Good-bye.
Mr.Albert.
Candy.
Pretend you don't know me.
Sorry for the trouble I caused, Candy.
Your letter is here.
I want to give you a surprise.
Is it from Terry?
Finish it in the park before you go home.
Thank you, Mr.Albert.
Candy, what's wrong with you?
I am your boyfriend.
And you live with Mr.Albert.
I can't forgive you
no matter what the reason is.
Terry.
I am just kidding!
Of course, it's not ok
if the person is someone else.
But it's Mr.Albert!
Of course I am fine with it.
Naughty Terry!
You are now...
must be tired from taking care of
Mr.Albert without his memory.
If it's ok,
I would like to
share the responsibility with you.
The show is going to start soon,
so I can't leave.
Hope you can come to see me in the show.
Terry is the main actor.
He invited me to go to Broadway.
I am looking forward to seeing
the Romeo Terry will be playing!
Mr.Albert will be happy for me.
Any guest?
Vice principal.
Candy, did you lie to me?
Sorry.
But, Mr.Albert is getting well.
Good.
From now on,
your job is to take care of him.
My job...
I am the administrator of the hospital.
Your behavor, I can't just sit by.
Vice principal, Mr.Albert is a patient.
From now on,
you don't have to come to the hospital.
If you move back to the dormitory,
I will reconsider it.
Vice principal.
Let's go!
Please wait!
Wait, Vice principal.
The carrige is going away.
Candy is struggling.
She can't leave Mr.Albert here,
and return to the hospital.
In order not to make Mr.Albert worried.
Candy decided to pretend
that she is still happy.