Safex
Candy couldn't root for Anthony
who was in the rodeo competition
Not caring whether
Anthony would win or lose...
Candy only prayed that
he wouldn't get hurt
And then, Anthony won
The first date.
Anthony! Do your best!
Go, Don't give up.
Kurin! Sorry to woke you up!
I had a dream that I was
at the rodeo.
What happened!?
Fire!
Mr. Stear, are you okay?
Stear!
What happened, Stear?
Today's experiment... failed.
Just what kind of experiment
was that?
Fireworks
Fireworks!?
Why were you making those
things during the night?!
Anthony won in the rodeo,
I wanted to make fireworks for him.
Stear, you did that for a friend...
You're not going to
hold a celebration!
Forget about the rodeo,
like it never happened!
But aunt, haven't you rooted for
Anthony as well?
I played along
with the circumstances.
Anyway...
The embarrassing rodeo competition!
It's the only time
that an Adley participated in.
Why should I be ashamed
of the rodeo?
Anthony!
Are you talking back to me?!
Who is it?
It sounds like a knock.
Come in!
Please enter!
Who is it, so late at night?
Anthony!
Welcome!
Are you alright?
You mustn't enter the house!
The explosion must have scared it
away and it came running here.
Anthony
why is this thing in the house?
It's a prize from the rodeo
We hid it from you since we
were embarrassed...
You shouldn't have
made that explosion!
Stop making fun of me!
The Adley property
is not a farm!
Get rid of it!
You understand me?
I didn't ask you for an opinion!
Don't come close!
Stop!
Candy! Miss Candy!
What are you doing, Huck?
Madam told me to get rid of this calf
but...
I hate animals and...
Come on, you're a good boy.
Huck, I'll take it somewhere
instead of you
Miss, you will...?
Let's go!
Miss Candy
be sure to get rid of it!
You don't need to worry
I'll take you to Tom's herd
where you'll be okay.
Brother, look at this
Candy?
Dressed like a hillbily again
She's an embarrassment
to the Adleys
Go to the Adley's .
-Candy took the calf...?
-That's right, grand aunt!
I was so embarrased that I hid
my face all the way till I got here!
Me too!
Damn it, this Candy...
If townspeople see her like that...
This isn't good.
Tom is nowhere to be found.
They must have went on to
some other place...
Hey, Candy!
Anthony!
You still haven't found anyone
to give this calf to?
No.
I haven't found any good places...
I see
It would probably get dark by the
time you'd reach Tom's herd...
Aren't there other ways?
I guess we'll have to find a
new home for you by evening
What's the matter?
We're worrying so much about you!
Candy
Let's go to the town together
and find a new home for this calf.
Let's do that!
Would you like this calf?
You'd really give it to me, miss?
I'd be glad to take it!
-Oh, no!
-It's a butcher shop!
Wait, mister! Give it back!
Hey! You promised
haven't you!
Hear! merry-go-round!
One round and
your dreams will come true
Two rounds and
your love will blossom!
Come, you two.
By the way, Mister
would you like to take this calf?
What, a calf?
You must be kidding!
I do my business with horses
I have no need for cows!
Candy!
Mr. Steve!
So you came to town
looking for Tom!
I'll take this calf to him for you!
Thank you!
Thank you for your help.
Send my regards to Tom.
Hold on there!
I can't just take this calf
from your hands for nothing
I'll pay you for it
But we don't really need money...
That's right, Mr. Steve!
Candy, this calf may be a nuisance
to a rich lady like you
But it's a valuable asset to me.
I won't take the calf
unless you take the money.
What should we do, Candy?
I'll take the compensation!
I see. It's a deal then!
Thank you!
Say " moo" to everybody for us!
That's right!
You'll make many friends
at the farm!
See you again!
Thank you!
Goodbye, little calf!
Goodbye!
We earned money!
Candy, do you know
what will you spend it for?
-I've never spent any money!
-Me too!
I got everything I wanted
directly from aunt.
I was too poor
while you were too rich!
Neither one of us
ever spent any money...
Candy, let's spend it together!
Want to buy something?
No, let's just spend it!
How can you spend it
unless you buy something?
We could go there!
That's right!
I never rode on it!
Me neither!
Mister?
If it's about the calf, I'm busy.
We'd like to ride!
Really? I'll let you ride longer!
Because you're my
first customers today!
Here.
Wish for something!
One round and
your dreams will come true
Two rounds and
your love will blossom!
Two rounds!
Okay! The flower of love!
He meant...
if the children in Pony's home
got to ride on this wooden horse
I wonder
how happy they would be...
Candy's heart was overwhelmed
Sister Pony, Sister Lane...
Is it okay to be this happy?
Anthony was leading the calf
together with Candy?!
Townspeople have seen them
walking together
And what are they doing now?
I've sent a servant to the town
and he'll bring them back
Find them and bring them back
as soon as possible!
I understand
Ever since Candy arrived...
the Adley family
has become such a mess...
Madam Elroy will yell at me
if I don't find them soon...
Anthony's horse!
They must be close by!
Mr. Anthony! Miss Candy!
Anthony, I think the situation
is getting hairy...
I won't let us get caught!
We still have some money left!
Mr. Anthony! Miss Candy!
He saw us!
Let's hide in that diner!
Miss Candy! Mr. Anthony!
He went by.
Hey, you two!
You can't play hide and seek in here!
We're not playing!
Are you customers?
Yeah...
If you're customers...
then behave and get on
the other side of the counter!
He didn't have to point like that...
You said something?
No, he was talking to me.
Anthony, I'm hungry.
Uh... aren't there any chairs?
What? Chairs?
Anthony, in this place
people eat standing up.
Two, please!
I've never eaten while standing!
There!
-Uh...
-Is there a problem?
Can I have a knife and a fork?
What?
Hey, runt
are you making fun of me?
Is that a way to treat customers?
-Wanna piece of this?
-Please stop!
He's never eaten a hot dog before!
Huh? So he's not an American?
It's not that...
Anthony
you eat these with your hands.
With my hands?
It's tasty!
Of course! My hot dogs
are best in America!
It's good! I've never eaten
something this good!
What a weird customer...
I think I've seen you somewhere...
Mister, can I have another one?
That's right! You're that...
He's not!
Candy!
Mister, don't tell we're here!
Could you spare a moment?
a 13 years old girl,
and a 16 years old boy,
have you seen them?
A boy and a girl, huh...
I don't know...
I see. Anyway, thank you!
Thank you, mister!
Come on! I protected you
because you are brave!
Everyone, it's the guy
who won in the rodeo!
Really?
Now, eat this! It's on the house!
But we'd like to pay for it...
-Come on, it's okay!
-The drinks are on me!
You're the winner, after all!
I'm so full.
Yeah... but
we haven't spent anything.
I don't think we'll be able to
spend it before the day is over...
No, we'll spend it for sure!
It's difficult to spend money
when you don't buy anything...
What is that?
It's a fortune teller
We can spend money there without
getting any goods in return!
You've been through
many painful moments...
Not too many!
But eventually
you'll become happy.
Really?
I'm absolutely sure.
That's great!
Anthony, it's your turn now!
I don't care about this...
-We still have some money left!
-I see!
Read my fortune, then!
Is something wrong?
I'll have to do this again.
This is impossible!
What's the matter?
Is something bad about to happen?
Please tell us.
I'm not afraid of anything.
Please, go home now
without asking anything.
That's stupid.
Candy, do you believe in
such fortune telling?
But...
I'm not the old Anthony anymore
Whatever happens
I'm not going to give up
That's right...
Where do you want to go now?
-Somewhere high!
-Somewhere high?
Just like when I was in Pony's home...
Whenever something bad happened
I would climbed the big old tree...
Allow the wind to take away
all unpleasant things...
Okay, let's go!
Won't we get in trouble for this?
It's okay!
I can see everything!
This is the highest building
in all of Lakewood
This wind...
It's taking away
all unpleasant things
Candy!
There's still some money left?
Exactly two pieces.
Take one of them
as a memento of this day
-Now, take one
-Yes
A memento of this day...
-Anthony, I understand!
-What?
The bad thing...
it was this bell!
That's right! It really is bad!
There's somebody up there!
-Mr. Anthony!
-Miss Candy is together with him!
-Mister Anthony!
-Miss Candy!
More bad things
seem to be happening!
Really!
Aunt is going to be mad...
Are you afraid?
Not at all! I feel refreshed!
Me too.
We had so much fun today
That's right. I've never had
as much fun as I had today.
That's right
Candy was happy
She managed to spend a wonderful
day with her beloved Anthony.
However...
that black trump card instilled ominous
feelings in the corner of Candy's heart.