Safex
Candy and Terry finally reunioned.
Terry is still not able to reveal
the accident of Suzanna.
Once in a while
he would appear to be uneasy.
The openning bell
that touched the heart.
Mr.Albert then lived with me.
Although he doesn't remember you,
he wants to meet you in person.
We're here!
It's the hotel you're staying at.
What a luxury hotel!
Candy, I'm going to
prepare for the final rehearsal.
Good luck, Terry!
Let's chat after the show tomorrow.
Bye!
Terry,
I will be cheering for you
in the audience tomorow.
Thank you.
I come to Broadway,
walking in the street with Terry.
I see him and review the past
with him.
Terry,
sooner or later we will reunion.
It really came true, but...
Terry appeared to be uneasy
once in a while.
Is it because of the show tomorrow?
It must be. It is the first time
he plays the main character.
Alright, the rehearsal is finished.
Good job, everyone!
Good luck tomorrow!
Terry, you seemed to be distracted
in the rehearsal today.
Will you be alright tomorrow?
Distracted? No, I wasn't.
Really? You seem to be bothered
by something.
Is anything bothering you?
No, nothing.
Don't take it seriously.
Terry, I think so, too.
Terry, take things as they come.
Just focus on playing your role well.
Rest well tonight.
Yes.
Candy will eventually find out
the thing about Suzanna.
I won't be able to hide this thing
from her forever.
When it happens, Candy will...
No, I have to concerntrate.
I have to concerntrate on my play.
Candy came all the way
from Chicago.
I have to present the best show
for her.
Terry should be home by now.
For the best performance tomorrow,
you need to rest well.
I really want to cook breakfast
for you.
Coffee, ham, salad, toast.
Send you to the door,
wish you luck for the performance.
When will this dream come true?
It was a long trip,
she must be in sleep now.
Ok, I have to do my best tomorrow!
Good night, Candy.
Only those who never suffer
from painful experience
would tease the scars
in others'hearts.
Wait a moment!
Why is there a gleam from the window?
There is the east.
Juliet is the sun.
Rise! The bright and charming sun.
Lighten the darkness of the night.
You didn't come to visit today.
Suzanna was very upset,
she was expecting you.
Suzanna is smiling every day.
Thank you for coming to see her
every day.
Please don't abandon her.
I am leaving first.
Suzanna, I am late.
Terry, I thought
you were not coming today.
You met her?
Is she still that active?
Candy is so lucky.
Moving around freely,
and getting your hugs.
She will go to the
openning show tomorrow, right?
Good luck, Terry!
Stop the car!
Wait!
I want to give the flowers to Terry.
Great!
Terry is the big star on the poster.
Eleanor Baker.
The hair was dyed black
on purpose...
But it's really Terry's mother.
Eleanor Baker.
She is so low-keyed.
She must care for Terry very much.
Isn't this Candy?
Candy, why are you here?
Don't try to sneak in.
Thanks for caring,
but I have a ticket.
Who gave you the ticket?
Terry gave it to me.
Your face didn't even blush
when you lied.
Still that harsh.
I am not lying.
The ticket is here.
It is really the ticket.
You must have found it on the street.
That's right. This kind of people...
tear it off!
Neil
That's too much!
Why? Neil.
Let me go!
Let me teach you a lesson.
Stop!
-Candy
-What?
Three people bully one.
Mind your own business.
Want me to give you a fist?
Don't bully the small and weak.
Let go!
This woman asked for it.
A nonsense guy.
Let me beat you down with a fist.
How could you hit a woman?
It's not your business.
Bitch!
Why? Neil.
You have no right to call
Master's name.
Right.
Wait a second.
Invalid ticket.
Please.
Don't waste your time.
Besides,
there is no area number on it.
Get out.
The area number is on another half
of the ticket.
Take out the other half.
That car...
How many times
do you want me to say it?
I 'll say it again.
Invalid ticket.
I'll buy another ticket, is it ok?
Of when?
Of course today.
Unfortunately,
today's tickets are sold out.
How can I see Terry then?
Terry? The main actor?
Right. I am his friend.
No, you are not going to get in
by fooling me.
It's true.
The ticket was given by Terry.
You can ask him about that.
The actors are not allowed
to see any visitors before the show.
Understand?
Right! I have an idea.
Excuse me.
Who are you? No visit here.
I have flowers for Terry.
Alright, give it to me.
Can I see Terry?
Will he see you?
Hold on, let me go ask.
My name is Candy.
Got it.
Great! I can get in.
Please.
Terry, flowers from a fan.
Thanks.
She wants to see you,
what should we do?
It's not a good time now.
Refuse her.
Ok.
No? How could it be possible?
I am sorry. You have to wait
till the show is finished.
Alright. Where are the seats
for the audience?
Go straight ahead...
Hold on.
You entered from the back door?
Yes.
Do you have a ticket?
Let me see.
I...
Want to sneak in
with a bouquet of flowers?
-It's not that.
-Get out now.
Please let me explain.
Let me see Terry,
then things will be clear.
It's not possible, please go out.
Wait a second.
Candy, aren't you Candy?
Karen.
You know her?
Let me handle it.
Candy, follow me.
So you came here...
You couldn't find Terry.
Why not coming to me?
We only met once.
I was not sure
if you remembered me.
I remember very clearly.
Thank you for solving the problem
for me.
Later, if anyone bothers you.
My signed picture can save you.
My friend, Candy.
Thank you.
Candy, enjoy our show.
I will cooperate with Terry.
Sorry you still can't meet Terry.
You can play Juliet?
That's great!
Are you teasing me?
No, I didn't mean that.
Only Suzanna can play this role?
Of course not.
Even a backup is ok, too.
I will do better than Suzanna.
For the role Juliet.
Karen Clairs
will not let you down.
Why is she angry?
Suzanna is her competitor.
Maybe that's why.
Karen took over Suzanna's role.
In another word,
Suzanna was going to play Juliet.
But Karen replaced Suzanna.
What's going on?
What happened to Suzanna?
I don't understand.
How did you sneak in?
I did not sneak in.
I walked in from the front door.
Liar.
You were making a scene
at the entrance. Everyone saw that.
Who was making a scene?
It was you.
How would Brother make a scene?
How could Candy say that?
Elisa, forget it, let's go.
Candy, I'll go find a staff.
Go ahead. I have this.
The signature of Karen Clairs.
Where did you steal this?
Look at the signature on it.
My friend, Candy.
Karen and I are old friends.
She gave me this at the backstage.
Good-bye.
Arrogant.
It's very rare to
get such a positive review.
New man Terry will play Romeo.
It's worth expecting.
I am expecting it, too.
Poor Suzanna.
She got hurt when she was
trying to save Terry.
It wasn't easy for her
to get this role Juliet.
Terry, watch out!
Only those who never
suffer from painful experience
would tease the scars
in others'hearts.
Wait.
Why is there a gleam
from the window?
There is the east.
Juliet is the sun.
Rise! The bright and charming sun.
Brighten the darkness of the night.
I had no idea that,
Suzanna got hurt from
trying to save Terry.
Terry kept a secret from me.
Terry went to see her every day.
She got hurt because of you.
You must be blaming yourself.
Could it be possible that
the uneasy look on his face...
Terry, how did it happen?
Why did you keep a secret from me?
Terry.
The last scene.
Terry did a good job.
A rising star.
Karen also did a good job.
If Suzanna was here...
she might do better.
Suzanna was taking care of Terry
when he had a fever.
I heard that
Terry would marry her.
Suzanna loves you,
sees you as someone
who can depend on for life.
Terry, please stay by her forever.
Company her all your life.
Terry, don't keep it in mind.
I...
Suzanna is going to marry Terry?
That's so mean!
No matter how much she loves Terry,
she shouldn't have done this.
This is not love.
I want to see Suzanna.
Excuse me...
It's you again.
Which hospita
is Suzanna staying in?
You are going to visit her?
It may be...
Jacob Hospital.
Thanks.
The break is over.
But...
But, I am not in the mood anymore.
Candy couldn't help
walking towards Suzanna's hospital.