Safex
Jim wanted to be an soldier
After Candy's persuade,
he decided to stay and take care of the fıeld.
Candy left Boni's home.
The troublesome love
I haven't seen Chicargo's street for a long time.
So many people.
I want one too.
Ok,thank you.
What's taste?
I like chocolate.
Ok.
Here,Chocolate.
Thank you.
Delicious.
It's dangerous to drive so fast.
Strike.
How can he drive like this.
He's too bad.
No one wants to help him.
Are you ok?
Nil.
Candy.
Everyone's all right. Back.
Wounds.
If you worry about it
go to the hospital tomorrow.
Na.
None of your business.
Ok. I must go now.
Nothing changed a bit. So he had the accident.
This is the second time she saved me.
Candy,I thought I hate her.
But now,I pay attention to her
I always think about her.
Come to buy it,it's cheap.
The orange. Come from California.
It seems delicious. Buy some for Arupate.
Please buy some.
Perhas the Vitam C can make
the brain move quickly.
Delicious.
Give me two
Ok,thank you.
But we sell five one time,please buy five.
Madam?
Your husband will be happy too.
I am not madam.
Come,come.
That's impolite. Call such a young lady madam.
Ah.
Help me.
Ha,ha,ha.
The people here all call the woman as madame.
Oh.
If you said you will come back earlier
I will cook more food.
This is enough.I will do the left.
Mr. Arupate,help me for the dishes.
En.
The sound of the dishes attacks me.
The fire is too big.
I can't do it.
Only cream with the vagetable?
I will do it. Candy,go to set the dishes.
It seems I can't be a good wife.
No,Candy,you will be a very good wife.
You can be so sweet to me.
I think that's enough.
Ha,ha,ha. Pupy...
The big hospital is different.
The clinic in the hill can't compare with it.
Candy,you have guest.
Guest?
He's in the guest room.
Guest room? Thank you.
Who?
It's me.
Hai.
Guest is Nil?
Please see me.
See you?
Cure.
Don't use the word like that.
If you come to see the doctor
can't stay in the guest room.
Please go to the front desk.
Wait,Candy.
What others?
I am ok now.
What else do you want?
I want to date with you.
Date?
Yes,go to change now.
What do you think?
Nothing. I want to date with you.
You want to thank me for saving you?
If so,it doesn't matter.
You go to change first.
I refuse it.
What?
Because I am working now.
I have talked to the dean.
You said you are from Aldrey's.
That's nothing.
It's something to me.
If you think you can solve everything just say
you are from Aldrey's,that's wrong.
Though I don't know what the dean say to you,
I have my patient,sorry.
Candy.
He wants to date with me,what does he think?
That's impolite.
How can she refuse me?
I don't want to quit,I will date you.
What can I use?
I have a friend who's worry about it.
Because I have no experience.
You should use your gentle words.
Gentle words...
Listen,don't say to anyone else.
Yes.
It's brother.
Where does he go with the roses?
You go back first.
See you.
See you. See you tomorrow.
Nil?
Candy.
Is this for me?
En.
Brother,he... what does he want?
As a change,you should date with me.
Don't say you're on duty now.
Are you happy?
Ha,ha,ha.
Of course,I can't be happy.
Candy.
You take my flower and reuse me,what do you want?
If so,give it back to you.
I don't want to date with you.
Good bye.
Brother is so bad looking.
Too bad.
She,she...
How can I love such a girl?
That's that.
She fools me.
Why should I date with Nil?
I will spit while imagine it.
It's terrible.
I can't stand it.
I will not sell it to you.
Please give me five.
Welcome.
Hurry,you will trouble the customer. Go back.
Please,just for this time.
Can anyone sell wisky to me?
Go out.
Please.
No,money,money.
Wait,you can't throw
her out just for she has no money.
Oh,what did you say?
Forget it,just a whisky. I will buy it.
I don't want ice cream any more.
Wait,miss.
I can't say such words.
How much?
I know,I know.
Only this time.
Mr. Maqin?
Thank you.
Is he a really doctor?
Doctor Maqin.
Wait.
Ha,ha,ha.
Thank you,Candy.
Doctor,what's the one like.
The life needs acting.
No medicine to cure him.
Just because the doctor is like
this,so no one come here.
There are so many people.
Just always forget to collect the money.
So,I only go to cure Mr. Arupate.
HA,ha,ha.
That's all right.
How abut Mr. Arupate?
For he don't want to say anything to me.
For he doesn't know what to say?
For recovering the memory
I will go to see you at the first time.
Ha,ha,ha.
Here,this is for you.
Ah,wisdom ring.
For you ran out as you are very unhappy.
This is best when you're angry.
Thank you,doctor.
Good bye.
The wisdom ring is really hard.
That's like this. No.
This sound is...
Yes.
Where is the prince in the hill?
Neally ten years.
But I can remember it clearly.
Little thing,you are lovely as you laughed.
You and Antoni are like princes.
I broke up with Deli.
With Deli.
You should forget it.
Candy.
Brother.
Brother
I find you for a long time. You have guest.
Guest?
Dalman.
Who's she?
My friend.
Brother sees she in the party.
She said she wants to make friends with brother.
She's the daughter of the rich man.
If so,she can dry Candy out of Chicargo.
Do you have the plan?
Yes,Brother wants to do so.
En.
What's the plan?
I am angry because we have no detail.
Alo brought Stiya from the battle.
Even to ask for the Gorge
because the old lord is there.
The old lord is not healthy.
George has not good face color.
He seems very old.
If the big old lord die
then Mrs. Alo is the biggest.
Then,we can dry Candy out.
I will pray it.
Pray Lord William to die?
Yes,I can't stand Candy laugh all day here.
If only she change another place.
Ah.
Brother.
You will be Daisy's friend. Do you know?
Ah.
Dalman. Such bore woman.
Dalman,do you see my brother?
No,not yet.
I thought he comes here earlier.
Then,Nil said he's not comfortable.
Brother,he...
Brother,brother.
Brother.
Run away. I want he to forget Candy.
Ah,this is...
Candy.
This is Candy's.
Brother is so good to Candy.
Can't be forgive.
Nil to Candy.
No...
Mother,no...
It must be Candy lure brother.
She gave this to brother.
Handkerchief.
So I am sure brother loves her.
What's this?
Soon,brother will say he wants to get married.
Can't be forgive. I will not allow it.
Yes,I will not agree.
Mother,if let Candy stay in Chicargo
there must be problem.
Brother must be cheated by Candy.
Poor brother.
Ilasha,ask the driver to prepare to go out.
Now,Ilasha.
Ok,mother.
Wait,I will go too.
No,this is the our talk,go.
That's over,Candy.
What did you say?
He he,nothing.
Are you Mrs. Rogan?
What's wrong with you?
No,I came here for Candy.
Candy?
Please fire her now.
Fire,what did she do?
Don't ask too much.
No reason,it's really hard for me...
Please remind your own position.
Er?
If I say to my husband,
Then,it's easy to stop to stop your hospital.
Don't destroy yourself because of Candy.
Why do you hate her so much.
She troubles me.
Ah.
Later,the boy and the girl go to a little room,
it's made by bread,and the roof is biscket.
Candy,doctor Rainat are looking for you.
Ok.
Wait,I will be back soon.
Come in.
What do you want?
Candy.
I can only let you stay here till today.
Er?
What's wrong?
Though I feel pity for you,
I have received the inform to fire you.
Candy feels very bad.
She doesn't remember
she did anything should be fired.
She was attacked
evey it's hard for her to stand up.