Safex
A new day in the old capital.
Cheers!
-Congratulations, Captain.
-Thank you.
Congratulations on your last journey.
Thank you, Candy.
Thank you, everyone!
I will remember this happiness
for a very long time!
Cheers!
What a fog!
It's really cold on the deck.
And the fog is getting denser.
I wonder if Stear and Archie are
waiting for me.
If I'll be together with those two
any place could be wonderful.
Somebody is over there.
Anthony?
On the deck of a ship
heading to London
Candy was suddenly
rendered speechless.
He looks...
Anthony...
It looks just like him from the back.
Impossible...!
Anthony!
This can't be for real.
His hair isn't blond.
And he's taller than Anthony.
He's crying?
Is somebody there?
Yes... I'm sorry
I was going to say something
but you seemed too sad...
Sad? That's a good one!
Like I was being sad!
He really looked as if he was crying.
Maybe I was mistaken.
No, I wasn't .
I'm sure he was crying.
Maybe you were daydreaming
Miss freckles?
Hey, aren't you a gorgeous one?
You probably have a face buried
underneath all these freckles!
That's so sad!
Just for your information
I happen to like these freckles!
So that's the reason you have
a whole collection of them.
Yes, and I want to have
even more of them!
Oh boy...
Are you jealous because
you don't have any freckles?
In that case, are you proud
of that flat nose, too?
Of course!
Miss Candy?
Is Miss Candy over there?
-Bye, Lady freckles!
-What's up with that!?
Miss Candy, you're going to
catch a cold if you stay here.
Say, George, who was he?
Is Mr. Grandchester
an acquaintance of yours?
So his name is Grandchester...
Yes. He's an English nobleman.
Nobleman? No way...
Do you have any business with him?
No. I thought he looked a bit
like Anthony from behind.
Like Mr. Anthony?
But it turned out that
he's nothing like Anthony.
Anthony was...
much better than him.
Miss Candy, please return
to your cabin.
What a horrible fog.
It feels like I'm in a dream.
I feel that if I stay out here
Anthony might suddenly appear
before me.
Mauretania, with Candy on board,
finally landed in Southampton.
-It's Mauretania!
-Candy's ship!
Candy!
She can't hear you yet!
Candy! Alright!
Here it is!
What's that?
Anyway, look at this.
Candy!
I can't hear a thing.
That's strange.
Your inventions always end up like this!
It doesn't work? Now that's strange.
Candy!!!
England!
We've arrived to England, Kurin.
-Candy!
-Candy! It's me!
Archie! Stear!
Candy!
I missed them.
They haven't changed at all!
There she is! Candy!
Stear! Archie!
-Candy! It's been a long time!
-We missed you so much, Candy!
Both of you haven't changed at all!
Candy, you too!
And now here's one to welcome
Candy to England!
What's that thing?
Just look.
Poor Stear!
Why do your inventions
always end up like this?
Maybe it's stuck...
The crowd would've gone insane
if you fired the gun!
Yes, that's right...
That's strange...
What's the matter, Candy?
It's nothing!
Our carriage is here.
Everyone, this way.
Let's go, Candy!
Kurin, that castle looks as if it
came from a fairy tale!
It's probably a nobleman's mansion.
Nobleman?
I wonder if he lives in a place
like this.
Don't tell me that
they own everything around here.
What's the matter, Candy?
It's nothing.
George, don't tell me that we're
going back immediately.
We should use this opportunity
to see London a bit.
We're heading to the zoo.
Zoo?!
You've gotta be kidding us!
We're almost adults!
We'll drop off Kurin.
George! What's the meaning of this?
The school you'll be attending
has very strict rules.
You won't be allowed to keep animals.
But...!
Candy, it would be for the better
if you listen to what George said.
Yeah, they won't let you enter the
St. Paul academy with him around.
They will inspect all your luggage
at the entrance.
But why'd you put Kurin in the zoo...?
The London zoo is the best zoo
in the world.
I'm sure they will take good
care of Kurin.
I won't let you put Kurin in the zoo!
It's him!
I'm very sorry.
Damn it, who gave him
a driver's license anyway?
Kurin! Stear, catch Kurin!
-Wait, Kurin!
-Candy!
Miss Candy!
Wait up, Kurin!
Kurin wait
Kurin, where are you?
This isn't good.. where did he go?
He ran away because he thought
I'd put him in a zoo.
Kurin!
Kurin, get out!
I won't let anyone put you in a zoo!
I promise, Kurin!
Kurin, where did you go?
Come back!
Kurin?
Kurin, where are you?
Kurin!
Kurin, come down.
You and I will be together forever
okay?
From now on we'll stick together!
You understand, right?
Come down.
Wait!
Don't shoot!
That raccoon is my...
Kurin!
I heard a gunshot from over there!
Ow.. ouch! Stop that!
That way!
That's horrible!
How can you shooting an animal!
-You're horrible!
-Ouch!
Don't be unreasonable!
You're the unreasonable one!
I would have you hanged for this!
Candy!
You're horrible!
What happened here
Miss Candy?
Candy?
He's dead... Kurin was killed!
Kurin?
You're the one who fired?
Yeah...
I thought it was a weird raccoon...
Give him back!
Give Kurin back!
Miss Candy?
George, all of this happened because
you said you'd take him to the zoo...
There isn't even a single scratch
on Kurin.
Huh? But then...
You didn't know?
Raccoons will sometimes play dead
in order to protect their own lives.
Play dead?
Kurin!
Kurin, it's me!
It's true! You're alive, Kurin!
Now I'll never ever let go of you!
I'm so glad...
However, Miss Candy
even though you say that
when you enter St. Paul academy...
Candy, I have a good idea.
Don't tell me you'll whisk out
one of your weird inventions again!
Nah, it's not an invention
it's a brand new discovery!
Keep Kurin dead, the same way
he was " dead" a minute ago!
That's Big Ben.
Wow, it's big!
Over there is Westminster Cathedral.
It's high, isn't it?
This is Trafalgar square.
That building is the London tower.
And the London bridge.
Those soldiers are so cute!
Candy, let's give it a try here.
Okay. Kurin!
Everyone will think that
Kurin is a fur collar.
Stear, you joker!
George, now we won't have to
stop at the zoo!
But...
If you're worried...
why don't we repeat the test
in a more crowded place?
We'd better head back.
This is Piccadilly circus.
So they have a circus here?
Miss Candy.
Candy, in England
a" circus" means...
a large, circular street intersection.
Oh well...
Oh, this is a raccoon collar...
I see.
It was really fishy when you
stepped up to explain the collar!
Uh, maybe so...
George,
let's repeat the test a few times.
Mr. Stear, we really need to
head back to the school.
You're always so strict.
Candy is in this town
for the first time.
It's okay with me.
I can go sightseeing
whenever I want, right?
You wish!
Candy, the two of us are seeing
London for the first time, too!
But you arrived here two months ago!
Once you end up in jail
you don't get out so easily.
Jail... you mean, St. Paul academy?
They let you out only when your family
member dies, or something like that.
Mr. Stear, there's no need for this act.
They are that strict?
Candy, if you want to see or
do something...
now is the time!
From tommorrow, a very strict
kind of life awaits you.
There is someone who is waiting for me.
Waiting for you?
Here in London?
Grandfather William.
Miss Candy!
It's most unfortunate, but Mr. William
can't see you at this time.
It was grandfather William who
enabled me to study in England, right?
Also, it was him who adopted me
into the Adley family.
He's always looking so much after me
I've never got the chance to meet him.
Actually, it's just like Candy said.
Come to think of it, even the two of us
never met grandfather William.
We'd like to see him, too!
Mr. William currently isn't in London.
Strange
Weren't you planning to return
to America with grandfather William,
after escorting Candy to London?
Mr. William
suddenly departed from London.
George, which hotel is
grandfather William staying in?
That's right! He must be in Savoy!
The best hotel in London!
-Let's go!
-Okay!
Please wait!
Here!
To hotel Savoy.
In which room is William Adley?
Just a moment.
William Adley is in apartment 812.
-Room 812, right?
-Let's go!
Please wait!
Kurin, you're heavy, get off!
-OH MY GOD!!!
-I'm so sorry!
It's here.
Room 812.
Grandfather William?
It's Candy.
It's open.
Grandfather William?
It's me, Candice White Adley.
We came here to thank you.
Grandfather William?
Is that a recital?
So this is our grandfather?
Impossible!
Who are you?
The guy who stayed in this room
forgot this.
Oh, Mr. Grandchester
your room is next to this one.
I know.
The door was open so I took a peek.
Mr. William abruptly departed
a short time ago.
All of his luggage will be sent
separately after him.
But...
But he wrote this letter to me?
It's from grandfather.
My dearest Candy,
There is no need for you to
meet me right now.
You need to study hard in order
to become a prominent lady.
However, I'll make sure that
you meet me someday.
Until that time, William.
Candy.
I know, George must have notified
him about our arrival.
Miss Candy.
Mr. Archie, Mr. Stear.
George!
Now, Miss Candy, let's go.
Grandfather William...
Now, Candy, take a look.
This is our prison, St. Paul academy.
Now, Candy, Kurin has to stay still
around your neck as a fur collar.
Now it's for real!
I understand.
Kurin, do your best playing dead!
Miss Candy?
Candice White Adley, right?
Yes.
The director has been waiting for you
for the past three hours.
Three hours already?
You've wasted a lot of time
from the time your ship landed ashore.
I'm sorry.
And you two
return to boys' ward immediately!
-Yes
-Hurry!
And so, Candy finally landed in jail.
Candy paused before the gates
of the St. Paul academy.
They say that this school is the
strictest one in all of England.
What kind of fate awaits Candy?
Moreover...
just who was the young man whom Candy
met aboard the ship?