Safex
Instead of going to Southampton
in order to board a ship to America.
Candy mistakenly
went the opposite way.
Candy had to work for food,
since she had no money.
The star I saw from the barn.
This sea...
it extends all the way to America
where Terry is living now.
and also to Africa and Mr. Albert.
I want to hurry back to Pony' s home
and start a new life!
What' s the matter, Kurin?
Kurin, you...
Don't shake hands with the crab, Kurin.
Let' s go! Kurin.
We need to get to Southampton.
I' ll ask for a job there.
You want a job...so what can you do?
I can do anything!
I can clean, do laundry, and cook!
But you know, we don't really...
Please! Give me something to do!
Well...you could do the laundry, then?
Yes! As you wish.
Can you carry that much?
I can manage!
Don't force yourself!
With something this light?!
I don't think so!
All the troubles in Eliza' s house
are paying off now.
I can do everything now!
I' m done with the laundry...
Thanks. I prepared a lunch for you
so why don't you take a break now.
Thank you!
Who is that girl?
She wants to earn money
in order to travel to America.
Oh, that must be hard.
You were a great help.
Here, this is your pay.
Please take it.
Thank you!
Take care of yourself, Candy.
I will! Let' s go, Kurin.
Everybody has been so kind to me!
I could return to Pony' s home
sooner than I planned.
Miss!
Oh? You are...?
Yes, we met at that restaurant
a little while ago.
I heard you' re going to America?
Yes!
That means that you' re heading to
Southampton.
Yes.
I could give you a lift.
I have something to do in the vicinity.
Really?
Okay, get in.
Thank you!
Please!
Well, let' s head to Southampton!
You renounced the name of the
Adley family which adopted you?
I can't rely on them
if I want to find my own path in life.
Have you informed the Pony' s home
that you' ll be coming back?
No, I still haven't!
It' s better that way.
Hold on a minute.
I' d like to speak to a friend.
Yes, no problem!
Kurin, I' m so glad we met
such a friendly person.
We might make it to Southampton
by the evening.
If I find a ship which will
let me work in exchange for a fare...
We could make it to America!
Anyway, we need to try!
You found a good girl, there.
Old man,
she worth a good price, right?
The sailors' diner down the road
needs servants.
Well then, I' ll sell her there.
That' s good.
Really, it is.
Sorry to make you wait.
No!
Now, let' s go!
I' ll see a friend here, as well.
You have a lot of friend!
Candy, why don't you come with me?
You can wait inside.
Don't worry, Kurin, I' ll be back soon!
-Let' s go.
-Okay!
Candy, sit here and wait a bit.
I' ll have a word with the landlady.
I guess I' ll wash my hands, too!
Eh? You want to sell that girl?
What do you think, madam?
She worth more money.
That' s right...
Most of our customers
are thugs and sailors...
If we bought such a girl
we might start getting more customers.
She is healthy, so you could
work her hard with no problems.
Those people are slave traders!
I have to escape now!
Who is that?
She overheard us!
Wait! Hey!
-My carriage!
-You can use my horse!
Alright! I' ll catch her for sure!
He caught up to me!
Damm it,
whom do you think you' re kidding?
Alright, you' re not getting away!
Protect yourself, Kurin!
Let' s flee as far as possible
while we can!
I must flee! Anywhere!
I have to flee further.
Kurin, we' re saved!
Where did that girl go?
Kurin, hide in the straw.
Let' s leave everything to God now.
Stop!
God came to our help.
Mom! It' s Mr. Carson!
Pretend you didn't see him!
He refused your help as well?
Yes. The villagers wanted to help him
but...
Carson was doing better
while his wife was still alive.
He turned into a violent eccentric...
Can't this lazy old horse go any faster?
These guys are annoying
like everybody else!
It' s dady!
Brother, dad' s come back!
-Dad, welcome back!
-Welcome back!
Everybody, you doing well?
I brought you some apples as present.
Dad, I' m sorry. I burnt the stew
and it' s become all black.
Why worry about that?
You' re gonna get it someday.
Dad, I' ll take care the horse.
Sussy, what' s the matter?
You didn't say anything.
Dad, ther aren't any apples.
But there' s a girl sleeping in here.
A girl? What are you saying, Jeff?
It' s true!
You didn't mean to bring her, dad?
What?
Eh? She ate all the apples.
Who is she?
Dad... she woke up!
What are you?!
You went into my wagon without asking!
Forgive me!
Kurin, hide in the straw!
Get off, or I' ll pull you out myself!
Sorry! I was tired and fell asleep.
I' ll get off now.
But I slept so well!
Sis, you' re good!
Thanks.
Mister, I' ll pay you for the apples.
It' s gone!
No!
I must dropped it while I was running.
I... I lost my money.
Nonsense!
You had no money to begin with!
Mister, is Southampton nearby?
It' s a long way towards there...
I missed again...
Uh, mister...
Shut up! Get lost!
I don't have any money...
If you let me stay here,
I' d work to pay you.
No way!
There is no room for you!
I' d do anything...
Sam, Jeff, Sussy! Come inside!
Dinner!
You tighward!
I thought you' d be unfriendly
but I wasn't expecting this!
Come! If you' re okay with that
you can stay in the barn
without our dad knowing.
Thank you!
Sis, hurry!
Quiet!
Let' s hurry before dad sees us!
What' s the matter? Are you okay?
I' m okay.
Sussy, don't scare me!
Thank you, everyone.
I wouldn't know what to do
now that it' s gotten dark.
We' ll welcome you instead of our dad!
Okay?
Sorry for eating all of your apples...
You were hungry, weren't you, sis?
Sis, take care, it' s dark in here.
It' s okay.
Well then, sis!
Make sure our dad doesn't see you!
Okay. Thanks.
Those kids saved me!
Kurin, we' ll staying here tonight.
So warm! The smell of hay...
What a wonderful bed!
I wonder if grandfather William
already received my letter.
Grandfather William,
Archie, Stear, Annie, Patty...
Everone, I' m so sorry.
I wonder what is Terry doing right now.
I ran till lost my breath...
But I came too late to see him.
I only stood there in silence.
Terry was slowly moving away from me.
Terry went away.
And I' m in the barn
of an unknown family...
Dad fell asleep.
And you came to see me?
Sis, you' re hungry?
Here! Milk.
You...
Here.
Everyone... thank you.
I' m not worthy of such hospitality.
It' s okay! Sis
it' s because you' re our guest!
Yeah!
I' m Sam.
I' m Jeff.
I' m Sussy.
And I' m Candy. Nice to meet you!
This is my raccoon, Kurin.
Hello!
I've never been a guest in such a
wonderful place.
Thank you so much!
Ever since mom went over
the Mount Rodney...
nobody comes to our place anymore.
Mount Rodney?
Look! It' s that mountain over there.
Mom went over that hill but
she didn't come back.
I want to see mom.
Both of you
how many times have I told you?
Our mom is dead! She went heaven!
Heaven is behind the Mount Rodney?
No. You wouldn't understand
even I explained it to you...
Sam.
Mom won't be coming back
those two keep waiting for her...
Be quiet! You' ll wake up dad...
Sorry, Jeff.
Heaven is behind Mount Rodney
after all.
Is that true, sis?
Yes...
Then, mom will return one day?
Why don't you return to your rooms...
Sis! Sussy has...
Sussy! What' s the matter?
Sussy!
She is burning.
Sam, hurry and wake up your dad.
What are you doung in here?
Quickly, call the doctor
Sussy has a fever!
What?
It' s true.
Hang in there, Sussy!
Why didn't you say anything, Sussy?
Sussy, hang in there! Sussy!
Mr. Carson, hurry and put Sussy in bed.
Sam, call the doctor.
Sam!
That' s impossible, sis!
The doctor won't come!
Why?
The doctor ain't gonna touch her!
It' s his fault that my wife died!
Those villagers and doctor
killed my wife!
If that guy shows up here again
I' m gonna tear him apart!
Sussy, what' s the matter?
Open your eyes.
Sussy!
Mr. Carson! Are you trying to kill Susy?
Sam, lead me to the doctor house.
I' m going to to call him over.
No way!
Mr. Carson!
Don't shout around sick people!
Her disease will get worse!
Sam, let' s go!
Sussy, hang in there!
The doctor should save the patient
No matter how...
Candy ran into the fog.