Safex
Candy, Annie and the others
finally had a reunion.
Soon after that, she returned to
St. Joanna Hospital.
Terry's melody.
I will do my best and work hard
from tomorrow.
I am back, Blanny!
What happened?
A bus crushed into other cars,
many people were injured.
I'll change my clothes right now.
Sorry, I am late.
Blanny, where are the patients?
In the surgery. Practice nurses
don't need to show up right now.
Blanny,
excuse me...
May I talk to you for a minute,
Blanny?
What do you want to say?
Didn't you take a vacation?
The nurses can take a vacation,
but the patients can not.
Only you went out during the break.
Only me?
Right. Natalie and Judy
were in the hospital standing by.
Only me went out.
What can I say?
You are a princess from the Adleys.
It's not true.
I am not related to the Adleys.
I am just a practice nurse.
Are you?
Please quit playing around.
The most important thing is
to get used to the new environment.
Yes, you are right.
I will do my best and work harder
from tomorrow.
Don't bother my study
if you don't have anything important.
I am sorry.
The hospital are full of patients
because of the accident last night.
The practice nurses from Joseph Hospital
who are still on vacation...
did a great job.
It was an excellent act.
The head of our hospital
is very happy about it.
Hope everyone
won't forget the spirit last night,
and become an
outstanding nurse soon.
From now on, you will take turns
to have the night shift.
- Tonight is Blanny.
- Yes.
- Tomorrow is Natalie.
The day after tomorrow is Candy.
Yes.
This is not an elementary school.
Sorry.
Stear?
Aren't you Stear?
What happened to your hand?
I just want to look around
in the hospital.
But I am afraid to be suspected.
That's why.
Then, your hand...
The result from driving.
May I borrow your time?
Annie
Candy
Annie, what is it?
Good news!
Terry is coming to Chicago!
Terry?
Terry's troupe
is going to perform here.
Terry?
Terry is coming.
Terry's troupe
is really coming to Chicago.
I just couldn't wait to tell you.
Thanks, Annie.
I didn't think
Terry would become an actor.
I wonder what role he is playing?
I will go find out.
Thank you.
I shouldn't be so uneasy.
Terry,
I will go see you act!
Terry, I miss you so much.
I am going to beg the head nurse
tomorrow.
- Switching the shift?
- Yes.
I have seen a lot of practice nurses.
You are the first one
who asked for a shift change.
I have a friend who I must see.
I have to treat every nurse fairly.
Candy, if I say "yes" to your request,
how do I face the others?
There won't be next time.
Candy,
The shift sheet is not arranged
by alphabet.
I arranged it
according to your personality.
It's not changeable.
Even if I can't go to the performance,
I have to let Terry know
that I am in this hospital.
Terry,
It's here.
What's wrong, Terry?
This station...
This station leads to Candy's home.
On that day...
I went to Pony's Home
for what Candy said.
The heavy snow is whirling.
Candy, where are you?
Annie, sorry for the wait.
There's no problem now, Annie.
Really?
I am sure
the Adleys has ten invitations.
Candy's is included.
Of course.
Great!
Candy must be happy.
This is why.
There was a serious accident
couple days ago.
Save the patients.
We can't waste any minute or second.
Especiall for the nonstop bleeding...
Tonight.
After tonight, when is the next time
I'll be able to see Terry?
Candy, what are you thinking?
I am sorry.
Turn up the light.
What? No way.
Come on, let's rehearse again.
Rehearsal on progress.
No visit.
Excuse me, I am looking for Terry.
Terry?
I am a fan of Terry.
I want to see Terry soon, too.
Is Terry...
He doesn't respect his job.
This swollen-headed guy
didn't come to the rehearsal.
Terry is not here.
He must have gone to look for Candy.
Won't you leave the flowers to us?
I can't believe
Terry has this kind of friend.
Terry?
Knock before you come in,
Miss.Nurse.
I am sorry, the harmonica sound...
You heard it?
Did you play it?
Last time I played it,
a nurse with glasses stopped me.
It must be Blanny.
Candy
Blanny
How can you put the medicine
in the wrong place?
I am sorry.
You need to be more responsible.
I will pay more attention to that.
How can I do
to let Terry know that I am here?
Wait.
Are you a practice nurse?
Yes.
You must know Candy White.
We were in the same class.
Anybody came to look for her?
No visit allowed on duty.
Candy's shift ends tomorrow morning.
Tomorrow morning?
Did she ask people to
switch the shift with her?
If she asks you,
don't switch it with her.
I won't.
This is the pay.
I can't take it...
Please tell everyone.
Stop!
It seems like
he didn't come to the hospital.
Where are you, Terry?
Terry, you are here!
Everyone is looking for you!
I don't want to go to the
performance tonight.
Terry...
The audience are all rich people.
We have no right
to pick our audience.
Is it?
I don't want to serve the celebrities.
But, this is a charity show.
A charity show? Sorry.
Terry, let's go back.
Susanna, would the poor
really be helped by this?
This...
A real charity show
should be held for those
who can't afford the tickets.
It is right.
That harmonica...
Harmonica?
Everytime you are troubled in mind,
it would show up.
From now on, let's replace the
cigarette by the harmonica.
It must be very important to you.
Something replaces the cigarette.
The show starts in thirty minutes.
After tonight, when will be
the next time I see Terry?
I want to fly there.
That child...
What's wrong?
It hurts so much!
Nobody talked to me,
so I started playing the harmonica...
I'll go find the doctor.
Thanks.
I can't leave the patient
to see Terry.
Natalie, didn't you...
Didn't you get off work?
I want to know the reason.
The reason?
Who do you want to see?
why did you want to switch the shift?
Forget it, I already gave up.
A guy?
You want to switch the shift
with me for a date?
We live far away.
We don't know
when we will meet again?
So...
You like to cry.
Stop it.
Is that person like you?
Drop it, Natalie.
I'll switch it with you.
Natalie.
Blanny is in the library, it's ok.
Are you sure, natalie?
I was always afraid to
get into trouble since I was a child.
And now I am Blanny's follower.
Then why would you...
Blanny won't blame me.
Natalie.
Honestly, I don't really like you.
But, I met someone
who I dislike more.
Who tries to win people's hearts
by money.
Was it...
Give her back the money!
She is about the same age with us.
You know who she is, right?
Elisa?
Go change your clothes.
Thank you, Natalie!
Don't let Blanny find out
about this.
Candy is so slow.
The show starts in five minutes.
Annie, she is not here yet?
Not yet.
Sorry, please hurry.
I am going to see Terry soon.
Terry, I am coming!
We will be able to see each other
in five minutes.
Candy's heart is full of joy.
The rapid sound of the Carriage
along with Candy's expectation
and unease,
is echoing in the street.