Safex
Grand aunt Elroy
arriving from Chicago...
invited Stear, Archie and the others
in order to introduce Annie to them.
Annie transferred to St. Paul academy.
On the other end
Annie's foster father Mr. Brighton...
secretly met up with Candy
and asked her to look after Annie.
Revived smiles.
Everyone, allow a new friend
to introduce herself to you.
I'm Annie Brighton.
I'm from America.
How do you do.
We already have two Americans
in this class.
Eliza Leagan! Candice White Adley!
Please stand up.
Yes!
Candy...
To meet her so soon...!
I want both of you
to take good care of Annie.
Yes, sister!
There is an empty desk next to Candy.
Annie, you can sit there.
Uh, sister...
I'm an acquaintance of Eliza...
so please...
Annie...
Annie is avoiding me!
She isn't glad to see me!
Sitting next to Eliza is...
Uh, sister... I'll sit next to Candy.
Alright, let's do that.
Well then, Annie, be seated.
What's the matter, Candy?
It's nothing.
Patty, thank you for sitting next to me.
Be quiet.
We'll begin today's lecture.
Candy, I'm sorry.
I can't sit right next to you...
I could have accidentally
said something to you.
Say, that Candy...
she was brought up in some
Pony-thing or something like that...
and after that
she became a daughter of Adleys.
Louise, it's not " Pony-something"
It's " Pony's home!"
It's up in the mountains
but it's such a beautiful place!
Remember this well!
I can't say it! I can't say that
I came from Pony's home, as well.
Really! The girl from Pony's home
is so rude!
-Oh, Annie, what's the matter?
-You don't look too well.
It's nothing!
Annie, you're probably thinking that
I'd blurt out the secrects in Pony's home.
Don't tell me that
you've come to hate me!
I still treasure the ribbon
you left me in the barn.
Annie.
Stear!
Hello, Candy.
I've been looking for you.
Stear, you'll get in trouble
if they find you here.
It's okay. Sister gave me permission.
-A permission?
-Yeah.
Introduce the Adley family members
to the Brighton's Annie.
So I thought you'd like to accompany us.
Stear, you!
Now, let's go to the main hall.
Archie and the others are waiting for us.
Archie and the others?
Annie already caught that Archie guy.
Annie seems to be a lot into Archie.
Hello, Candy!
I waited for you!
Annie, you remember
our former dogsbody, Candy?
Yes, we're in the same class.
Nice to meet you!
Call me Candy!
I... I'm Annie.
Annie. you're just scared, aren't you?
You haven't changed inside, haven't you?
That's right, Candy
Aunt Elroy got this scarf for you.
Wow, for me?
You're a member of the Adley family
after all.
We haven't stopped complaining
until she let you have this.
Thank you, Archie.
Let's see how it suits you.
Not bad, Candy!
Let me see.
-What's up with that?
-Archie and Candy...
are getting along well, aren't they?
That's right.
Archie likes to watch over Candy.
Talk about inappropriate.
You haven't seen anything yet!
Those two are always sticking together!
We're going back to our rooms.
See you!
Those two haven't changed at all.
They must spoil the mood
whenever somebody is having fun.
Uh...
I'll return to my room as well.
I don't feel too well.
Maybe she's tired from her long journey.
Archie, why don't you escort her
to her room?
-Go, go!
-Archie!
Annie, I'll escort you to your room!
-Are you okay?
-Yes...
Archie likes Candy...
It can't be! But...
Archie?
Please... could we walk more slowly?
Oh, sorry!
You sure you don't want to see a doctor?
Maybe some medicine could help you?
It's okay.
Well then, hold on to my arm.
You can trust me.
Archie... I like you.
It's not true that you like Candy,
right?
I realize you're not feeling well
but walking together like this...
This place has very strict rules,
you know?
Yes. Mama want me to be educated
to become a good wife and mother.
Annie, wouldn't you become all that
without coming here?
Archie...
-Annie, I have a favor to ask of you.
-What is it?
I'd like you to become Candy's friend.
Candy is such a good girl.
She was brought up in Pony's home
but...
which wasn't a bad place at all.
Candy is cheerful, carefree but...
it's just that whenever
Eliza discovers something like this
I'd be very happy if the two of you
could get along.
Please.
Annie, what's the matter?
I'm tired. Sorry, Archie!
Annie?
Archie... you like her that much?
You don't understand my feelings
at all.
Annie,
I'd like you to become her friend!
She was brought up in Pony's home
but she's such a good girl!
Candy. you're exactly like in the past.
Cheerful, cocky,
friendly towards anyone...
Candy, good morning!
Good morning, Patty.
Annie...
She's so quiet...
what is she knitting?
I've never seen her
do anything like that.
What are you knitting?
I know. It's for Archie, right?
Tablecloth?
Uh...
Archie's birthday is drawing near.
Archie is... Archibald Cornwell?
That's right. Candy's friend.
Just what is she saying? That Eliza...!
Candy!
Annie!
Annie, I wanted to speak to you!
Candy, please... Don't take Archie!
Please... Please, Candy!
Annie, you don't have to worry!
We are just friends!
Archie likes gentle girls,
just like you.
Candy.
Annie, you!
You're still a crybaby.
Now, smile!
Candy...
Terrius G. Grandchester!
Don't scare me!
I thought it was sister Gray.
Say, wanna smoke?
You're doing it again?
Cut it out!
You can't smoke at my Pony's hill!
Instead, I'll let you have this.
Harmonica?
It's my favorite instrument.
Hmmh, your favorite instrument?
I see, you want me to kiss you
indirectly.
Terrius!
Silly, I was just kidding.
It pains me to do this, but
I'll have to accept your gift.
Some things you do and say
are so harsh...
The class is beginning!
Listen up. I'm going to class.
Play the harmonica instead of smoking!
See you!
What a nosy freckled Tarzan!
Candy!
Archie!
What's the matter?
Why are you looking at me like that?
You are hooking up with that guy!
With that nobleman!
He's got an eye on you!
Hook up... uh... I don't really...
Candy... you'd better leave him alone!
Why? It's just that
nobody unsderstands him.
Actually, he's not such a bad person!
He's deceiving you!
Why are you protecting him, Candy?
Protecting... but...
What's gotten into you, Archie?
You're not your usual self.
I... I don't want that guy to take you!
Archie!
For that bastard to take you...
From the first time I saw you
Candy, I...
Stop it!
Please, stop it!
Annie... why are you here?
I wanted to give this present
to Archie...
But now...
Annie!
"Happy birthday."
"I made this with all my love."
"Annie."
Candice White Adley!
Annie Brighton!
Louise, Eliza
go and look for them.
Annie, please, don't cry.
You promised...
that you wouldn't take Archie!
Annie, calm down.
I know everything! Archie likes you!
Not me...
Annie...
Eliza and Louise. This isn't good.
Class must have started and
they went out to find us.
Annie, anyway, we'd better
head back to the classroom.
We'll talk later... okay?
Don't touch me!
Candy, you were always like this!
Even back in Pony's home...
the teachers liked you more than me!
Annie, don't say that!
Oh, I see. You were in Pony's home.
The same place Candy came from.
What a surprise!
Does Archie know?
Your disguise was pretty good.
Annie!
Leave her alone!
By the way, Candy...
you knew about Annie
but you kept quiet till now?
Covering each other...
what a wonderful friendship!
People from Pony's home are all alike.
Annie... poor Annie!
Candy, I'm scared...
won't you sleep together with me?
Candy, Tom wants to beat me up!
Candy!
Annie, I'll protect you, no matter what.
Rain.
If Annie disappears now...
Annie!
Director, Annie Brighton
hasn't been found yet?
Anyway,
we'll split up and search for her.
Annie!
Annie...
just where did you go in this rain?
Don't touch me!
Candy, you were always like this!
Even back in Pony's home...
the teachers liked you more than me!
Annie, that's not true!
Sister Pony and sister Lane
worried so much about you!
Candy, don't make Annie cry!
Candy, look after Annie!
Annie... just where are you now?
Annie!
It seems though we're the only ones
looking for her...
and the forest is so big.
I don't see too well
with my glasses being wet.
Brother, sorry.
You ruined your suit for my sake.
Come on!
It's you who's gonna flop over
first before finding Annie!
Even if I flop over
will it change anything?
Just how blind I was?
I didn't lie to Candy back then.
I thought about her from the
very first moment.
But, hiding the fact that
she was in Pony's home...
The fact she desperately tried to hide...
The one who thought about me...
"I made this with all my love."
"With all my love."
Oh, Candy.
Archie, I've been looking for you.
I found Annie.
But... I couldn't do it.
Annie doesn't want to listen to me
anymore...
Archie, she needs you.
Where is she?
In a cave near the other Pony's hill.
Archie, please, you can help her.
Nobody else!
Candy, you don't need to worry.
I'll bring her back for sure.
Wait, I'll go...
Candy, Archie is on his way now
no need to worry.
Let's go back to the classroom.
Yes.
I wish I could disappear into the ground
together with this rain.
Just why did my papa and mama
insist on sending me to England?
Just why did they want to hurt me
because my past in Pony's home?
If not for Archie?
But it's all over now.
Annie!
Annie, it's me.
Come out!
Everyone is worried about you!
Archie!
You found yourself an incredible place!
You don't have to hide inside anymore.
Leave me!
I've deceived you!
Deceived you!
I'll stay right here until you get out.
Say, Annie...
Does it matter where you from?
After all, you are you.
Be strong!
Never fear those who superficially
judge others by their exterior!
Archie!
Now that you know about me
can you accept me like this?
Yeah. I'll be here forever.
For me...
Of course!
Archie!
Archie.
Say, did you hear?
Annie was in Pony's home
just like Candy!
She hid that well!
As expected, Eliza's doing.
Everybody in school already knows.
Oh, Candy, good morning.
Your friend has a fever.
Yeah, though you were both
in Pony's home...
Annie is more delicate than you.
Annie is a daughter of
a good Mr. Brighton!
Doesn't matter who adopted her...
an orphan is always an orphan!
-Eliza!
-Candy!
What a fright!
She goes crazy in a second!
People from Pony's home are so vulgar!
Candy, not all students are like them.
There is Annie...
and I am here, as well!
Patty!
That's right, Annie!
I'm here as well.
Candice, please watch over Annie.
She is waiting for you.
Waiting?
Annie is waiting for me!
Annie is...
Archie!
Candy.
She is asleep now.
Before she fell asleep, she said that
she wanted you to stay next to her.
If she has you next to her
Annie can feel at ease.
-Right, Archie?
-Uh...
Take good care of Annie, okay?
I understand.
See you!
Annie looks so peaceful.
She's sound asleep.
Annie!
I wanted to see you, so much!
Annie, don't get up.
Sorry for all that happened until now.
Deep inside, I missed you so much
during this time.
Hiding my past in Pony's home...
I was stupid.
It's okay, Annie.
Candy, thank you.
Again, I'm sorry.
I'll cheer up! I'll be true to myself!
Just like you always were.
You haven't changed at all.
My dearest Annie!
Candy remembered the old days,
they're running to the Pony's hill.