Safex
Fate-guiding cross.
Candy, doing such a thing...
I got money, you won't
have to go to Mexico to work.
Candy sold the precious rose
she got from Anthony...
in order to save Mr. Walther.
Candy continue her journey,
accompanied by scary Mr. Garcia.
Dear Anthony, how are you?
How are Stear and Archie?
I'm writing you this letter from
halfway till Mexico.
Anthony!
Anthony, wait!
Don't run around!
Anthony
mama can't catch up to you!
Mama!
Candy!
A dream?
It's already noon.
I couldn't sleep all night.
And just what kind of
dream was that?
Does it mean that something
could have happened to Candy?
Anthony, get up!
It's open!
What, you're awake?
It's done!
Look at this!
I built it during the night!
It's a Candy-detector!
Candy detector?
That's right.
It'll lead us right to
where Candy is now.
We'll depart as soon as possible!
Great! But does it really work?
Why, of course!
It follows the smell..
Forgive me Anthony
I was so stupid!
What's the matter?
I didn't think of this before I
completed the machine...!
We can't use it unless we have a
piece of Candy's clothes!
But now we can't get it anymore!
Brother
don't make so much noise.
My head hurts like it's
going to split in half.
Archie, you've been drinking?
I've had a pretty bad night.
Just thought about one thing.
I couldn't sleep because she was
banished to such a faraway place.
Who was banished
to a faraway place?
Aunt!
You've been noisy all morning!
What's up with that?
And just look at your clothes!
You've become loose under
Candy's bad influence!
Aunt, please borrow me
that handkerchief.
In return, I'll give you this.
What is it?
Run for it!
Wait! Stear! Archie! Anthony!
Now that was some noise!
Now if Aunt approaches us
we will hear the alarm!
Just in the right time!
A good solution for the Aunt issue.
Candy is such a good girl.
I don't even know how many memories
she kept giving us every day.
How many memories
did you give us...
Candy, if I knew where you are now,
I'd come after you right now.
Don't move!
Candy...
You were bitten by a rattlesnake,
but you'll be okay if I do this!
Candy!
Now, let's go!
Alright, you wait here.
There is someone I need to pick
up and take to Mexico.
I have to go somewhere, too!
Where?
To the post office.
I want to send these letters to
Pony's home and Anthony.
Just when did you write these?!
Give them back!
You were badmouthing me
in these letters!
I wasn't !
You won't be able to send letters
once you arrive in Mexico!
That's terrible!
What is it? You're going to
get all weepy now?
I won't . Who is crying?
That's good. If you cried
over things like these...
you wouldn't be able to
continue the journey.
Sheriff!
That girl belongs to you,
I suppose?
No, I was entrusted with her
until I take her to Mexico.
Is he telling the truth?
Yes. Why do you ask?
Lately there have been many
abductions in this area.
Abductions?
They kidnap children and sell to the
european families who want children.
-European...
-Be extremely careful.
We know that kidnappers
are using an automobile.
Automobile?
If strangers ask you to take a ride
with them, don't even think about it!
I understand.
Thank you for your concern!
Candy, listen up!
We'll be leaving immediately!
Aren't you going to pick up someone?
There are kidnappers around here
and we're not ready for them.
Instead of taking her to Mexico,
I can make more money by selling Candy.
I'm not going to resist kidnappers
if they come after her.
What would I do if I get abducted?
Europe is much further than Mexico.
I'll never see Anthony again.
How does one get discovered
by the kidnappers?
Kurin, it's okay now. Let's go!
Hey, it's done!
Alright now, it's done!
You even made the bread yourself?
Doug, the cook at the Leagan's
estate taught me how to make bread.
Still a child, and yet
she can make things like these.
I'll get pots of cash for her.
-Don't touch that!
-What?
You need to pray before meals!
What?! Pray?
I've never done that!
Why don't you start from now on?
I have no need for such things!
I'll take the meal then.
Are you stealing that from me?!
Children who didn't want to pray in
Pony's home were given little to eat!
What?
What is that Pony's home?
It's a place where children with
no parents gather.
Children with no parents?
A gentle sister Pony and sister Lane
were like our real mothers!
We pulled pranks on each other,
but we were good friends.
John, Sam, Milly... I miss them!
Put your hands like this.
Our Father, who are in heaven.
hallowed be thy name
the kingdom come.
Lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil.
Give us this day our daily bread
And forgive our trespasses
as we forgive those against us.
Amen.
Huh? What is this?
I'll give it to you, Mr. Garcia!
-To me?
-Sister Pony gave it to me.
But why are you giving it to me?
If you keep it around your neck...
you won't forget to pray.
Wake up!
Just spare my life!
Anything in there?
They have no money or valuable things.
That's right!
We have nothing to hide!
So this plan backfired.
Can't help it then
Let's kill them and go back
Don't do that! Spare my life!
What should we do if you have no money?
Give up already.
Help! Help me!
I'll tell you where I have
a lot of money instead!
A lot of money?
I'm listening!
Promise you'll spare my life for that!
-Alright.
-Where is the money?
It's her!
Take her
and you'll make a lot of money!
You can sell her
and earn a lot of money!
Mr. Garcia!
That's right!
I've heard that children
sell for quite a lot lately!
Okay. We'll sell this girl then.
Help me, Mr. Garcia!
Then, will you spare my life
like you promised...
You're still here?!
Mr. Garcia!
Anyway, we'll find a buyer in
San Antonio tomorrow.
Yeah, that's right.
I wonder how much we'll earn.
Come on, that girl can't possibly
sell for much!
We'd better find another job!
They'll sell me to someone
tommorrow
What should I do?
Damn it! I was this close
to getting killed!
I've got to get out of here!
I'll be okay if I already
came this far!
I was saved thanks to Candy.
Candy.
You were bitten
by a rattlesnake...
but you'll be okay if I do this!
You need to pray before meals!
Our Father, who art in heaven
hallowed be thy name
the kingdom come.
I'll give it to you, Mr. Garcia!
If you keep it around your neck...
you won't forget to pray.
Candy.
Just what did I do?
Candy...
Candy!!!
I'll set you free.
Keep quiet.
Thank you, Mr. Garcia!
You planned this from the
very beginning, right?
Well, that's ... yeah.
I'm sorry
I already thought that
you wouldn't come back to save me
Now, let's go, Candy.
Yes.
We're going to run with the carriage?
Yeah. It's my carriage.
You think I'd let them have it?
Aren't you tired?
I'll have plenty of time
for that later!
Who's that!?
They're running away! Fire!
You released the saddles, right?
That will give us a head start!
I can see them!
Looks like they've caught up to us!
If we go into that forest,
we could make it out of this!
Mr. Garcia, now I understand
for the first time...
What?
What people meant when they
told me never to give up...
even when things are looking bad.
Candy, I'll return you this!
Why?
I'm a cold-blooded killer!
-That's not true!
-Candy
You don't know what it means to
kill a man!
Your heart is still pure!
But mr. Garcia, I know you
worked hard to save me back there!
A killer would never do something
like that!
Candy, I've done something
for someone else!
This is the first time
Candy, take this and keep going!
What will you do?
I'll hold them off here!
Mr. Garcia!
Now stop the carriage!
Candy, run! Run for it!
There they are!
You did it, Mr. Garcia!
The kidnapper!
Help me!
-Candy!
-Mr. Garcia!
Candy!
-Candy!
Mr. Garcia!
Candy!
Candy.
Because of me... Candy...
Forgive me!!!
Who are you?
Where are you taking me?!
Let me out!
If you don't let me out
I'll jump out myself!
Kidnappers have caught me
after all.
Where will I be sold off to?
Anthony...
Anthony!
Where is Candy being taken to?
Her small chest trembled in fear