Safex
Candy went for a vacation to
a Summer school in Scotland...
where she happened upon
Terry's real mother.
Terry, however...
kept insisting that the woman who came
from America to see him...
isn't his real mother.
The link between a mother and a child.
Kurin, it's still too early to get up.
I see... you want us to play
before everybody gets up?
Wait up, Kurin!
You're tickling me! Stop that, Kurin!
Kurin, you!
Got you!
Kurin, it's been a long time since
the two of us played like this!
It's because you always have to hide
so that people don't see you.
From now on, I'll get up earlier
so I can play with you.
Now, let's run!
Wonderful!
Alright!
I haven't climbed a tree
in a long time, too!
I'm not gonna give up!
I haven't felt so good for a long time,
Kurin!
Beautiful!
Terry's mansion is over there.
Eleanor Baker?
Terry's mother.
Terry, please, open the gates.
Back! I already told you last night
that I never want to see you again.
Please...
hear my story for the last time!
If you keep yelling here, somebody
is going to come. Got it?
It would be a disgrace, that
an American actress has such a son!
Terry, I'll be returning to America
this evening.
That look on Terry face...
it's the same look he had
on the day we first met.
Frightened... sad...
I have nothing else to say to you.
Terry, please wait!
Don't go!
Terry.
Uh...
Oh, no! The breakfast!
Kurin, let's take a shortcut!
Romeo and Juliet.
A scenario book.
E.B.
Eleanor Baker.
This book belongs to Terry's mother.
I'll return it to her
during my free time in the afternoon.
You're the only one who hasn't
shown up for the breakfast!
You haven't told anybody
about your leave...
Where were you going this early
in the morning?
Uh... for a walk...
I see. In that case, you'll spend
the free time in your room.
But... I don't want that...
I won't be able to return this book.
Good morning, sister!
Candy, thanks for your help!
Mark.
Sister, Candice came to help us
with milking.
We got this much.
Candice helped out with milking?
She was a great help to us!
Why haven't you honestly
told me about this, Candice?
Yes...
In that case, I'll allow you out
due to the circumstances.
Thank you!
-Lady! Mark!
-Hello!
You just saved me.
It's okay!
Even lies are sometimes useful.
Oh! Both you and Mark
winked your left eyes!
Come to think of it...
I never realized!
Parents and their kids see things
he same way...
Let's go, mom!
Okay. Well then, miss!
-See you!
-Goodbye!
Is there a way... Terry and
his mother can get along like this?
They're family!
This is probably it.
The hotel
where Terry's mother is staying.
-What a pity, bro.
-Maybe we'll get another chance.
Stear!
Hi, Candy!
Do you have any business in this hotel?
Yeah... a little.
What are you two here for?
Tell her, bro!
Anyway, it's ...
Be a man, say it out loud!
Bro, you're in charge of things
like these!
But you're better in this than me...
-We came here to get an autograph.
-An autograph?
We heard rumours that Eleanor Baker is
staying at this hotel.
Then... did you get her autograph?
We barely missed her.
Looks like
she already departed to America.
To America?
By the way
what did you come here for?
It doesn't matter anymore.
Hey, Candy...
I can't change Terry's stubbornness
anymore...
What about me?
Terry!
I'm happy to see you calling out my name
alone like this...
He looks completely different from
what I saw this morning.
Maybe he spoke to his mother?
Say, I had no idea that...
I'm on your mind at times
when you're alone.
Don't talk such nonsense!
You always reinforce your words
with fists!
Candy, that book...
To whom do you think it belongs?
To whom... maybe...
Here!
-It's my book!
-Your book?
Terry, you read scenarios?
I'm surprised! How come?
Say, Candy...
If you turn into a old granny.
you'd still be Candy, right?
Don't say such weird things!
If I become an old gentleman.
I'd still be Terry, right?
Hm! You were the only one
who looked cool now!
Then, are you saying that
we can't turn into other people?
But the thing is - acting is different.
You can become someone else
on the stage. Even a king.
You can even kill someone.
And... you can love, too.
Terry!
I was just kidding!
My partner would have to be
much cuter.
Some things you say!
There is a small world on the stage.
A wonderful world
overflowing with dreams.
Terry's face lit up.
I've never seen such a vigor
in his eyes.
But I've already seen a person
with such an expression!
Anthony?
It was Anthony, at times when he
was tending his roses.
Anthony.
Said something?
Nah, it's nothing.
Say, wanna stop by?
I'll put the kettle on.
Terry, you'll make tea?
Can you manage?
When you put it this way...
Terry!
You're still loitering around?
I wanted to speak to you one last time
before returning to America.
Go back.
I don't want to speak to you.
Terry...!
Somebody is coming. Terry, you'd
better open the gates.
Terry, I'm begging you...
please hear my story!
Shut up!
After what you said back then...
I don't have a mother anymore!
Please understand, Terrius!
There was nothing I could do back then.
America in winter...
The cold journey.
But you were even colder than that.
You didn't want to see your son
who came to the theatre to see you.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry, Terry.
After all, wandering off to America
was stupid of me.
I ran after you immediately
after the incident.
I don't want your excuses.
Go back!
Stop that!
Terry, be more truthful to yourself.
I am trutful to myself.
That's not true!
You're showing off by
chasing away your mother...
whom you love more than anyone else!
"Mother" , was it?
Don't make me laugh.
Please take a look at this.
That's ...
Terry is studying drama.
Don't say unnecessary things!
Regardless of how he feels about you...
mother's blood is running through
Terry's body.
Terry...
Candy, if you keep speaking like that...
I... I have no father or mother.
Not that I wanted them too much.
That's right. does it matter
if one has parents or not.
I had friends and kind sisters,
I've never felt lonely.
But once I arrived to Scotland...
You look tired...
When I saw that family,
I felt so jealous.
It doesn't matter how good
your teachers or friends are...
they can never replace a mother.
I... I want a mother.
Any mother would do!
I just want a mother!
Candy!
I was just a little younger than Mark...
when it happened in the port - -
Terry!
Say, who is that woman?
Some stranger.
Terry! Don't take him away!
But she's calling out my name.
Terry! My Terry!
Papa, is that woman...
Terry! Don't take him away!
Look out!
Now, it's too cold on the deck.
Let's go to the cabin.
But...
Terry!
So that was mama.
The real one.
Terry.
Terry!
Our books are exactly alike.
Books?
I wanted to underline all the
important parts but...
you've already underlined everything
for me.
Terry...
I wonder what is going on...
With Terry and his mother.
Candy, is something wrong?
Candy, lately you haven't been
spending your free time with us...
have we hurt you somehow?
Not at all! From tomorrow, I'll spend
my free time with you again!
I'm so glad!
We're lonely without you!
Won't you ride a boat with everybody?
Annie, you've got a tan!
Aww, what'll I do!
There is a good way to protect us
against sun!
Really?
Something to keep the sun away!
Annie, you got sunburnt in the boat?
Of course! Right, Patty?
My, my! What's this
an uniform matching' practice?
Terry!
I'm afraid...
Candy, I'd like to have a word with you.
Annie, Patty, go on without me.
You'll be okay alone?
I'll be with you in a moment!
They think I'm a rabid dog.
Can't blame them...
You're the worst punk in school!
I see. I'm glad you made up with her.
I must thank you.
It was all because of you.
When you say that...
I felt as if I had somehow
trapped her inside my body.
-So your body lighter now, Terry?
-Yeah.
-It's your turn now.
-My turn?
I'm going to free you from your shell.
Now, Candy!
Let go of me, Terry!
Where are you taking me, Terry?
A horse?
-Candy!
-No... I don't like horses!
Horse riding remembers you of Anthony?
No!
You will ride it, Candy!
No! Please! Don't do this, Terry!
I don't want to ride!
Now, let's go!
Please, put me down!
You'll fall if you keep struggling!
The sound of hooves...
on that day...
Look out!
Anthony!
Say it out louder!
Cry out louder!
Stop... I'm begging you!
Cry Anthony's name again!
Cry out to him!
Terry!
If you're so afraid
cry out to Anthony!
Cry out to him anytime! Just call him!
Stop... I'm begging you...
What's the matter, Candy?
Won't you call out his name? Call him!
Stop!
Dead people won't return!
They can't come back!
Forget him!
Wait, Anthony!
Candy! Open your eyes and look!
Now!
Take a good look around yourself!
Don't turn back towards the past
take a good look towards the future!
Green land... dazzling sun...
grass, trees and flowers...
every single of them
is overflowing with life.
Anthony is dead.
But the two of us are still alive.
We're as alive as these trees
grass and flowers.
The burden you're carrying...
Leave it in this forest, Candy!
While Candy was hearing Terry's words...
The sad memories in her heart...
were being slowly taken away from her
into the distance.