Safex
Excitement at the end
of the summer.
After spending three months
in beautiful Scottish countryside...
the end of vacation is almost here.
There is only one week left
before everybody leaves Summer school.
I'm not good at writing, though there's
so much I'd like to write about.
It's impossible to write what happened
in three months within only one week.
Patty? How come you're doing so well?
There's only one thing
I'd like to write about.
Only one? During all this time?
Yes. I only want to write about
how I met a wonderful friend.
A friend?
Alistea...
Don't look!
Sorry, sorry!
I'm glad that
Annie found someone as well.
Candy, you have someone, too?
Me?
Terry.
You've got to be kidding, that punk!
You really think that he's a punk?
Patty, you're all serious!
Candy!
-It's an emergency!
-What's the matter?
Archie will die!
Archie?
Terry is going to kill him!
What do you mean
Terry is going to kill him?
They are duelling!
Duelling?
Hey, Archie!
Why don't you call it a draw?
Okay? Archie?
Bro, pipe down!
I'm going to show this cheeky bastard!
You're only big on your words, boy.
Shut up! I'm going to close that
rude mouth of yours once for all!
-Terry!
-Stop, Archie!
Stop this stupidity, both of you!
-It's dangerous, don't get close!
-You stay away!
They're serious.
Stear, how come this happened?
They wanted to fight each other
for a long time now.
Stear, what is this?
It's a safety armor; my invention!
If something happened to Archie
I would fight Terry instead!
Stear!
Candy, please, make them stop!
It's okay, Annie!
Both of you, hold it!
-Candy!
-What do you think, Patty...
isn't it silly that
we are the only spectators...
so why don't we invite more spectators
from the village?
Hey, Candy!
Stear!
Come! I'm ready!
You've got some guts.
Annie, get a hold of yourself!
Let's call it a draw.
-Annie, pull yourself together!
-Stear! Stear!
-I'm glad.
-Yeah, I'm glad too.
I would've died if Archie got killed.
Why do men do such horrible things?
Candy, isn't there a way
to make them get along?
Hardly!
They didn't fight because one was
clearly wrong and the other was right.
In all, they just couldn't
stand each other, right?
And that's why they duelled?
Probably!
Horrible!
Neither Terry or Archie
are in Summer school.
We can't keep our eyes peeled on them.
Candy, please ask Terry!
What?
To stay away from Archie.
Yes. I'll ask him first thing
in the morning...
Hello, Terry!
Terry is in the hangar!
Where is it?
That way.
An airplane!
Can I help you?
Terry...
What kind of airplane is this?
It's my dad's toy.
But it's become broken-down and useless.
That's it! I'll use this airplane.
Say, Terry... would you like to have
this airplane repaired?
I'm fine with that, but
who would ride it?
I'll stop by later!
-Bye!
-Hey, Candy!
What's up with her?
What? A broken airplane?
It must be Fleet model 1 7!
Stear, you like cars and airplanes?
I love them!
Candy, take me to that place!
Alright!
Brother! You'll go to his place?
I might turn my dream of flying
through the skies into reality!
-Well, Archie?
-No!
-Let's go anyway...
-I won't !
-Hurry!
-Candy
if those two meet again...
It's safer for them to meet
when we are around.
-Hurry up, now!
-Come on!
-Why are you so slow?
-No!
I don't want to see that guy!
Come on!
He even has a Fleet model 1 7!
Does it matter
if you're a bit mad at him?
But even you said that you didn't
want to have anything with that guy!
But it's a whole different story
now that I know of that airplane...
Hurry, this way!
Come on! See, Candy is calling us.
Hey!
Hurry...!
It'll be the first time Terry will
spend time with all of us.
Will Terry give up his stubbornness?
What a wonderful mansion!
I didn't expect anything less!
Where are Stear and Archie?
No! I'm going back!
Archie, if you go back now, it will
look as if you got afraid of him.
Terry!
Terry!!!
Thank you! My heart was going
to split when I heard about this!
Incredible!
This really is Fleet model 1 7!
Patty, won't you pinch me?
I don't want to do such a bad thing...
-I'll pinch you!
-Ow!
It's not a dream! It's really true!
Mr. Terry!
Hear the sound of my pounding heart!
I'm completely indebted to you!
I see you
in a whole different light now!
Thank you for letting me
repair such a treasure!
It's my pleasure...
Let's get down to work!
Archie, help me out here.
Brother!
I'll do all I can to make it fly
while we're still here in Scotland!
-What a grimy place.
-Archie...!
Oh?
American hangars have carpeted floors?
What was that?
Archie! No, Mr. Terry...
as you can see, the manners of my
brother leave something to be desired.
When he acts up, just laugh it off!
-Now, hurry...
-Brother!
It's going well with Archie and Terry.
Candy,
I'd like to have a word with you.
What is it?
How long have you been studying drama?
What do you mean?
You'd better not try to
pull some strange tricks on me.
You knew?
I can easily see through women's tricks
and where they are going.
Terry, I'm not pulling tricks...
Finally, this is the last day of
Summer school.
Meaningfully spend your last day
in Scotland.
-Candice! Annie!
-Yes!
What is it? What are you doing?
Free time... no, I mean
we're talking about studying...
You'll spend your free time inside!
Teacher!
Candy, do you think that Archie
and Terry are fighting again now?
You don't have to worry
while Stear is with them!
Patty will be back soon.
It's probably nothing but...
Patty! How did it go?
So they duelled again?
When I went to the mansion
I ran into Eliza...
Eliza?
Go back.
Why?
Tell Candy that she'd better remember
that I am the one whom Terry likes.
Eliza thinks that Terry likes her?
That's a good one!
But you don't know what Terry thinks.
Say, you don't know what's going on
with Archie and others?
It looked like that they will
repairing that airplane overnight.
Overnight?
He's trying to make that plane airworthy
while we are still in Scotland.
Archie, take off that lever...
We need to complete the overhaul
till dawn.
We'll pull yet another all-nighter?
Don't complain
one more night won't hurt you.
Brother, I'm tired of this!
You were all over that guy
with your compliments!
Archie, do I look like the kind of man
who'd flatter other people?
But you were fawning over Terry!
I was just sincerely thanking him.
Why would you want to thank that guy?
A real man doesn't sneak around
badmouthing other people.
Don't tell me that a real man
would be eavesdropping then?
Alright! Come get some!
Stop that, Archie!
Mr. Terry, my little brother is quick
to pick a fight... please, forgive him.
Brother! I'm not going to
put up with him anymore!
Same here!
You're pretty good, boy.
You too, Terry!
Stop that! The precious airplane will...
Look out, Archie!
Terry?
If you got killed, I would have
lost my fighting companion.
Terry?
Today's lecture is over.
Annie, Patty, it's finally time to
put our plan into action.
Tonight?
If somebody sees us...
They can't punish us...
because we'll be leaving Scotland
by tomorrow morning.
That's right.
Huh?
I've never pushed such a cart before!
Good thing that we have moonlight.
I'm sure I'll never forget this night!
-But still, we look like thieves!
-Aww, Candy!
Brother, give up!
My stamina is gone after working
all night long...
Mr. Terry.
Could you please excuse my brother
today?
He's too tired to fight you.
My enemy is the engine over there.
Mr. Terry.
You want to get it flying
by tomorrow morning?
-Thank you.
-Archie!
One, two, three...
Say, it turned out like this...
It's better that way!
I've never cooked before...
Annie, soup!
Oh, no!
Now, engine test!
Strange.
Now!
It's running!
Candy!
Congratulations, Stear!
The meal is ready!
Great!
I like this.
What's this?
I'm sorry!
Look, the dawn.
Now, it's a new day
let's do some miracles!
Do your best, everybody!
Candy, what are you doing?
I'm giving you the tempo!
One - two! One - two!
But you only move your mouth, right?
That's right! Oh, no!
This direction is good.
Now, let's fly!
-Stear, will you be okay?
-Sure thing!
I'll give it a spin through the air.
Brother, let's go!
Alright! Archie, do it!
Okay! One, two, three...
Stear, don't do anything unreasonable!
Don't get hurt, okay?
Now, let's fly!
He did it!
Stear's airplane is really flying!
I lose.
I didn't think it would've flown.
Hey, I'm flying!
Stear!
-Stear!
-I'm okay.
Stear!
Well? I'm pretty sure it was flying...
Yeah, it was flying!
Right through the air!
That airplane wound up
like my father's youth.
Your father's ...?
Back in the days while he was
flying that airplane...
my father fell in love with a woman
from America.
And thus I was born.
And then, he gave up the skies.
He didn't marry my real mother.
Why was that?
He didn't want to ruin his
noble bloodline.
I didn't want to follow
my father's way of life.
I always wanted to be honest to myself.
Terry is not a punk.
He just wanted to be true to himself.
-Candy, let's dance.
-Terry?
To remember Scotland.
Why did you stop so suddenly...?
Terry...
You punk!
You're horrible! Punk, after all!
A playboy!
Now I'm a playboy? A punk?
How can you say that?
You're a punk because you are one!
I was just being honest to myself.
You're horrible... rude...
Terry, I hate you!
One after another
tears filled Candy's gaze...
until she could see no more.
The wind fluttered Terry's hair
somehow felt cold...
autumn was drawing near.