Safex
In order to give the turtle to
Mr. Albert...
Candy secretly escaped from the
contemplation room.
It turned out that
Terry was at Albert's place, too.
Candy got into a fight with Terry
over Anthony.
Mr. Albert found that
Candy was banned from the May festival.
He was very disappointed.
And so, the day of May festival
is finally here.
Fairy of the school festival.
So pretty.
I was supposed to be on that float.
Poor Candy.
Can't you help her
with some invention?
I could've gotten a good idea
if I had more time...
So you're saying that it's impossible?
Exactly.
I can't have any fun knowing that
Candy is so unhappy.
We too.
Candy!
Patty!
They'll scold you if they find you here!
But... this was my fault
I'm sorry...
I've taken care of Yuli.
How?
I escaped through that window.
Candy!
Don't worry, Yuli is in very good hands.
Candy, thank you!
Now, Patty, leave quickly
before somebody sees you.
I brought you a package and a letter
which arrived for you!
For me?
Here.
I brought it to you because I thought
you'd be impatient to see what it was!
Thank you!
Well then, Candy, I'm off!
Thank you, Patty!
I wonder who sent it...
It's from grandfather William!
Miss Candice White Adley
Mr. William is unable to attend
because of work.
To compensate for this, he ordered me
to send you these dresses.
Mr. William is delighted that
you are becoming a beautiful lady.
George.
I'm so glad!
Grandfather William isn't mad.
Huh? What kind of costumes are these?
A male and a female costume packed
next to each other.
They look like they are for
Romeo and Juliet.
There's even a wig in here!
Grandfather William couldn't
remember if I was a boy or a girl?
Men's clothes...
But it's a good idea!
Terrius!
What's the meaning of this?
-Terrius!
-Strange!
He'll participate in May festival?
Where'd she go?
She appears to have slipped
out of the contemplation room...
Don't tell me that she simply
waltzed into this hall...
I had a feeling
that she would've escaped...
Terrius.
I'm looking for a dance partner.
Won't you dance with me?
Oh, I'm honoured.
But I have a bad habit of
stepping on one's feet while dancing.
Lady, it would've been inexcusable
of me to step on your feet.
Please, find a different partner.
What a guy!
Neil was right about him.
But he called me a lady...
Maybe this is a good place to jump down.
May festival is going smoothly.
I don't want this ruckus
to turn into a tradition.
Excuse me!
That boy... I don't remember
seeing him in our school...
Dangerous...!
I'd better keep my cover.
But not even sister Gray noticed!
Annie?
-Miss, would you like to dance?
-But...
Annie, it's me!
Candy!
I'm glad you escaped!
Say, Annie... do you remember?
Back when we were little...
We were always together!
We held each others' hands like this
and ran around Pony's hill!
Candy, you!
Sorry.
-Say, who is dancing with Annie?
-Dunno...
He's handsome!
Now that Candy isn't around
Annie is getting all the attention.
Archie, I thought that
you were dancing with Annie!
He's handsome! Who is he?
Hey... let's trade places.
Oh, Archie! You're welcome!
Who was he?
-Stear! It's me!
-Hah?
What a surprise!
It's a present from grandfather William!
The costumes of Romeo and Juliet.
Grandfather William sure gives out
some strange presents!
I was able to come here because of him!
-I'd like to tell you some news.
-What?
Thanks to grandfather William
Aunt Elroy didn't get mad either.
Really?
Now I can dance without worry!
Stear?
Isn't it boring for
two guys to dance together?
Won't you dance with Louise?
Please.
Uh... I will.
Won't you dance with me?
I'm very sorry, miss...
but I just remembered something - -
Please, pick another partner.
He's avoiding me, exactly like Terrius.
But... who was he?
Disguising as Romeo was a huge success!
Candy!
How did she escape
from the contemplation room?
That's right...
what will happen if I blow her cover
in front of everybody?
Now, let's change into Juliet.
This is much more fun than just dancing!
Grandfather William, I'm so grateful!
If I get into trouble,
I'll be able to make a run for it!
Now, back to the hall!
Nobody will know that I broke free
from the contemplation room.
Let's go!
Did you bring a monkey costume, too?
Freckled Tarzan.
Te-Terrius! You were watching
while I was changing?
You were in my sight
but I wasn't looking.
You're rude!
On a different note...
Eliza found out the secret of Romeo.
Eliza?
Say, have you prepared the
contemplation room?
I made it look like I was in bed...
You'll be okay then.
Eliza won't be coming back.
For the time being
let's go to your Pony's hill.
What a wonderful day!
I feel great!
Once,
I went for a picnic on a day like this.
I was two or maybe three years old...
I don't remember very well...
but the sky looked exactly like this
And I played cheerfully.
The smiles of my dad and mom...
their happiness is the only memory
that hasn't faded with time.
Mom... actress Eleanor Baker.
She must have been a gentle
wonderful mother.
Those are beautiful memories!
I'm jealous!
I only remember that day.
Remembering just one day is enough!
On the other hand
I don't have any memories!
Say, Terry, promise
we'll go for a picnic one day!
Candy.
This is...
I danced with Anthony to this music.
It's a nice melody.
It would be my honour, princess Juliet!
May I ask for a dance?
Memories are coming back...
this green grass...
sunlight streaming through leaves...
But the one who's here is Terry.
However...
He has Anthony's gentle smile.
What's the matter?
I danced with Anthony for the first time
to this music...
Terry?
Anthony again?
Please stop comparing me to him!
Terry!
He's dead!
He fell off a horse and died!
Don't say that, Terry!
The dead don't come back to life!
Stop! I hate you!
Terry, I hate you!
Yes! You keep thinking about
that dead guy...
I hate people who are like that!
Eliza, are you sure it was Candy?
Of course I am!
Maybe you were mistaken?
Anyway, wait and see.
I'll tear the mask off your face.
Eliza... she thinks I'm still wearing
the Romeo costume.
Didn't notice me at all!
Stear! Archie!
Candy!
I'm Juliet.
Candy, this costume suits you better.
Many people have gathered in the garden.
Yes, the guests are pouring in.
The guests...
I feel so sorry for Mr. Albert!
He looked so disappointed.
I always wanted to see him
in dress clothes!
Patty is alone?
-Patty!
-Ca...!
You escaped just to come here?
Your grandmother didn't come?
Yes, she had some urgent matters
to sort out...
But now that you're here
I won't be alone anymore!
I promised that
I'd introduce you to Stear.
Candy...!
Now, princess Juliet
the dance is about to begin!
Hurry!
Uh, Stear!
Sorry, I'll introduce you two
when the dance is over.
Nobody was able to tell that I'm Candy.
This is so much fun!
Patty and Stear are dancing together!
-Forgive me...
-Uh, me too...
Uh, my glasses fell somewhere
around here...
And my glasses...
-You wear glasses too?
-Yes.
You look so cute without glasses!
And you look very handsome this way!
In that case, let's dance like this!
The two of you
won't you move aside a bit?
That's right, you're bothering others.
And I still haven't introduced them
to each other.
Eliza, Candy isn't going to come.
This is strange...
Maybe you were mistaken, after all?
that's it. Let's make sure
to the contemplation room.
But you can't freely go up there!
Leave it to me!
-Bro, you're a great dancer!
-But you know...
Sister Gray!
-You'd better hide.
-It's okay!
Sister Gray!
Sister Gray
we'd like to ask you something.
What is it?
We'd like to take some fruit to Candy
she's in the contemplation room.
Poor Candy...
Very well.
I'll respect your kind thoughts.
You have my approval.
We can open the cell and go inside?
Yes.
But don't talk to her too long.
You mustn't interrupt her contemplation.
Yes, sister Gray!
This is bad!
Candy, you must return to the cell
before Eliza gets there!
We'll try to hold them off a bit!
-Candy, hurry!
-Yes!
Just wait and see.
-There's no way that Candy is in there.
-Eliza!
Wait!
What is it?
Are you going to see Candy?
It doesn't concern you
where we are going.
Won't you let us go as well?
I'll ask for permission
could you wait a bit?
Fishy.
Stop trying to hold us off
to buy her time!
Eliza!
Wait!
Please! Eliza, wait!
Shut up!
Damn! Turned up just a second too late!
Candy!
Of course, you're not going to answer.
She must be sound asleep.
We can't know like this.
That is, unless I uncover her.
See, she is here!
Eliza, you were mistaken, after all.
I'm sure she escaped somehow!
I won't forget this, Candy!
This was close!
Candy!
Then... who is in your bed?
Terrius?
Just what I thought!
Without me, You'll get trouble.
Freckled Tarzan!
I snuck in here since I expected that
something like this would've happened.
Thank you, Terry!
Candy!
I finally found you!
You're supposed to be
in the contemplation room...
what are you doing here then?
I allowed her to.
Sister Gray!
Terrius G. Grandchester was the director
of this year's school festival.
Now that the festival is over
Candice White Adley
is free to join all activities.
-Candy!
-I'm so glad!
Thank you!
Everybody, thank you!
The flame of resistance
burned brightly in Candy's heart.