Safex
Candy went back to Pony' s home
where she left for a long time.
She brush past with Terry.
Candy understand that
Terry wants to earn his own living.
She makes a decision for herself
she can't be defeated by Terry.
The naughty teacher.
Here.
Kurin.
Are you oKay? Kurin.
Candy,
sister Pony' s looking for you.
Ok. That's the end of today.
Keep me at home alone?
No, with other children.
Sister Pony and I
have to attend a meeting.
Greeting to those people who helped us.
Go ahead! Leave everything to me.
That' s great!
Cany is not a girl anymore.
you' re a lady now.
It' s embarrassing.
-Please, then.
-Ok.
I' ll be your teacher today,
nice to meet you.
It would be funny today.
I' m a teacher,
how can you do this to me?
Just for fun.
Just for fun?
You bad...
So. You want to be hostile to me?
Attack! Everybody!
Somebody in the house.
Why don't you play with everybody?
Tiny can't come out.
Why?
She is uncomfortable.
Uncomfortable... where?
I don't know. Watch out!
Candy, over here quickly!
Just a moment.
Won't you Come out?
to play with everybody.
Tiny! You can't hide indoor forever.
Can I go out?
Certainly!
Teacher, we' re ready.
Ready! Start to climb the tree.
Keep the distance!
Kurin' s the winner.
Tiny, do you want to climb the tree?
I can't.
Nobody can climb trees innately.
When I was a child,
there is a girl just like you.
Her name is Annie.
Annie is timid.
After practising,
she climbed up the big tree at last.
We sit on the tree together,
looking at the beautiful world.
Teacher, I like to try.
Let' s go.
-Tiny can't do this.
-No.
Why?
If she gets hurt,
sister Pony will be angry.
Don't worry, I' m good at tree climbing.
Tiny, take some deep breath!
Let' s challenge it. Step on my back.
-But...
-Come.
Launch your hands and help her.
Here, give me your hand.
Tiny is coming up.
Try yourself from there.
You must do it by yourself.
Go! Tiny, do your best.
Yes, teacher.
Tiny, do your best!
Tiny, are you ok?
I am fine.
-Tiny, do your best!
-It' s almost there.
Tiny!
Tiny, do your best!
-Tiny, are you ok?
-I' m fine.
Tiny, you make it.
Tiny, well done!
Teacher...
It' s like a dream,
sitting here watching the Pony' s home.
Where there is a will,
there is a way.
Yes! I feel like a bird.
A bird?
The bird always enjoys the scenery
in the height.
It makes sense.
Pony' s home looks like a dream land.
Tiny, shout loudly!
How?
Like this...
Louder!
Tiny shouted so loudly.
Mr. Matthew.
It' s Candy, still so naughty.
That one nearby...
Tiny, it' s Tiny.
Candy, Stop that! Tiny' s sick!
Candy, Let her down, Quickly!
Mr. Mathew, you want to come up?
It feels so good up here.
Is that right? Tiny
Tiny.
It' s alright!
I climbed the tree for the first time...
What's the matter? Tiny!
Candy, Tiny' s fainted.
Everybody come to help.
Yes!
Fortunately, she is not hurt.
What disease has she suffered from?
Hemophilia.
Hemophilia?
If she injured,
the blood will flow incessantly.
You shoudn't let her climb the tree.
I do not know that.
You must not let her climb the tree.
Tiny can't climb the tree,
she should know that.
Tiny, I am sorry for that.
Bird! I want to be a bird.
Tiny, the doctor' s coming now.
Looks like she has a fever.
Teacher... Candy...
Tiny, I' m not a good teacher.
Doctor' s coming. Hurry up!
-Mr. Matthew!
-Please! Doctor.
No injured?
Candy
help me to open the suitcase.
How is Tiny? Doctor.
There is no life danger.
Doctor,
the hemophilia is really hopeless?
At present,
there' s no suitable treatment.
This kind of disease,
usually happened to the adult.
She' s so young, what a pity!
Well, I should leave now.
Thank you, Mr. Matthew.
It' s nothing.
We should help each other.
But, Mr. Matthew, aren't you
coming here to deliver the letters?
That' s right!
Candy, a letter from London.
From London?
It' s Annie.
The teacher's friend?
Tiny, You have woken up.
Candy, I don't know that
if you were in Pony' s home or not.
So I wrote this letter.
London is foggy now.
The St. Paul academy is also.
The fog came deep inside
to the heart of Pattie and I.
Stear and Archie became Listless.
The school became lonely without you.
Your seat is still empty.
Pattie and I hoping that
someone can fill in that vacancy.
Everytime I looking at that vacancy.
I missed you so much,
the tears flow without end.
Candy, If you receive this letter
Please write back as soon as possible.
Please tell me your whereabouts,
Annie.
-Annie.
-How nice!
The teacher's friend?
That' s right,
Tiny will have a good friend, too.
No way!
Why?
-I am sick.
-It doesn't matter.
I can't play with everybody.
Can't play with others,
you still can have friends.
Didn't Annie ever played with you?
This...
You played together all the time.
I can't even play with others.
Tiny.
You' re back, sister Pony.
Thank you, Mr. Morely.
Good-bye, sister.
What happened to Tiny?
Something happened.
I am sorry,
I don't know that Tiny' s sick.
No, It' s our fault.
You have no idea about her condition.
Tiny' s so sick,
How can you take her to climb the tree.
Maybe we should tell the children
about Tiny' s situation.
Yes, In case of she got injured...
Who is it?
Tiny.
What are you doing?
You should stay on bed.
Sister Pony, sister Lane,
please don't blame Candy teacher.
Tiny.
No! We didn't.
That's great!
Come, back to your room.
-Will you stay with me?
-Certainly.
Tiny, sleep already?
No, I can't fell asleep.
Why?
I' m trying to remember
the scenery on the tree.
Teacher,
can I see that scenery tomorrow?
You can see that everyday.
I' d like to become a bird
one more time.
She' s up already?
Good morning!
It is cold.
You must clean your face.
-Good morning, everybody.
-Good morning!
Where Is Tiny?
-I don't know.
-I do not know either.
Nobody knows.
Toilet maybe!
Candy, what happened?
I can't find Tiny.
Tiny?
Kurin.
Have you found her?
Tiny.
Come down!
You do it by yourself?. Tiny.
That' s right, I can see the scenery now.
The place where the sun rises.
It' s so beautiful.
Candy, go help her.
Tiny.
It would be awful,
if the blood keep flowing.
Awful?
Isn't there styptic medicine?
I have already done the best.
Please, doctor.
There' s nothing I can do.
climbing the tree...
It' s all my fault.
Candy!
Tiny.
-What should we do?
-Is she keep bleeding?
The doctor said...
It exceeds 1/3 to lose blood
The life will be dangerous.
Will Tiny die?
If she keeps on bleeding...
She' s so pity, What should we do?
I got it!
We can give her our blood.
-That' s right!
-I' ll do that.
Count me in.
Let' s talk to the doctor.
No way!
It doesn't work
Sister Lane!
Why can't we?
Your blood type are unknown.
You can't do the blood transfusing
with wrong blood type.
How can we have the type test?
We don't have the equipment
in the village.
And Tiny...
She will be fine. Come!
Let' s pray to God,
Bless Tiny to fully recover.
Okay!
Let' s do the pray.
This kind of wound
would never hurt any common people.
Why is there this kind of disease
in the world?
Candy, take some rest,
I' ll deal with it.
No, I' m fine.
You can't cut off the pray,
Tiny' s in danger.
God, I am sorry.
You' re still a baby, York, go to bed!
I' m okay.
It' s stopped.
Sister Pony!
Just let her sleep, It' s okay now!
Thank you!
That's great!
That's great! Tiny.
Do you hear that? Tiny.
They are all your friends.
My friends?
Yes, all are your friends.
They pray for you all night.
They are your friends.
They' re willing to give you their blood,
they are your friends.
Candy teacher,
I climb the tree by myself.
Yes, and you saw the sunrise.
Candy teacher!
Go write the letter
to your friend in London.
It' s already done,
I won't upset my good friend.
I never know that
Tiny can sing so loud.
Candy,
you are my teacher this time.
Sister Pony.
We've been protect her too much.
She lose the confidence of life
instead.
Candy keeps thinking about...
Because of her careless,
almost kill Tiny' s life.
There are all kinds of terrible disease
in the world.
Candy keeps it in her heart...