Safex
It is the first time for Terry
to be the main actor.
He reserved the best seat for Candy.
Suzanna cried and asked Terry
not to...
invite Candy.
A treatment stimulated by love.
Please, Terry.
Do you have to invite her?
Suzanna,
why are you so against Candy?
Terry.
I like you, Terry, I love you.
Suzanna,
The first time I saw you, I...
Excuse me,
is this the Stellas troupe?
I am here for the acting test.
I knew at that moment that
this person would be chosen.
After that, you played a
supporting role in King Lear.
I was so happy.
Standing on the stage with you,
I felt so blessed.
I don't care about the long trips.
With your company,
I always felt so happy.
Then Candy suddenly showed up
when we arrived Chicago.
You saw Candy? When?
She came to the hotel to look for you.
I sent her back.
I got her away with lies.
You are angry.
You can blame me for everything.
Sorry, I know I made a mistake.
I didn't want her to
steal your heart away.
Tell me, your real feeling.
I have always...
Don't!
I will never give up my love
for you!
Whether it's Candy
or anyone else.
Suzanna.
I don't hate you.
But, my heart has always
been occupied by Candy alone.
The first time I met her
on the ship.
It is true that I already
fell in love with her at that time.
My love for her will never change.
Good morning.
Let me do it.
It's ok, go ahead and eat.
You are late for the hospital.
Sorry I overslept.
You seem like you didn't sleep well.
I had nightmares.
You called Terry's name
at least twenty to thirty times.
Really?
Just kidding.
Mr.Albert is so naughty.
I don't know what you dreamed.
Believe Terry.
He will give you the free ticket.
Of course I believe him.
You've got me.
Candy, look!
Pattie.
Is it her?
What brought you here so early?
I am here for you
For me?
Stear...
What's wrong with Stear?
He is going into the army.
The army?
He is going to be a soldier?
How would that be possible?
Stear can't even fight.
Archie and Annie
kept trying to convince him.
Stear just didn't want to
hear anything.
I didn't think he would insist on
doing this so much.
If you go talk to him,
maybe he will accept your opinion.
Ok, I'll go at noon.
Thank you, Candy.
Your temperature is ok now.
I want to leave here
to see my grandson.
Your grandson?
Yes. His name is Terry.
Terry?
Why are you all blushed?
He must be a good kid.
Of course.
What happened?
A fire?
Everyone, please keep calm.
It's Stear.
Be quiet.
Don't worry, everyone.
It's alright. It'll be fixed soon.
Sorry. It was usually ok.
It was broken as soon as
it got to the hospital.
Stear, I heard
you were joining the army?
Who told you?
Don't make Pattie sad.
Nosy.
Pattie is very worried about you.
Candy, I have decided.
Stear,
do you really understand war?
I read the newspapers.
But, Mr.Albert
lost his memory in the war.
Some of the army nurses that
the hospital sent died in the war, too.
More and more people will sacrifice
their lives in the war.
Stear.
If we don't seize the war.
America will become the war zone
one day.
America?
I have to fight the war in Europe
because of this.
Why do you must go?
Candy.
You want me to hide here
to invent some stupid things,
and live an easy life?
Of course not.
I am not afraid of death.
Good-bye.
Stear.
Pattie.
Pattie, everything will be fine.
I don't want to lose Stear.
I don't want him to fight in the war.
Maybe
Mr.Albert can convince Stear.
But, Mr.Albert...
I have to try to help him
regain his memory.
The treatment for Amnesia...
To stimulate the patient
is one way of treatment.
I got it,
the stimulation treatment!
I am back!
Didn't scare him at all.
Kids'trick.
It has to be successful this time!
Mr.Albert, can you help me?
No problem.
I am going to set the table.
It feels strange.
What do we have for dinner?
Candy,
are we having popcorn for dinner?
Still not responding.
Have a seat first.
What's going on?
Sit down first.
Ouch!
I am sorry, Mr.Albert.
I want to help you
regain your memory.
The sound of a train.
There is a sound
of a train in my mind.
The train Mr.Albert took
was attacked and exploded.
Mr.Albert is remembering it.
Sorry, I did it too hard.
No, my head is hurting so much!
The things happened in the train,
you can remember them now?
No, just the sound.
You just heard the sound?
And other sounds, too.
I also heard them.
Mr.Albert, there is a fire!
Candy, the window!
It's Stear's car.
Is it...
That smoke...
Stear
-What's going on?
-Nothing.
Just an experiment.
Idiot!
My Rider One.
I see. You are trying to help
Mr.Albert to regain his memory,
The book said that rebuilding the
setting at the time memory lost
is helpful for memory restoration,
so I...
I've always wanted to stop you.
Listen! I'll get you out of here
if you ever make trouble again.
Really sorry about it.
We'll pay attention.
Please forgive our naughty acts.
Are you saying that
you did soemthing, too?
No.I am gonna go make some tea.
Thank you
for caring about my health.
No, I...
I hope you can convince Stear
not to go to the frontline.
Brother needs a favor from you.
What is it?
I hope Mr.Albert can help me
convince Grand Aunt Elroy.
Grand Aunt Elroy is against
Stear's going into the army.
Of course!
Mr.Albert
must understand my feeling.
Stear,
I am afraid I will let you down.
Right. Who would want you
to fight in the war?
The Mr.Albert now
may agree with me.
If Mr.Albert has his memory back,
he will support me.
How could this be possible?
There are no inland doctors in Africa.
Didn't Mr.Albert
took part in that, too?
What I am thinking now, is just like
what Mr.Albert was thinking then.
I was a doctor in Africa?
You will understand me
when you have your memory back.
Candy.
Can you understand why
Brother pretended there was a fire?
I see.
We all want to help Mr.Albert,
with different purposes.
The war occupies Stear's mind now.
He only wants to go to the frontline.
Pattie, calm down!
Let's have a picnic
for our next vacation.
Thank you, but I am not
in the mood right now.
Pattie, do you still remember
the summer school in Scotland?
We were without worry,
spending each day happily.
It's breaking down.
Brother, is it alright?
Stear, come on!
There is no other way.
The girls stay in the car,
the boys push the car.
Leave it to me.
Archie, Mr.Albert.
Boys should get off and push the car.
Candy,
do you really think you are a boy?
I made a mistake.
Thanks for the work, Mr.Albert.
I prepared some cocoa.
Let me peel the apples.
I'll help.
You should take a rest
once in a while.
Once in a while?
Mr.Albert cooks most of the time?
oops!
Mr.Albert is feeling better.
Doesn't look like a patient
from room zero at all.
With such a nice weather and scenery,
anyone would want to stay alive.
Candy, thank you for everything
you've done to me.
This is good enough.
Mr.Albert, the lunch is ready.
Stear, hurry,
the cocoa is getting cold!
I am coming!
Thanks.
Candy.
I have a new invention,
watch it clearly.
Stear, what are you doing?
Mr.Albert, how do you feel?
The is a memory restoration machine
that I invented.
Nonsense, Stear!
This is made by rubber,
it won't hurt.
It has a trick here.
It will jump off when pressed.
Just the noise is kind of loud.
My head is not hurting,
but my butt is.
Sorry, Mr.Albert.
Candy has tried
the stimulation treatment.
Candy does violent stuff, too?
No... I...
Pattie.
You eat first.
Stear, you are thinking about the war
even on a picnic.
Pattie.
We are supposed to be happy today.
I...
Pattie, it will be fine.
Mr.Albert wouldn't encourage Stear
to go to the war,
even if he restored his memory.
You don't need to worry about it.
Everyone is waiting for you.
Come on, let's go back!
Mr. Thomas?
Pattie, I'll be right back,
you can go first.
Mr. Thomas.
My wife and my son
are buried on the hill.
You came to sweep the tomb?
I saw them being burned to death.
It was twenty years ago,
but it feels like yesterday.
I often awaken
in the middle of the night.
Sometimes
I envy Mr.Albert so much.
To lose memory?
Mr.Albert lost his memory,
because he didn't want to
remember the pain in the past.
You tried so hard to help him.
Once he is recovered,
all the bad memory will come back.
Mr. Thomas is right.
All we did,
may only make it
more painful for Mr.Albert.
Good afternoon, Mr. Thomas.
Let's have the meal together.
No, thanks.
You are...
We see each other every morning.
It really is you.
Every morning?
I go to the church to pray
every morning.
Pray for my daughter's safety
in Italy.
Pattie prays for Stear everyday?
It doesn't matter
if Stear hates me or not.
I only hope you can stay alive.
Pattie.
Stear, I am actually half alive.
Before, how did I spend my days?
How did I think?
I don't remember either of them.
There is only one thing
I am sure about.
Even if I regained my memory,
I wouldn't support your decision
of going into the war
Mr.Albert.
He seems to be recovering.
Stear starts to wonder
if his decision is right.
Seeing Pattie and Stear
getting back together,
makes Candy want to fly to Broadway
right now,
to stay with Terry.