Safex
Candy saved a girl
on the train with her kind heart.
Candy knew a boy called Dell
on the train.
And continued their journey.
A beautiful competitor.
Dell, orange yard.
We can reach them with our hands.
Dell, are you ok?
You are so obsessed with you job.
But...
I am so jealous of you.
Why?
You can head back to Chicago
as soon as you deliverd the documents.
And meet up with your boy friend
in Broadway.
Dell,
Nothing to bother about.
You too.
I can't go back to Chicago.
Just seeking help from people.
Your uncle works in
newspaper company?
That's so good for you.
Dell, I was adopted when I was little.
Was it hard for you?
Of course it was hard for me.
But I felt happy sometimes.
Look, Dell, the sea.
It's my first time
to see such beautiful coast.
Feel so good, so comfortable...
Candy,
Florida is still summer,
America is so big.
Here we are, good luck
Take care, Dell.
Are you going to your uncle's house
Yes.
Good bye.
Thank you for everything,
Candy.
Be good, Dell.
Time to go.
Houses here are so beautiful.
Villas all over.
Kids from the Pony's home
will love this place.
Kurin and Mina,
how are they now?
Where is principal Clairs' villa?
I guess it's here.
Excuse me...
Principal's daughter?
You had a long journey,
you must be tired.
Are you principal?
Nice to see you,
I am Candice White.
Candy,
How's it going?
Good and bad.
Excuse me...
Reknapp made a good decision.
Why is that?
I asked him to send
a strong nurse here
Strong?
You are strong.
You should stay here for a few months.
That's too long.
You are going to like this place.
But I need to go Broadway
next week.
What a coincidence,
The patient you will be looking after
just came back from Broadway.
She is my relative's daughter,
she is very naughty.
You are welcome.
Yes.
Did Karen eat anything?
No, just some crepes.
That's not good.
What is wrong with her?
Karen doesn't need
doctors or medicine.
She needs a friend.
But just like I said...
The current situation shows that
Karen might kill herself.
Suicide? Why?
She just won't speak.
Maybe a young friend could
open her heart.
Karen, it's me, open the door.
She shut herself in the room
whole day.
You said she was from Broadway.
Karen was an actress
from teh Stellas troupe.
Stellas troupe?
Terry's troupe.
You know about it?
That's great.
Karen, Candy from Chicago
heard about your troupe.
-Karen,
-Uncle don't come in.
-But...
-Come in.
Sorry to disturb you.
Did uncle tell you anything?
Nothing, he just thought
you might be bored.
Let me tell you,
I am not sick at all.
Just protesting silently.
Principal is worried about you.
You heard about Stellas troupe?
I watched their show
in Chicago's Elmoe Theater.
King Leo.
That's was a bad performance.
I don't know much about play.
I am sure you could tell.
That actress didn't know how to act.
Which actress?
Suzanna.
Suzanna Marlu of course.
Suzanna?
An amateur playing Juliet,
come on.
So she was Suzanna's rival.
You had the same thought, right?
Sit down.
Thank you.
Did you know the reason why
I couldn't play Juliet?
Because Suzanna would do anything
to get the role.
Harry Grant and Suzanna Marlu.
I can do better if I
work with Terrius
She is obsessed with Terry.
Terry?
No, Mr. Terry.
He has a bright future.
I thought so.
But Suzanna used him.
Suzanna used Terry?
Would she?
I will never lose to Suzanna
if we are talking about talents.
The showbiz is complicated.
Sooner or later
I will show my talents to Suzanna.
Let's go get something to eat.
I...
To thank you for bearing with
my complaints.
Karen said she wanted to eat?
Yes.
Great,
it's so good to have you here.
Principal,
I would like to go back tomorrow.
You don't need to be that hurry.
I must go back...
No.
I want you to stay here for a while.
Is there any problem, uncle.
Candy, I will inform Reknapp.
What should I do?
I need to leave
before tomorrow noon.
Otherwise
I will miss Terry's show.
What a nice restaurant.
I know what you are thinking.
You must be thinking about Terry.
-No,
-Stop pretending.
You called him Terry just now.
I...
You and Terry must be very close.
Are you in a rush to Broadway?
Karen.
I think you better give up.
Why?
I am not against you and Terry.
So why?
I want the audience to be less
when Suzanna is performing.
This is not a reason.
Before the show ends
you will stay here.
You will see Terry
whenever you want after that.
Terry has sent the invitation
to Chicago.
I must go to Broadway tomorrow.
I can't stay here and
waste my time with her.
Please be quiet.
Candy,
Good night.
Practising your tricks?
What do you think?
This is Florida's fruit wine.
Thank you.
I didn't know
you love Terry so much.
I didn't.
Stop pretending.
I am an actress,
I saw you through straight away.
Please let me go to Broadway.
I am sorry but
I am afraid Terry won't
Why?
There is a rumour
in the Stellas troupe,
The actor and actress
playing Romeo and Juliet,
will eventually fall in love.
How is that possible?
Captain's Robert's wife.
She used to play the role Juliet.
The same for everybody else.
Terry and Suzanna
have been practising day and night.
That's it.
We both lost to Suzanna.
Good bye.
I don't believe in rumours.
I just believe Terry.
Terrius believes in me too.
Terry.
Adjust the lighting
more to the right.
And focus on those two people.
Let's do it again.
Romeo and Juliet
come up to each other.
Start from the banquet.
What a beautiful princess,
so elegant and gorgeous
like a diamond.
I never fell for anyone
until this moment.
Only this princess...
Terry, watch out!
Suzanna!
It's dawn.
Terry,
I guess he finished his rehearsal.
Terry, watch out!
Despite her tiny size,
she sacrificed herself to save me.
Suzanna, you can't die.
Candy.
Dell, it's you.
Good morning, I will be delivering
newspapers today onwards.
So many newspapers?
Right, let me help you.
Can you do it? Candy.
No problem.
Wait for me, Candy.
Quick, we can't be late.
-I am relieved now.
-Why?
You looked upset just now,
I was worried.
You look so energetic.
Uncle has been good to me.
Let's carry on.
Ok.
Doctor, Suzanna...
She is fine.
Thank you.
But her right leg...
Right leg?
I did what I could do.
She needs to have amputation
in order to live.
Amputation?
Suzanna.
Poor girl.
Suzanna was trying to save me...
That's it.
Thanks.
So lucky to have you to help.
Work hard!
You going back today? Candy.
I was.
Not going back anymore?
No, I have to go back.
I must let them know my situation.
I have confirmed the documents.
I will go back to Chicago
in next year's spring.
I can go back to Chicago?
Karen is fine now
Karen?
She went back to New York
this morning.
Come and gone.
She went back to Broadway.
Miss Karen? Yes.
Got this morning message
from New York.
What it says?
Maybe boy friend.
She looked nervous.
No wonder.
Back to Chicago and
heading towards Broadway.
Finally Candy is going to meet Terrius
Candy didn't know,
Karen is going to replace Suzanna
and perform the show in Broadway.
She has no idea,
At the other end
of this warm south country,
The freezing Broadway
is awaiting her visit.