Safex
A rose-scented birthday.
It's Annie's ribbon.
Lightly tied to the barn,
there was Annie's ribbon.
It was a seal of friendship for
two girls who grew up together.
Good night, Candy.
God, please take care after me,
Annie Brighton, and Candice White.
Let us always be happy.
Slept well! Huh?
What a nice smell!
Is it Annie's ribbon?
It's not it!
Roses!
Anthony!
Anthony must have brought
them here!
I slept sound and
didn't hear anything...
Oh, no! Anthony must have seen
me in an embarrassing pose!
What'll I do?
She won't even notice if I turn
this into a prank.
Look, some are missing!
Anthony, does it matter if one
or two got stolen?
So many are blooming now!
But whoever came in here must
have known what he was doing!
That's right! He must knew that
these roses more than anything to me.
Anthony, maybe you picked them
yourself and then forgot about it?
I wouldn't do such a violent thing!
Roses are living creatures, too!
Hey, brother!
What is it, Archie?
Don't tell me that you took these
roses as a present for Candy!
Archie, just why would I want to
take these to Candy?
If I'd give someting to her, then it
would've been one of my inventions!
-But...!
-Archie!
How many times
have I told you!
Now you're getting upset over this!
Suspicious!
-What?
-Stop that!
I don't think
either one of you did this!
Of course!
But I won't forgive the one
who did this to my roses.
Good day, Anthony.
Look what the cat brought in.
You look surprised.
What did you want, Eliza?
I made a tasty pie
and I'd take it to Anthony.
We've got some things to do.
Let's go, Stear.
We'll be at Candy's place.
Anthony, let's go to your room.
I'm not in the mood for pie.
Are you saying that you won't eat
this because Candy didn't make it?
Anyway, I don't want to eat it.
Anthony
You like Candy that much?
Stop saying things like that!
That's right! Candy isn't just
someone to toy around with!
Are you saying that you
didn't bring those roses to Candy?
Eliza? Candy has roses...?
Yes. I thought that it was you who
brought them to her in the barn...
Candy has...
Anthony
I'm sure Candy didn't mean any harm.
She probably took them
because they're so pretty.
-Right, Archie?
-Yeah.
I'll tell her about this.
I'll tell her too.
Candy has...
What?
I'm surprised that
it wasn't a present from Anthony!
Also, Candy can't tell that
which thing is hers or not.
You'd better be careful.
Stear!
I've been looking for you!
Hop in!
What? Anthony wasn't the one
who brought those roses?
It would be better
if you apologize now.
Anthony is mad at the person
who took his roses.
Stear! Even you think I did it?
But.. nobody else...
Go over to Anthony!
I'll join you later!
Candy! Wait!
Wait. the car...
Candy!my car...
Wait!
Good morning, Dorothy.
Again! Neil!
What is it, Candy?
You're having your breakfast
pretty early today.
Mind your own business.
Yesterday you went to bed pretty late.
Does that have anything to do
with you?
Neil?
Show me your hand, Neil!
What are you doing?
-Show me!
-Let me go!
It hurts. Let go of me.
I said, show me your hand!
Just what is this wound?
You got this from rose thorns,
didn't you?
I don't know! Let me go!
You stole Anthony's roses
during the night, didn't you?
You're hurting me!
Candy!
Mother! Candy is being mean
to me again!
I'm not! Neil has...
That's enough!
I wonder just
who is responsible for this mess!
You say something to her and
she goes crazy in a second.
What are you looking?
The carpet is getting soaked!
Yes!
I'll help you.
Candy, you stay here.
I want to talk to you.
Before that, there's something
I'd like to show you.
Something to show me?
Yes.
You're saying that Neil stole
these roses from Anthony's garden?
There is a wound from rose thorns
on Neil's hand.
Neil! Show me your hand.
Neil!
Explain how you got this wound!
It's ...
Neil!
Neil, be a man and tell the truth.
Candy, you be quiet!
Neil!
It's cat!
I got this while playing with Sylvia.
Is that right, Sylvia?
Neil, you haven't mentioned the
cat until now!
That's right
It does look like cat's scratch.
Neil, you liar!
Huh? Isn't this the ribbon that
got stolen from Annie the other day?
That's ...
Candy?
You'd steal our guest's ribbon?
She stole it!
She even stole these roses and now
she's trying to put the blame on me!
Neil!
Candy,
explain how you got this ribbon!
It's ...
No wonder she doesn't want to tell!
I mustn't tell them.
Annie will be hurt
if they find out that she is my friend.
Hey, Candy!
What is it, a cat ate your tongue?
She's trying to fool us by crying!
Candy, what is it then?
I haven't stolen anything!
Wait! Candy!
How far will they go?
How unfair will they get?
I mustn't cry.
I must not give in to tears.
I mustn't cry. Don't cry, Candy!
Anthony.
If I tell this to Anthony,
I'm sure he will understand.
How did it go?
He said that he doesn't want
to see you right now.
Anthony? Anthony said that?
Even Anthony has doubts in me.
What am I supposed to do at
a time like this, Annie?
I want to see you, Annie.
I wonder where does this river
lead to.
If I take on this boat
Will it take me back to Pony's home?
Candy has disappeared?
She looked strange last time I saw her
She left Leagan's estate but
never came back!
Isn't she somewhere around here?
I heard this from Leagans themselves.
She isn't back yet?
Eliza!
She might not come back at all!
Because we found out that she stole
Annie's ribbon and Anthony's roses.
They said it wasn't their problem.
Stear, I'm going to look for her.
I got it now, Anthony!
I know who stole your roses!
Really, Archie?
I saw him leave this place
during the night!
I don't know!
I don't know anything!
Neil!
Wait, Neil!
What's up with this wound?
-A cat did that!
-Let him go, Anthony.
Neil, this is a lie detector
I built myself.
If you tell a lie, this
lamp will go off!
I don't know anything!
No!
I knew it, you're lying!
-Anthony...
-Well, Neil?
I snuck in here during the night...
And then you made it look like
Candy did it?
ldiot!
Stear, Archie, let's find Candy
before it gets dark.
-Ok!
-Let's go!
Candy, it's dangerous!
It's okay, Annie!
Annie is worrying so much.
It's dangerous!
You're a coward, Annie!
Look out, Candy!
I must have fallen asleep.
Oh no! The boat is moving too fast!
This is bad. I think that
the flow is getting faster.
And there is no oar!
What's that sound?
Candy!
Candy, where are you?
She probably isn't around here.
Let's go this way.
Let's go!
Wait up!
I'll give you some light.
This lie detector is a biggest
lie in itself!
It's a Stear illumination device!
Let's go, we have to find Candy!
It's the sound of a waterfall!
Help me!
Help me, somebody!
Candy!
Help me!
The boat is gone.
Maybe Candy took it?
This is bad!
If she went downstream,
It will take her to the waterfall!
Candy...
Help!
Help me, Annie!
Anthony!
Candy!
Candy, where are you?
This girl...
What happened to me?
Are you awake?
Hey, I saved your life,
and you thank me
by flopping over again?
Is my face really that scary?
There it is! The waterfall!
Let's hurry, Anthony!
You're a funny old guy!
You're a merry one, too.
It's tasty.
Hadn't I pulled you from the
water beneath the waterfall,
you'd be in heaven right now.
Thank you.
Mister, you look much prettier
without your sunglasses on!
Light hurts my eyes. And besides,
I'm hardly a " mister" yet!
-Sorry.
-I'm Albert.
Mr. Albert?
Candy!
That voice, it's Anthony!
Candy, where are you?
Anthony is calling me...
Candy!
Anthony!
Looks like he's here to help you.
Anthony, I'm here!
Anthony!
Let's go!
Candy, anything happen to you,
you can write me a letter.
Put it in a bottle and
allow southern winds to take it.
Your note will surely reach me.
Thank you, Mr. Albert.
Candy! Where are you?
Anthony! I'm here!
Anthony!
Candy.
Candy, why are you in such a place?
The boat almost took me to heaven.
Don't joke with me!
Anthony!
Did you think just how
worried everybody was?
I'm sorry.
I was so sad,
since you didn't want to see me...
It wasn't because I thought
you stole those roses.
Then...?
I didn't want to see you until a
new kind of rose bloomed in my garden.
New kind of rose?
That's right. Remember what I
promised you on that day?
Candy, next time we meet,
it will be your birthday.
I wanted to give you this
new rose for your birthday.
But because they haven't bloomed yet,
I couldn't have met you.
So that's how it was.
And I was so...
Is someone else here?
Yes. A man who saved me,
Mr. Albert.
Mr. Albert?
He disappeared!
Anthony!
Candy!
You're okay, Candy!
Alright! Let's go back!
-Now, come on, Candy.
-Okay.
Let's go!
Wait up, Anthony!
-Anthony!
-Candy!
It's blooming.
The new rose is blooming.
Beautiful!
This is a new rose, right?
How do you call it?
-Sweet Candy.
-Sweet Candy?
I will give it to you as a present.
And today is your new birthday.
Thank you, Anthony.
The morning light shone upon it,
Candy admired the
Sweet Candy rose.