Safex
A pigeon that carried friendship
Instead of being
taken away to Mexico
Candy was suddenly adopted
by the wealthy Adley family
It was the beginning of a hectic
change for her.
Slept well!
You're awake?
Good morning!
Dorothy!
And what is this place?
I've been riding in the carriage
for so long
Every time I'd wake up
I was at a different place
You don't need to worry
anymore!
Miss Candy is an Adley daughter
no matter what anyone says!
Come on, stop with this
"miss Candy" thing...
Haven't we promised each other
that we'd remain friends?
I wanted to call you " miss Candy"
ever since the time you came here.
Dorothy...
I think I would be happier that way
But
when the two of us are alone...
Uh! As I Think...
what kind of addressing should I use
when speaking to you
It would be a problem
I don't like this
"Miss Candy" thing.
Don't do that!
You mustn't undress by yourself!
I'm not a baby anymore!
Ladies of the high class
don't change by themselves!
Oh, boy.
I'm almost like a
kissekae doll now!
After breakfast, go the
butler's room exactly at 8:25
At 8:25?
At 8:30, please go to
madam Elroy's room.
I was called only to hear that?
Yes
This is so stupid.
Why couldn't they tell me
from the beginning...
right to go to
aunt Elroy's room ?
Rich people have way
too much time on their hands!
Aunt Elroy's room was...
It wasn't here, wasn't it?
I wanted to see you exactly in 8:30.
Forgive me
I lost my way inside the house...
From now till 1 1 :55, you'll be
studying this. All of it.
What is it?
A register of the Adley family.
You need to memorize everyone's
genealogy and names in one day.
-Memorize all of this?!
-That's right.
I guess that rich people
obsess over dumb things...
That's right! I wonder if Anthony
and the others are in here as well.
There he is!
But I like the real one better!
Stear and Archie are here, as well!
Miss, please start from
the first page
Yeah
Don't do that.
She's still in there!
We'll save her
with my new invention!
An earthquake!
Oh no!
It's dangerous
the ceiling could collapse!
Candy! This way!
What do you think?
It's a self-oscillating generator
I invented!
It wasn't a real earthquake!
Miss Candy!
Candy...!
We got out all right!
Aunt Elroy is out and she won't
be back before evening!
We're free to do anything, Candy!
Where is Anthony?
He's on a date.
Date?
He went horse-riding with Eliza.
Anthony went with Eliza?
Anthony, what's the matter?
Hurry up!
Eliza, is it far from here?
We should be there soon!
But we've been riding for
two hours already.
Anthony, you don't need to
worry so much about your roses!
Eliza,
you haven't told me the truth?
You told me that
there's a new rose garden around here?
Are you lying?
I'm sorry!
Eliza!
I just wanted to ride with you
Anthony.
And that's why you lied to me?
Don't get me wrong!
Eliza, you're...
You're upset?
I'm going back!
Wait, Anthony!
If Candy were the one
to invite you for a ride...
You wouldn't be mad
if she lied to you?
Candy is not a kind of person
to tell lies!
Watch out, Eliza!
Stop the horse, Eliza!
Eliza, you're going right at them!
Eliza!
Stop!
Hang in there, Eliza!
It hurts...
I thought that I'd die.
Hang on to me.
You appeared right
in front of me,
Where the hell were you looking?
Sorry. let's go.
Wait!
Are you running away?
We're not!
I want to get her
to the doctor quickly.
Yeah and who's gonna pick up
all of those?
What is your name?
I'm Tom from the Steve farm!
I'm Anthony of the Adley family.
See you.
Hey! Wait!
Stewart
I heard that Anthony
and Eliza were hurt.
Only miss Eliza was hurt.
What? He must have punched her
finally.
And how is she feeling now?
Go away, Candy!
Neil!
You're rude, Neil!
We came to see her
because we were worried!
She doesn't want to see anybody
but Anthony!
Anthony is in there, right?
Yeah. Right next to Eliza.
Anthony...
It still hurts you, Eliza?
Hurts like I'm going to die...
But doctor couldn't find
anything wrong with you...
You'd trust that quack?
Anthony, take my hand.
You take my pain away
when you do this...
I think Eliza is pretending to be hurt
so she could be alone with Anthony.
Poor Anthony!
I wonder if Eliza was hurt badly...
Candy, you don't have to
worry about her!
-But...
-You can't go in there!
What's going on?
Where is Anthony...
Please calm down!
Mr. Anthony will come to see you.
I wonder about that!
What business do you have
with Mr. Anthony?
Just a man-to-man talk!
Tom! it's you!
Candy!
What's the matter, Tom?
You, too!
What are you doing here!
I don't really know why or how
But I got adopted into Adley family!
Adley?
Then, this...
Alright then!
This Anthony guy lives here, right?
Yeah! But he's not in here
right now!
He ran away, after all!
I don't know what this is all about
but...
Anthony doesn't just run away
from things.
He goes after every skirt, but...
when a real man confronts him
he just flees!
Anthony doesn't usually
chase women around...
Shut up! He was chasing a woman and...
almost crashed my carriage!
I had a huge mess!
You're lying!
Candy!
You're wrong!
Anthony would never
do such a thing!
Candy... are you saying that
I'm the one who is lying?
You know that
I've never told lies!
I'm not saying that...
Now that you've become
a rich lady
You don't even want to talk to me
anymore?
Tom...
Madam!
Who is this filthy looking kid?
Actually...
Pay him and get him out of here.
Money?
I didn't come here for money!
Anyway
get this eyesore out of here.
This is an Adley' entrance!
I understand.
What are you doing?
-Don't do anything to him!
-Candy!
Candy, you've become one of them
as soon as stuffed you with money!
Tom!
Now that you've become a rich lady
You don't even want to talk to me
anymore?
That's not true! I'm still me!
But why did Tom refuse to
listen to me?
I've come to trust him during
the ten years I lived with him.
I also believe what Anthony said.
I wonder who is that...
So late at night.
Anthony?
-Anthony!
-Hello, Candy!
How is Eliza?
She's okay.
I finally managed to get out.
I see.
By the way
There is something
I'd like to speak to you about.
Miss Candy!
Don't leave your room
dressed like that!
I just came to speak to Anthony...
Please return to your room!
Or they will scold me again.
-Dorothy.
-Candy!
We'll talk in the morning.
Yes
Please call me whenever you want
to put on your gown!
Even for something like that?
That is my job.
Dorothy, I like doing my own
things by myself.
If you do that, I will be fired!
Oh, boy. It seems that I'm free
only when I'm sleeping.
Should you have a nightmare,
please call me
What? I'm not even free to dream?
Good morning
What is that thing?
It's his new invention
self-moving excercise machine!
What do you think?
Want to try it out?
By the way,
where is Anthony?
Haven't seen him
since this morning
Maybe went to Eliza's place?
He keeps coming home so late.
Maybe...?
Hey, Candy!
A...Archie, stop this thing!
Anthony!
Good morning!
I've been waiting you
for two hours already.
Do you have any business
with me?
Of course
I wanted to apologize to you
I'm really sorry.
To hear something like that
from a rich person.
I'm really sorry
for what happened yesterday
Really?
And that's why
I waited for you here
I'll show you
what I think about this
What are you doing?
This is our cowboys' way
of doing.
I see. It's a slightly painful
way of greeting someone.
By the way, you want me
to greet you back?
You can try.
Is it really okay?
Someone stuck-up like you
could never feel this otherwise
Forgive my words then!
It hurts...
Are you okay, Tom?
Anthony!
They went this way!
I... I give up
Me too, I'm done for!
What's up with you two?
We're sorting out matters like men.
Yeah, a problem
between two friends
What happened here?
Candy, Anthony isn't the kind
of person who runs away.
Candy, now there is finally someone
who is both your and my friend
Tom, Anthony!
Tasty!
-It's great!
-It's from one of my cows
Are you okay, Tom?
What, this?
Candy
Let's help him take
this milk to the town.
-Great!
-I can do it alone!
Tom, we are your friends!
Yup, friends
That's ... Mr. Anthony
of the Adley family!
How could you do such a thing?
Have you no shame?
I don't think it was something
to be ashamed of!
Anthony
Have you forgotten that
you are the pride of the Adley family?
I haven't !
But... Adleys don't go around
carrying milk!
I was just helping out a friend!
A friend? That filthy cowboy
is your friend?
Tom is something like
a brother to me.
Candy
your social status has changed.
Forget about the old days.
My status has changed
Does that mean that I'm supposed
to change friends as well?
Of course!
Pick friends who are
more suitable for an Adley!
Aunt, your ideas are all wrong!
Friends are not something
you own!
It's easy to abandon friends
But you can't just replace them
with some new ones!
Anthony!
Are you talking back to me?!
I'm just speaking the truth!
What.. what words!
Candy, all of this is your fault.
Ever since
you came to this house
Anthony and the others
became completely insolent!
Our eyes were opened!
That was the first time in my life
I've beat up someone
Fighting somebody...
and being so exhausted...
You're speaking like a savage!
Anthony, I'm ordering you now
I will separate you from Candy
for a while
You will live in a forrest mansion.
Aunt?
Candy, you are forbidden
to meet Tom
Moreover
you must not leave the estate!
A few days have passed since
Anthony parted from her
With Anthony gone
even roses are feeling lonely
-Miss Candy
-Dorothy?
Does becoming a rich lady mean
that I'm supposed to be alone?
That I'm supposed to be
imprisoned in here?
I hate it. I want to go back
to Pony's home.
I don't care about being poor.
I want to see people whom I like.
I want to fight with my friends.
I want to live a life where
I'm allowed to laugh freely
A pigeon
It brought a message!
Come here!
It's from Anthony!
Candy, how are you?
Tom trained this carrier pigeon
I'm not discouraged yet!
Living with Tom taught me there isn't
anything in this world I can't do
I might be far from you, but...
I can still send you these messages
Don't give up yet
If something unpleasant happens
it's always easy to run
I'm doing my best for the
Adley family
Candy
Let's do our best together
For happiness
Anthony, I won't give up!
A new hope
appeared in Candy's heart
The pigeon from the forest...
brought her new courage.