Safex
A pretty young boy
appeared before Candy.
He reminded her of the Prince
on the hill.
"I'd like to meet you again."
Candy wished upon the pendant.
Am I elegant?
That's not good, Candy,
the fire is burning too strong!
Okay, now that's better!
You'll be in trouble if madam
discovers you here, Candy!
But there is no other place
I could make bread.
That's right, you'll make good
use of anything you learn here!
But Doug...
Madam is so fussy about us
having to be separate from them.
What? it doesn't matter at all!
Hey, Candy, it's done.
It's done!
It looks really nice!
I'll let you have it!
Thanks, Doug!
It's done!
That Candy, she's going
to see Kurin again.
I have a good idea, Eliza.
Mother, why don't we go
for a ride in a carriage?
Let's go, Mother!
Well, that's a bit unusual
to hear from you.
Bring Candy along with you.
What, Candy?
That's right.
After all, Candy is Eliza's playmate.
Now, call her.
But Candy is not here right now.
Where did she go?
I saw her running around the garden.
From time to time, she acts out
so selfishly.
I don't like that.
Well, Kurin? Does it taste good?
I made it myself.
If I work harder
I might get a chance
to meet the Prince again.
Kurin, hide quickly!
To find you in such a place
Candy!
What are you doing in here?
Something fishy!
It's not like that...
Are you telling the truth?
Yes...
I wonder...
Candy!
What's up with this bread?
That's ...
Candy! Have you been eating in here,
the food you stole earlier?
It's not that!
Then who was eating it?
The girl from Pony's home,
she is so filthy!
Candy, my intention was
to take you for a ride with us
but now I've changed my mind.
Go back to your room!
Brother, let me do it!
Eliza, you're not strong enough.
It'll be ok!
Eliza! Don't drive them like that!
Sorry!
I wonder just what I'm supposed
to represent in this house.
Kurin!
It's okay. It wasn't your fault.
I'm not sure you're good enough
to become one of the Leagans
but you'll have to learn a lot.
But I wonder if they want me to become
one of them in the first place.
If I had a pretty dress,
like the Leagan's women have...
That's right!
I'm sure the Prince will...
He won't disappear so quickly!
He might want to stay next to me!
Okay! I'm gonna work hard to
become elegant like Leagans!
Did you enjoy the ride?
It was so fun, Father!
What happened to Candy?
That girl is incorrigible!
What?
You caught Candy stealing?
Maybe that girl from Pony's home is
unfit to be Eliza's companion, after all.
t won't be good for
the children of this household!
No. Children of this house
need someone like Candy.
But... a girl who steals food...
That can't be good!
Alright.
I'll have her hear from me.
Women in Leagan family
walk like this.
That's how a classy girl
should walk in public!
Enter, please!
Uh...
Oh, Dorothy! Please enter!
Mr. Leagan wants a word with you.
Huh? Mr. Leagan?
Candy. I'll have to go on a
long business journey.
-When will you be coming back?
-I don't know that.
While I'm gone
I'm sure you'll get along well with
Eliza and Neil.
Yes.
That's all, you can relax now.
What's the matter?
I thought you were mad at me
for some reason!
However, I'm a bit angry
about one thing!
What about?
It's not good that you
stole that bread.
It was not like that!
What happened then?
It's ...
I want to hear every single bit.
Would you please come with
me to the barn?
To the barn?
Please... let me keep Kurin here!
I beg you!
Kurin, ask him yourself!
But if I let him stay here,
won't he quarrel with the horses?
It's okay! Kurin and
horses are already friends!
I understand, Candy!
So... it's okay for
him to be here?
Kurin, you can stay here!
I'm so glad!
What? Kurin is in the barn?
Since... since when?!
Ever since you drove him
from the house.
Candy pretended to have chased him away
but secretly returned him to the barn.
And you two...
If you knew about this
why didn't you tell me?
Kurin...
That Candy!
I allowed her to keep him if she
promised not to let him in the house.
Don't want to know about it!
You're good, Candy!
What happened, Candy!
It's nothing!
Sister Pony, sister Lane.
Everyone at Pony's home.
How are you doing?
Right now, I'm working hard to
become a member of the Leagan family!
What, Candy?
It doesn't suit her at all!
Don't laugh!
You should support her
in her decision!
I feel like she went so far away.
All little birds
eventually grow up and leave.
Because they wish to fly away
and see a new world.
Everyone, I would like you to
look up to Candy's new flight.
What's up with that walk?
Are you by some chances
trying to look elegant?
Even Sylvia can walk in a
more elegant manner than you!
Look at this.
Sylvia is so pretty.
Yeah, unlike the girl
from Pony's home!
Mother, Candy has...
Oh, I'm so sorry!
Candy!
What a violent girl!
If you keep doing these things,
You'll never become elegant!
Not even a monkey would do this!
That's horrible!
It's like Mrs. Leagan said, after all.
I still don't understand the kind
of life Leagans are having.
That's right! I'll have everyone
teach me all kinds of things!
I can teach you, but madam...
Keep it a secret then, okay?
Please!
I want to learn everything about
the Leagans' way of life!
I understand, Candy.
Thank you, Mary!
Listen up, Candy!
I'll teach you where plates,
knives and forks go on the table.
Okay!
That girl...
Candy
before washing the dishes,
throw a lot of soap into the water.
Okay? Now look.
Incredible! Can I try, too?
Candy, you're in high spirits
aren't you?
My, my
you've got soap under your nose!
-Really?
-It's like an old man's beard!
Come on!
Miss!
Mother!
Eliza?
Candy... she doesn't want to be
my playmate anymore!
Just what are you saying?
Candy is happier to be with the
staff, than with me!
Candy, this is how we dance for
the time of harvest.
Now, I'll teach you
dance with us!
She came to such a place...
Mother, why don't you turn
Candy into staff then?
Candy might like it more that way.
From today, tomboyish Candy will
be reborn as elegant Candy!
No, no! From now on I won't
be the same old Candy!
Well, Kurin? Do I look elegant?
I soon won't be able to
climb trees anymore.
Okay!
The prince would get quite
a fright if he saw me up here!
But this is the last time...
Wait up, brother!
What's the matter, Eliza?
I heard big news!
Upon Mother's orders, Candy
is going to become staff!
Really?
Mother says Candy will become
our personal servant!
If that comes true, she won't have
the freedom she enjoys now!
We'll make her work from
the dawn till late at night!
And Candy knows nothing of it yet!
Servant...?
I was trying so hard to
fit into the Leagan family.
But now...
I wonder if it is possible at all.
I wonder what's with Annie.
She must be so happy.
Candy came to the rose gates
Where she met the young boy
the other day.
No good.
No matter how long I wait
at the gates
the prince is not going to show up.
Maybe if I look around a bit...
I might find a small entrance.
What a beautiful forest!
There are so many birds and
cute animals here!
Incredible!
These gates, they look ancient!
That sign again!
Maybe this entire estate belongs
to Adleys, just like Stewart said.
But the Adleys...
Maybe the Prince
has something do do with them?
The Prince.
That smile...
and the light
breeze on my favorite hill...
I want to meet him again...
I'll go look around the forest a bit.
Come, Kurin!
Yet another gate!
A small waterfall is flowing over it...
is it a dam of some kind?
That sign again!
The same one on three gates!
In that case
maybe their household
is much larger than Leagan's ?
I wonder, how is one supposed
to open these gates?
Don't touch that!
You, why did you do that!
I could've gotten wet!
I'm so sorry...!
I...
Don't apologize
throw the rope instead!
Boat is going downstream!
Where is that rope?
Right over there!
I'm quickly going downstream!
Rope...
Thank you, Kurin!
Hurry up!
Okay! I'm good with the lasso!
Nice.
I was afraid that I might
have to swim back!
You got so scared...
you can't swim?
No, I'm a good swimmer.
Then, what was it?
See this silk shirt?
It was expensive!
I didn't want it to get wet.
He's dressed so well!
And... he smells so nice!
By the way, miss tomboy,
you're really good with the lasso.
Really?
Yes. Where are you from?
I'm Candy
White from the Leagan estate...
Leagan estate...?
Oh my.
My ride.
Miss tomboy, see you again!
I'm Archibald.
He... he winked at me!
He kissed my hand!
He praised me!
Archibald...
I wonder if he has
something to do with the Prince.
With her sadness soothed,
Candy returned to her more cheerful,
hopeful self.