Safex
Falling flowers in the spring.
Mr.Markba is very sick.
He is painfully calling the name ''Mina''.
However, Mina is not a person's name.
It's a St.Bernard dog.
You are Mina?
I am such a dim-wit!
It's not time to play.
Your master is dying.
Do you understand what I mean?
Come on.Follow me.
This dog is coming with you?
Please... Mr.Markba wants to see it.
He wants to see a dog before he dies?
What a strange old man.
Mr.Markba is not going to die.
Mina, get on.
Please do me the favor.
I hate dogs.
Especially their smell.
Mina, good dog.
I am bringing you to see your master.
I am bringing you to see Mr.Markba.
Markba.
Come, Mina.
Good kid, come on.
Forget it!
It's not listening to you.
I have an idea!
What? I am busy.
Mr.Markba's belongings.
Do we have any here?
The master's....
Suites or shirts.
Don't be kidding.
I am not the master's wife.
You know what Mr.Markba is like.
I am going to let Mina smell his things.
I refuse.
Fishing tackle?
Aunt.
Why are you still here?
Is this Mr.Markba's fishing tackle?
That's the master's favorate....
-I'll give you back.
-Wait! That's....
Come on, Get on!
Mina, your master is waiting for you.
Follow me, Mina, Come on!
Come on, Get on!
That's right. Good kid.
Good. Get on.
Good. Mina.
Where are you going? Mina.
Wait.
Mina.
Where did you go?
I don't have time
to play games with you.
Where are you going?
Where are you bringing me to?
What a beautiful place!
I see.
You wanna take me to go fishing?
I get it! Mr.Markba must
often bring you here to go fishing.
A huge fish!
Look! Mina. A huge fish!
We are so lucky!
I can imagine Mr.Markba going fishing.
But, Mina.
Your master's life is in danger.
He wants to see you.
Come on,
let's get on the carriage together.
Candy.
I have been looking for you.
I am sorry.
It's time to go back to the hospital.
The headmaster is very wordy.
No problem now.
Mina....
Why isn't Mina getting on?
Forget about that dog.
No, I'll walk it back.
What? It will be dark
when you get to the hospital.
Maybe it will be faster this way.
Whatever.
But, the carriage will not go with you.
It's ok.
You go back first.
Don't tell the headmaster
that Mina is a dog.
Mina, come out.
Let's go.
-Dim-wit.
-Sorry.
She insists to find Miss Mina.
Did you see Mina?
Well....
Headmaster.
Hurry! Mr.Markba...
Unconcious.
He can only make it
till tomorrow morning.
Headmaster.
Still haven't found Mina?
The patient's sheet slipped.
Nurses must hang on to the end.
Remember that.
Yes, I understand.
Mina.
This wouldn't happen
if we have taken the carriage.
He is coming back.
You think
this carriage is coming back for you?
That's alright.
I won't force you to take the ride.
Mina.
What happened?
-Mr.Markba's dog?
-No! Mina.
It got on itself?
Oh well....
You are going back to mr.Markba's?
You know it?
Not very well. It's always like this
when taking my ride.
Get off.
This is for people.
It hates the carriages.
Why did it get on itself?
Mr.Markba took this carriage
when he went to the hospital.
You will see Mr.Markba
if you take this carriage.
I try to avoid
getting close to Mr.Markba's house.
Get off.
Could you take us to the hospital?
I am a practice nurse
at Joseph Hospital.
Mr.Markba wants to see it.
Is mr.Markba serious?
Yes.
I will take it to the hospital
for neighbor's sake.
Please.
I will pay you.
Deal!
-Please hurry!
-OK.
Doctor Frank, the pulse is not stable.
Check the temperature every two hours.
Check the pulse every ten minutes.
-Understand?
-Yes.
Blanny.
Candy.
You must be tired. Let me do it.
You are so irresponsible.
It's you
who asked to take care of Mr.Markba.
Sorry.
Didn't find Mina?
Let's talk about it later.
Did the headmaster know?
Of course.
Have some rest in the room.
Check the temperature every two hours.
Check the pulse every ten minutes.
-Write it down clearly.
-Ok.
Candy.
A nurse needs to
have a sense of responsibility.
Yes.
I am back, Mr.Markba.
Mina,
animals are not allowed in the hospital.
You have to be good.
Good night, thanks a lot.
No! Mina, do not bark!
Mina.
It's from Mr.Markba's room.
That dim-wit is making trouble again.
Candy.
Good evening, headmaster.
That's ok.
What was that noise?
Sounds like a dog.
It's from the outside of the window.
Some curs are fighting.
They ran away.
Dr. Frank.
Look!
This....
pulse is accurate?
Yes, the record is thorough.
The pulse is ok.
Mr.Markba will be ok?
Not sure.
I can only say,
things are getting better.
That's great!
Let me know
as soon as there is any situation.
It's all yours now.
Yes, I know.
Mina, keep it down.
Mr.Markba.
Mina is here to see you.
You...
Mina.
Doctor Frank, what are you looking at?
A miricle.
A miricle?
Recovering in ten days.
As a doctor, it's unbelievable!
That old man smiled.
Yeah, first time seeing it.
You are great that
you thought Mina was a person.
Yeah, I thought it was a beautiful lady.
To me,
Mina is more important than people.
In this world, I only believe Mina.
Now, there is one more person.
You.
I am a dim-wit.
No, you are great!
You knew it was a dog.
But still brought it to me.
Mina wants to see you, too!
When I get better,
I will bring it to visit you.
That's great!
I am going to charge for it.
You money lover!
Candy.
-William Adley....
-Grandfather William?
Yes. I said bad things about him...
No, I recognized a wrong person.
You know grandfather William?
I have never seen him.
I've only heard his name.
He must be a nice person
to be willing to adopt you.
Sure.
Grandfather William is better than you.
I am sorry.
I'll bring Mina to see you next time.
No,
I'll bring it to meet you next time.
Right!
I have a pair of ribbons for you.
Ribbons?
The one like Mina's?
It must be pretty.
And,we can go fishing together.
To that beautiful lake?
You know it?
Mina told me.
That place is my secret.
It's the secret between three people.
No.
It's two people and one dog.
You have to get well soon for this wish.
I feel much better.
I've never been in such a good mood
for a long time.
Let's decorate the ward with petals.
It must smell very good.
It feels like snow flakes are falling.
So sleepy.
I am going to pick the petals.
Please wait for a moment.
Mr.Markba.
Mr.Markba, look! So many...
Come on. Let's go back to the room.
These petals....
Mr.Markba.
Wake up, Mr.Marka!
We are going fishing after you recover.
You promised me.
How did this happen?
I took care of you so hard.
Mr.Markba.
No matter how we call,
no matter how we cry,
Mr.Markba will never open his eyes.
The petals are falling like snow flakes.
Candy recalls Anthony
who is sleeping in the petals.
She can't help but feels sad.