Safex
Terry protested after Candy was locked
up in school' s tower, but to no avail.
Stear and Archie tried to
reveal Eliza' s plot...
but it too ended in failure.
In that moment
Terry made a decision.
Terry' s decision.
It' s already morning...
I must have fallen asleep
listening to Terry' s harmonica.
Terry?
Terry!
Terry.
He probably went back to his room.
He stood here all night, playing the
harmonica to console me.
Terry.
Thank you!
Because you
I wasn't feeling lonely at all.
Kurin.
Sorry Kurin. Of course that
it was because of you, too.
You snuck out of school in the morning
in order to speak to me?
I didn't expect you to do such a thing
over such trivial matters.
To you, Father, it may sound trivial
but it' s something important to me.
So that Candy-or-something girl...
you expect me tp help her?
Please, Father.
You only called me father at time
like this.
The school' s methods are way too cruel.
They expelled her without
even trying tp find out the truth.
Candy' s innocent.
Terrius!
I've always tolerated your whims
but this time, I won't.
It' s only reasonable that
she was expelled.
In that case, why wasn't I expelled?
Because I spoke up in your favor
at the school.
That' s why I need your influence now.
It was all my fault that
Candy wound up like this.
-Therefore...
-No!
It looks like it' s better that
this girl isn't near you.
Are you saying that you won't help her.
father.
Exactly.
I knew it. I shouldn't have come here.
I knew it would've ended up like this.
But, what if...
what if I ask them...
Father.
Father, I have no right to come here.
To trouble you with my issues.
However
Whatever happens from now on
I won't go around with
my head bowed down
I will resolve everything on my own.
Terrius!
Today' s mass was different, wasn't it?
Sisters are probably concerned
over Candy and Terrius.
But dating in the barn...
That' s quite simething!
-They've git some guts!
-Really!
Candy is done this time.
Everybody is talking about Candy.
Because it' s the first scandal
in the history of this school.
No wonder she got expelled!
Elisa.
-Terry!
-He' s coming this way.
Terry.
Terry, I...
What a guy!
Are you alright, Elisa?
Go away!
Come in!
Terrius!
Sister Gray, I' m here to speak to you.
Don't you realize that you' re
confined to your room?
Just give a few moments.
I won't. Get out immediately!
Sister Gray!
This is my first and last request!
It' ll will only take a minute!
I've never seen him like this.
Very well.
I' ll give you a apecial permit.
I' m expecting you to be brief.
Thank you.
What do you want to talk about?
Sister Gray
Miss Candice' s expulsion is irreversible?
You' re still dwelling on that?
I' m not going to change my mind.
I can't have you two in the same school
after you caused such an incident!
In that case, I want to be expelled
instead of her!
The point is that
two of us aren't in the same school.
I will be the one to leave!
Are you serious?
I am serious.
I can't allow that.
Firstly, what would Duck Grandchester
say about it?
He did not object.
What?
He had not objections, sister Gray.
From today, I am renouncing
my Grandchester name.
What?
Excuse me.
Wait, Terrius!
Farewell, sister Gray.
Terrius...
Terry!
This hill
looks exactly like my Pony' s hill!
That' s why I' m calling it
''Other Pony' s hill''
Freckled Tarzan.
What, Freckled Tarzan?
You' re so rude!
It' s better this way.
I won't be able to come to this hill
and see Candy anymore.
If I' m going, I' d better leave quickly.
Brother, the class is going to begin
if don't hurry!
I' ll be done in a moment.
Terry!
Hi, Terry!
Would you care to take a look
at my newest invention?
What is it?
It' s a lie detector.
Brother stayed up for this
so he could help Candy!
This thing will reveal Eliza' s plot.
-Brother, let' s go!
-Okay.
Terry, won't you come with us?
What' s the matter?
I thought about how much I owe you.
I won't have to worry about Candy.
You got that right.
Your hands are soft.
Perfect for working with mechanics.
Say, maybe we could cooperate together?
Someday, for sure.
Bye.
What' s going on with him?
He' s not his usual self.
My youth is passing.
My love is coming to an end.
Farewell, Candy.
I wish they' d bring my something to eat!
Cinnamon eggs, apple pie and
chocolate drink...
Oh! I did it again!
It won't get any luxurious than this.
Candice!
Yes!
Are you alright?
I' ll open now.
Sister Margaret brought me some food.
Hide quickly!
Good morning, sister Margaret!
Are you feeling alright, Candice?
My stomach is growling! No, I...
Say, the food...
Come. You' re getting out.
Sister Gray want to see you.
Then, this means that someone from the
Adley family came to pick me up?
I don't know any details.
But, Candice...
Yes?
Whatever happens...
don't let youself be crushed.
Thank you!
-Now, come.
-Yes
Sister Margaret
I won't forget about you
when I get out of this school.
Now, let' s go.
Kurin?
Let' s hurry.
Yes.
Sister Gray
I brought Candice White Adley.
Thank you.
-Go.
-Yes.
Candice, come here.
Yes!
-Candice.
-Yes.
I have changed the measures against you
instead of special explusion...
your punishment will be changed to
a week of room confinement.
So that you could thoroughly
reflect upon your actions.
Is that for real?
You can step down.
Thank you so much. sister Gray!
Sister Gray, just one thing...
I' d like you to understand this
After receiving those notes, both of us
went to the barn without thinking.
But Terry and I...
Step down!
Yes. Sister Gray.
Terrius and Candice are saying
the exact same thing.
Maybe it really was a trap.
But their meeting in the barn has become
a hottest topic discussion in school.
If I allowed both of them to stay
in this school...
other students could have
stared doing the same.
Having said that...
Freedom is the best!
But why have they revoked
my punishment so suddenly?
Maybe
Terry had something to do with this.
-Eliza! It' s an emergency!
-What happened?
Candy' s punishment was reduced from
expulsion to a room confinement!
Impossible!
Patty!
Why did Candy...
Somebody is standing behind this.
Otherwise
this would have never happened!
That' s right. Something is strange.
Terrius.
It' s Terrius!
Terrius had his father, Duke Grandchester
make pressure on the school board!
That must be it!
He has no power to do that!
Be quiet!
Eliza, stop talking about things
that are beyond your knowledge.
Then, why Candy' s punishment reduced?
Say it frankly!
Every one of us
wants to know what happened!
This incident was the first scandal
in history of this school.
Towards that end, we must manage
such matters with discretion.
We have found a better solution,
both for those two and for school.
This is most important.
Are you saying that reducing Candy' s
punishment was the best solution?
Those measures seemed the best to me!
That strict nun has become this meek?
Yes, it' s strange.
She became soft all of a sudden.
What' s going on?
Be quiet! Quiet!
Today is time for Director to
hold her special lecture.
Today we' ll be studying...
Students
havent't caught on to the truth.
But they will eventually find out
what happened to Terrius.
When that happens...
am I going to regret allowing
Candice to stay in this school?
It' s already night!
Huh? There is no light in Terry' s room.
What happened?
Alright!
Terry?
Terry, I was worried about you.
Terry!
Everything is put in order.
A letter?
To the thoughtful finder;
Give this letter to
Miss Candice White Adley.
Terrius.
Terrius!
Candy, I decudeed to quit school
and go to America.
There is something I' d like to do.
Wherever I might end up
I' ll be praying for you happiness.
Terrius.
Wherever I might end up
I' ll be praying for you happiness.
Wherever...?
Terry...went to America.
Terry...what an easygoing letter.
Almost too easygoing, Terry.
How could you...
How could you leave like this?
Candice, instead of special expulsion
you will be confined to your room.
Come to think of it
they forgave me too easily.
Special expulsion... don't tell me...
don't tell me that Terry did this for me.
I' m sure he did.
He played his harmonica
all night long for me.
But he was trying to say goodbye.
I heard that
Terry was expelled from this place!
It' s Neil!
For the better! He was a weird one.
Hey, it' s his room!
He allowed himself to get expelled
instead of that dogsbody.
Neil!
Hi, Stear and Archie.
Is it true what you said now?
Let go og me!
You said that
Terry left instead of Candy!
It' s true!
That' s right, sisters were talk about it
and we overheard them.
It' s true.
Brother...
So back then
he was bidding us farewell...
So that' s what it was.
And where did Terry go?
To America.
He said that he would be leaving
by morning ship.
Let' s go.
-To America?
-By morning ship?
He left so I wouldn't have to...
So quickly.
Parting from him so quickly.
No...!
I don't want to part from you!
No!
I turned up late.
I couldn't see him.
Terry I...
I love you.
Candy! wherever I might end up
I' ll be praying for your happiness.
Terry!
Just my imagination.
I must be imagining it
since we first met on such a ship.
The shore is already far...
Candy, be happy.
But someday... for sure.
Terry, what should I do?
What should I do?
Did you think that staying here
would've brought me happiness?
Terry!
While this painful parting
was taking place.
Candy would have herself
expelled from school.