Safex
After knowing the dean is ill from Tom,
Candy went back to the Boni's House.
But,this is only lie
to stop Candy to risk her life
in the moutain area.
Lina's cry.
What about Tom?
Fix him.
What about shoes?
How?
The clothes on the wall.
In the bag.
Kelin,Kelin,do you know where's my box?
Use that face.
Help me to find it.
I can't go out like this.
The set of the Gulei,many boys
ran away from there.
Will Candy die there?
Perhaps.
Stop her.
Yes,stop her.
Brother.Brother.
Where have you been,John?
Even she wants to go,she can't.
Why,John?
Candy.
Wore dean's shoes.
Tom.
Morning,Candy.
Not good morning.
Why like a fox?
Fox?
Yes.
You know after looking at me.
What did I do?
The shoes.
I hide them.
John.
I will not say where I hide it.
I will not allow her to go
to such dangerous place.
Candy,don't go there.
Though you stop me,I am happy.
But,I am a nurse.
You can be a nurse anywhere.
Even in the Boni's House.
Please.
Boby,you didn't say a word beofore
but you agree me to go.
Boby,why do you agree?
Do you hate Candy?
The mark after the operation?
My father brought me to the set,
and I am ill there.
If there's no doctor,I am dead.
How old are you then?
Three. I only remembered the nurse.
I will never forget her face.
So I agree her to go.
Yes.
Boby is new,he's not worried about Candy.
Yes,yes.
Say it again.
I can say several times.
What?
You two,stop.
Dean.
Dean,you must be against Candy
to the dangerous place?
Yes,against.
That's right.
Dean.
If Candy is not a nurse,
So,Dean is.
So many people are waiting for Candy.
What about Sister Grainen?
She agrees with me.
Thank you,Dean.
John,Candy is a lady now.
She can't always wear
the nightdress,it's not polite.
Do you understand,John?
Where did you hide,tell me.
Father's tree.
I didn't climb it for a long time.
One,two,three.
There's nothing change here.
I will back soon. For the children in the house,
what's the gift?
Heave. It seems a lot.
Kelin.
What,Miss.
Nothing,nothing at all.
I will help you.
No,I go to the last stop.
You should change in the back. This is the end.
Yes,hurry,Kelin.
Yi.
Are you calling for me?
Are you Mr. Kelin?
Formally,it's Clinton
But they always calls me Kelin.
Don't mind.
It's all right for you to show your face.
I feel lonely.
What? The News. What?
Kawado,Smido,Hixiu,John.
You are frightened by the photo.
It must be the Benzun this time.
It seems ok.
It's day time now.
It's too hard for you,Kelin.
You can walk for a while.
I will do some excise.
What's wrong,Kelin?
There seems someone.
I am sorry.
Kelin,please hide for a while.
If someone see you,you will be killed.
The specility of the face,it's white
and the sound is like a girl.
That's right.
Let he know.
I can't stay with a murderer.
Where do you bright me to?
The hell.
That's too back. I am shaking.
No fever.
Thank you.
There's no beating of the heart.
Can't breathe.
Hurry to the stop.
It's too slow. Hurry,hurry.
It seems the master is not here. The face.
Yes,there must be someone.
Sorry,good afternoon.
It stops again. Are you a girl?
It may be a girl.
That's all right.
I met a girl in this station for the first time
Even the wathc was afraid.
Campare with the murderer in the train,
Murderer?
Yes That's in the news and rewarding.
For me,you are a bigger problem than a murderer.
So relaxed. Report to the security.
There's nothing in the mountain
Who are you looking for?
I will work here as a nurse.
What?
Look.
Miss,you can't work here.
But.
I mean,it's better for
you to go back to the city.
Please let me see the doctor first.
Doctor?
Yes,the doctor of the clinic.
He ran away one month ago.
No doctor now?
Where's the set?
Four hours for walking there.
Please write down your name and adress
I can inform your family if you dead.
There's stones falling down on the way.
Excuse me.
Back,there's traini two hourse later.
Start out.
Wait.
Like to sit in the empty box.
That.
Go back,miss.
I want to be back too.
Catch.
Don't worry about it,Kelin.
He is laughing,he's not a bad guy.
You two,pray to the god,don't be like that.
Boni.
Bend over.
Dangerous.
We have prayed to the God.
It's not enough.
The volcano is break up. Run,run away.
Dangerous.
It's too dangerous.
You baster.
Inspector.
You know the breaking up time.
Sorry,the watch is stopped.
This is the last cars.
The car is more important than people?
Don't talk. Who are you?
I am the nurse of the clinic.
What? Nurse.
We need a doctor,but not a nurse.
That's rude.
The car is more important than people
The nurse can't stand it.
You are too noisy
This is not the hospital in the street.
Dry this miss away.
Inspector.
Too bad.
Inspector,that's too bad.
What?
Is some one hurt in the volcano?
Yes.
He has a high fever.
Idiot. Miss,let's see your skill.
Call me Candy.
Too bad.
What about it,Miss.
It needs to operation.
Do it now.
I?
Can't you?
Yes,I can only wrap the wound.
Get away.
What do you do?
We can do that too.
Then,take him away.
But,it will be worse then.
Do as inspector said.
No,I am the nurse.
Throw her away.
Come,miss.
Stop,stop.
Hurt,hurt.
What's that?
The patient.
You are...
I will do the operation.
What are you?
I am the doctor.
The new doctor here.
Hurry up.
Yes,yes. Everyone,don't bend dow.
It's ready.
It needs time,Candy.
Who's the doctor?
I want to say the murderer
but she's the new doctor.
I want a man,but a woman.
The terrible day for Candy will last.