Safex
The ticket from Terry.
Looking at the ticket from Terry,
Candy's heart is full of joy.
In the meantime,
the accident of Suzanna
is causing painful feeling for Terry.
Candy, without knowing the accident,
is departing tomorrow.
The desired reunion in the dream.
Are you ready for tomorrow?
Almost.
I will see Terry tomorrow.
Candy.
What? Mr.Albert.
You are thinking about something.
I am not.
When I was in London Zoo,
although I don't remember clearly,
did I often see Terry?
You were like brothers back then.
I should miss him a lot.
Yes. Same does Terry.
Say hi to Terry for me.
OK.
It's getting cold.
It might snow tomorrow.
-Mr.Albert.
-Yes?
When I am not at home,
if your memory is back,
don't go anywhere.
I won't, Candy.
Don't worry about me,
enjoy your trip.
Thank you, Mr.Albert.
You need to get up early tomorrow.
I'll take care of this,
you can go rest early.
Ok.
Not in sleep, Brother?
I gotta finish this new thing.
I don't know what you are so busy for.
Sleep early.
Brother, will Candy come back
after she sees Terry?
Of course.
What if Terry deosn't let her back?
Mr.Albert's memory
has not been back yet.
Candy is a very responsible person.
She will be back.
Sounds right. Good night.
Good night.
Where is the ticket?
Not here.
Found it!
Good morning, Candy.
You don't have to walk me.
The hat is not right.
Ok, go back to rest,
don't catch a cold.
You are not used to getting up early,
to catch the first train,
it must be tiring.
Good morning, Poopet.
It's freezing outside,
isn't it?
I am gonna go now,
I am getting late.
Candy, let me walk you out.
No, I don't want you to catch a cold.
I'll bring you a gift. Bye!
Candy!
She is always doing things alone.
Candy, be back soon.
As long as I have you beside me,
I don't mind losing my memory.
I will be satisfied
just to live in peace everyday.
There are not many people
taking the first train.
Candy
-Candy
-Stear
I made it!
I thought I wouldn't be able to make it.
Stear,
did you come to see me away?
You don't have to, it's so early.
You are traveling to a faraway place
by yourself. Poor girl.
Nonsense! I'll be back soon.
Stear,
why are you so different today?
Nothing.
Say ''hi''to Terry for me.
No problem.
I'll bring back some gifts.
Are you cold?
Get on the train, Candy.
It's ok, I'll be leaving soon.
-Candy
-Stear
What? Candy.
We have never talked alone
like this.
It's true.
Stear, I...
The train is leaving.
I am going.
-Candy
-What?
Give you my new invention.
What is this?
A music box of happiness.
What a great name!
It's so pretty.
Thank you, Stear.
Candy, this melody
will lead you to happiness.
Thank you, Stear.
You have to be happy, Candy!
You are so strange, Stear.
We are not saying good-bye forever.
Good-bye, Stear!
Candy
What? Stear.
I am leaving.
Candy
What? Stear
Good-bye, Candy, be careful!
Good-bye, Candy.
I am going to meet Terry again.
Terry!
Candy!
Terry
You are finally here, Candy.
Long time no see, Terry.
Wait for me, Terry.
I am coming!
Beautiful melody, lady.
It made me recall
many beautiful memories.
Going to see a good friend?
Yes, to New York.
It's good to be young.
I don't have any friends.
Grandpa,where are you going?
To visit my wife's tomb.
So bright!
It's so beautiful,
feels like wishing me good luck.
New York is getting closer,
Terry.
Just wait for a little while, Terrry,
I am almost there!
New York. I am finally here.
There are so many people
in the station.
Where is Terry?
There are so many people,
will he come to pick me up?
How should I greet Terry?
Terry, finally seeing you.
It's boring.
Why is Terry late?
Letting a lady wait for so long.
Terry, I miss his back sight.
Didn't change at all.
Terry, I am here!
Seeing me, what would
Terry's face look like?
Gently smiling, and then...
Terry
You don't look like...
Look like what?
Nothing,
I recognized a wrong person.
Why are you grabbing me?
You can't fool me so easily.
Let me go or I'll bite you!
You are still so violent.
Terry
Candy
Terry is in front of me.
You didn't change a bit.
Candy,
I want to hold you so much.
But, I can't say that out.
You matured a lot,
and grew up a lot.
-You...
-did not change.
You are so mean, Candy!
Sorry, I didn't mean it.
You are really the same.
I can't believe
they let you in the nursing school.
You are rude. I am a nurse.
That's right!
You are a real nurse now.
Congratulations! Freckle girl.
You are so mean, Terry.
Terry,
congratulations on your Romeo role.
Thanks, Candy.
I miss you so much, Terry.
Me, too.
I even dreamed about you.
I would like to take this chance...
Terry,
why didn't you show up earlier?
I thought that person was you.
I saw that. It scared you.
I thought you had
some problem with your eyes.
His back looked like you.
I didn't expect you would make up.
Of course I have to make up.
I make a living out of my face.
It's cool, but...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's not romantic at all.
We have been looking forward
to this reunion for a long time.
It's really not a right place.
Let me take you to the hotel first.
I want to see the place
you live first.
The place I live?
I want to see how it looks like.
OK, I'll take you there.
Is this all your luggage?
You are carrying the luggage for me?
It's rude to let the lady
carry the luggage.
Good!
You finally think I am a lady.
Of course, freckle lady.
You are so mean.
You, too.
Candy, I have always wanted
to take a walk with you.
Candy, get on.
This is your car? Is it working?
Of course!
It is better than Stear's.
Stear said ''hi''to you.
That's right. Stear!
How are they? More mature?
Gained weight?
Archie, Annie, Pattie.
Say the names clearly.
Yes! Teacher Freckle.
Terry
Candy, I feel so happy with you.
Does this city never rest?
Right.
So pretty, I can see the breasts.
Terry, that one, too!
You didn't change at all.
I didn't expect you
would become a nurse one day.
Miracle.
Yes, only if there is a miracle...
Only if there is a miracle,
otherwise, Suzanna will be
sitting in a wheelchair all her life.
Suzanna loves you.
She sees you as a person
she can depend for life.
Terry, don't abandon her.
Terry, watch out!
Terry,
please be beside her forever.
Company her all your life.
I am already seeing someone.
Why not letting her know it?
Suzanna, are you alright?
Suzanna
It's not your fault.
I can't lie to Mother.
Don't worry about it.
Focus on your show.
You are with her, right?
You ruined my daughter's life.
You have to be with her
all your life.
Be with her all your life.
Terry
Terry, what's wrong?
Nothing.
We are getting close to my house.
Come in, please.
Why are you standing there?
It's so surprising!
I thought it would be messy.
The cleaning woman
cleans it every three days.
Mr.Albert helps me clean the house.
Candy,
you let Mr.Albert do the cleaning?
Oh no!
That is too much.
Mr.Albert insists
I stay away from the cleaning job.
You always find a excuse.
This photo doesn't look like you
at all.
It's not a photo, it's a painting.
What a nice job!
I thought it was a photo. But...
But what?
I thought Suzanna would play Juliet.
Didn't expect it to be
Karen Clairs.
Karen must be happy.
That's great!
Suzanna must be disappointed.
No.
I can't tell her about Suzanna.
Candy, the tea is ready.
How is it if I change the name
to Candice White?
Just posing.
I can play Juliet, too.
You are such a blower.
Terry, do not tease me.
Candy
I didn't want Candy to leave me.
But...
Terry
why do you look so serious?
The tea spilt,
let me make you another one.
Let me do it, you are the guest.
Candy can sense that there
seems to be something wrong with Terry.
However, after the unease...
the feeling of happiness
that Terry brought her,
has already spread out
in Candy's heart.