Safex
Anthony and the others...
found that it's Neil and Eliza's ploy
to send Candy to Mexico.
Aunt Elroy was supposed to find out
the truth in the morning.
However...
the escort from Mexico
turned up early.
Candy without even saying goodbye
to Anthony and others...
departed to distant Mexico
On the distant, dry wastelands.
I've come this far already.
There's no way I could turn back now.
If I had wings, I'd fly back
as fast as I could.
Back to Anthony's place.
Alright! We'll take a rest there.
Wait!
Until we get to Mexico,
you're just a servant!
Remember that I'm the master.
I'm hungry as hell.
Kurin!
Here you go.
I forgot something else.
Alright.
Damn it!
Haven't I told you not to
waste water?
And on such a thing!
Sweet Candy is...
We're not on a picnic!
What's with that flower?
It has no use!
From now on, every one of us gets
only one cup of water per day!
Then, it's okay to water the
rose from my part?
Yeah.
It's your raccoon's part, too.
His part, too?
If you have a problem with that, dump
the raccoon and the rose here.
A farm!
Yes, that's where we were going.
Thank god!
We'll get all the water
we need here!
The millet has all dried up!
Yeah, it hasn't rained in
a very long time.
It's a disaster.
It hasn't rained?
Nothing ever comes from the clouds!
This place is totally dead!
Kurin!
Do you understand now?
Water isn't important to you alone.
Hey, Walther!
Walther, I've come to pick you up!
Yeah, I'll be there in a second!
Now, say farewell to
grandpa and grandma.
What is going to happen to them?
They are going to work in the fields
just like you.
- Like me?
- Yeah.
That's what the family
sent you for.
That's not what I've been told.
You must be forgetting things!
Who'd think that there
are things like this.
I might have been living in the barn,
but...
I've always had plenty to eat.
Now, let's go.
So you're going to Mexico as well?
But...
if you don't want to go to Mexico
Aren't there some other places
you could work?
I guess you don't know
how hard life can be, right?
Hard life?
Why are you going to Mexico?
I didn't want to go.
But I couldn't help it.
Just like us.
We couldn't help it.
But isn't there a way for us
to quit this job?
You can't do that.
Why?
I lent money to this family.
That's the reason they didn't
go broke until today!
And now I'm taking them back to
Mexico until they pay off their debt!
I wish this rain had come
a bit earlier!
Those are cowboys, right?
They're cool!
Water, it's water!
Alright, we'll set up a camp here!
Why, what a cute calf!
Probably belongs to those
cowboys.
You got separated from your mama?
Hello!
Alright, I'll catch it!
Or the jackals will get it first.
Jackals?
Just a moment!
- What are you doing?
- I'll catch it!
Stand still!
Hey, Candy, you got it!
Let me borrow your horse.
I'll return this calf.
There'll be no need for that.
We found it
so we'll take it with ourselves.
You can't do that!
You don't really get it?
It's best for a child to
stay next to its mama!
I won't let you take it!
You got some nerve!
What are you doing to her?
What? Are you talking to me?
If I hadn't taken you...
You'd be starving
in your house right now!
I'll take this calf.
What's the matter?
Is that calf yours?
This calf, of course!
It is yours!
I knew it!
I was going to bring it to you!
Thank you, miss!
See you then!
Don't separate it from mama!
- This runt!
- Stop that!
You know that penalty for cattle
stealing is death by hanging?
Candy just saved you.
Mr. Walther, thank you.
No problem. Now
gather some firewood.
Okay!
Hey, why don't you give some
to your brother, too?
No!
Come on!
- No.
- Come on.
Don't do that!
Calm down!
I'll tuck you in.
Mama put her baby in the basket...
Sister Pony, sister Lane,
where is my mama?
Candy, I and sister Pony
are your mamas.
You were born in that basket.
And then you were given
to Pony's home!
What's the matter?
Shut up! Make it stop crying!
I'm sorry. Please sleep.
Bear through this.
Your mother
doesn't have milk for you.
So that's it...
I'll make it quiet!
Wait!
What? Move it!
Let me handle this.
That's funny
If you don't make it quiet...
I'll go nasty on you this time.
Just a moment!
I'll borrow it for a minute!
What are you doing with my horse?
Who is it?
Good evening!
You are...
I'm Candy.
Candice White.
Are you alone? This late?
I came to ask you for a favor.
Can you help me?
What is it?
Could you fill this with milk?
You came just for that?
Yeah, that's right!
You have so many cows...
Candy, be careful!
Jim will take you back to your camp.
Thank you for giving me this much!
Well, now.
Candy, thank you.
- Let me.
- Yes
Stop the carriage!
The baby has a fever!
If we don't get to the doctor soon...
You'll have to bear it
until we get to the next town.
How much until next town?
Around one day maybe.
That much?
Wouldn't it be faster if we just
returned to the town we passed before?
You're kidding me!
If we return to that town,
we'll turn up late in Mexico.
Will there be enough time
for doctor to see the baby?
I don't know that!
It depends on many things.
That's why it's better to stop
in the next town.
Then, you're saying that it doesn't
matter what happens to the baby?
Death is a part of life, too!
There is no way
we're heading back now!
These are my ways!
What a cold person!
Please,
at least stop the carriage...
until we give medicine to the baby!
At least do that!
I understand. Better do it now.
No good, baby spit out everything.
That medicine doesn't work!
Shut up! Hold still.
Okay.
Where are you going?!
We're going back!
What are you doing, you idiot?
Come back here, Candy!
You're going to leave me here?!
You did a terrible thing.
There was nothing else I could do!
Thank you, Candy!
You're a brave girl.
- Darling!
- What's the matter?
The baby looks strange!
Candy, please hurry!
Where is the doctor?
Thank you!
Mr. Walther, this way!
- Candy!
- Sis!
Can he save Jimmy?
I'm sure he can.
Why didn't you come sooner?
Doctor...
This was unnecessary!
Something smells great!
They're late.
It's this!
What a wonderful rose!
Listen up,
you can't take this baby to Mexico!
Baby might die if you do!
I understand.
Mama, how is Jimmy?
He's okay.
Great!
It's beautiful!
But we must get to Mexico.
We already spent all the money
we got from Mr. Garcia.
There is no other way.
You and Jimmy stay here.
Mr. Garcia will forgive me
when I tell him the reason.
I'll work as much as I can in Mexico
and I'll send you back the money.
It seems there is no other way...
Don't do that! Parents shouldn't
part their ways!
Now listen me well.
Jimmy is ill.
Continuing the journey
would've been bad for him.
In order to help Jimmy...
mama will stay here
together with him.
Okay? You understand me?
You understand, too?
I know you can bear it.
Papa
It's okay.
Mama!
This is too cruel.
This rose is yours?
The person who grew this rose
has a very gentle soul!
I, too, have been growing
roses for a very long time.
But I've never been able
to make something this pretty.
Anyway... would you like to
sell it to me?
No! I can't sell you this!
I'd give you anything for it...
Well then, take care of yourself.
Please take care of the kids.
If I had any money...
Anthony
you'll forgive me, won't you?
Mister!
I'll sell you the rose!
Alright! It's sold!
Mama, the train is coming!
Candy, doing such a thing...
I got money, you won't
have to go to Mexico to work.
But what are you going to
do about mr. Garcia?
I had a good chat with that old man!
I'm going to pay off your debt with
the money I got when I sold the rose!
Now you don't have anything
to worry about.
Now, get on! Hurry!
Candy is... Dad!
Candy is still on the station!
Lmpossible!
Candy... you are really...
Farewell, Candy!
Thank you, Candy!
Damn it! Garcia was screwed
over by such a girl...
Idiot!!
She... she's back.
That idiot is really back!
It would've been better
if you just ran...
why did you come back?
I felt sorry for you, Mr. Garcia.
Come on, you don't have to be
sympathetic to me...
The difficult journey continues.
Candy then said to herself,
"I'll make it for sure".